<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject3674</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Connect with other TableTop gamers, Find Events, Find Stores</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 21:26:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 23:29:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can also try posting a 'Looking For Players' post. We have a users reach back out to use that they have been able to meet people and play at their local gaming stores through LFP posts, including a few AoS players.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 00:33:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good deal, should be able to help with that as well!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>GameFor Review and Interview - Find Local Tabletop Players and Events</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 20:24:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Gamefor  #8211; Spieler verbinden</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 12:21:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to Find Tabletop Gamers and Events Near You</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 14:13:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Adam was on the Skirmish Supremacy podcast talking about GameFor and more</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 22:44:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>GameFor interview on Veteran Wargamer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 22:45:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Coach Interviews Adam from Tabletop Minions</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 22:54:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Interview with Uncle Atom from Tabletop Minions!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 22:59:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>GameFor App - Adventure Party #85</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 23:01:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>GameFor presents their community connect app for gamers at GAMA 2018!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 22:00:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 03:21:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi, one of the GameFor guys here. We are just a small group of devs and designers that have been building apps and websites for many years, this was our passion project and we just launched... but we are growing fast. The thing that is different about GameFor, is that even if you do not see other users right away locally to you, there are still things to do. We are built around stores and events. Make sure you favorite local gaming stores are listed (if not let us know), post a 'Looking for Players' post... there might be others not willing to be the first. Let gamers around you know. Getting the word out about GameFor is going to grow it and the communities. We just added the first part of our groups/clubs support and are working to get the rest of the initial features (like custom locations) added shortly. We are also working on multi-lingual support and other large features. We also try to add small features and fixes/improvements release about every 2 weeks. So far we are seeing an amazing growth and support and we want to see that continue so that more people find more game events which means more gaming. See something missing? Let us know and we will see about getting it into an upcoming release. See you around the game table!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 03:45:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are definitely worldwide launched, just sometimes harder to find in app stores in some countries than others, but getting better. We are working on multi-lingual support as well though to make it easier for everyone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 03:49:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>We also have just started a sub-reddit for everyone as well if you are interested. Would love to see users use it to give us suggestions on items you want to see added and how you are using the app to find more games. - gt; https://www.reddit.com/r/gamefor/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 04:15:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>for playing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 04:21:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>In a friendly session, I generally do if it is fixable (not something that other moves were based on and would be difficult to rollback to). I also will sometimes say no if this is happening more than once in the same game and/or they are not paying attention. I like to remind myself that while I always want to win, having fun and learning is why I play games... so if it helps that, I try to make it work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 15:20:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please let us know if you continue to have issues... shoot us an email at support@iamgamefor.com and we will help you out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What to do when there are no events around you...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 15:39:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even though we are signing up a new players and verifying new stores every day... it happens. You log into GameFor, and there are no events near you. Now what? **1. Create an Event** You do not have to be a store or group to create an event. Decide on what you want to play and set up an event near you. We have heard more than a few stories of users trying this out and finding that there were more local users than they thought. Look at nearby LFP listings for ideas of events that others might be looking for. **2. Talk to your local store(s) about verifying on GameFor.** It is FREE, and most stores can get all of their current scheduled events listed on their store in less than an hour. Letting your local stores know that you are using GameFor, tells them that the time to enter their events is worth it. **3. Create a 'Looking For Player (LFP)' listing** This works even if there are events near you, but not ones that you want to play. Let people know that you are around and looking for games. Some stores are already looking at these to decide on what events they should host. We are growing, and a lot of that growth is coming from players letting their friends, groups and stores know about GameFor. Let us know if you have other ways that you have found that work in getting events growing by you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 15:41:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>We just verified a store in Singapore. If that store is not near you (or even if it is), let other stores know! Here are some other things you can do: https://www.reddit.com/r/gamefor/comments/8795q0/what_to_do_when_there_are_no_events_around_you/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 17:35:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>:) No problem. Let us know if there is any translations that will benefit that area. We have been putting together our list of languages to support for our first rounds of localization.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What are you experiences with using the GameFor app?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 21:41:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Gamefor's Uncle Atom interviewed by Beasts of War at Adepticon 2018</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 23:04:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 18:35:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Saw a few people coming from this link, wanted to share our website with more information and an iOS link: http://iamgamefor.com/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 18:37:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have been getting a lot of new users from the Glasgow area. I would check out the "Looking for Players" area in the app if there are not already events near you. Should be able to help you find some players nearby. http://iamgamefor.com/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 19:16:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>At this rate... maybe another hour or so...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 04:43:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair questions. Let me see if I can answer them as best as I can. We are doing some work with publishers and have plans to streamline game entry into GameFor, we just have some other features that are currently being worked on ahead of it. But that will be coming. So far, we have seen very rapid growth. We have grown by 500% in user accounts in just the past month, signing up verified stores daily and developing a number of features and promotions that we are that we feel will continue to cause us to grow. That being said, we are gamers, and this project is our passion. While we have a tech background, this project was never meant to be a "Build it and Sell it" product. We are in this industry to help it grow and to help others grow. We are using our knowledge and experience to really help get more people playing more games. We are in this for the long run. We are definitely talking with companies and partnering with ones that we feel will help GameFor grow and are aligned with our goals. We are always open for talks, and we love to hear feedback on how GameFor is (or is not) working for users, so that we can make it better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 04:56:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I went from 2.5 to 5. I think others nailed some of the bigger items (the removal of THAC0, change in AC.. and such). If the person has a chance to read the PHB, that can help. I found watching some Critical Role or other YouTube videos that ran some 5e, I was able to see pretty quickly how the general flow worked with actions, bonus actions and such. If you help them to make sure their player sheet is right (using a free one on DnDBeyond might help here), keeping them with a more vanilla class/race for their first time out, and just reminding them what dice to roll (ie. Perception check, everyone roll a d20) to get the rust out... they will be fine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are you participating in International Tabletop Day this year?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 17:15:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>This year's Tabletop Day (https://www.tabletopday.com/) is on April 28, 2018. We have added support to list and view events in GameFor, and the team is attending some of the activities at one of our LFGS. Do you have plans? If so... what are they? If you are in our local area and do not have plans yet, why not join the GameFor team?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Geek and Sundry - These Gamers Built An App To Help You Find Local Gaming Events, Clubs  amp; Groups | Geek and Sundry</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 21:44:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 16:24:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another member of the team here. We are still seeing a lot of lurkers, vs people posting. Which is why a lot of previous similar apps have failed. This is why we have been working with FLGS to get their events added to the app to help fill the "empty" gap. We are definitely more Wargaming heavy at the moment (though less than we were) because our designer has a very successful YouTube channel that servers the wargaming crowd and they made up a large portion of the early adopters. Between the G amp;S article last week, working with them for International Tabletop Day, attending conventions and getting ready to do more advertising, we are starting to close that gap, but we need board gamers to help us too. I did start a quick subreddit post to talk about how: https://www.reddit.com/r/gamefor/comments/8795q0/what_to_do_when_there_are_no_events_around_you/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 16:27:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Matt from the GameFor team here. We are more Wargaming heavy because when we launched, one our designers talked about it on his YouTube channel that is very large in that community so that group were the biggest early adopters. That is starting to change. I am just starting to play some miniature and rpg games now, but I come from a very heavy board game background so we were definitely targeting that genre as well. Group support that is in the app and the full version coming in 3.0 next month should really help the board game groups. We have been working with several early adopters to make sure it helps them and will reduce their costs that they see with using Meet Up and helping gamers to find them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 16:49:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>And this is why we focused on in-store events right from the start. We will be allowing additional locations soon, but feel we are doing it in a way to still push towards stores and public locations first. We really do not want anyone to get eaten.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 16:50:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep, we have had more than a few do the same and suddenly see that there were a bunch of other users around them that just did not take the initiative. Also make sure your local game stores know about us and that you are looking to find their events in the app. Our local area was targeted first and the adoption and event postings in our area is really growing fast. (Appleton, WI if you want to look at it yourself)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 21:37:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is odd. It is launched worldwide and we have had many German users so far. I will investigate further.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 00:25:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Custom locations will be out in a couple of weeks. And if a store is not listed, let us know and we will add it. We have added over 300 since we launched submitted by owners and users. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 04:12:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not yet, it is something we want to bring is soon though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 04:15:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are definitely more RPG/Wargaming events in the app right now. That is because our initial early adopters came from that realm, mostly due to our designer (Uncle Atom) has a large YouTube channel that is based in that genre. With the Geek amp;Sundry article, our support for Tabletop Day and our future plans, it should start to even out in the next few months. We are only 4 months old in the store, and only have been starting to market in the past 2.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 00:08:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, found where we missed setting that. Appreciate the help! Will be fixed in the 3.0 release.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>3.0 is available in the App Stores for both platforms</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 23:49:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>**New features in version 3.0!** We've been working hard to get the newest requested features and other pieces we've been working on behind the scenes into the most recent version of the GameFor app. If you haven't updated yet, what are you waiting for? **You've asked for custom locations, and now they're here!** The one request we've gotten from gaming groups and clubs more than any other has been access to custom locations for their events. Not all gaming groups and clubs meet and share events at gaming stores. However, for safety concerns, we need to make sure that events open to the public stay in public safe spaces. That's where 'verified custom locations' come in with the new groups and clubs subscriber model. If you and your friends want to have events in custom public locations - like libraries, pubs, restaurants, church basements and more - you now can by signing up your group to become a paid subscription group. For less than five dollars (USD) a month (or use offer code **V3LAUNCH** before 7/1/2018 to get one dollar off for the lifetime of your subscription), your group can have as many members as you want (free groups have a limit of 10 members) and you can get public locations verified by GameFor so you can have your events outside of a local store. **Other new features in version 3.0:** You can now link to the social media platforms you like to use (including Board Game Geek) in your user profile. This will allow people who look at your profile to find your Twitter, check out your YouTube channel, or even look at your game collection on BGG. You can also list what languages you speak in your profile, which can greatly help some of our European users. We've also worked on bug fixes and other code optimizations, so help make your GameFor experience even better. Download the new version and let us know what you think at feedback@iamgamefor.com!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pair Of Dice Paradise - GameFor Update - Big announcement! With Uncle Atom of Tabletop Minions</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:58:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 23:21:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey Matt from GameFor here. Right now groups have the capability since we found that is who normally does these types of events. This is still relatively new and we are testing some features with group leaders. Once we feel that everything is set and working correctly, we will start allowing individuals to do this as well. Groups also can do repeating events for weekly and bi-weekly gaming nights. Hope this helps!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 23:31:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey! Just encase you have not heard... no more coupon codes... everything is now FREE. Read our full explanation here: [Blog Post](https://medium.com/@iamgamefor/effective-immediately-using-gamefor-for-your-groups-and-clubs-including-custom-locations-is-now-4a3e279e46c0)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found a gaming group? FLGS? How has GameFor helped you play more games?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 16:39:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have gotten a number of fun stories sent to us these last few months. Would love to have people share them here. It might also help others understand how the app might help them. Share away!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 17:31:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fun story from Origins 2018, not in-app. Was talking to a couple that run a gaming group in Pennsylvania about how they could get the app running for their group. Guy that was looking at stuff at the booth next to us over heard them, and said something like "I wish I had a gaming group near me in Pennsylvania, that sounds like fun, but I am pretty much in the middle of Amish country". The couple ask him where and they quickly realized they were just minutes from one another. They exchanged information and it sounded like another person had found a gaming group near him that he did not know existed. It was fun for us to see what we keep hearing about happening inside the app, happening right in front of us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 03:45:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Normally board game cafes are added. If that location is hosting location backed gaming events we add them. Otherwise adding them for your group is easy to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 22:11:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it makes a lot of sense. Have to keep this under control and all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If they decide to ban everyone how will we know who is left? Mods might be playing the long game to clean up Reddit. All of the  #8220;Posting so I get banned #8221; is only encouraging it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 22:14:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 22:15:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my favorite interviews to date. The green screen post edit was absolute gold.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Best /r/ Recruiting Idea Ever? The Ban was a lie!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 18:07:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Petition to make Bruce BANner our mascot on our isle of misfits.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 05:40:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 05:53:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now that would be fun. Except for the ghosts. They can screw off right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 05:58:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is talk that after the next movie we might all be released from the stone. We will have to see</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So.... did Jedi make it? I think that is what I really wanted to know.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 06:04:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 03:35:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Community centers, churches, coffee houses, some pubs and libraries are some of the more popular locations. Many of those I have used myself and I see a lot of people using them in GameFor when a FLGS is not an option.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 03:36:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>You got an upvote just for my spit take.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pair of Dice Paradise - GameFor Update  amp; Big announcement! With Uncle Atom of Tabletop Minions</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 17:36:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 17:41:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh sorry, still new-ish to Reddit. Thought I had been active enough in BoardGames to share the video. No worries. Thanks for letting me know!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 19:50:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey one of the devs here. Thanks for finding us (and sharing!). We are indeed still rather new. Pushed to the stores for a soft launch at the very end of 2017, and did an official launch in Mid-March. So far we have 6200 stores listed worldwide, over 300 of them verified and listing their events in the app already. 25,000+ downloads (over 18,500 accounts created), most of that since the March timeframe. We are still growing and adding features. 3.X has been focused on Group support, to try and fill the need that we found was lacking with Facebook groups and MeetUp (and free!). We are still working on getting the word out (attending conferences and trade shows, talking to game stores, doing interviews). If you are a content producer, and want to talk to us check us out. We have past interviews and articles posted on our site: [https://iamgamefor.com/news](https://iamgamefor.com/news) Please feel free to try it out (very small app), and let us know what you think. We are building this for the gaming community to help FLGS and groups and gamers all connect more easily. Just a small developer/design team from Wisconsin that make apps and websites for a living, and wanted to build something we felt the community needed. We have a subreddit as well: /r/gamefor</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 20:11:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Question, where are you at? The one issue we are finding is that a lot of people that use the app like to lurk, so while we might have 30 gamers in your area, nobody is trying to schedule events or creating a "Looking For Players" post. So we sometimes see posts like this or get emails, but then someone does a post, creates a group or whatever... and that area becomes really active. The team has been brainstorming some ideas so that the app can give you a better indication of potential gamers in your area for upcoming releases. If you have any ideas, I would love to hear them. I also created this post for ideas as well: [Reddit Post](https://www.reddit.com/r/gamefor/comments/8795q0/what_to_do_when_there_are_no_events_around_you/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 20:18:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>No problem, I appreciate the feedback. Yeah there is definitely people in that area just from looking at Google Analytics for people that have downloaded the app. We have been trying to carefully balance helping people find events in their area, without forcing any user to 1) Create an account until they are ready to post (guest mode is pretty functional), 2) Be searchable by others if they are not ready to be. Between player safety and player privacy, those are two biggest concerns whenever we look at new features or changes. Sometimes that makes the app look more sparse in some areas as we grow... but we had (so far) only positive feedback regarding people feeling that they were safe using the app.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 20:21:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>For anyone reading this later.... all group features are now available for free (and will remain free)!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 20:35:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the feedback. Expiring events notifications are upcoming. Members of the group already will get notifications for new chat messages, or new events created (or update/cancelled). 3.3 in testing right now will show RSVPs in the app (username if going, and # of watching), and allow fully private groups so that only the "Share" link will let people find your group. We did Origins, but did not submitted in time for GenCon. I might be there for another project our company is doing for a paid client, and we have a few people going that are planning to hand out information cards and wear shirts, but we are always looking for more grassroots volunteers. We have been talking to the BGG people about banner ads as well, just trying to find the right time to try them out to see what kind of response we get. Some of the group features were must-haves for the boardgame crowd we felt before we went to heavy on the marketing there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 20:54:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the feedback. Search/Friends is one of the bigger upcoming set of features, as well as expanding the search filters. Right now if you want to view events outside your area, you can do it (I admit not a great UX... which is why we are working on it), but turning off location settings and changing your app location. This will work for Groups, Events and Looking For Players (Store Finder already allows you to search in other places). The other stuff, as you said, will be tricky with privacy... which is one of the reasons search is taking longer. Having people in your area join your group is how we are doing it in our area (no cost, so add multiple groups as needed... for example I have a BoardGame groups and Wargaming group with different people). But adding friends will be coming so that this is a little easier... we just have to include reporting/blocking/invisible modes likely as well at the same time. But definitely agree that it is needed. Wish we were at a point that our team could work on this full time and get these features to everyone faster! As a side note... if you see an event (or attend an event), you should be able to view that user's profile and see other events (and groups) that the user is a part of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 21:01:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey. Great questions. Let me try to answer (let me know if I am unclear or missed anything). Ohio has become a lot more active in the past month since we were at Origins and met with a lot of groups and stores in that area. We do not show users that are in your area, only events or post from people looking to find gamers. This allows people to use the app and be as anonymous as they would like. We are looking into ways to give users a better indication of potential users in your area without compromising user privacy. In March, we were likely still on version 2.X, so at the time events were limited to be hosted at FLGS. With 3.X we have now allowed groups to schedule events at private locations (for people wanting to set up games at each others houses) for private events, and allow users to get locations verified as public for public events (think libraries, coffee shops, community centers, churches, schools...). We did this approach to try to keep people safe while finding gaming events around you. So if you see a public event, you can feel confident that this is being held in a public area. It usually takes  lt;1 hour to get a location verified (usually depends on if we are online or not, sometimes as little as 5 min with some of the tools we created for verifying). We will looking at opening this up for users as well in an upcoming release, once we feel that the approach we took with groups is working and have incorporated any feedback we have received.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 21:11:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah with private groups and private events you essentially will get that, you just have to have your friends in your group... but yes that will make that a lot nicer for more spontaneous gaming!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 01:36:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the insight, we will give it a look. Sounds like a great way to handle that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 04:25:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, just got to the verification, should have gotten a message. You are all set! Thank you for reaching out again!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 04:28:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is definitely a need for more users being active to make the app useful. Checkout my other post on how to get started on getting your area active if you are interested. Us developers now game regularly with a few people we never knew were in our area playing because we started a local group and someone saw it and replied. I appreciate the feedback either way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 15:41:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah one and done. Nice one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 02:45:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meh. Alec Baldwin stole this from the Russians years ago. Sean Connery helped.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 19:31:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>For me, if I know a game can have a score that greatly varies is nice when playing with friends. It makes close margins of victory (or defeat) seem more significant. But for family games, anything to keep me from blowing away the kids (so I do not have to deliberately lose and can show them different strategies) is a huge plus. So yeah, going with the default "it depends".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New 40k Kill Team Unboxing and Painted Terrain - Tabletop Minions</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 21:57:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 22:03:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>This looks amazing and the price is really good. This will be an even better way to get new players to 40k. Anyone else planning on getting it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 00:19:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Came here just to say that. Thank you for doing my good work for me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 00:47:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Been a few times. Have not seen the memorial. Where is it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 05:16:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had a high schooler do this to my son who was ten at the time for a foul ball. Just took it from him and sat back down with his parents. Game was almost done so my wife took him to the car because was in near tears. I went and found the spot where you can get Game souvenirs and got him one of the strikeout balls. He still keeps it next to his bed. Look on his face when I got it for him was 1000x better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 05:14:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>!snapme</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 05:15:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>!snapbuddy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How many were snapped?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 05:19:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just saw my number and did not realize how high I was. Was curious how close I came to not being one of the chosen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Origins 2018: Day 2</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 21:55:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 21:58:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey thank you for letting us know. Typically our process is pretty close to what you already did... let us know ([stores@iamgamefor.com](mailto:stores@iamgamefor.com) is the most often monitored, but places like this work as well), we then verify similar to what you described by checking out website/email/Facebook responses, and then we mark them as closed. This removes them from the listing but does not remove any history so that we can re-add if a store re-opens or was marked closed incorrectly. Again, thank you for taking the time to let us know!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 21:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am shocked, really did not think they would get it. But how well they did with Fireball Island, it is definitely deserved. HeroesQuest next?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 23:34:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just need it to be available to the mass market again :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 17:50:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>A female deer!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 00:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>So my kid wants a new Ten Box?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Gameosity Podcast Episode #20: Adam Loper on GameFor</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 07:37:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:07:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would be less interested in what the dog said compared to the fact that the dog spoke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 14:15:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. Same. That was both nice and evil of the OP to offer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 03:46:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very nice. Strong chills.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 03:48:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or his snap would just remove two people on another balanced seesaw.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 03:52:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>What makes you think it was random and not perfect balanced?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 04:05:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>But maybe he.... crap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 04:17:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shit. Sorry about that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 04:46:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry! I keep fucking up. That was the last time!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 17:03:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Upvote. Been a while since I have seen a long joke here I had not seen before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Our village #8217;s windmill must be in distress!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 17:42:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 19:32:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Done in one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 19:42:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something like this? [sheet](http://rolesrules.blogspot.com/2012/09/putting-two-great-encumbrance-ideas.html?m=1)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 20:15:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>NP. Not finding anything else close yet. Will post if I do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 03:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow. Sad this is needed. But great idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 04:01:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know. Figured at least get [this](http://whatculture.com/tv/the-big-bang-theory-21-easter-eggs-you-probably-missed?page=16)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 05:20:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Digital versions I use DND Beyond. Otherwise my FLGS. They usually have sales or other benefits to buying in store.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 05:23:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>What does that mean in non technical terms?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 06:28:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 06:45:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool. Was not sure if it was a promotional thing or what.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 04:16:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lost me at the ending. Something to tie the stab wounds to the original death or the thing leaving would really help. Other than that I enjoyed it. Thanks for sharing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 04:18:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Critical Role is great. Critical Hit is what I listened to that got me back into DnD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 04:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great build up and ending!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 06:15:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Paperback is my personal favorite. Word logic and deck building combined.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 06:22:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I own it. But it has not made the table since I got it. Summer break is ending. Will give it a try. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 14:32:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because he had not said anything she diagnosed him with laryngitis (losing your ability to talk). Him asking a question meant she was wrong. Close to a dad joke but made me smile. Got an upvote from me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 14:37:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>A: Oh. Good idea! I will post it there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 05:31:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for sharing. That was really interesting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 22:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>You might also want to contact the states insurance commissioner office. I had an issue getting an answer from SF about a different matter. The office was able to tell me exactly what SF was legally supposed to do and how I should approach them to get answers. And how they would get involved if I did not get anywhere with it. Situation was resolved 5 min into my next phone call.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 22:43:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Np. Sorry for you loss. Hope you can get some answers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bad password instructions... 1 special characters... cannot have special characters</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 05:41:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 05:47:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is horrible. I hope you like crumbs for breakfast...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 05:57:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>It actually allowed like 4, but had to be the special characters they wanted me to use. And the "s" on characters annoyed me too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 06:04:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually this was web for a top 3 cell provider. Part of their "New and better security". I was on Chrome on a Mac though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 14:48:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>That makes me sad. Upvote for you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 15:00:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only if their parents played</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 02:58:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would probably end some dates pretty quickly.  #8220;Let me explain! #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 03:01:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>A thesaurus almost makes more sense as he has found the word sorrow already?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 03:06:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like he could get a job as a spy though. You know.... like us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 03:16:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Arggg. There are comments in the comments section. I hate this app!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 07:15:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope the community rises to the occasion to help out. It is the yeast they could do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 07:21:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>And stories like this is why I should not check out this section before bed. Can you still whistle?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 07:53:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmmm. Woulda only guessed they were protected in Iran.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 07:55:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://youtu.be/iIpfWORQWhU</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 07:57:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least they are red...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 08:00:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just leveling up my dad jokes. Seriously good find though. They are crazy here and I am in the middle of Wisconsin...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 08:03:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Geez. Good x-post for r/nosleep</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 08:11:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man. I have had a similar thing (early gmail beta user so simple address) but no luck getting revenge. Thanks for giving me hope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 13:10:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now if you could do it every time you got Karma... we could all join in the fun!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 13:14:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. Only major thing was when someone in the Army was sending personnel files to me instead of his actual address and would not respond to replies. Had to report that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 13:22:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Took me a minute to find it. Seems destined for r/OSHA as well. Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 13:26:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s exactly what I said</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 13:36:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just think of the pile of scraps that contain the missing piece somewhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 15:43:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice. When I started r/gamefor, making sure we verified email addresses was number one on my list because of stuff like this. I had some guy who refused to pay his Verizon bill for 12 months... and Verizon had no way to respond to them (required last 4 of SSN to reset password or anything, and always sent from no-reply). Someday my boat will come in.  #8203; I did almost get a cruise. My name is also the same as a "famous" economist, and was asked by a college to join their faculty on an Alaskan cruise to speak with them. I accepted and asked them which of my computer programming talks I should give. They revoked the invite...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 16:37:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn QA Engineers...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 19:59:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Got it. I love the template, saving that for myself. Just a pain when you get it from the no-reply emails, but a general service/support email is probably available to send this to instead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:13:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>New to me. Easy upvote.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:14:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow. Did not know. Thanks OP! Is this why prenatal and neonatal heartbeats are so fast or something else?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:17:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I admit. Spent a few minutes to try to explain how logic would have saved ya. Came up short. Damn computer cheater.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:19:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me watching the video:  #8220;And a video I will not show the kids... or maybe it #8217;s a good idea #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:20:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Arghhh. One job!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:21:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay that was great. Will be using this tomorrow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:23:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was surprisingly not shitty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:23:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>And that wife was the OP...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:27:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Karma is not scarce. We should all get it. +1 from me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:29:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because our smart forefathers made a system that could change since they knew they would mess something up but no one wants to admit that a 50 round semi-auto will not aide in overthrowing our government if it becomes corrupt as they tried to protect, but removing it could limit casualties overall.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:30:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep and the  #8220;any size you need #8221; ones just have more spots to rip.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:35:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seriously this company is going as low as it can go these past few weeks. Need an FCC or someone that can actually protect consumers again. Sorry for your loss OP. If it is a burden set up a quick GoFundMe and I will gladly help. This is just the worse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:36:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! Appreciate the info!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:43:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m taking note of your attitude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;ll get no symphony from me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:50:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well you orchestrated this whole rest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:59:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. And I was looking forward to sleeping tonight too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 07:01:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I apologize if I struck a chord. Let #8217;s leave one another in a symbol of harmony.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 09:53:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since 76 was before and I do not know what happens in it. Hard to say that the events of the game or events after and before 2 did not do something. Short of being on the creative team, not sure you can guarantee that you are right. That all said. Karma for me is less about right and more about showing who is a decent person so I will give ya an upvote. And heck, been a while since I played 2... could have been more specific than I remembered and you are exactly right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 09:57:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>For good measure let #8217;s duet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 10:00:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Totally. And agree that it is unlikely. I swear some people just vote down or revote what others did without consideration. But thus the world of fake internet points.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 08:01:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really? That is too bad. :(. Came to say Etsy but did not know about that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 08:10:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I ask you if you are a mod you have to tell me if you are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is your army big enough?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 23:28:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 23:39:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>From Rick and Morty / D amp;D crossover comic #1. Made me laugh. Hope it will for others too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 22:46:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the share. Why unless they are rude to me I am nice to customer reps. Not their fault and I am sure they would be willing to do what they can to help if they could. Karma is a bitch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 23:09:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because you are doing it completely wrong. You pull that tab. Don #8217;t rip it sideways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 23:11:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Arghhh. Well then that sucks. Seen a few on here that pull it the way you are showing. Start with the whole tab. Sometime you might have to unroll the edges. Looks like that is cause too much resistance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Was excited for the extra drawer space outside our bathroom in the new house. But I let my wife choose her side first.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 23:16:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 23:25:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>What sound does a Stormtrooper gun make at church? Pew! Pew! Pew! Pew! Pew! Pew! Pew! Pew! Pew! Pew! Pew! Pew! ...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 23:32:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was thinking that or planing the back side of the one door frame. Just have not gotten to it yet and drives me a little nuts when I think about it. Since it was done about 10 years ago with the previous owners. Wish they had fixed it or made the builders (was an extension)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 23:39:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good call. Will do. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 23:45:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no! Sorry. Thought I had it muted. Volume was off on my phone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 00:01:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>My same thought. Would imagine lights and alarms would be going off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 00:07:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Arghhh. Resisting urge to remove my dumbness. But let it live on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 00:09:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I assume before trim went up. But maybe the house shifted?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 00:21:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. Was an empty zip lock bag with white label area that has fallen in (had to go check what it was)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 00:31:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>No... but realized I had zero clue what it was. Had not noticed it before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 00:36:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>But then the drawers would be off centered and I would have to make a new post. Would be hard to move them small enough without the other screw holes interfering.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 00:37:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>New to us. But still a valid observation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 01:04:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am waiting for some nice Reddit user to tell us what he found...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 01:19:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still would have to take the door trim off to get into the drawers... but that does sound like a clean option. Thanks! (upvoted)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 01:37:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Planer or belt sander (have both). Sander does seem easier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:03:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Metric/Imperial System conversion. Like Miles vs. Kilometers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:06:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like where you are going with that. Though my phone draining has been a little crazy. Will definitely update everyone with the fix.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:18:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely good advice for everyone. In our area, new houses have a 1-year warranty... or did on our first home... so we had the opportunity to get some stuff fixed that first year that was noticed post move-in. This was an existing home (new to us). We checked water pressure, lights, flushing toilets (most drawers), just missed this. And with the great deal we got, not sure we would have complained. I do a lot of stuff around the house, so will be able to fix it (and got some better tips already from everyone... so will be better than what I was thinking I would do).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:19:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL. True, and since I fit everything into the drawers in the bathroom, would have to be a jerk not to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:43:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. To be fair... almost a 5,000 sq-ft house with a finished basement and an extra 1 car garage... and the previous owner re-model has cabinets everywhere. I think There are 15 doors in that bathroom alone. Not an inspector, but not sure it is something they would mark down (but I am sure would have given us a heads up if they saw it), so if it is not a checkable item... probably easy to miss.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:48:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good point. That would really make me annoyed since this trim is not available anymore. (We found out when we re-modeled a room in the basement that had been the only one not updated in the whole house for some reason... and had to custom cut everything, since the whole house is done in that style, and my OCD could not handle a mismatch in 1 room)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:54:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:01:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is an entry-way vanity outside the bathroom door, leads to walk-in closet. Because yuck. Found one house like that once (white shag to boot), and that was when I refused to look at it more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:19:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep, exactly what I am going to do. Of all of the suggestions, this seems the easiest and less prone to me making something worse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:21:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think her and my daughter? This is outside the actual master bathroom, so I think they both do their hair here since they do not have to wait for someone to exit a bathroom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:24:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love it. When I get it fixed, will post both sides... but feel free :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:01:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>The was fun! Thanks for sharing. You were lucky to have known her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:36:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>More like #4. Enter witness protection or being last rites. I would rather go kick over some bikes in front of a clubhouse than do that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:37:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope, outside. This is a small ready area outside the bathroom door between the master bedroom and closet. I will try to include it in the "fixed" video. Definitely understand the confusion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:38:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>:) I have two. Hence only mildly frustrated. Just need to get around to that part of fix up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:40:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. So I can fix it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:49:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is hitting the door trim. Will have to slim it down to fix. Otherwise would be greatly infuriating. Just another thing on my To Do list.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:51:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats! Best advice I got when I closed my first house was this... "There are always going to be projects. And special projects require special tools. So you always get an excuse to go to the hardware store and buy yourself something when you need to" Since then, I have a pretty well equipped woodshop and with the help of friends and Youtube, can fix most things in the house (I leave high voltage and wiring into a fusebox to an electrician). Enjoy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:52:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, great call. Love trying to get people praise when I can. I figure it probably happens too rarely. Good to hear I am not alone!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:04:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep exactly. There is a full set of drawers and sink in there as well, but exactly what this is for. Daughter uses it as well so that she does not have people waiting on her to get out of the bathroom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:17:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>??? These are built in cabinets... (I am so waiting for another damn wooosh)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:26:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why not? Keeps cabinets from being off-symmetrical and since this the backside of that entry, being slightly slimmer should be unnoticeable. I am not seeing a downside, but if there is one... please share!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:32:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Suggestion from a few people is that the trim went on after. Not sure why they would do it that way, but makes sense to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:36:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow... this far in, and I believe the first pun. Bravo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:19:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have 2 drawers and cabinet space in the bathroom. So no real need, and she needs the space more than I do. Will use it when I get this fixed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:25:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably "my" side because it is broken.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:28:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>We just remodeled a room downstairs (only one that was not touched out of many) and trim is no longer made, had to custom order ones to match for that room (40 or so doors in the house, and windows all have matching trim as well). For fun... we had the stain matched for us... but they gave us the wrong one. Got halfway through the custom wood before realizing it. Now have to work out with the paint/stain company to get the right version and replace the wood.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:32:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Makes sense. Wife is with you when she got home and I caught her up on this thread going crazy. Had some PMs that had suggestions from cabinet people on some other things I can do to the mounts as well that I will probably try first, but yeah this may be my fix afterall.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:57:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. This is outside the bathroom. Hallway between bedroom and closet. Right side is this, left side is door to bathroom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:58:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or someone who does not carpet the bathroom. This is outside it. Slate tile in the bathroom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>