<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject9197</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The combining of 2 campaigns and the boss that ended the world.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 11:57:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was dming 2 games of dnd 5e. The second group came about due to interest after word spread that i was running a game. However, due to the fact that my first game already had 7 players, i created a second group, with 8 players. A hell of a lot of work, but made for a lot of fun. The two groups played independently for several months, only aware of the other's adventures through conversations. The two groups would soon realize that their campaigns were set on the same continent when the second group discovered the ruins of a town the first group had destroyed. (long story about an adult white dragon etc etc). This discovery came about when one of the players recognized the name of the town from an old conversation, and sure enough, they eventually discovered the name of one of the other campaign's characters engraved on a wall. (1 character had died to the white dragon. He was renowned for forgetting his name when he was revived, so they inscribed his name so he would find it when he came back). Both groups would find little things like this linking the two campaigns, and as the two grew more powerful, they began to hear word of the other's feats. They were not destined to meet until the warlock of group 1 discovered a statue, holding an ancient evil. He broke the statue, unleashing the evil that escaped into the world, where it festered and grew more powerful as time went by. Both groups became aware of the darkening world, and the once lively forests and plains that were beginning to die. Eventually, they'd discover the cause of this chaos. A night walker. (For those who don't know; think 20ft tall shadow giant of pure evil and darkness. Very powerful magic). The groups were both lvl 6 at this point (I leveled them up slowly because they felt that rushing through was boring). When Group 2 came across this nightwalker for the first time, they realized very early into the fight that they were incredibly outmatched. They ended up fleeing, only barely escaping with their lives. That was when the party bard asked me if he could send out a message. Intrigued, i asked him what he would like this message to say. He told me that he would like to put out a notice for groups of adventurers like them to band together to defeat this foe. Little did he know I had already planned this, but I enjoyed the idea so much I let him do it. The very next game, group 1 found a notice in their home town, detailing the call for aid from the bard. The players knew this was the other group, their characters had heard word of this other party. Sure enough, they started heading off to meet this other party. 2 games later. Chaos. For the first time in almost a year, all 15 players sat at the same table, their characters telling stories and greeting each other as new friends. I was feeling pretty overwhelmed to say the least, but it was an amazing feeling. Like the Infinity War of D amp;D. They came together, and ventured into a nearby forest, now dubbed, 'The Dead Woods', due to its decayed state after the NightWalker's habitation. After formulating a plan that took 3 hours out of game to come up with, they finally engaged the Night Walker. 5 hours. The fight took 5 hours. In expectation of the sudden influx of players, i had buffed the nightwalker's stats slightly to cope with the heavily outweighed action economy. This lent a hand into creating the most intense fight any of us had ever seen. After the 3rd round, every turn of the nightwalker would claim a life, if not several. Finger of Death, Cone of Cold, Crown of Madness, Blight. You name it, this monster cast it. A memorable moment was the death of both party's barbarians. They had ran in to strike the nightwalker with their axes, screaming bloody fury. Group 1's cleric was close behind them, keeping them buffed. Cone of Cold, on already weakened foes, wiped out all three of them. 4 and a half hours later. 12 of the 15 had fallen. The night walker stood, weak and almost out of spell slots, facing down the final three players. A wizard, a fighter, and the hexblade warlock that had broken the statue in the first place. The table was silent as the three gave their final goodbye's to each other, in an amazing show of roleplay and friendship, and jumped in to deal as much damage as they could. Half an hour later and with only 28 hp left, the nightwalker slew the final enemy, the wizard and emerged victorious. The table was silent as i described how the continent was consumed by darkness, the nightwalker calling in more reinforcements from the shadowfel to combat the waves of adventurers rising up to challenge it. When all was done, all 15 players congratulated themselves and thanked me for giving them the best game they'd ever had. No one was a sore loser about being killed. They all felt that they had played their part and that I had just played smart enough to barely scrape a win. Both campaigns ended, and i don't think i'll ever be able to top that in my future of dming.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 00:29:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Many thanks. It was chaotic af and unbelievably stressful but my god was it worth it. Cleaning up after everyone had left was a bitch though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 00:31:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>We set a dystopian campaign in the remains of that world. Only 5 players though. Very night shade and shadow fel heavy. Fun though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 09:11:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. I rolled in front of them so they could see i didn't fudge. There were several lost opportunities, such as fireballs, that just happened to roll low damage on their parts. Ultimately, it was close, but i expected at least a few deaths. I had to play as smart as i could just to scrape by a victory for the nightwalker. 15 v 1, even with a lot of power, is extremely difficult to win</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 01:36:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>MOUNTAIN MAAMMMAAAAAAA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 11:21:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Motive for first kill. Party hated the barbarian. The barbarian was an alcoholic character that frequently threatened to abandon the ranger to die if the bbeg caught up to them (It was after her because of a mark in her am). He even challenged all of them to a 6v1 bare fist fight and almost came out on top. I told him that he might be abandoned and he was accepting of that. The player is nice, the character was not, and after he was abandoned, i gave him the option of finding a way back to them or creating a new character. He decided to create a new one. IC and OOC, the bard and ranger were getting really pissed at the cleric for constantly following them around. I talked to him about letting people have their own little moments, (everyone had at least a few of them), and he'd say ok, but then just keep doing it. Therefore, i believed that if the ranger could get away with it, she was justified. If she couldn't get away with it, she would be punished by the party, and she accepted that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 11:23:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Motive for first kill. Party hated the barbarian. The barbarian was an alcoholic character that frequently threatened to abandon the ranger to die if the bbeg caught up to them (It was after her because of a mark in her am). He even challenged all of them to a 6v1 bare fist fight and almost came out on top. I told him that he might be abandoned and he was accepting of that. The player is nice, the character was not, and after he was abandoned, i gave him the option of finding a way back to them or creating a new character. He decided to create a new one. IC and OOC, the bard and ranger were getting really pissed at the cleric for constantly following them around. I talked to him about letting people have their own little moments, (everyone had at least a few of them), and he'd say ok, but then just keep doing it. Therefore, i believed that if the ranger could get away with it, she was justified. If she couldn't get away with it, she would be punished by the party, and she accepted that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 11:24:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Read my reply to comment above yours. Everyone involved was willing to accept the consequences and they all had their reasons for doing what they did. The barbarian was given the option of keeping his character, but decided not to</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 11:32:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oi, watcha doin m8</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The little mimic that could</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 07:42:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>\ gt;be me; skeleton bard. Finally not dm for a game \ gt;be not me; dwarf fighter, human sorcerer, elf ranger, tortle wizard \ gt;exploring ruined castle with dead green dragon outside \ gt;2 spooky 4 me \ gt;fight a few ghosts, I laugh at their disembodiment \ gt;stumble upon chest \ gt;alarmbells.mp3 \ gt;sorcerer nukes it \ gt;destroys half the loot inside \ gt;it was a normal chest \ gt;continue on. Fighter has a shiny new sword now \ gt;fight a few more ghosts. Ranger tries to reason with them and ask why they fight \ gt;bs about not being able to move on, yadda yadda \ gt;inform them that they are whining and should suck it up \ gt;get hit for that \ gt;hit them back \ gt;they die \ gt;normies.jpg \ gt;find another chest \ gt;alarmbells.mp3 \ gt;sorcerer nukes this one too \ gt;destroys all the loot inside \ gt;find 3rd, tiny chest \ gt;tell sorcerer not to nuke it without testing it \ gt;poke it with spear \ gt;mimic springs to action \ gt;fighter thinks it's cute \ gt;I think it is too \ gt;then it bites me \ gt;stuck to my arm \ gt;remove arm and place mimic on ground \ gt;punt that f\*cker across the room \ gt;it lets go of my arm \ gt;tortle is obsessed with transfiguration and pokemon \ gt;gottacatchemall.png \ gt;he uses shrink/enlarge to make small mimic small enough to fit in palm \ gt;ties little rope around it to make sure it can't bite him \ gt;stuffs it in his pocket \ gt;tortle repeatedly casts spell to keep the mimic small for 2 more games \ gt;mimic bides it's time \ gt;3 games later, fighting white dragon \ gt;tortle is hit \ gt;misses his appointment \ gt;mimic grows without anyone noticing except tortle \ gt;rest of us fight dragon while tortle is punished for his crimes \ gt;we kill dragon only to find tortle gone (character was eaten) \ gt;mimic is back to being a chest \ gt;is sitting on dragon loot \ gt;sorcerer attempts to open it (hasn't put 2 and 2 together) \ gt;surpise.jpg \ gt;little f\*cker bites him too \ gt;already weak and without spell slots, we're powerless to stop it as the mimic eats him too \ gt;fighter goes to kill it \ gt;down the hatch \ gt;ranger can't shoot for shit \ gt;pulls out scimitar and runs in \ gt;gone too \ gt;just me and mimic \ gt;i try explain that i wouldn't be tasty as it stumbles over \ gt;try say i have no meat on my bones \ gt;doesn't look like it understands \ gt;say fuck it and bring out my shortsword \ gt;this skeleton is going out a hero \ gt;nope \ gt;get eaten too \ gt;mfw we got tpk by a mimic that we abused \ gt;mfw karma is a bitch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 07:52:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Legend</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 08:04:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>All I can say is OOF</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Race blaming doesn't always go well</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 10:30:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>\ gt;be me; dm for 2 groups at the time \ gt;be not me; party 1: black dragonborn cleric, half elf ranger, halfling bard, half elf wizard, half elf paladin, half elf druid, human barbarian (barbarian dead. Druid player away) \ gt;staying in town \ gt;meet gnome npc who was cursed with the shrink/enlarge spell, making him small enough to fit in a hand \ gt;meet gnome everywhere \ gt;realize gnome can clone himself \ gt;tfw gnome owns half the businesses in town \ gt;cleric tries to sell giant slayer axe to the gnome \ gt;wants to buy a mace \ gt;gnome tries to undersell him by almost 30gp (in truth, i had no idea how much it was worth) \ gt;cleric gets mad, calls out his bs \ gt;gnome insists that he doesn't like paying full price, because one of his items had been stolen back off of him \ gt;tfw the thief was a black dragonborn \ gt;cleric player gets the biggest smirk on his face \ gt;ohshit.jpg \ gt;"oh is that what this is about?" he asks \ gt;gnome is visibly confused \ gt;table knows what's about to happen, several have grins on their face \ gt;cleric is basically beaming at this point \ gt;"is it because i'm black?" \ gt;table loses their shit \ gt;gnome gets flustered and tries to back track \ gt;cleric smirks, thinking he's played the winning hand \ gt;gnome insists he meant no such thing \ gt;cleric tells gnome he will be forgiven if he pays full price \ gt;rolls persuasion with advantage \ gt;2 \ gt;gnome's face becomes stone \ gt;tfw he points mace cleric wanted to buy at him \ gt;"nobody threatens me in my shop" \ gt;cleric's confident smirk fades \ gt;"all you tall folk think you can bully me into getting what you want just because i'm short huh?" \ gt;table losing their shit again \ gt;cleric's turn to backtrack \ gt;gnome places a hand on the mace \ gt;ranger finally decides to step in \ gt;apologizes for the cleric \ gt;gnome, seeing a more favorable customer focuses on her \ gt;cleric sheepishly leaves the shop as ranger buys mace for him \ gt;mfw cleric never tries to use the race card again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Traps, fear and a happy dog</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 01:46:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>\ gt;be me; DM for 2 groups (this story is for group 2) \ gt;be not me; human monk, half orc barbarian, awakened dog bard, aarakocra sorcerer, drow rogue, air genasi cleric \ gt;post tpk by mimic, pre tpk by night walker \ gt;party used to death in my campaigns \ gt;doesn't stop them from getting attached to characters \ gt;oof.png \ gt;exploring dungeon \ gt;barbarian notices a fine white dust in the center of a corridor \ gt;barbarian sprints towards it despite party's warnings \ gt;trap.jpg \ gt;walls begin to close in \ gt;"I want to snort the dust and then rage" \ gt;f\*ckingwhat.jpg \ gt;rolls strength check with advantage \ gt;nat 20 \ gt;holds back the walls from closing \ gt;inform barbarian that he just snorted crushed remains of a skeleton \ gt;barbarian accepts this knowledge without blinking \ gt;clicking.mp3 \ gt;important note: party had spent the majority of this dungeon running from a homebrew monster that wandered it's halls. Inspired by aliens from 'A Quiet Place'. Past attempts to fight it had gone horribly wrong \ gt;party loses their shit \ gt;sprints through the walls and tries to run \ gt;barbarian tries to run too, forgets he's holding the walls \ gt;dex save \ gt;barely succeeds \ gt;walls begin to retreat as soon as he's off the pressure point \ gt;clicking gets louder as monster closes in on the sound \ gt;party decides to go still and try be silent \ gt;monster walks into hallway \ gt;party freezes and tries to be silent \ gt;group stealth check \ gt;monster walks up to the trap, making a clicking sound \ gt;make perception check for it \ gt;18 \ gt;it jumps over the pressure plate, putting it right in the middle of the group \ gt;table irl goes completely silent \ gt;awakened dog bard player "i want to use minor illusion to create a sound down the hallway" \ gt;makes sound of party running away \ gt;monster sprints after the sound (party low key scared shitless as they realize monster would've easily caught them if they'd tried to run) \ gt;bard player shouts at the table "f\*ck yeah! I'm a f\*cking genius" \ gt;grin.jpg \ gt;I describe how the bard's tail begins to shake with his happiness \ gt;anyone who has a dog knows what happens next \ gt;tail starts to hit leg of cleric \ gt;leg has armour \ gt;makes repeated clanging sound \ gt;party glares at bard as the monster stops and slowly turns \ gt;ohshit.jpg \ gt;rogue decides to abandon the group and run \ gt;making lots of noise \ gt;I tell him that the monster is right on his heels \ gt;hfw i tell him to make a dex save \ gt;hfw he forgot about the trap \ gt;mfw he fails the save \ gt;rogue trips over and lands smack in the middle of the trap \ gt;player irl gives mini shriek as monster dives on his character and begins to tear him to shreds \ gt;walls close \ gt;player and monster killed instantly \ gt;party leaves dungeon \ gt;rogue rolls up new character; wizard. Proficient in perception checks based around traps</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An overly obsessed item</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 06:28:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>\ gt;be me; dm of 2 campaigns \ gt;be not me; human monk, half orc barbarian, awakened dog bard, aarakocra sorcerer, tiefling wizard, air genasi cleric \ gt;wandering around world, getting small jobs \ gt;hearing word of another group of adventurers (the other campaign's group) \ gt;explores cave \ gt;meets medusa \ gt;cut out her eyes before she can speak \ gt;beat her up as she screams \ gt;loud thud from further in the cave \ gt;ohshit.png \ gt;a large figure in a full suit of black armour steps into their torch light \ gt;achallengerapproaches.jpg \ gt;points to the medusa who still isn't dead \ gt;claims he was hired to bring her to his employer \ gt;monk says no. Claims medusa is theirs \ gt;figure draws massive sword \ gt;asks again very politely \ gt;bard barks aggressively (actually casts vicious mockery) \ gt;it doesn't work \ gt;monk runs up to punch newcomer \ gt;catches the fist \ gt;ohf\*ck.mp3 \ gt;fight ensues \ gt;6 rounds later, newcomer is dead, sorcerer is unconscious, monk is on his last death save and cleric has massive sword embedded in his chest \ gt;monk is stabilized and woken up \ gt;medusa still screaming \ gt;monk kicks her until she shuts up and walks over to body of newcomer \ gt;realize armour is undamaged \ gt;goes to touch it \ gt;armour disassembles and attaches to him \ gt;body of previous owner left in dirt \ gt;monk likes new armour \ gt;hears voice in his head \ gt;is armour \ gt;tells monk that he is it's new master \ gt;alrighty.jpg \ gt;monk learns over time that the armour can be donned and doffed by asking it (bonus action) and that it gives him immunity to physical damage from non magic weapons \ gt;next game monk wants to leave his suit so he can inspect body of gnoll he killed (armour makes it hard to kneel) \ gt;gnoll that was playing dead jumps up to attack him \ gt;rest of party is too far away to help him \ gt;he has low hp and without the armour, low ac \ gt;player thinks this is the end of his character \ gt;armour steps in front of him and grabs the gnoll \ gt;armour lifts gnoll off ground by throat and crushes it's wind pipe \ gt;monk thinks this is cool \ gt;rest of party is concerned \ gt;try to tell monk to leave the armour behind because they don't like that it's able to kill so easily \ gt;monk refuses and steps back into the armour \ gt;party gives him final word of warning before moving on \ gt;fast forward 3 games \ gt;party beginning to get concerned about monk \ gt;barely comes out of the armour anymore, even to eat and drink \ gt;players know armour is talking to him but not what. Characters have bad feeling \ gt;they try convince him to get out of the armour but he refuses \ gt;drunk patron notices argument and stumbles over \ gt;pushes monk and challenges him to a fight \ gt;monk says no \ gt;armour says yes \ gt;monk's arm is suddenly pulled forward as he sucker punches the patron \ gt;drunk guy dies immediately \ gt;monk concerned that he had no control \ gt;tries to leave the armour \ gt;armour initially refuses but relents \ gt;monk comes out \ gt;doesn't go back in for a long time \ gt;fast forward \ gt;fighting hag \ gt;monk dealing damage but getting his ass handed to him \ gt;refuses to go back into the armour despite it's insistance \ gt;hag drops him to 3 hp \ gt;finally decides to accept it \ gt;armour takes control \ gt;monk is left as a passenger as the armour obliterates the hags \ gt;asks to be let out \ gt;armour says no \ gt;monk tells party it won't let him out \ gt;is stuck in armour \ gt;party gets idea \ gt;sorcerer and wizard work together \ gt;wizard casts fireball while sorcerer casts control flames \ gt;armour begins to turn red hot after a few seconds \ gt;monk starts screaming on the inside \ gt;party tells the armour that if it doesn't let the monk go, they'll melt it \ gt;monk begs them to try something else \ gt;party doesn't relent \ gt;bits of armour begin to bend with the heat \ gt;monk taking lots of fire damage \ gt;barbarian thinks this is taking too long and jams his hand into the armour \ gt;armour is soft enough that he can push his hand through \ gt;he grabs monk and yanks him out \ gt;throws monk in nearby lake \ gt;armour begins walking towards water to retrieve monk \ gt;entire party blasting it with magic to try stop it \ gt;barbarian taking swings at the metal with his axe \ gt;bard controls the water and slams it into the armour \ gt;armour begins to steam as it cools \ gt;steam clears, armour has been partially melted \ gt;legs fused together, only 1 arm can move \ gt;they stopped it \ gt;monk comes out of water, hair is gone \ gt;barbarian's hand is coated in metal. His hand is now fastened securely to the axe \ gt;armour continues to telepathically speak to the monk long after they leave it behind, begging him to come back \ gt;mfw monk almost did several times</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 09:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>it just wanted a friend</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 09:46:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was a homebrew armour. I have the notes somewhere of stats. If you wanted to see those i could go looking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A cleric, getting charmed and the good succ</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 10:14:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>\ gt;be me; dm of 2 campaigns \ gt;be not me; human monk, awakened dog bard, half orc barbarian, tiefling wizard, aarakocra sorcerer, air genasi cleric \ gt;travelling the world, just passed town other campaign's party destroyed \ gt;worldbuilding.jpg \ gt;stumble into small town \ gt;party goes into tavern/inn \ gt;talks to inn keeper about places to stay and stuff to do in town \ gt;inn keeper describes lake, market and mini travelling circus \ gt;party pays for rooms and decides to go to circus \ gt;bard player begging party not to go. Player is terrified of clowns and is worried they'll have an encounter with them \ gt;character's tail tucked between his legs entire time they're there \ gt;exploring circus, watching performance \ gt;aarakocra told off for sitting in the rafters by guards \ gt;tries to stay there until they pull out bows \ gt;ends up spending the night in jail for ignoring guard's requests \ gt;smart enough not to resist or try break out \ gt;meanwhile in circus, air genasi player asks me if there's popcorn or other snacks \ gt;i tell him yes \ gt;decides he wants to shout the party and walks away to get them snacks and drinks \ gt;while walking to vendor, meets a stunning young lady \ gt;she tells him he's quite handsome \ gt;player is bi, character is bi. Both lean more to men. Initially not interested \ gt;roll wisdom saving throw for character behind dm screen \ gt;fail \ gt;pc is charmed by charm person, doesn't know \ gt;i describe how woman holds his arm and presses her chest against it while looking up at him \ gt;player immediately rolls for insight \ gt;because he is charmed, i tell him that she seems to genuinely find him attractive and might be dtf \ gt;raises eyebrow at me but decides to play along \ gt;asks if she'd care to join him for a trip to the lake \ gt;smoothoperator.mp3 \ gt;woman agrees, both walk off \ gt;rest of party ooc think he's gonna have some fun \ gt;ic they think it must be a long line for food \ gt;cleric and woman visit lake \ gt;cleric flirts with her by showing off magic skills \ gt;i tell him she seems entranced by it \ gt;he gives small smile and decides to be a bit more forward \ gt;tells woman she's beautiful \ gt;she blushes and scoots closer \ gt;player raises eyebrow at me and says "i do hope we're going to have a fade to black soon. Can't be disrupting pg 13 setting can we?" \ gt;if only he knew \ gt;woman holds his hand, player says he strokes her hair \ gt;goddamn.png \ gt;both lean in for kiss \ gt;i tell him she reaches behind and caress back of his head \ gt;then tell him something feels off \ gt;he opens his eyes \ gt;woman still there \ gt;sees horns \ gt;sees wings \ gt;ohshit.jpg \ gt;tries to back out \ gt;realizes hand was to stop him from doing that \ gt;rolls constitution save \ gt;fails \ gt;mfw succubus rolls 10,10,10,7,9 +5 for (5d10+5) damage \ gt;mfw player dies \ gt;party goes looking for him after getting concerned \ gt;don't find him initially \ gt;wizard sees a group of attractive women, knows cleric is a smooth operator \ gt;suggests to party "he may be getting the good . . . \*pauses and stares me dead in the eye\* . . . succ" \ gt;whole table groans. Cleric buries head in his hands \ gt;find his body next morning \ gt;body is shrivelled \ gt;cleric rolls up new character. Gnome cleric (he liked clerics and knew there was a church in the next town) \ gt;mfw everybody trash talks player for months \ gt;mfw running joke that cleric died from the good succ</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 10:20:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Archimedes' Armour of Protection Damage invulnerability: piercing, bludgeoning and slashing damage from non magical sources Telepathic link: Must be on same plane of existence Doff and Don: Bonus action. Armour is animated without host Attunement: Previous owner must be dead Cursed: The armour will try to protect the owner by any means, including imprisonment I more go off mental notes than physical. I had a mental note that to resist the movements and break out of armour was a DC 16 strength and DC 18 wisdom check respectively</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 14:24:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Toxic players break campaigns. Shame. Seemed like it was shaping up to be a good story</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 01:29:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>A few members from that group had a habit of meta gaming when they knew something was up. Therefore, early on, we unanimously agreed that I would be allowed to make some rolls for them in secret, if it was something like a charm person or other subtle effect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 03:47:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>HOW CAN SHE SLAP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A gnome, an oni, and the arm wrestle of the century</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 04:23:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>\ gt;Be me; DM of 2 campaigns (story is for group 1) \ gt;be not me; half elf ranger, half elf paladin, half elf wizard, halfling bard, gnome barbarian, tortle cleric, human monk \ gt;go into tavern in small town \ gt;see massive crowd around one table \ gt;investigate what's up \ gt;find person sitting at table. Massive pile of gold next to him \ gt;person sitting opposite of him, puts in 2 gold pieces and places his arm forward \ gt;original person places arm forward too \ gt;arm wrestling competition \ gt;spectator gives countdown of 3 \ gt;challenger starts pushing just before 1 \ gt;champion's arm doesn't budge \ gt;champion slams challenger's hand onto table. Sound of breaking bones \ gt;champion doesn't let go of hand, pulls glaive out from behind him \ gt;"You know the rules. If you cheat but lose, i take what you use" \ gt;cuts arm off with glaive \ gt;tavern mixture of cheers and vomiting sounds as challenger falls to the ground in a crying heap \ gt;gnome looks at party, looks at big pile of gold \ gt;"i'm going in" \ gt;party isn't able to stop him as he walks up and jumps onto the seat opposite the champion \ gt;champion towers over him \ gt;spectators laugh as gnome places 2 gold pieces in the pile \ gt;party sighs ic and ooc \ gt;gnome's character is based off being a physically weak scholar who wanted to try become a barbarian \ gt;"what do i win if i beat you?" he asks the champion \ gt;champion simply gestures to the pile of gold \ gt;gnome smiles and puts his hand on the table \ gt;champion shrugs and places hand opposite him \ gt;spectator gives a countdown \ gt;wrestling competition begins \ gt;gnome rolls straight d20 with strength modifier \ gt;4 in total \ gt;champion laughs in his face \ gt;ask gnome to roll a strength save \ gt;natural 20 \ gt;the champion goes to slam hand on table but frowns as he realizes hand won't move \ gt;gnome gives him a small smile \ gt;party tells gnome to rage, now supporting him \ gt;gnome refuses, gives them a cocky smile \ gt;"I ain't gonna cheat" \ gt;rolls strength \ gt;2 \ gt;champion tilts his head to look at gnome's elbow, trying to see if there's a groove or something \ gt;strength save \ gt;natural 20 again \ gt;champion's face goes red as he realizes he's being embarrassed by a gnome a third of his size \ gt;looks gnome dead in the eye \ gt;"come on now buddy, why don't you give up? I'm saving you the embarrassment" \ gt;tell gnome to roll wisdom saving throw with advantage \ gt;natural 20 \ gt;gnome gives champion a smile \ gt;"can't charm me friend, i'm darya glitterson. I'm the gnome that's gonna beat you" \ gt;rolls strength check \ gt;18 \ gt;champion strains but barely manages to prevent his hand from touching the table (19 save) \ gt;party on the edge of their seats \ gt;spectators in chaos \ gt;champion grits his teeth and looks gnome in the eye \ gt;gnome sees blue skin and square jaw briefly flicker before the face returns to normal \ gt;gnome nods his head \ gt;"cool, an oni. This makes a lot more sense now" \ gt;"well, i guess it'll be a lot more embarrassing for you to know that you were beaten by a gnome then" \ gt;rolls save \ gt;14 \ gt;eyes go wide as i describe how his hand begins to lean towards his side of the table \ gt;oni begins to laugh. Ditches it's disguise \ gt;spectators go nuts \ gt;gnome's hand disappears into blue hand \ gt;"not today you blue freak" \ gt;rolls strength \ gt;natural \ gt;fucking \ gt;20 \ gt;the gnome, from a losing position, slams the oni's hand onto the table \ gt;walks towards oni's glaive, which is now massive \ gt;picks it up, barely able to hold it \ gt;"You know the rules. If you cheat but you lose, I take what you use" \ gt;swings glaive towards oni's head \ gt;cleaves head in half \ gt;oni drops to ground, half decapitated and most certainly dead \ gt;gnome pockets the gold and walks away smug \ gt;mfw gnome hardly gets a nat 20 for rest of campaign</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The yeti that ate cats</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 11:26:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>\ gt;Be me; DM of 2 campaigns \ gt;Be not me; half elf ranger, half elf paladin, half elf wizard, halfling bard, gnome barbarian, tortle cleric, human monk \ gt;Party walking through mountains chasing yeti \ gt;Yeti ate paladin's cat \ gt;Understandably pissed \ gt;Camping out at night \ gt;Bard plays some music to entertain others (Country Roads of course) \ gt;Next morning, begin tracking yeti again \ gt;Meet snow leopard \ gt;Paladin wants to tame it; misses his cat \ gt;Rolls animal handling \ gt;Nat 20 \ gt;Has a new, larger cat \ gt;Names it Sir Snuffsalot \ gt;Leopard has stats of tiger \ gt;Sir Snuffsalot helps them track yeti with good smell \ gt;Find yeti cave \ gt;Bard suggests paladin send Sir Snuffsalot in, cause darkvision \ gt;Paladin initially says no \ gt;Rest of party agrees with bard \ gt;Paladin relents \ gt;Sir Snuffsalot enters cave \ gt;Minute passes \ gt;Another minute \ gt;Another \ gt;Paladin losing his shit \ gt;Party agrees to go in \ gt;Paladin calling softly for Sir Snuffsalot \ gt;Finds body of snow leopard \ gt;Paladin's face when he thinks i killed his cat \ gt;Inform him it's not Sir Snuffsalot \ gt;Relaxes a tiny bit \ gt;Venture further in \ gt;Find more bodies of leopards and skeletons \ gt;Paladin's face when he sent Sir Snuffsalot into a leopard grave yard \ gt;Paladin's face when he hears chewing \ gt;Party sees yeti crouched over something, eating \ gt;Paladin brings out hammer, ready to kill it \ gt;Infuses hammer with fire \ gt;Yeti sees light, turns \ gt;Paladin player yells irl as i describe what it's eating \ gt;You guessed it; Sir Snuffsalot \ gt;Paladin runs in, infused with the fury of a thousand suns \ gt;Party just stands back and watches as Paladin 1v1's the yeti \ gt;Yeti dies a brutal death \ gt;Paladin decapitates Yeti and mounts head on his wall in memory of his 2 cats</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My party played The Thing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 06:28:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>\ gt;be me; DM of 2 campaigns \ gt;be not me; human monk, half orc barbarian, awakened dog bard, aarakocra sorcerer, drow rogue, air genasi cleric \ gt;as DM, like oni #8217;s a lot \ gt;used one for group 1. Gnome arm wrestled him \ gt;used one for group 2 much earlier \ gt;party is lvl 2 \ gt;babyadventurers.jpg \ gt;meet young girl on road alone. Has small backpack and wearing dirty clothes \ gt;sorcerer activates mother mode \ gt;take girl into their group \ gt;get rooms in nearby inn. Girls sleep in same room \ gt;no one decides to go on watch \ gt;fools.png \ gt;girl gets out of bed around midnight \ gt;taps sorcerer on shoulder and tells her she needs to go to the bathroom \ gt;sorcerer gets up reluctantly, mother instincts too powerful though \ gt;walks girl out of room and takes her towards bathroom \ gt;girl enters bathroom \ gt;comes out, says she heard a monster \ gt;sorcerer sighs and enters the room \ gt;door closes behind her \ gt;turns \ gt;girl is standing in front of door, evil smile on her face \ gt;sorcerer doesn #8217;t want to hurt the girl \ gt;transforms into oni \ gt;sorcerer wants to hurt the girl \ gt;too slow \ gt;oni blasts her with cone of cold \ gt;sorcerer not dead, but frozen against wall, unconscious \ gt;oni disguises itself as sorcerer and walks back upstairs \ gt;enters room of cleric and bard \ gt;bard sleeping on cleric #8217;s lap \ gt;bard looks up as oni enters room \ gt;tail originally wagging \ gt;sees glaive in sorcerer #8217;s hand \ gt;rolls insight based on smell \ gt;sorcerer smells different \ gt;starts growling and barking \ gt;cleric wakes up in time to see bard drop unconscious as oni uses sleep \ gt;starts yelling for help before summoning magic flail \ gt;it #8217;s on \ gt;barbarian and rogue begin kicking down door \ gt;cleric gets stabbed three times by glaive, 1 hp \ gt;door finally kicked open \ gt;oni goes invisible just before \ gt;barbarian and rogue enter room \ gt;begin searching for oni \ gt;oni leaves room, disguises as inn owner \ gt;enters room again \ gt;party flailing wildly for oni \ gt; #8220;what the hell is going on? #8221; \ gt;they warn oni about the oni \ gt;oni tells them to come downstairs \ gt;barbarian picks up bard and carries him out of room \ gt;cleric goes looking for sorcerer \ gt;finds her frozen in bathroom (stable but a statue) \ gt;cleric comes back, tells oni to get all the other people in the inn to come downstairs \ gt;oni leaves \ gt;without players knowing, kills actual innkeeper before retrieving other patrons \ gt;oni disguises as random dragonborn \ gt;about 20 people in tavern part of inn, about 1:00am \ gt;cleric looks around before thought strikes his mind \ gt; #8220;oh shit #8221; \ gt;turns to other players at table \ gt; #8220;we #8217;ve got a Thing scenario here #8221; (party had a movie night where we watched The Thing a couple months prior) \ gt;table goes silent \ gt;brief pause \ gt;barbarian  #8220;dibs being Kurt Russel #8221; \ gt;party begins trying to find out who is the oni \ gt;asking people questions only they would know \ gt;realize this is flawed because they don #8217;t know what the true answers are \ gt;ask people who are in groups to question each other \ gt;after a good hour irl, huddle all individual people into another group \ gt;fairly confident that oni is one of them \ gt;bard wakes up; player had been wanting to say something for a good hour but didn #8217;t want to meta game because character was asleep \ gt; #8220;about bloody time. Where #8217;s the inn keeper? #8221; \ gt;party does quick head count \ gt;realize inn keeper isn #8217;t there \ gt;don #8217;t want to lose sight of people \ gt;decide to send barbarian to look for inn keeper \ gt;goes upstairs \ gt;without players knowing, as soon as party looks away, oni disguises as small baby \ gt;begins to cry \ gt;random woman tries to calm oni baby down \ gt;cleric doesn #8217;t want woman to leave room \ gt;crying becomes extremely loud \ gt;rest of patrons getting annoyed \ gt;other woman grabs baby, walks off \ gt;cleric grabs her arm, her husband grabs him \ gt;chaos ensues \ gt;in chaos, several people leave room. One couple even leave the inn entirely \ gt;fight finally ends after cleric uses thaumaturgy to shout out for everyone to stop \ gt;looks around \ gt;there are a lot less people \ gt;barbarian runs downstairs \ gt;tells cleric he found something \ gt;cleric tells rogue to go with barbarian \ gt;rogue comes upstairs with barbarian \ gt;walks into room \ gt;rogue sees unconscious body of actual barbarian on the floor \ gt;turns around in time to see oni shapeshift in front of him \ gt;dodges the glaive swing and begins sprinting downstairs \ gt;yelling that barbarian is the oni \ gt;oni as barbarian sprints after him, yelling that rogue is the oni \ gt;both enter room at same time, immediately jump away from each other \ gt;cleric asks what happened \ gt;rogue quickly explains \ gt;oni says he found the inn keeper and rogue tried to kill him when they went to investigate \ gt;oh god.jpg \ gt;several people immediately leave the inn upon hearing this \ gt;cleric tries to stop them, fails intimidation check \ gt;only 3 other people beside party left \ gt;party unsure who to believe \ gt;roll insight on rogue \ gt;3 \ gt;roll insight on oni \ gt;5 \ gt;they have no clue \ gt;bard has idea to cut both people \ gt;what.mp3 \ gt;suggests that the oni will heal while the other won't \ gt;party goes with it \ gt;cut rogue \ gt;rogue doesn't heal \ gt;cut barbarian \ gt;oni shifts the disguise to keep blood flowing \ gt;plan ruined \ gt;monk looks down at dagger \ gt;thinks for a moment \ gt;asks rogue for extra dagger \ gt;rogue gives him one \ gt;monk wipes blood on shirt before cutting both again \ gt;dagger cuts rogue. Blood on metal \ gt;dagger cuts oni. Blood on body. No blood on metal \ gt;oni realizes the jig is up \ gt;changes form and attacks \ gt;nearly decapitates the rogue, manages to drop the cleric \ gt;party finally kill oni \ gt;tfw party never trusts an npc in trouble again props to barbarian player. I passed him a note about the fight, saying he was knocked unconscious and asked him to roleplay the oni for me. Brilliant roleplaying. God i love this game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 09:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>For this group, the town had been a tad notorious for losing people. The party went there initially because of this. The oni itself was more of the, 'murdering is fun, but murdering after manipulating people is better' kind. It saw they were adventurers and that they might be more of a threat than the villagers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 12:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>oops. I ran 2 parties. Brain gets scrambled sometimes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 12:26:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like oni's. I like The Thing. What can i say? I preferred the mystery over straight death, as i feel the deaths would've felt very unfair. Die without any chance to fight back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 23:20:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>The players didn't think much of it. I was really worried there. It seemed so obvious but they just didn't pick it up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 23:21:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I ran two campaigns. I trusted this group to not meta game. Perhaps not the other though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 23:22:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Player. I passed him a note. It was up to him how he wanted to respond to comments, but my note said "the oni snuck upstairs and knocked you out. Can you voice the oni pretending to be you?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why my party has a phobia of water</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 00:54:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>\ gt;be me; DM of 2 campaigns \ gt;be not me; half elf ranger, half elf paladin, half elf wizard, halfling bard, gnome barbarian, tortle cleric, human monk \ gt;go into dungeon \ gt;exploring it \ gt;find bit of loot \ gt;as they're walking, floor breaks underneath them \ gt;try running \ gt;not fast enough \ gt;fall through floor into massive underground lake \ gt;torches immediately extinguished \ gt;begin swimming towards bank \ gt;ranger never really learnt how to swim \ gt;is terrified that they can only see in grey and can't see any depth below them \ gt;tortle cleric swims back to her as rest of party reaches the bank \ gt;ranger feels something grab her leg \ gt;pulled underwater \ gt;party loses their shit \ gt;cleric casts light on a copper coin and holds it in front of him \ gt;sees ranger struggling underwater with something \ gt;sees ranger go completely still \ gt;cleric swims over \ gt;thing that attacked her disappears deeper into the water \ gt;cleric grabs ranger and begins pulling her to surface \ gt;breaches surface, begins passing her to barbarian \ gt;ranger is stunned and took in a lot of water \ gt;cleric feels something twist his mind \ gt;cleric grabs barbarian's hand and pulls him into the water \ gt;tortle vs gnome underwater \ gt;tortle grapples gnome and begins swimming down (no movement penalty because gnome is small) \ gt;gnome tries hitting tortle, misses \ gt;gnome tries breaking free, fails \ gt;going deeper and deeper \ gt;about 60ft deep now \ gt;lake doesn't look like bottom is anywhere near \ gt;wizard shoots magic missile into water \ gt;hits cleric \ gt;cleric tries to make save against control \ gt;fails \ gt;begins pushing gnome further down with more gusto \ gt;tail suddenly emerges from water, hits wizard \ gt;con save \ gt;fail \ gt;wizard is stunned \ gt;tail wraps around his leg \ gt;begins pulling him into water \ gt;monk starts beating tail with quarterstaff \ gt;tail retreats \ gt;pull wizard away from edge of water \ gt;gnome and tortle 90ft deep \ gt;gnome punches tortle dead in the nose \ gt;save against control \ gt;fails \ gt;gnome breaks free of grapple \ gt;begins swimming up \ gt;dashing \ gt;can only move 24ft up per turn \ gt;tortle can move 30 without dash \ gt;tortle catches up \ gt;gnome player freaking out \ gt;tortle grabs his leg \ gt;tries to grapple \ gt;gnome kicks him in the face \ gt;control save \ gt;14 (save is 15) \ gt;bard looking into water, holding attack \ gt;tail comes out of water \ gt;bard hits it with shatter \ gt;thunder damage echoes through cave \ gt;thunder damage amplified underwater \ gt;shatter hits gnome and tortle \ gt;gnome takes 30 damage \ gt;tortle takes 15 \ gt;gnome drowns \ gt;tortle succeeds control check \ gt;grabs gnome \ gt;starts taking him up to surface \ gt;monster attacks him \ gt;ohhellno.mp3 \ gt;summons magic trident \ gt;stabs monster in face twice \ gt;monster disappears \ gt;gnome taking death saves \ gt;impossible to be stable underwater (even if they succeed, will have to keep going) \ gt;tortle takes gnome to surface \ gt;gnome has 2 failures \ gt;just before they reach surface, gnome fails final save \ gt;cleric breaks surface, drops gnome onto bank \ gt;monk beams him in the head with quarterstaff \ gt;cleric takes a nice nap \ gt;begin dragging party away \ gt;wizard launches 3rd level magic missile into water \ gt;monster breaks surface, begins running towards them \ gt;paladin kills it with hammer \ gt;is kopru \ gt;party finds exit, leaves dungeon without searching it any more \ gt;revive gnome \ gt;never return \ gt;mfw party refuses to fight in water ever again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 13:21:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I honestly thought you said thatsalotadamage on first look</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:35:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I waited until everyone was as loud as possible to slip it into his hand under the table. I was lucky he was close</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sometimes size does matter</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 04:13:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>\ gt;be me; DM of 2 campaigns \ gt;be not me; human monk, half orc barbarian, awakened dog bard, aarakocra sorcerer, tiefling wizard, gnome cleric \ gt;in town \ gt;monk player asks if there's a brothel \ gt;sigh.mp3 \ gt;no \ gt;monk frowns \ gt;"are there any attractive women?" \ gt;partysigh.mp3 \ gt;roll perception \ gt;16 \ gt;yes. Tavern owner \ gt;"i go up to them" \ gt;herewego.jpg \ gt;"i want to woo them" \ gt;f\*ckit \ gt;go along with it \ gt;monk tries his best to woo woman \ gt;woman is unimpressed \ gt;bluntly suggests he has large member \ gt;woman leans over counter, laughs \ gt;monk goes red \ gt;half orc barbarian walks in \ gt;woman's jaw drops as she sees him \ gt;barbarian orders drink \ gt;woman gets it for him immediately \ gt;eventually starts hitting on her \ gt;she's very receptive to it \ gt;monk sitting there fuming \ gt;barbarian inquires if she'd like to join him for a drink in his room later \ gt;rolls persuasion \ gt;nat 20 \ gt;she asks if they can do it now \ gt;barbarian winks at monk and takes her upstairs \ gt;2 hours later \ gt;comes downstairs \ gt;woman's hair is a wild mess \ gt;monk sitting next to fireplace, drinking heavily \ gt;barbarian sits down opposite him \ gt;"size matters mate" \ gt;pats him on shoulder \ gt;mfw</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 08:13:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>He tries to hit on himself, is rejected and laughed at for his member size by himself, picks himself up, sleeps with himself and tells himself size matters?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"Eating people is fine so long as we all agree on that now"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 13:38:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>\ gt;Be me; DM for past games and this new one \ gt;Be not me; lizardfolk ranger, lizardfolk fighter, lizardfolk sorcerer, lizardfolk barbarian, lizardfolk cleric \ gt;New campaign after old one ended \ gt;mfw everyone showed up to session 0 with characters made up \ gt;mfw noone had planned for everyone to be a lizardfolk \ gt;mfw i scrap my plans for first game and tailor it to begin in the swamps \ gt;party all meet up in swamp after troll attack makes loud enough sound so they all can hear it \ gt;beat troll \ gt;subsequently turn almost every bone into a javelin or dagger. One guy even wears the skull as a hat \ gt;this will be interesting \ gt;session 1 \ gt;party enters new town after lizardfolk chiefs request a group go out into world to gather information about suspected threat \ gt;sees lots of humans and elves \ gt;only ranger has ever seen human before \ gt;tries talking to them while other lizardfolk stare at weird races \ gt;mfw party unanimously agrees to dub all of the humanoids without scales "fleshies" \ gt;robbery occurs, guards taking cover from crossbow shots \ gt;lizardfolk look on with curiosity \ gt;no lizardfolk ever really steal, so this is new to them \ gt;see that people are scared \ gt;also new to lizardfolk \ gt;fighter gets hit with crossbow bolt \ gt;culprit realizes terrible mistake as fighter charges at him \ gt;lizardfolk pounces on him, tears him to shreds with sword and spear \ gt;culprit dead \ gt;begins taking out bones and carving off meat pieces \ gt;rest of culprits take in this display \ gt;immediately run for their lives \ gt;ranger and sorcerer kill them \ gt;barbarian drags other bodies over, begins to de-bone and flay them \ gt;town guards unsure what to do \ gt;onlookers mortified at what occured \ gt;ranger finally pokes fighter and barbarian on shoulder, suggests they stop \ gt;after pocketing bones and meat, party make camp outside town, not comfortable with sleeping in an inn \ gt;beside fireplace, ranger speaks up \ gt;"Ok, we're going to need to make some rules" "When we're not in the swamps, we have to tone down a little of what we do so we blend in" \ gt;fighter frowns as he takes bite of cooked piece of culprit \ gt;"we can't eat them?" \ gt;ranger pauses for a second \ gt;"eating people is fine so long as we all agree on that now" "1 rule. Just don't eat in front of fleshies. Don't eat dead friends of fleshies. They don't like that" \ gt;party agrees. Dictate ranger as spokesperson for the party in fleshy based conversations \ gt;mfw we unintentionally started a lizardfolk campaign \ gt;well. This is going to be fun. Maybe a year of lizardfolk based fun. What could go wrong?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:14:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>We play on Mondays and Thursdays. My posts will probably slow down if i'm going to focus on this campaign but sure, why not. I will embrace Lizard DM</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:35:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would be down to, however, quite a few of my players aren't too keen on the idea. Maybe at a later date</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wow</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:38:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Umm. Wow. Lizardfolk story got a lot of attention. Alrighty then. Well, we play Mondays and Thursdays. I have 1 other story, since that was last weeks story, however, after that, there will be a slow down in lizard related posts. Thanks for the upvotes. I can still post stories from the old games i used to DM, but for lizard related stories there will be a half weekly delay. Thanks again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lizardfolk 2: Reptilian Boogaloo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 03:12:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>(This is the last lizardfolk story until maybe around next Tuesday) \ gt;be me; DM of the lizards \ gt;be not me; lizardfolk ranger, lizardfolk fighter, lizardfolk sorcerer, lizardfolk barbarian, lizardfolk cleric \ gt;camped outside the town of Mildenbar \ gt;on mission to learn about potential threats to lizardfolk home and, if possible, deal with them \ gt;party enters Mildenbar, ranger at front because he somewhat understands what 'fleshies' are like \ gt;see man dictating orders to town guards \ gt;ranger walks up to him \ gt;party getting a lot of weird looks \ gt;man looks over, guards put hands on hilts of swords \ gt;they heard about or witnessed what happened yesterday \ gt;ranger bluntly asks if there's any nearby threats \ gt;man very confused \ gt;ranger thinks for a moment \ gt;"thing that hurts people?" \ gt;man looks at them \ gt;"uhh, there are a few thieves in the area. I heard you dealt with some yesterday" \ gt;"where they?" \ gt;one guard shakes his head, armour is better than others \ gt;tells ranger that guards will deal with threat (likely don't want to have any more people eaten) \ gt;ranger shakes his head \ gt;"we deal with them" \ gt;man scratches his jaw and looks at group. Small glint comes into his eye \ gt;"how badly do you want to help?" \ gt;ranger looks at him \ gt;"we deal with them. No more threat to home" \ gt;man nods \ gt;"offer a fee, and we'll let you help" \ gt;guard nods, liking idea \ gt;barbarian steps forward, pulls out bits of human meat from yesterday \ gt;tries to give it to guard \ gt;guards and man suitably disgusted \ gt;"no, i mean money" \ gt;lizardfolks unfamiliar with money (their society runs on sharing through necessity) \ gt;man points to ranger's bow \ gt;"you hunt?" \ gt;ranger tells him they all do \ gt;points to nearby building \ gt;"that's a butcher. He'll buy meat off you. Come back when you have that" \ gt;ranger tells rest of party \ gt;they leave Mildenbar \ gt;group agree to split up in order to get the most food possible \ gt;ranger, sorcerer, cleric \ gt;fighter and barbarian \ gt;ohgod.mp3 \ gt;ranger, sorcerer and cleric go hunting in forest, end up hunting 2 deer and have to fight off pack of wolves who want deer \ gt;meanwhile, fighter and barbarian see small building \ gt;building has fence next to it \ gt;inside is goat \ gt;they sneak up, fighter pulls out shortbow \ gt;shoot goat \ gt;goat begins screaming in pain \ gt;run up and kill it with dagger \ gt;farmer comes outside as they pick up the goat body and begin walking away \ gt;understandably mad \ gt;fighter tells farmer that he shot it fair and square (doesn't understand that goat was owned by farmer) \ gt;farmer tries to take goat back \ gt;barbarian sees man as aggressive \ gt;kills him \ gt;proceeds to take more human meat \ gt;wife and children mortified \ gt;lizardfolk ignore them \ gt;leave for butcher \ gt;ranger, sorcerer and cleric already delivered their deers, waiting outside \ gt;barbarian and ranger walk in, put unskinned goat on counter \ gt;butcher stares at them \ gt;butcher stares at goat \ gt;"where'd you get this?" \ gt;"shot it" \ gt;butcher looks at goat, sees tag on ear \ gt;"you got this from David's farm" \ gt;"shot it fair" \ gt;"what did you do to David?" \ gt;lizardfolk not sure why he won't accept the meat \ gt;barbarian offers human meat \ gt;butcher screams at them to get out \ gt;guards come \ gt;see lizardfolk \ gt;reluctant to engage \ gt;ranger comes in, sees issue \ gt;tells fighter and barbarian to leave butcher alone \ gt;guards take lizardfolk to town mayor \ gt;butcher follows \ gt;butcher explains situation to mayor \ gt;other man is there (turns out he's captain of the guards) \ gt;mayor looks at lizardfolk \ gt;"you stole David's goat and killed him?" \ gt;fighter steps forward \ gt;"shot it fair. He try take" \ gt;"it was his goat though" \ gt;doesn't get it \ gt;ranger steps forward \ gt;"we are sorry. We won't do it again" \ gt;mayor tells them to leave Mildenbar \ gt;ranger nods, tells group they have to leave \ gt;guards begin escorting them out of town \ gt;as they pass tavern, hear argument inside \ gt;door opens, man in silver armour and wielding nice sword steps out, yelling at tavern owner \ gt;tavern owner yells back \ gt;"you're no different, you have to pay for ale" \ gt;"i protect this town. I keep your business from being run down by thieves. I am on business from Baron Highwater himself. You want to keep your ale? Go ahead. I'll watch this tavern burn and smile as it happens" \ gt;man leaves \ gt;tavern owner looks at procession of guards and lizardfolk \ gt;tavern owner asks guards to arrest man, says he threatened him \ gt;guards shrug \ gt;"he works for Highwater. If we piss off Highwater, he won't give us funds for protection from the thieves" \ gt;tavern owner sighs and walks inside but not before giving lizardfolk weird look \ gt;party kicked out of Mildenbar \ gt;sitting at camp, eating human and goat meat \ gt;hear someone coming \ gt;ranger and fighter pull out bows \ gt;tavern owner just about shits himself \ gt;they drop bows when they realize he isn't armed \ gt;"you're looking for threats?" he asks \ gt;ranger nods \ gt;"i'll give you as much information as possible and pay you, so long as you protect my wares from people like Highwater" \ gt;party gets first job \ gt;game ends there You wanted updates. Next game is Monday. I might post stories from old games still but i'll keep tuesdays and fridays for lizardfolk posts if you want me to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 06:59:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a minimalist with my notes. I write plot points, encounters and important people, but i rely a lot on improv, because past games have proven to me at least, that we have more fun that way. I knew they'd need money, i suggested hunting. Player asked if there were any farms, i obliged by making one and they took it from there. I kind of just thought through my head. How would people actually react to this? I worked the plot hook in that was planned for later, because i didn't know they'd make a camp outside the town, because it just seemed like a good enough spot to put it. A lot of it is improvisation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 09:29:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please do this for all of them. I saw it last time. Beautiful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 13:57:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't give details, because my party are aware that I post these, but yes, there will be a long term arc, or multiple as in the past</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 13:59:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm from Sydney, Australia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 15:08:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>USSR anthem blares</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 03:12:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>How would I go about that? I'm kinda new to reddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 03:13:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, they're not allowed to enter the town anymore, which will conflict with their new job. If they continue to murder, there may be more attention from higher ups.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 03:17:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>cheers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 07:21:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the advice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lizardfolk 3: Getting smashed, enemies abound and the plot thickens</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 13:55:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>\ gt;be me, lizard DM \ gt;be not me, lizardfolk ranger, lizardfolk fighter, lizardfolk sorcerer, lizardfolk barbarian, lizardfolk cleric \ gt;outside Mildenbar: Have been kicked out for disruptive behaviour \ gt;tavern owner offers them job as his guards \ gt;party accept offer \ gt;party proceed to sneak back into Mildenbar under the cover of night \ gt;after a lot of close calls and fast talking by tavern owner, they finally reach the tavern \ gt;tavern owner (named Brom) gives them rooms in above floors \ gt;society.jpg \ gt;about 9:00pm at this point \ gt;as they #8217;re trying to figure out sheets and why these beds are squishy, they hear a commotion downstairs \ gt;ranger sneaks downstairs, sees angry guy from earlier arguing with Brom \ gt;sneaks back upstairs and tells rest of party \ gt;barbarian smiles and brings out massive bone sword (crafted from jaw of blue dragon. It has a tooth for a crossguard and has a  #188; chance of inflicting 1d6 lightning damage \ gt;all go downstairs \ gt; #8221;are you seriously going to refuse me a drink? I work for Highwater you daft idiot #8221; \ gt; #8221;I don #8217;t need your protection anymore, Hillborn #8221; \ gt;Hillborn guy drops hand to sword hilt at his side \ gt;barbarian swings his own sword, imbeds it in the wood of the counter centimetres from Hillborn #8217;s hand \ gt;Hillborn looks up \ gt;goes to stand up, sees rest of party, all with weapons at the ready \ gt;barbarian leans in really close, so close he could easily bite off Hillborn #8217;s nose if he wanted \ gt; #8221;you not win. Leave #8221; \ gt;rolls intimidation \ gt;18 \ gt;Hillborn stands up, looks at Brom \ gt; #8221;you trust savages over Highwater? Oh boy, you #8217;ve made a big mistake #8221; \ gt;barbarian gives a long, deep growl (think crocodile growl) \ gt;Hillborn leaves \ gt;ranger walks up to Brom \ gt; #8221;who he? #8221; \ gt; #8221;Farin Hillborn. Member of the Grimnar Knights. He gets his orders directly from Baron Highwater #8221; \ gt; #8221;who Baron Highwater? #8221; \ gt; #8221;a Baron of Isopin (country they #8217;re in). He owns all the land from the coast to the Darkpeak mountains #8221; \ gt;ranger player asks me where swamp is \ gt;I tell him that the swamp sits smack dab in the middle of the fief \ gt; #8221;he does not own home #8221; ranger tells Brom \ gt; #8221;he knows that and he #8217;s not happy about it. He doesn #8217;t like the idea of anyone being allowed to ignore his rule #8221; \ gt;ranger turns to rest of party and repeats info in draconic \ gt;Fighter:  #8221;Highwater is a threat to the swamp. We #8217;ll deal with him #8221; \ gt;Ranger:  #8220;We don #8217;t know that. Let #8217;s focus on the bandits first #8221; \ gt;ranger asks Brom about bandits \ gt;Brom tells him that the bandits showed up a few months ago and began raiding towns occasionally but mostly sticking to disrupting trade routes. Every town pays Highwater for protection \ gt;ranger thinks for a moment then recites info to party \ gt;just as that happens, party hears sounds of heavy footsteps and voices outside \ gt;Brom goes pale and tells everyone to hide in the cellar downstairs \ gt;party close cellar door just as guards enter tavern \ gt;barbarian player immediately looks at me \ gt; #8221;what #8217;s around us #8221; \ gt; #8221;several closed barrels #8221; \ gt; #8221;I open one. What #8217;s inside #8221; \ gt; #8221;roll perception #8221; \ gt;nat 1 \ gt; #8221;it #8217;s a liquid, but you have no idea what the hell it is #8221; \ gt; #8221;ooc what is it? #8221; \ gt; #8221;scotch #8221; \ gt;player smiles \ gt; #8221;would I know what alcohol is? #8221; \ gt; #8221;give me a straight d20 #8221; \ gt;3 \ gt;no clue \ gt; #8221;im taking one for the team in the name of science and exploration #8221; \ gt;chugs it \ gt; #8221;give me a constitution saving throw #8221; \ gt;2 \ gt; #8221;you are utterly f\*cked #8221; \ gt;guards begin coming downstairs \ gt;knock on door \ gt;hear Brom say it #8217;s just the cellar \ gt;guards tell him to open it \ gt;Brom sighs and they hear sound of keys \ gt;sorcerer takes quick look around him and casts major image just as door opens \ gt;guards enter \ gt;see empty room \ gt;nod and leave \ gt;closesave.mp3 \ gt;as soon as guards are out of earshot, barbarian collapses to the floor in a drunken mess \ gt;next day \ gt;many shenanigans as party tries to figure out information in town without people knowing they #8217;re lizardfolk \ gt;basically a lot of terrible disguises, incredible persuasion and deception rolls and a whole bunch of laughs \ gt;(I #8217;ll post at a later date if you want to hear more detail) \ gt;that night, series of bangs and clashes from the door \ gt;party prepares weapons, expecting guards \ gt;door kicked open \ gt;hooded people wielding clubs, shoddy swords and flaming torches \ gt;bandits \ gt;chaos ensues as party engages bandits \ gt;Brom desperately trying to put out fires as party battles bandits \ gt;barbarian getting 3v1 #8217;d \ gt;stabs one in chest with dagger, bites the throat of another and kills the final one with his sword \ gt;almost all bandits dead when ranger sees one going for fighter #8217;s turned back \ gt;shoots floor in front of him \ gt;bandit turns to see ranger nock another arrow \ gt; #8221;leave #8221; \ gt;man doesn #8217;t need any more convincing \ gt;leaves \ gt;tavern is silent once more except for the crunching and squelching of barbarian and fighter skinning bandits, taking bones and carving off pieces of meat \ gt;guards enter tavern just as barbarian is almost done \ gt;see blood everywhere and barbarian with his arms full of bloody human meat \ gt;all draw weapons \ gt;ranger shoots lead guard in arm \ gt; #8221;let us leave or we kill all of you #8221; \ gt;intimidation roll \ gt;19 \ gt;guards clear door as party move out, barbarian still with arms full of meat \ gt;cleric snaps jaws at youngish guard as he passes, teeth inches from face \ gt;guard pisses himself \ gt;party leave \ gt;ranger turns to rest of party \ gt; #8221;I let one bandit go. If we track him, he should lead us to the others #8221; \ gt;begin tracking remaining bandit \ gt;catch up, but ranger tells others not to advance, instead follow at a distance \ gt;group stealth check, aided by pass without trace \ gt;bandit has no clue they #8217;re there \ gt;follow bandit deep into woods \ gt;bandit leads them to hidden camp in there \ gt;ranger tells others to stay low as they scout the camp \ gt;too many to handle safely \ gt;hear hoofbeats \ gt;so do bandits \ gt;small defence set up \ gt;party agree to just watch \ gt;guards arrive at camp \ gt;players initially happy \ gt;party see guards led by Farin \ gt;no longer happy \ gt;Farin calls out a word \ gt;bandits call out other word \ gt;both groups relax \ gt;ohshit.jpg \ gt;Farin:  #8220;You need to move. There are some lizardfolk in town that are stirring up trouble. They #8217;re looking for you #8221; \ gt;bandit: #8220;You killed Samuel, he was my friend #8221; \ gt; #8220;Idiot didn #8217;t know when to retreat, and we have to maintain that we are stopping you #8221; \ gt;Give us our payment. We #8217;re starving out here #8221; \ gt;Farin throws bag of coins over \ gt; #8220;Payment from Highwater, as promised #8221; \ gt;One guard begins backing away, shaking his head \ gt; #8220;We were meant to stop them. You #8217;ve been behind this the whole time? My father died because of these bastards #8221; \ gt;lead bandit pulls out sword. Farin raises hand and stops him \ gt; #8220;Let him run #8221; \ gt;Guard begins to run. \ gt;Farin pulls out crossbow. Shoots him in the back of the head \ gt;Farin sighs and begins reloading crossbow \ gt; #8220;See, now we have to make it look like there was a fight #8221; \ gt;Farin shoots random bandit in the chest \ gt;Several guards stab their comrades in the back while bandits do the same \ gt; #8220;Leave now. We #8217;ll go back, say we found your camp and that you escaped. You #8217;ve got your payment and your orders #8221; \ gt; #8220;What about the lizardfolk? #8221; \ gt; #8220;We #8217;ll deal with them. Put it down to public nuisance or something #8221; \ gt;party watches as what remains of guards turn to return to camp \ gt;Farin #8217;s eyes pass over their section of the woods before stopping directly on them \ gt;his eyes narrow and a small grimace sets on his face before he gets his horse to continue forward \ gt;game ends Chapter 1: [https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/97riuv/eating\_people\_is\_fine\_so\_long\_as\_we\_all\_agree\_on/](https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/97riuv/eating_people_is_fine_so_long_as_we_all_agree_on/) Chapter 2: [https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/97y18e/lizardfolk\_2\_reptilian\_boogaloo/](https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/97y18e/lizardfolk_2_reptilian_boogaloo/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lizardfolk 3.5: Deception, disguises and lack thereof</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 04:26:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>\ gt;be me, Lizard DM \ gt;be not me, lizardfolk ranger, lizardfolk fighter, lizardfolk sorcerer, lizardfolk barbarian, lizardfolk cleric \ gt;having just hidden from the guards in a cellar, the party wishes to go out into town to find information \ gt;will get kicked out or arrested if they are discovered \ gt;sorcerer casts disguise self to appear as tiefling \ gt;ranger puts on cloak (they originally didn't wear clothes besides belts or backpacks), and tucks tail up against back \ gt;puts backpack over top \ gt;not perfect but might work if people don't pay attention \ gt;barbarian tries to figure out the clothes Brom gave him \ gt;eventually puts on clothes, still doesn't look very good \ gt;god help them \ gt;sorcerer casts minor illusion on fighter to make him appear human \ gt;it's shoddy and looks very obviously fake under scrutiny \ gt;cleric has no idea how to disguise himself, decides to use bless on himself, barbarian and ranger in a desperate attempt to help himself persuade people \ gt;this can only go well \ gt;leave tavern and enter town \ gt;to further decrease suspicion, the group splits up \ gt;ohno.jpg \ gt;ranger immediately goes and sits beside a group of people in nearby market \ gt;tries to listen in on stuff \ gt;ask him to roll stealth to listen in unnoticed \ gt;12 \ gt;some people look over and move away \ gt;ranger sighs and settles down to listen in to some conversations \ gt;barbarian and sorcerer walking together, decide to go up to a market stall \ gt;ohno.mp3 \ gt;sorcerer steps forward, tries to divert attention from barbarian \ gt; #8220;hello. Do have good knowledge town? #8221; \ gt;dwarvish stall owner staring back at what appears to be a tiefling with potential learning inhibitors \ gt; #8220;I #8217;ve lived here for the last 50 years, yes #8221; \ gt; #8220;Do know Highwater? #8221; \ gt; #8220;I know Baron Highwater, but I don #8217;t see the relevance here. I sell fish. What do you want? #8221; \ gt;sorcerer looks at fish \ gt; #8220;how much to buy? #8221; \ gt; #8220;1 silver a kilo #8221; \ gt;barbarian pulls out human meat \ gt;places it on stall \ gt;dwarf looks at it with disgust before looking up at him, noticing him for first time \ gt;notices distinctly reptilian features \ gt; #8220;you #8217;re one of them lizardfolk, huh? #8221; \ gt;barbarian shakes his head, tries to think fast \ gt;"I tabaxi" \ gt;facepalm.mp4 \ gt;"roll. . . roll deception . . ." \ gt;nat 20 \ gt;omfg \ gt;the dwarf looks at him for a bit \ gt;barbarian gives forced toothy smile (first time he's ever done it. It looks horrifying) \ gt;dwarf shrugs, returns attention to sorcerer \ gt;"i can't accept this . . . meat. Silver or nothing" \ gt;sorcerer puts 2 gold pieces on counter \ gt;dwarf shakes his head \ gt;"1 silver. Those are gold pieces" \ gt;"2 gold. You give fish. You tell about Highwater. You don't question" \ gt;rolls persuasion \ gt;17 \ gt;dwarf slowly pulls coins over and pockets them \ gt;leans in close \ gt;"what do you wanna know?" \ gt;"who Highwater?" \ gt;dwarf proceeds to give sorcerer and barbarian information about Highwater \ gt;they learn about his arrival 3 years ago, his installation of the Grimnar Knights, his hunger for power and more \ gt;meanwhile, cleric is stumbling around with fighter \ gt;has no attempt at a disguise \ gt;as they're walking, see guards patrolling market \ gt;fighter and cleric move to hide in between stalls as guards pass \ gt;as they're hiding, cleric feels tug on his tail \ gt;he turns around, sees a group of about 5 kids hiding behind stalls nearby \ gt;small blonde girl, maybe 8 years old, standing behind him, very clearly the suspect \ gt;cleric moves his tail behind him \ gt;"go away small fleshy" \ gt;"you look funny mr lizard" \ gt;cleric looks at girl, pokes her hair \ gt;"why have this? Look bad" \ gt;girl's eyes begin to water \ gt;cleric looks at her, very confused as she quietly begins to cry \ gt;cleric turns to fighter \ gt;"small fleshy is leaking" \ gt;fighter turns around, sees girl crying \ gt;has no idea what to do \ gt;pulls out dagger \ gt;ohno.jpg \ gt;girl looks up, sees fighter with dagger \ gt;opens mouth to scream \ gt;mother comes around corner and runs over, swinging at fighter with a bread stick \ gt;fighter cuts her with dagger and pushes her over, disguise has fallen away \ gt;"go away fleshy" \ gt;"you horrible savages, what kind of monster attacks a child?" \ gt;"small fleshy attack me" cleric insists \ gt;"she's just a child! She doesn't know any different" \ gt;"stupid hatchling die in swamp" \ gt;"you're not in the swamp, you're in Mildenbar. We don't kill people who annoy us here!" \ gt;lizardfolk think for a moment \ gt;see that they're getting attention \ gt;fighter leans down and gives small girl the dagger \ gt;"now no die in swamp" \ gt;small girl wipes away tears and looks at dagger \ gt;lizardfolk walk away just as guards approach \ gt;guards walk up to them \ gt;"oy! Lizardfolk, you're not supposed to be in town" \ gt;cleric looks at guards \ gt;"we not lizardfolk you look for" \ gt;omg.jpg \ gt;mfw he just pulled a jedi mind trick \ gt;rolls deception \ gt;2 \ gt;guard raises an eyebrow \ gt;"you're kidding me, right?" \ gt;fighter tells me he wants to throw a bone dagger above their heads \ gt;throws it \ gt;6 \ gt;the dagger embeds itself in a guard's shoulder \ gt;guard begins to scream \ gt;fighter sprints at the guards and pushes one aside \ gt;cleric close on his heels \ gt;short chase ensues before lizardfolk miraculously manage to escape \ gt;fighter looks at cleric \ gt;"stupid fleshies" Chapter 1: [https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/97riuv/eating\_people\_is\_fine\_so\_long\_as\_we\_all\_agree\_on/](https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/97riuv/eating_people_is_fine_so_long_as_we_all_agree_on/) Chapter 2: [https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/97y18e/lizardfolk\_2\_reptilian\_boogaloo/](https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/97y18e/lizardfolk_2_reptilian_boogaloo/) Chapter 3: [https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/98sy1i/lizardfolk\_3\_getting\_smashed\_enemies\_abound\_and/](https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/98sy1i/lizardfolk_3_getting_smashed_enemies_abound_and/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 06:41:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>We loved the idea of him getting smashed on his first drink, so we didn't care about his modifier when we saw the 2</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 06:41:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Legend</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 06:43:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only 2 players specified what they looked like based on real life lizards. The barbarian described himself as a crocodile, ridges included, however, a far shorter snout. The sorcerer described himself as a monitor. Everyone else were just generic, photo inspired lizardfolk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 06:48:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is Overlord? I've seen it mentioned so many times, and the cleric himself admitted it was his inspiration for making a lizardfolk, but i have no clue what it is outside of a show</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 06:54:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, i was wondering how to do that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 06:55:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm happy to hear that my players and I have that influence</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 07:09:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds interesting, might look into it if I have time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 09:30:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once again, perfect as usual</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 09:49:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>When speaking to each other, they use draconic and speak normally</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 11:16:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>fixed it now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 23:00:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Caught me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 06:42:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not really sure how to implement that, but the next game starts in about an hour. I'll post either tomorrow or late tonight</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 06:43:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the support</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lizardfolk 4: tooth and sword</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 14:01:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>\ gt; be me; LizarDM \ gt; be not me; lizardfolk ranger, lizardfolk fighter, lizardfolk barbarian, lizardfolk sorcerer, lizardfolk cleric \ gt; having just discovered secret that Baron Highwater is behind the bandit attacks, party hiding in woods next to bandit camp \ gt; late at night \ gt; party watch as what remains of guards leave the scene \ gt; bandits begin cleaning up \ gt; ranger leans in to group;  #8220;Highwater is a threat to the swamp. We have to deal with him #8221; \ gt; sorcerer;  #8220;what about the bandits and guards? #8221; \ gt; ranger looks out at bandits as they begin to pack up camp \ gt; ranger;  #8220;we deal with them now. Then we deal with the guards #8221; \ gt; party proceeds to plan their attack \ gt; with the aid of a lot of well rolled stealth checks, the party begins to circle the camp \ gt; leave single area open in an effort to shepherd bandits that way \ gt; path leads to open ground, where they will be easy pickings for ranged players \ gt; when they #8217;re all in position, sorcerer looks at group, ask if they #8217;re ready \ gt; with a few nods of confirmation, the chaos begins \ gt; the sorcerer casts minor illusion \ gt; the thundering sound of a roaring black dragon echoes across the camp \ gt; bandits go still, all looking around for the dragon \ gt; many begin scanning the skies \ gt; the sound echoes again, coming ever closer to the camp \ gt; as the bandits began to chaotically scramble for ranged weapons or to find cover, the party strikes \ gt; running in silently, the party engages the bandits, many of which barely recognise the real threat until it #8217;s too late \ gt; before a proper defence was set up, 8 freshly killed bodies of bandits lay on the ground, with only 5 remaining \ gt; the fight was over almost as soon as it began \ gt; there was no need for the open field plan, as the party decimated the bandits without hardly breaking a sweat \ gt; as the barbarian and fighter promptly began skinning the bandits, the cleric and ranger began searching the camp \ gt; recovering 65 gold, 23 silver and 6 copper pieces, alongside an abundance of swords, spears, crossbows and daggers, the party felt pretty accomplished \ gt; the party packed up their things and began to return to their camp, not worrying as much about stealth \ gt; that was a mistake they regretted \ gt; the party ventured home, celebrating themselves on the abundance of loot they #8217;d recovered \ gt; on their walk, the ranger had a sudden thought, and the player went very pale \ gt;  #8220;how far do you think the guards got before we started fighting? #8221; \ gt; the table went silent for a moment before the ranger spoke \ gt;  #8220;I #8217;d like to roll a perception check to see if there #8217;s anyone nearby #8221; \ gt; 13 \ gt; out of the corner of his eye, the ranger sees something shift in the grass around them, and slight movements in the trees \ gt; ranger turns to say a word of warning \ gt; the air is filled with crossbow bolts \ gt; through insurmountable luck, most of the bolts miss, however, the sorcerer is nearly dropped on the first round \ gt; guards burst out of the trees and grass, rushing forward to fight the party \ gt; roll initiative \ gt; the sorcerer gets off a fireball just before the guards clash into them, managing to kill about 5 people \ gt; the barbarian swings his sword, cleaving a guard completely in two before taking several hits \ gt; the fighter, desperately swinging with his sword, manages to take about 3 people out before he #8217;s knocked out \ gt; the cleric heals him up to about half health and the fight continues \ gt; suddenly, there is a ringing voice above the sounds of combat \ gt;  #8220;everybody, stop! #8221; \ gt; the party and guards go silent and turn to the source of the sound \ gt; they see Farin, adorned in his marvellous armour, holding the barely standing sorcerer in a choke, a sword pressed closely to his throat \ gt;  #8220;drop your weapons, or we #8217;ll find out if your friend bleeds red #8221; \ gt; the guards take a few steps back, holding their weapons steady \ gt; party isn #8217;t looking so good \ gt; most have less than half health, cleric has burned through a lot of his spell slots \ gt; ranger looks at Farin and draws bow tighter \ gt;  #8220;lizardfolk no fear death #8221; \ gt;  #8220;you might not, but are you willing to live with the knowledge that you got your friend killed? #8221; \ gt; barbarian takes step closer to Farin, swinging sword in slow arcs \ gt;  #8220;you not win #8221; \ gt;  #8220;I disagree. I #8217;d say this is over #8221;.  #8220;Drop your weapons, or you all die here #8221; \ gt; suddenly sorcerer looks at me \ gt;  #8220;does Farin have a dagger? #8221; \ gt;  #8220;yes #8221; \ gt;  #8220;could I use my tail to take it off of him and put it in my hand? #8221; \ gt; party #8217;s expressions go from grimaces to smirks in a heartbeat \ gt;  #8220;roll sleight of hand #8221; \ gt; 18 \ gt; slowly and carefully, the sorcerer draws Farin #8217;s dagger from its sheath, manoeuvring it into his hand \ gt;  #8220;I #8217;d like to stab this f\*cker in his ribs #8221; \ gt; rolls to hit \ gt; nat 20 \ gt; with a grin, the sorcerer jams the dagger deep into Farin #8217;s ribs \ gt; Farin lets out a yell of pain and drops him \ gt; the party, who had been holding their actions, all attack him at once \ gt; Farin barely gets a second to breathe before his shoulder is struck by an arrow, his thigh speared and a large gash is torn through his armour \ gt; he stumbles back, and the party watches on, expecting him to die \ gt; after taking a short breath, he yanks the dagger out of his chest and gives them a look of fury \ gt;  #8220;savages. YOU DARE! #8221; \ gt; he rips the arrow out of his shoulder, and they watch as the hole, the spear wound and most of the gash closes over \ gt; ohfuck.jpg \ gt; he swings his sword, slicing a deep wound across the sorcerer #8217;s chest \ gt; the sorcerer falls to the ground, not dead, but bleeding out \ gt; an odd, black vapour trickles from the wound, alongside the red blood of the sorcerer \ gt; the guards go to step forward but Farin raises a hand \ gt;  #8220;no. These savages want to fight? They can have a fight #8221; \ gt; combat begins \ gt; ranger looses two shots, only one of which hits \ gt; it imbeds itself in his chest, but he barely seems to notice \ gt; the barbarian swings his sword \ gt; Farin deflects both blows \ gt; fighter throws his spear before running in with sword \ gt; spear cuts open Farin #8217;s arm, and the sword follows by widening the gash \ gt; the cleric tries to run to the sorcerer #8217;s side, 5 ft away from making it without dashing \ gt; Farin #8217;s wound begin closing over, and he gives a smile \ gt; party notice his teeth for the first time \ gt; more specifically, the two distinctly pointed ones \ gt; ohno.mp3 \ gt;  #8220;I have to thank you for dealing with those bandits. They were weak at best and I knew I #8217;d have to remove them eventually #8221; \ gt; he swings his sword, barbarian barely deflects before second swing opens cut on his arm \ gt; barbarian now below half health \ gt; ranger takes a shot \ gt; nat 20 \ gt; the arrow pierces Farin #8217;s right eye \ gt; Farin lets out a roar and stumbles back \ gt; barbarian takes two swings with advantage \ gt; rolls for chance with his sword \ gt; two 4 #8217;s \ gt; the third and fourth time he #8217;s dealt magic damage this campaign \ gt; cleric casts sacred flame \ gt; Farin fails the save \ gt; takes 8 radiant damage \ gt; sorcerer fails second death save \ gt; Farin #8217;s wounds don #8217;t close over, cuts litter his body and his breathing seems to be laboured \ gt; Farin suddenly jumps forward and grabs fighter \ gt; bites him \ gt; fighter #8217;s head swims and he drops to one knee, not unconscious but close \ gt; ranger jumps forward and pushes Farin \ gt; Farin fails his save and falls prone \ gt; ranger jumps on him and bites his throat \ gt; Farin lets out a scream of pain and ranger gets some of his health back \ gt; while Farin is down, fighter stabs him \ gt; Farin curls around the sword, severely hurt \ gt; barbarian manages to miss both swings even as cleric uses spare the dying on sorcerer \ gt; Farin #8217;s wounds begin to heal up \ gt; rolls to hit ranger \ gt; nat 20 \ gt; party watches in horror as Farin grabs ranger by the throat and rams his sword into his stomach \ gt; 5 hp off an instant death \ gt; ranger drops to the ground as Farin stands up straight \ gt; he swings his sword, cutting open the barbarian #8217;s chest \ gt; not looking good \ gt; ranger succeeds first death save \ gt; fighter tries to stab Farin, misses both hits \ gt; barbarian hits Farin with another lightning hit, but misses the second swing \ gt; cleric lets off a sacred flame \ gt; Farin makes the save \ gt; Farin begins to heal up \ gt; he kicks fighter in the face, fighter knocked unconscious \ gt;  #8220;I #8217;ve had enough of this #8221; \ gt; he waves to guards \ gt; guards walk over and kick out the back of barbarian and cleric #8217;s knees \ gt; bring them to kneel before Farin \ gt; Farin raises his sword, but hesitates just before he brings it down, as if he #8217;s hearing something \ gt;  #8220;of course my lord #8221; \ gt; Farin sheathes the sword and turns to the guards \ gt;  #8220;grab the cage, Highwater wants to see these savages in person #8221; \ gt; guards knock out barbarian and cleric First post: [https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/97riuv/eating\_people\_is\_fine\_so\_long\_as\_we\_all\_agree\_on/](https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/97riuv/eating_people_is_fine_so_long_as_we_all_agree_on/) Previous post: [https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/98z8vb/lizardfolk\_35\_deception\_disguises\_and\_lack\_thereof/](https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/98z8vb/lizardfolk_35_deception_disguises_and_lack_thereof/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 14:10:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>The game continued for a little bit after this. I will post in a bit. Just thought that this post was quite long already Edit: by a bit, I mean tomorrow. I'm tired after that game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 22:41:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you. Repeatedly doing this has made my life so much easier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 22:44:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you take an amount of damage that equals or surpasses negative your max hit points, you die instantly. For example. A ranger might have 37 max hp. They have 1 hp during a fight with an adult red dragon. Red dragon blasts him with fire breath. Ranger takes 40 damage. Ranger immediately dies without saving throws.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 22:56:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>sorry for the misunderstanding, the ranger is fine. Mostly ...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lizardfolk 4.5: The strongest jaws on the planet</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 01:27:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>(continuation of "tooth and sword") \ gt;party wakes up in cages on a moving carriage \ gt;still late at night, a few hours from dawn \ gt;ranger and fighter in same cage, sorcerer and cleric in another, and barbarian is by himself \ gt;guards flank the carriage \ gt;they have no equipment \ gt;immediately, sorcerer tries to cast acid splash on the bars \ gt;nothing happens \ gt;the cages have sigils to prevent the use of magic inside them \ gt;party content with scoping out their situation \ gt;8 guards, 1 in front of theirs \ gt;Farin nowhere to be seen, party presume he's in the carriage \ gt;fighter; "how thick are the bars?" \ gt;"1 inch thick" \ gt;"shiiiiitttttt" \ gt;fighter tries to push bars and pull them apart \ gt;guard smacks his fingers with the shaft of a spear \ gt;"oy, stop that you stupid savage. That's solid steel. You ain't getting out" \ gt;fighter sits back down \ gt;continue riding for a few more hours, party fall into a dull silence \ gt;finally, fighter taps ranger on the leg with his tail \ gt; #8220;Darya #8230; #8221; \ gt;ranger looks up \ gt; #8220;yeah? #8221; \ gt;fighter pauses for a moment \ gt; #8220;what is a savage? #8221; \ gt; #8220;what? #8221; \ gt; #8220;what the fleshies call us. Savage. What does it mean? #8221; \ gt; #8220;oh. It #8217;s nothing #8221; \ gt; #8220;please tell me. What does it mean? #8221; \ gt;ranger sighs \ gt; #8220;it #8217;s what they call people not like them #8221; \ gt; #8220;lizardfolk? #8221; \ gt; #8220;sometimes. They call people they don #8217;t understand savages. It means uncivilized. Wild. It scares them #8221; \ gt;fighter pauses for a bit \ gt;"are we savages?" \ gt;"no. We live to survive. Fleshies don't understand that. We're not savages. We're just different" \ gt;ranger grabs fighter's shoulder \ gt;"we're not going to change to make them happy. We are lizardfolk, not fleshies" \ gt;when they're finished talking, barbarian looks at me \ gt;"what time is it?" \ gt;"from what you can tell, around 3 in the morning" \ gt;"would you like to hear a fun fact (DM)?" \ gt;what.jpg \ gt;"did you know that a saltwater crocodile can exert around 16,000 newtons of force in a single bite?" \ gt;"umm, yes, but why is this important?" \ gt;"I'd like to bite through the bars of my cage" \ gt;ohshit.mp3 \ gt;"if you do, people may notice" \ gt;"i'll do it quietly" \ gt;"you'll bite through steel quietly?" \ gt;"yes" \ gt;oh boy, here we go \ gt;"roll a strength check" \ gt;nat 20 \ gt;"roll sleight of hand' \ gt;nat 20 \ gt;nobody notices as barbarian proceeds to bite his way through his cage, leaving a hole large enough for him to escape through \ gt;"I'd like to do the same for the other cages" \ gt;"roll 2 more strength and 2 stealth checks" \ gt;strength checks: 18, 19 \ gt;stealth checks: 15, 15 \ gt;mfw \ gt;after a long process, he sneaks up to the other cages and bites a hole through each \ gt;whole ordeal takes about an hour \ gt;ranger looks at barbarian \ gt;"sneak back to your cage and wait until dawn. We'll escape with the sun" \ gt;rolls for stealth \ gt;4 \ gt;ohfuck \ gt;as he goes to sneak back, a guard looks over, seeing him out of the cage \ gt;lizardfolk and human stare at each other for a moment \ gt;human calls out an alarm \ gt;barbarian attacks \ gt;plan goes to shit \ gt;everyone gets out of their cages, rushing to fight the guards \ gt;after a brief contact, a few guards are unconscious, only 1 dead, and the party is looking hurt \ gt;party hears the carriage door click \ gt;barbarian: "i want to hold the door shut so Farin can't get out" \ gt;he runs over and plants his back against the door, digging his heels into the dirt \ gt;Farin goes to open the door \ gt;door doesn't move \ gt;strength check vs strength save \ gt;barbarian strains as Farin barely fails to push the door open \ gt;"i won't hold him for long" \ gt;ranger looks at me \ gt;"what's around us?" \ gt;"on your left is open fields, on your right is a drowned forest" \ gt;ranger gives me the biggest grin I think i've ever seen a person give \ gt;"everyone run to the forest and get in the water. (barbarian), count to twenty and then come after us. Don't look back" \ gt;party sprints for the forest, arrows and crossbow bolts raining around them \ gt;barbarian tries to hold off Farin \ gt;one successful save \ gt;two successful saves \ gt;fail \ gt;he is pushed aside as Farin kicks the door open \ gt;barbarian begins running \ gt;rest of party dives into waist deep water and begin to swim away \ gt;barbarian sprints, taking about 3 shots to his back \ gt;just before he reaches the water, he feels a hand on his arm \ gt;"you think it's going to be that easy?" \ gt;barbarian turns, sees Farin raising sword \ gt;barbarian grabs arm holding his \ gt;barbarian rolls to hit \ gt;nat 20 \ gt;barbarian bites off Farin's hand \ gt;Farin drops to the ground screaming as barbarian dives into the water \ gt;Farin gets to his feet as his hand begins to reform, about to follow them \ gt;then the sun comes up \ gt;his clothes begin to smoulder as he burns \ gt;growling in frustration he returns to his carriage, telling the guards to follow the party \ gt;party escape into drowned forest, no equipment, no food, nothing \ gt;game ends</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 08:01:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly like previous comment explained. He gave his reasoning, I believed that to be fair, and he did achieve the same thing with an 18. His stealth was more the focus here, but i gave leniency due to the fact that it was extremely dark. All in all, I believed it was justified, so i allowed it to happen. Also, i also believe a nat 20 shouldn't be an unjustified success. If someone watches you stab another person and then you roll a nat 20 on deception by saying "someone else did it", no, you have to come up with a genuine and justified reason something may work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 08:56:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are so many rolls you don't see in that game. I only highlight fun stuff in the game. There was a god awful amount of 5's in that game too. Fighter missed every attack for 3 rounds in the fight with the guards. And regarding proper grammar. They use proper grammar when speaking to each other. Otherwise they have broken language</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 08:58:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Many thanks. Also yes. I feel obliged to write every game. It was meant to be a one off post</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 09:45:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Additional thing. I've looked back, and they've always talked with proper grammar to each other. That came up even in the first post. Basically, the draconic is my player's way of not constantly having to speak broken english to each other.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 15:45:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Again, thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 15:47:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>The best way i found was to just ask if people were interested. I initially didn't think any of my friends would care for d amp;d at all, but after asking around, turns out a lot were interested to try.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 15:51:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just want to rehash how amazing you are. Thank you so much for this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 03:52:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>His sword had a 1 in 4 chance to deal 1d6 lightning damage. We rolled for that chance with a d4 every hit. A 4 meant magic damage. In the campaign so far, he had only dealt that extra 1d6 damage twice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 03:57:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>As mentioned to another person, there are so many god awful rolls that I don't mention. If you saw every roll, you'd be shocked by how god awful the fighter's luck is. It'd be amusing if it wasn't so detrimental.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Game brought forward</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 09:42:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone! We just finished our game today. Several of us were unable to play tomorrow, so we moved it to Sunday afternoon. I'll be posting the story soon. It will be in 2 parts, as this was a long game. Hope to see you then!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lizardfolk 5; "looks like we #8217;re going to be partaking in some guerrilla warfare. This ought to be fun #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 11:48:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>\ gt;be me; LizarDM \ gt;be not me; lizardfolk ranger, lizardfolk fighter, lizardfolk barbarian, lizardfolk cleric, lizardfolk sorcerer \ gt;having just escaped Farin by fleeing into a drowned forest, the party is item less and being pursued \ gt;ranger hides behind tree until rest of group can swim over \ gt;eventually, barbarian arrives too \ gt;fighter:  #8220;They #8217;re going to follow us #8221; \ gt;barbarian:  #8220;Not Farin, the sun is rising, there aren #8217;t enough leaves to shield him #8221; \ gt;fighter:  #8220;fleshies can follow us though #8221; \ gt;barbarian grins \ gt; #8220;fleshies are in our territory now. If they follow us, they will die #8221; \ gt;ranger asks me if he can use his primeval awareness (we #8217;re using revised ranger, UA) \ gt;he ducks his head underneath the water and stays there for about a minute \ gt;I tell him that there are 6 human guards approaching from the north, about 1 km away \ gt;he relays this info to the party, also informing them that there might be other, non-human guards that he can #8217;t find \ gt;sorcerer;  #8220;(cleric) and I have magic, but you guys don #8217;t have weapons. How are we going to win? #8221; \ gt;barbarian gives another grin \ gt; #8220;we #8217;ll have weapons so long as we can just take out one of them #8221; \ gt;ranger gives a smile \ gt; #8220;well, it looks like we #8217;re going to be partaking in some guerrilla warfare. This ought to be fun #8221; \ gt;party spend next few minutes formulating plan while they wait for guards to catch up \ gt;they hear the guards long before they see them \ gt;stepping through waist, and sometimes neck height water, they can #8217;t help but make noise as they go through the forest \ gt;most guards have opted to use spears and crossbows, as they aren #8217;t confident in their ability to fight with swords in water \ gt;party splits up from the tree, several sliding underwater as they depart \ gt;sorcerer looks at me \ gt; #8220;I #8217;d like to cast shape water, but use a third level spell slot to enhance it #8221; \ gt;fuckit.jpg \ gt;as guards are wading waist deep in water, they feel the temperature suddenly cool around them, becoming painfully cold in a span of seconds \ gt;the water begins to turn to ice around them, and the guards scramble to climb a tree in time \ gt;as most of them climb trees, one guard tries to climb, only to feel a hand grab his leg \ gt;the barbarian pulls him under, beginning to drag him away \ gt;rest of guards can #8217;t see anything under the ice anymore \ gt;barbarian asks how long guard can hold his breath \ gt;I tell him 2 minutes \ gt;barbarian frowns and shakes his head \ gt; #8220;that #8217;s too long. I think I #8217;ll change that #8221; \ gt;barbarian punches guard in the diaphragm \ gt;guard can #8217;t help but lose his breath \ gt; #8220;roll a strength save #8221; \ gt;10 in total \ gt;barbarian can #8217;t hold on as the guard tries to swim for the surface \ gt;barbarian smiles \ gt; #8220;I let him go. He can #8217;t get through the ice #8221; \ gt;sure enough, the guard can #8217;t \ gt;he fails 2 strength checks before he succumbs to a horrible, slow death, and his struggles finally stop \ gt;barbarian nods approval before dragging the body away \ gt;meanwhile on the surface, rest of party slinks away, the cleric using thaumaturgy to surround the area near the guards with sounds of people splashing through the water \ gt;party regroups several hundred meters away, and using a sharpened stone, begin flaying the body \ gt;pretty soon, party has a decent supply of human meat, about 24 curved, rib daggers and a mace made from the skull connected to a femur \ gt;goodgod.jpg \ gt;fighter looks at some of his bone daggers \ gt; #8220;are there any large branches I could break off around here? #8221; \ gt;rolls perception \ gt;6 \ gt;he finds one, but as he goes to break it off, he snaps the branch in half, emitting a loud noise \ gt;party cringes \ gt; #8220;they would hear that, we must move #8221; \ gt;as party begins to move, they hear the sounds of guards approaching \ gt;party about to go into water when tiefling guard grabs cleric \ gt;barbarian turns back and grabs guard in a choke \ gt; #8220;let go red fleshy. You die #8221; \ gt;tiefling gives out a strangled cry of warning for his fellow guards as cleric proceeds to shank him repeatedly with a sharpened rib \ gt;barbarian dumps body of tiefling just as guards approach \ gt;barbarian takes a shot from a crossbow and cleric takes 2 before they slink away into the water \ gt;as they #8217;re escaping, crossbow bolts being shot into the water \ gt;cleric takes another shot and starts bleeding profusely \ gt;blood trail in water starting to reveal his position \ gt;sorcerer comes out of water \ gt;casts fog cloud \ gt;guards can #8217;t see shit as party swim away \ gt;even so, sorcerer takes a lucky shot to the shoulder before he gets back underwater \ gt;party regroup about 2 kilometres away \ gt;cleric begins healing \ gt;burns through 3 spell slots \ gt;suggests a short rest to recover hp because he doesn #8217;t want to use too many slots \ gt;party disagrees. Think that guards will catch them if they take a short rest \ gt;fighter looks at me again \ gt; #8220;what about now? Any branches around? #8221; \ gt;rolls perception \ gt;2 \ gt;cleric, taking pity, says he wants to help look \ gt;fighter rerolls \ gt;14 \ gt;sees a nice branch \ gt;one issue \ gt;it #8217;s very high in a tree \ gt;fighter gives me biggest glare \ gt; #8220;I want to climb the tree #8221; \ gt;rolls athletics \ gt;16 \ gt;using his tail to wrap around the trunk like a rope, fighter begins climbing \ gt;as he climbs, I roll a chance d20 \ gt;as he puts his hand on another branch, it suddenly snaps \ gt;rolls dex save \ gt;5 \ gt;rolls acrobatics as he falls \ gt;10 \ gt;fighter manages to get his feet under him as he hits the water \ gt;there were roots under the water \ gt;he hits them, taking 2d6 bludgeoning damage \ gt;cleric burns another spell slot to heal him \ gt;barbarian;  #8220;I will get the stick for him #8221; \ gt;rolls athletics \ gt;19 \ gt;as he climbs, I roll a d20 \ gt;the tree begins groaning a lot as he gets near the branch \ gt;barbarian stops \ gt;looks at fighter \ gt; #8220;just how badly do you want this stick? #8221; \ gt; #8220;just get me the f\*cking stick already #8221; \ gt;barbarian sighs and climbs up a little \ gt;he grabs the branch and rips it from the trunk \ gt;as he does so, a voice cries out in the distance \ gt;barbarian looks over, sees guards pointing up at him \ gt;guard lifts crossbow \ gt; #8220;I let go of the tree #8221; \ gt;mfw \ gt;barbarian drops a good 40 feet out of the tree \ gt;rolls acrobatics check \ gt;1 \ gt;barbarian breaks his foot as he lands on the roots \ gt;cleric burns 5th spell slot to heal him \ gt;barbarian shoves stick into fighter #8217;s hands before walking off \ gt;party moves deeper into drowned forest \ gt;at next meet up position, party finally agree to take a short rest \ gt;ranger agrees to keep watch \ gt;after expending a few hit die, party looking better \ gt;fighter finally completes what he wanted the stick for \ gt;he holds up his new spear; a stick with 3 of the rib daggers protruding from the top, bound together by the guard #8217;s belt and a few pieces of torn clothes \ gt;barbarian does some bargaining with me, and we decide that his skull weapon is more of a mace than a club, and that it should use the appropriate hit die \ gt;as party finally begin to move off, they notice the sun begin to get lower in the sky, nearing the horizon \ gt;party gives each other a look of shared concern \ gt;ranger;  #8220;it might cost us a level of exhaustion, but I suggest we continue through the night. We aren #8217;t equipped to fight him again #8221; \ gt;cleric;  #8220;he could still catch up to us. We #8217;ll have to fight him anyway #8221; \ gt;fighter;  #8220;we could set a trap. We could hit him with so much before he even knows we #8217;re there #8221; \ gt;sorcerer thinks for a moment \ gt; #8220;if he figures out what we #8217;re doing though, we #8217;re in trouble. If he catches one of us by ourselves, we #8217;re dead #8221; \ gt;ranger shakes his head \ gt; #8220;he wants us alive. It #8217;s why he caught us #8221; \ gt;barbarian;  #8220;guard #8217;s sure shot us with a lot of crossbow bolts for people who want us alive #8221; \ gt;cleric;  #8220;we can #8217;t go on the assumption he #8217;ll let us live. We have to fight like we #8217;re going to die #8221; \ gt;ranger;  #8220;and if it goes wrong? #8221; \ gt;no one answers \ gt;party begins to set up their trap as the sun slowly drifts over the horizon, veiling the forest in darkness</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 11:48:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry for the repeated reposts. Title issues</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lizardfolk 5.5; Moonlight Battle</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 12:02:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>\ gt;be me; lizarDM \ gt;be not me; lizardfolk ranger, lizardfolk fighter, lizardfolk barbarian, lizardfolk cleric, lizardfolk sorcerer \ gt;as night falls, the party sets up their trap for Farin \ gt;the cleric, with only 4 spell slots, has 2 first levels, 1 second and 1 third \ gt;as they #8217;re setting up their trap, the ranger uses his primeval awareness to look for any other guards \ gt;he notes a trio approaching and warns the rest of the party \ gt;barbarian desperately wants a better weapon, so he creeps closer to try hit first \ gt;barbarian and fighter sit waiting behind trees for about 15 minutes, but no one comes \ gt;confused and on edge, party finishes off final preparations for their trap and waits \ gt;about 3 hours pass in silence as the party wait for any sign Farin might be close \ gt;ranger periodically uses primeval awareness \ gt;never finds anything \ gt;the sun is gone, and the moon has begun its ascent \ gt;shadows lurch from every tree, making a horrible visage of confusing darkness \ gt;sorcerer holds a stick in his hand, looking around in the darkness intently \ gt;suddenly, in the distance, he sees a movement \ gt;rolls perception \ gt;10 \ gt;a flash through the trees, little more than a blur \ gt;without another second, he snaps the stick \ gt;the sound is deafening in the silence of the forest \ gt;the blur stops, and he sees a shadow, indistinct amongst the others in the distance \ gt;it begins moving again, slowly \ gt;creeping towards them \ gt;sorcerer tries to slink back into the water as silently as possible \ gt;rolls stealth \ gt;15 \ gt;the water makes the tiniest of sounds as he retreats into it, leaving only his eyes above the surface \ gt;the shadow detaches itself from the surrounding trees, and Farin steps into a patch of moonlight, hardly making a sound despite standing in knee deep water \ gt;he peers around, looking for movement and listening for sound \ gt;and then the cleric hits the ground in front of him with Daylight \ gt;Farin is instantly blinded as the area fills with 60ft of bright light \ gt; the ranger peels away from a tree, throwing two rib daggers before returning to his hiding spot \ gt;one dagger imbeds itself in his thigh and Farin roars, even as the barbarian emerges from the water behind him \ gt;the barbarian swings his bone mace, slamming the skull against the back of Farin #8217;s head \ gt;after throwing a bone dagger that goes wide, the fighter jumps in, stabbing forward with his newly made spear, catching Farin in the stomach \ gt;the sorcerer hits with a lightning bolt, and without his eyes, Farin had no chance to dodge it before he #8217;s struck \ gt;the wound in his stomach begins to heal, even as he blinks the light out of his eyes \ gt;immediately, Farin swings his sword, cutting open a large wound in the barbarian #8217;s chest \ gt;he swings again, and the fighter barely manages to deflect the strike \ gt;the cleric runs in, summoning a spiritual weapon (a shining, bone and stone maul) \ gt;he swings it at Farin but the sword quickly manages to block the hit \ gt;the ranger throws two more daggers \ gt;16, nat 1 \ gt;the first dagger leaves a dent in Farin #8217;s armour, little more and the second dagger flies past his head, opening up a scratch on the barbarian #8217;s face \ gt;the barbarian rages and swings his mace 3 times \ gt;2 are easily deflected, but the third slams into Farin #8217;s knee cap, breaking it immediately \ gt;Farin stumbles to his knee, making him an easy target for the spear that stabbed him in the chest \ gt;the sorcerer launched magic missile at him, opening up a massive hole in Farin #8217;s back \ gt;Farin jumps up and grabs the barbarian, biting him in the neck \ gt;Farin #8217;s kneecap heals up and so does a lot of his back wound \ gt;barbarian fails save, hit points reduced by damage \ gt;cleric heals him up with cure wounds before swinging again with the maul \ gt;Farin ducks under the blow \ gt;the ranger, seeing Farin #8217;s exposed back, runs in, a dagger in each hand \ gt;he stabs both into Farin #8217;s back, using the hole the magic missile blasted in his armour \ gt;the barbarian tries to swing his mace \ gt;first swing; miss \ gt;second swing; miss \ gt;third swing; nat 1 \ gt;as he swings his mace, Farin turns, swinging his sword \ gt;the mace takes the hit, and with a crack, is cleaved in half \ gt;fighter stabs Farin in the thigh and tries to go for his head, but Farin manages to duck out of the way \ gt;sorcerer launches another lightning bolt at him \ gt;Farin passes the save, but still takes a heap of lightning damage \ gt;he turns around and brings sword down on ranger with a two-handed strike \ gt;nat 20 \ gt;rolls damage \ gt;full damage \ gt;deep cut from shoulder to hip opens ranger up, black vapour spewing out \ gt;Farin promptly slices open the cleric #8217;s arm \ gt;he #8217;s looking poor, but still far from death \ gt;cleric dives past Farin, barely avoiding an opportunity attack and uses his last spell slot to cast cure wounds \ gt;meanwhile, his maul takes a swing at Farin, catching him in the side of the face \ gt;Farin spits out some teeth \ gt;ranger gets to his feet, now that his innards aren #8217;t in danger of being on the floor and launches a kick at the back of Farin #8217;s leg \ gt;Farin stumbles but doesn #8217;t fall \ gt;barbarian shoves Farin, and after already being off balance, he falls \ gt; #8220;die dead fleshy! #8221; barbarian screams as he jumps on top \ gt;Farin raises an arm, taking the bite that would #8217;ve torn out his throat on the forearm \ gt;fighter stabs Farin, digging it deep into his stomach \ gt;the spear breaks and the fighter shrugs \ gt;jumps on top and sinks his teeth into Farin #8217;s shoulder \ gt;Farin lets out a yell of pain and tries squirming out of the two lizardfolk #8217;s jaws \ gt;the sorcerer uses misty step to close the distance, and, like his friends, sinks his teeth in \ gt;Farin #8217;s yells turn into panicked screams \ gt; #8220;GET OFF YOU SAVAGES! #8221; \ gt;his wounds desperately try to close themselves up, even as chunks of his flesh are torn off \ gt;he goes to stand up, but with the combined weight of three lizardfolk, can #8217;t \ gt;he desperately tries to swing his sword at the barbarian \ gt;nat 20 \ gt;barbarian yells as the sword cuts out his eye \ gt;cleric replaces barbarian \ gt; #8220;we tell you. You no win #8221; \ gt;holds Farin #8217;s head back by the hair and proceeds to close his jaws around Farin #8217;s neck \ gt;Farin #8217;s screams become horrific gurgles before they #8217;re abruptly cut off as the cleric rips out his throat \ gt;Farin goes limp and his eyes glaze over \ gt;fighter grabs his sword and uses it to carve into his body \ gt;party proceed to skin and devour Farin \ gt;after a long rest, cleric tries to heal barbarian #8217;s eye \ gt;the skin closes over, but the eye isn #8217;t restored \ gt;barbarian shrugs and asks fighter for the sword \ gt;fighter passes him the sword and barbarian proceeds to cut out a piece of Farin #8217;s armour \ gt;using a piece of Farin #8217;s clothing, barbarian makes himself a makeshift, metal eye patch \ gt;game ends</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 12:22:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. Over the time we've played D amp;D, we've played EtA and MoP, but other than that, it's all been homebrew games</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 13:34:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, but would you mind not repeating this message any more. It is incredibly annoying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 13:37:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would you mind explaining what it is i am doing wrong for it to not appear as green text? I am prefixing each line with a  gt;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 14:11:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is awesome. Thanks so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 15:49:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>He was too distracted to mourn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 23:08:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>We discussed how the skull acted like the head of a mace, as a skull, especially the front, is extremely hard. I guess we envisioned a club as little more than a large stick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 23:09:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Homebrew God. I can't give away answers as the rest of the party doesn't know who he serves and it's a major part of his character backstory.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 01:02:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>That may be a while. My campaigns tend to have quite a few arcs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 02:51:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much for this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 02:53:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be me unfortunately. I'm very new to reddit and this seems like a good format</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 02:56:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish. I'd be down to, but 3 of my players have gone on to say they don't want to. It's a shame, because I can see there's a lot of interest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 06:43:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>No</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 08:20:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>He didn't actually take Spirit Guardians. Probably will change that soon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 08:22:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>They have and they absolutely love it. They've being trying to avoid meta gaming as a result of reading the comments but they're just as amazed as I am at how popular these stories have become #8203;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 23:18:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>rule of cool? I dunno. None of us really did the maths but we liked the idea thematically. Ah well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 23:21:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't seen Ragnarok. Heard it was a good film though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 23:22:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>That may be true, if not for one key factor. Farin was a vampire spawn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 00:55:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Saltwater crocs. It's almost common knowledge here in Australia. Attacks are more common in the northern territory but quite a few people know how strong the bite is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 00:59:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks a lot. The d amp;d vampire lore runs more commonly with the Bram Stoker (Dracula) with a few minor changes to better suit a gaming scenario.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 01:13:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>We do not speak of those horrifying things here. Especially with socks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Several posts</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 08:16:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone. My players and I have a week off of work, so we'll be playing a lot more d amp;d. I'll be uploading today's game later, and who knows, we may play again tomorrow. Either way, expect an increase of posts until Sunday when we'll return to our usual schedule. Thanks and I hope you enjoy the stories to come!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 10:05:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>We all work at a small home media company owned by an older couple. They've been making home movies and some ads for other companies for about 20 years. Two of my friends and I were offered a job there and we met the other 3 people in the party there. We've worked together for about 3 years now.  #8203; Edit: we occasionally get a few days or a week off when work is slow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 10:27:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Regarding work. Pretty much. It pays well and it's a very relaxed scenario. They own a private company that helps other companies make advertisements and make their own small movies. I help write a lot of the screenplays for the ads and i got suggested to the couple after a piece of my work caught their attention.  #8203; Also, we live in Sydney. Not the capital city but probably the most well known. It's large, I think Melbourne might be larger though.  #8203; Regarding vampiric transformations. You'll just have to wait and see.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lizardfolk 6; he just really wants his sword doesn't he?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 11:24:21</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;be me; LizarDM  gt;be not me; lizardfolk ranger, lizardfolk fighter, lizardfolk barbarian, lizardfolk cleric, lizardfolk sorcerer (now level 6: We started at 5)  gt;party makes their way back to the carriages  gt;sun is up now and Farin #8217;s remains are stored happily in the party #8217;s stomachs  gt;as they approach the carriage, barbarian calls for everyone to slow down and approach with caution  gt;sure enough, guards are still there, waiting for Farin to return  gt;sorcerer launches fire bolt at one of them as the rest of the party jumps into action  gt;firebolt misses, scaring a lead horse  gt;it begins to bolt  gt;guards take one look at party, and seeing fighter wielding Farin #8217;s sword, get their own horses to start moving  gt;ranger desperately throws a dagger at the guards, but it falls short  gt;guards and carriages ride off  gt;party look at trail  gt;one way could lead back to Mildenbar, other would lead them to the carriage eventually  gt;party begins debate as to the best course of action  gt;barbarian decides for them by insisting that his sword was a gift from his village chief, and he refuses to leave without it  gt;party agrees to follow the carts  gt;after 3 days of travel, party fully aware that they likely won #8217;t catch up but being persistent  gt;crest a hill and see a massive city ahead of them  gt;immediately duck down so people on walls can #8217;t see them  gt;ranger asks if he would recognize the city  gt;rolls straight d20  gt;14  gt;he #8217;s never been inside, but he knows its reputation  gt;Xanimat; the sunshine city  gt;the city is renowned for its extravagant parties, full of the rich and noble  gt;it is also renowned for its expansive black market, where one could find just about anything they desire  gt;party contemplate disguises but end up deciding against them on the basis that word of them might not have spread this far  gt;party enter Xanimat; getting odd looks from the guards at the gate as they enter  gt;as soon as they enter, they realize they have no chance of finding the carts  gt;the streets are absolutely packed with humans, half elves, dwarves, gnomes and humanoids of every variety  gt;ranger casts locate item on the sword  gt;immediately gets a ping  gt;party begins heading off in the direction of the sword, pushing through crowds and attracting a lot of weird looks  gt;end up taking several side streets and alleyways  gt;end up in a more dishevelled part of the city; well away from the public eye and main streets  gt;as they walk, they see more shady appearing figures around them, casting them looks of suspicion and intrigue  gt;party keep following sword signal  gt;end up at small market in a quiet corner of the city  gt;party notices people standing in strategic positions, looking out  gt;immediately stand out as they approach  gt;as they walk in, they hear a small word of thanks, and a young, robe wearing man steps away from a stand  gt;he has the sword in his hand  gt;he begins to walk away  gt;barbarian immediately steps forward  gt;as he gets closer, a pair interject themselves between him and the man  gt;both adorned in intricately designed armour, one, a male elf, has a spear, while the other, a female human, wields a wicked looking scythe  gt;barbarian takes a step back as the two step forward  gt; #8220;move fleshies. I get sword #8221;  gt;woman shakes her head slowly  gt; #8220;back up lizardman. If you go for the sword, all you #8217;ll feel is this scythe in your chest #8221;  gt;rest of party nears, fighter drops hand to sword. (it rests in a simple scabbard on Farin #8217;s belt)  gt;woman #8217;s eyes narrow as she sees the sword, and her grip on the scythe tightens  gt;barbarian lets out a low growl  gt;the woman gives him a small, unimpressed smile  gt;party notices her teeth  gt;pointed  gt;immediately more on edge  gt;just before it looks like there #8217;s going to be a brawl, a young half orc steps in  gt; #8220;woah there. Let #8217;s just calm down, shall we? #8221;  #8220;I #8217;m sure this is all a misunderstanding #8221;  gt;elf gives a long groan  gt; #8220;what do you want Tiber? #8221;  gt; #8220;this is all a misunderstanding. These guys are new to town, they #8217;re with me. Friends of my old man on the eastern coast #8221;  gt;elf raises an eyebrow and casts an eye over the party  gt; #8220;they #8217;re with you? #8221; he asks, clearly unconvinced  gt;Tiber gives a winning smile  gt; #8220;yep. Help defend his boats from pirates. Don #8217;t you? #8221;  gt;ranger nods slowly  gt; #8220;we defend boat #8221;  gt;Tiber raises his arms in a  #8216;I told you so #8217; sort of gesture  gt;woman #8217;s eyes narrow but she relaxes slightly  gt; #8220;get your friends out of here. I don #8217;t want to see them again #8221;  gt; #8220;of course Milana, you won #8217;t be seeing them again #8221;  gt;with that, Milana and elf walk off, following behind the man wielding barbarian #8217;s sword  gt;Tiber turns and wipes a bead of sweat from his head  gt; #8220;better watch yourselves. Those Grimnar Knights are bad business #8221;  gt;fighter points at the pair; looking as the knights walk through a patch of sunlight  gt; #8220;they vampire. Why no burn #8221;  gt;Tiber shrugs  gt; #8220;something to do with the magic casters in the city. Highwater ordered them to cast protective charms on those two. Magic shit. I don #8217;t really understand it #8221;  gt;barbarian stares at pair  gt; #8220;have sword #8221;  gt;Tiber shrugs  gt; #8220;they #8217;ll deliver it to some rich fella, probably Wistmon. He likes collecting weird shit #8221;  gt; #8220;is mine #8221;  gt; #8220;tell that to Wistmon. It #8217;s his now #8221;  gt;barbarian grabs Tiber by the collar and pulls him close  gt; #8220;get sword back #8221;  gt;Tiber #8217;s eyes go wide, and he scrambles away as the barbarian lets him go  gt; #8220;jeez man, show some restraint. Who would want to help you with that sort of attitude? #8221;  gt;ranger steps forward  gt; #8220;he sorry. He just the very stressed #8221;  gt;Tiber raises an eyebrow  gt; #8220;why does this sword mean so much to him? #8221;  gt; #8220;it gift chief #8221;  gt; #8220;riiiiight #8221;  gt;Tiber gestures to disappearing figures of the two Grimnar Knights and the man  gt; #8220;well, they #8217;ll be heading to Wistmon. You #8217;ll have a hard time getting to him. Besides his parties, he could just as easily not exist for all we see of him #8221;  gt;fighter;  #8220;what a party? #8221;  gt;Tiber facepalms  gt; #8220;oh boy, you really are screwed aren #8217;t you? #8221;  gt;ranger;  #8220;you help us #8221;  gt;Tiber raises an eyebrow  gt; #8220;I help you? #8221;  gt; #8220;we pay #8221;  gt;Tiber gives a small smile  gt; #8220;you got money? #8221;  gt;ranger thinks for a moment  gt; #8220;money on cart #8221;  gt;Tiber suddenly looks at the fighter and gets a glint in his eye  gt; #8220;the sword. I #8217;ll help you if you give me the sword #8221;  gt;fighter immediately puts hand on it  gt;Tiber smiles  gt; #8220;no sword, no help #8221;  gt;ranger shakes his head  gt; #8220;we find way in #8221;  gt;Tiber shrugs  gt; #8220;suit yourself #8221;  gt;party walk away to try find some place to sleep for the night * * * * *  gt;after sleeping rough, party contemplate what to do  gt;fighter likes his new sword but also realizes that money is necessary  gt;party decide to hold off selling the sword until they really need to  gt;begin exploring city, trying to find their bearings  gt;party end up discovering massive houses, likely the homes of barons and rich people  gt;lizardfolk briefly visit a few stores before leaving because they don #8217;t have money  gt;spend most of day trying to figure out how to get the sword back  gt;finally get an idea as they walk through the streets  gt;a frail, old silver dragonborn passes them, carrying books and moving slowly  gt;the party stare at him as they pass, as only the ranger was aware of dragonborn #8217;s existence  gt;sorcerer runs up to him and begins speaking in draconic  gt; #8220;which clan are you from? #8221; he immediately asks  gt;dragonborn turns to him slowly  gt; #8220;what #8217;s that, young man? #8221;  gt;sees party  gt; #8220;oohh, green dragonborn. My eyes are failing me, but I would recognize your kind at any time #8221;  gt;sorcerer frowns  gt; #8220;we #8217;re lizardfolk. What #8217;s a dragonborn? #8221;  gt; #8220;are you sure, young man? You look distinctly draconic to me #8221;  gt; #8220;I #8217;m a lizardfolk. From the swamp #8221;  gt; #8220;from the swamp huh. You know, I #8217;ve heard there are lots of weird races in there. Best be careful. Us dragonborn have to stick together #8221;  gt; #8220;I am a lizardfolk #8221;  gt; #8220;that #8217;s very interesting, young man. Unfortunately, I #8217;m quite busy. Have to get ready for Wistmon #8217;s party tonight. It #8217;s supposed to be extravagant #8221;  gt;he looks at sorcerer and smiles  gt; #8220;I do hope to see you there. I would love to continue our conversation further #8221;  gt;walks away  gt;party gets their idea  gt;ranger proceeds to steal some clothes from a nearby store  gt;18 sleight of hand check  gt;he brings them back to the group and they proceed to put on clothes in an alleyway  gt;hide their daggers under clothes  gt;fighter decides to carry sword in his hands  gt;as night falls, the party sees one of the houses light up, and music ring out into the city  gt;decide to walk over, shoddy disguises in place and a whole lot of desperate hope  gt;mfw lizardfolk are going into a high-end party disguised as dragonborn in order to steal their sword back  gt;mfw next session is going to be very interesting First post; https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/97riuv/eating_people_is_fine_so_long_as_we_all_agree_on/ Most recent; https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/9aeike/lizardfolk_55_moonlight_battle/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 11:39:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fixed now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 13:06:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>brilliant</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 13:34:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which ever is easiest for you. This is very entertaining and it's been great to see how dedicated you are to this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 23:05:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>As i mentioned in a post on my profile; we have a few early days during the week and this current week, we have been put on notice until work picks up next week. So that means more games.  #8203; Edit: we also play on Mondays and Thursdays normally. Yeah, we have a lot of spare time, but our pay compensates for that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 23:23:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>If by that you mean maori, it's not too dissimilar to the voice he has. More of a mix between Australian and south African. Very amusing to make. I felt it suited him best. For example, Farin had more of a well spoken english accent. Not too heavy, but distinct enough to notice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 08:15:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. They enjoy the comments but try not to meta game because of discussions there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>yep, another notification</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 11:43:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. So we finished playing today. We'll also play tomorrow but Friday is off. Enjoy the next story! Episode 7 of the lizardfolk campaign will be out very soon. It'll probably be in two parts, as it was a long game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lizardfolk 7; things are going better than expected</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 11:46:38</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;be me; lizarDM  gt;be not me; lizardfolk ranger, lizardfolk sorcerer, lizardfolk cleric, lizardfolk fighter, lizardfolk barbarian  gt;party readying themselves to enter Wistmon #8217;s estate  gt;after talking with a silver dragonborn, the party has planned to disguise themselves as green dragonborns  gt;use minor illusion to make the sword appear like a cane after seeing some people use them  gt;how could this go wrong?  gt;as the night draws closer, the Wistmon estate has lit up and music is blaring through the street  gt;party, in as much of a disguise as they can muster, finally decide to approach the building  gt;the doors are guarded by a bulky half orc and rough looking human  gt;massive line stretching away from door  gt;people in line all wearing very fancy clothing  gt;lizardfolk in stolen clothes stand out like a sore thumb  gt;as they approach the line, barbarian tries to skip it  gt;ranger grabs his arm and yanks him into line  gt;half elven woman in beautiful white and gold dress turns to them and gives them the look down  gt; #8220;you #8217;re an interesting bunch aren #8217;t you? Who #8217;re you wearing? #8221;  gt;cleric frowns at her  gt; #8220;we have clothes though? #8221;  gt;woman gives very forced laugh  gt; #8220;oh and funny too #8221;  gt;cleric is very confused  gt;woman gives him a smile  gt; #8220;so, who invited you? I was invited by Wistmon himself. We #8217;ve been friends for years #8221;  gt;lizardfolk nod blankly  gt;woman lifts up a small white letter; pulling it open  gt;her thumb conveniently obscuring the name of the inviter, she shows them  gt;line keeps moving as sorcerer eyes the letter carefully before she obscures it  gt;woman ends up at front of line  gt;flashes guards a smile and her invite  gt;they let her in  gt;party walk up  gt;guards take one look at them and raise their hand to stop them  gt; #8220;invites? #8221;  gt;ranger ooc looks around table  gt; #8220;we did not think this far #8230; did we #8230;? #8221;  gt;sorcerer gives a cocky smile  gt;he steps forward and holds out an invite  gt;guard looks at him, genuinely surprised  gt;looks at invite for a second  gt; #8220;uhh, come in sirs. Enjoy your night #8221;  gt;party enters the building  gt;sorcerer;  #8220;prestidigitation baby. Gotta love it #8221;  gt;immediately assaulted by sound and light  gt;there #8217;s about a hundred people in the front foyer alone, all in elegant suits and dresses  gt;party realize just how out of place they truly are  gt;barbarian questions party about consequences of hundreds of witnesses  gt;fighter brings up the suggestion of scaring off all the guests, but sorcerer reminds him that that will just bring the attention of the guards, or even worse, the Grimnar Knights  gt;party decide that the safer option is subtlety  gt;their speciality of course  gt;ranger casts locate item on the sword, getting a ping immediately  gt;lizardfolk begin making their way through the party, drawing looks from several people as they pass  gt;a waiter walks up to them, bearing a tray covered in small delicacies  gt; #8220;finger food? #8221; he asks  gt;barbarian frowns  gt; #8220;those not finger #8221;  gt;waiter looks very flustered  gt; #8220;ah, of course sir. I #8217;ll uhh #8230; be right on it #8230; #8221;  gt;quickly leaves  gt;barbarian turns to cleric  gt; #8220;stupid fleshy doesn #8217;t know what fingers are #8221;  gt;continue making their way through the party  gt;as they climb a few stairs, they come across a ballroom  gt;ballroom is full of dancing party goers  gt;of course they #8217;re doing a sophisticated slow dance  gt;lizardfolk look on at the display with extreme confusion  gt;barbarian;  #8220;where is the sword? #8221;  gt;ranger;  #8220;other side #8221;  gt;barbarian nods and begins marching across the ballroom  gt;shoves past several people  gt;pushes between man and woman  gt;woman looks at him and grabs him, moving into a dancing position  gt;barbarian #8217;s eyes go wide as she grabs him, and he tries to push her way  gt;she thinks it #8217;s a dance  gt;man interjects himself again, casting a glare at the barbarian before dancing with the woman  gt;barbarian reaches other side just as rest of party walk around  gt;barbarian;  #8220;fleshies are so weird #8221;  gt;party unanimously agrees  gt;proceed to walk towards the sword  gt;they enter what essentially is a private gallery of prized art and items in glass cases  gt;a few guests walk around, admiring the art and talking in hushed tones  gt;a woman looks at a painting of a face on a blank canvas while a gnome beside her admires it too  gt; #8220;I think it represents the fear of man in a confusing world. The blank canvas represents the uncertainty and doubt that we face every day #8221;  gt;gnome blinks for a moment before frowning  gt; #8220;I think he just forgot to paint a background to be honest #8221;  gt;both have an intense discussion about it before moving to the next exhibition  gt;barbarian points out the painting to the ranger  gt; #8220;what purpose does it serve? #8221;  gt;ranger shrugs  gt; #8220;it doesn #8217;t. Fleshies just like to look at them #8221;  gt;barbarian shakes his head  gt; #8220;waste of space #8221;  gt;party looks through the cases to find the sword, passing small statues, vases and jewellery  gt;they finally come across a large glass case  gt;sword is inside  gt;silver dragonborn is admiring it  gt;ohfuck.jpg  gt;sorcerer steps forward and dragonborn turns around  gt; #8220;oh hello there, young man. I was hoping to see you here #8221;  gt;dragonborn gestures to sword  gt; #8220;interesting piece isn #8217;t it? I #8217;ve been trying to figure out what it #8217;s made of #8221;  gt;sorcerer looks at it  gt;sorcerer looks at dragonborn  gt; #8220;bone #8221;  gt; #8220;oh how intriguing. From what creature? #8221;  gt;long pause  gt; #8220;dragon #8230; #8221;  gt;dragonborn takes long pause before letting out a small;  #8220;oh #8221;  gt;sorcerer;  #8220;is there any way we can take it out and look at it? #8221;  gt; #8220;you #8217;d have to ask the man himself. Last I saw, he was by the bar #8221;  gt;sorcerer thanks dragonborn and recites information to party  gt;barbarian takes long glance at it before they leave to find the bar  gt;Wistmon isn #8217;t hard to locate  gt;a tall high elf, he #8217;s dressed in an elegant suit and surrounded by guests  gt;party wait until he #8217;s alone; a process that takes the better part of an hour  gt;party elect ranger to speak to him  gt;ranger walks up, mustering all the charm he can  gt; #8220;hello #8221;  gt;Wistmon turns to look at him  gt; #8220;why hello. I don #8217;t believe I #8217;ve seen you around before #8221;  gt; #8220;I foreign #8221;  gt; #8220;ah, of course. Well. My name is Daytir Wistmon. I #8217;m the host of all of this #8221;  gt; #8220;is party nice #8221;  gt; #8220;yes, I do believe it is #8221;  gt;ranger confused for a second but pushes on  gt; #8220;saw sword. Can look? #8221;  gt; #8220;well of course you can look at it. Every one of my pieces is on display for that reason #8221;  gt; #8220;can take it out? #8221;  gt;rolls persuasion  gt;17  gt;Wistmon pauses  gt; #8220;sure, why not. I will have to accompany you however. I don #8217;t want anyone making off with it #8221;  gt;party begins to walk back upstairs, led by Wistmon  gt;Wistmon holds his hand against the glass for a moment and with a blue glow, a sigil lights up  gt;a small click sounds and he removes the case, carefully placing it on the ground  gt;carefully, he passes it to the ranger  gt;ranger;  #8220;okay. I want to pass it to (sorcerer), and in draconic, I want to tell him to make a copy of it #8221;  gt;sorcerer;  #8220;if he touches it he #8217;ll know it #8217;s an illusion #8221;  gt;cleric;  #8220;and what if he speaks draconic? #8221;  gt;ranger;  #8220;then get ready to run like all hell #8221;  gt;ranger passes sword to sorcerer and says a quick sentence in draconic  gt;sorcerer rolls sleight of hand  gt;15  gt;party on edge of their seats as ranger casts silent image; making a replica of the sword  gt;at the same time he casts minor illusion on the real sword to make it appear like another cane  gt;sorcerer passes illusion sword back to ranger  gt;ranger smiles at Wistmon and goes to place the illusion back in place  gt;Wistmon holds out his hands;  #8220;oh, I #8217;ll do that #8221;  gt;ranger;  #8220;no, is pleasure #8221;  gt;rolls persuasion  gt;18  gt;party let out sigh of relief as ranger puts the sword on the pedestal  gt;Wistmon replaces the case  gt;it locks  gt;ranger thanks him and party go to leave  gt;as they reach the stair case, they see a familiar face at the bottom  gt;Milana begins climbing the stairs towards them, wearing a beautiful red dress  gt;party tries to walk past her, keeping their eyes down  gt;she looks up  gt;barbarian looks up  gt;they meet eyes  gt;she recognizes him  gt;she looks at sorcerer #8217;s cane  gt;she knows it #8217;s an illusion  gt;her mouth opens in a wide grin  gt; #8220;I don #8217;t think you #8217;re supposed to have that are you? #8221;  gt;barbarian panics  gt;grabs the sword off sorcerer  gt;swings it at Milana  gt;it cuts open her arm and she gives him a smile, even as the wound closes over  gt; #8220;now why did you have to go do something like that? #8221;  gt;she grabs his arm  gt;he tries to break out  gt;hfw she #8217;s stronger than him  gt;with another small smile, she throws him behind her  gt;barbarian goes off the side of the stairs  gt;falls about 20 ft and crashes through a table  gt;music stops as people scream  gt;jigs up  gt;ranger pulls a dagger from under his shirt and stabs  gt;nat 20  gt;he jams it into her eye  gt;she gives a scream of pain and backs off  gt;party begins to run  gt;she pulls the dagger out of her eye and gives chase  gt;party shove through people to get to the door, barbarian close on their heels  gt;they reach the door and sprint out  gt;guards at door don #8217;t get a moment to react before Milana sprints out after them  gt;party run away into the night, Milana letting out a laugh of wicked joy as she pursues  gt;all together, things are going better than expected First: https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/97riuv/eating_people_is_fine_so_long_as_we_all_agree_on/ Most recent; https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/9axf1p/lizardfolk_6_he_just_really_wants_his_sword/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 12:32:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have a week off work. We're not playing on Friday but we will also hope to play tomorrow. Besides, I enjoy reciting these stories.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 12:54:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Writing it currently. Sorry i'm slow. Just tad distracted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lizardfolk 7.5; blades in the night</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 13:18:54</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;be me; LizarDM  gt;be not me; lizardfolk ranger, lizardfolk sorcerer, lizardfolk cleric, lizardfolk fighter, lizardfolk barbarian  gt;group fleeing Wistmon #8217;s party  gt;being pursued by Milana  gt;ohboy.jpg  gt;having abandoned her heels, she #8217;s just as fast as them, if not faster  gt;party realize they won #8217;t lose her by just running  gt;sorcerer casts fog cloud behind them  gt;she runs straight through it without so much as slowing down  gt;has new idea  gt;runs next to some crates  gt;pushes them over and casts silent image to make it appear as if there are several more crates  gt;idea is that she won #8217;t know which ones aren #8217;t real  gt;his grin drops when she simply vaults over them, only gaining more ground  gt;ranger throws two daggers back at her  gt;both go wide because of disadvantage  gt;only lets her get closer  gt;party panicking now  gt;sorcerer looks at me  gt; #8220;how close behind is she? #8221;  gt; #8220;around 10 metres (close to 30ft) #8221;  gt; #8220;if I turn around and cast a spell, will she catch me? #8221;  gt; #8220;depends how long you take #8221;  gt;sorcerer gives out long shuddering breath  gt;player is actually really stressed  gt; #8220;okay. I turn and cast maximillian #8217;s earthen grasp #8221;  gt;Milana #8217;s demented smile widens as sorcerer turns. She reaches out to him, teeth bared  gt;a stone hand reaches up from the ground and tries to grab her leg  gt;strength check  gt;3  gt;party hears a horrible cracking sound as Milana #8217;s shin absolutely shatters from the sudden stop  gt;she lets out a horrible scream and collapses to the ground  gt;party sprint away, congratulating themselves on a good job  gt;then a spear imbeds itself in a wall next to them  gt;party barely get to blink before a sphere of force erupts from it  gt;mass strength saves  gt;ranger, fighter and cleric are thrown back 10 feet into a small vender  gt;barbarian and sorcerer manage to keep their footing but still are pushed 10 ft back  gt;everyone takes 9 damage  gt;party momentum stops immediately  gt;barbarian watches as spear detaches itself from the wall and flies up  gt;looks up  gt;sees the male Grimnar Knight staring down at them from the roof of a building  gt;with a groan of pain, Milana removes herself from the stone hand, now that the sorcerer #8217;s concentration is broken  gt;her leg begins to reform with a horrible series of cracks  gt; #8220;oh comeon Graves. Let me have this one. They were so close to being mine #8221;  gt;Graves gives a small smirk  gt; #8220;yes, I can see that #8221;  gt;Milana gives him puppy dog eyes  gt;it #8217;s a disturbing sight given the context  gt;Graves smiles  gt; #8220;oh go ahead. Have your fun #8221;  gt;Milana beams, her pointed teeth baring  gt; #8220;oh Milana #8221;  gt;she looks up at him again  gt;he tosses down an object, and with a dull thump, she catches it in her hand  gt;the scythe  gt; #8220;do be quick. All the screaming from last time was really getting annoying #8221;  gt;Milana sulks  gt; #8220;but I want to find out if these guys scream too #8230; #8221; she whines  gt;party slowly begin backing away  gt;Graves snaps his head towards them  gt; #8220;I do hope you aren #8217;t planning on leaving. I #8217;m so interested to find out how it is you killed Hillborn #8221;  gt;barbarian holds sword in front of him  gt; #8220;ate him. Eat you too #8221;  gt;Graves gives a small laugh  gt; #8220;oh how very much like you. Go ahead Milana. Have your fun #8221;  gt;Milana steps forward, smiling wickedly and swinging her scythe back and forth in slow arcs  gt;ranger leans over to barbarian  gt; #8220;we won #8217;t win. We need to run #8221;  gt;barbarian;  #8220;we beat Farin #8221;  gt; #8220;there #8217;s two of them and we only barely beat Farin #8221;  gt; #8220;get me a distraction. I #8217;ll slow down crazy fleshy. You run #8221;  gt;ranger goes to say something, but barbarian stops him  gt; #8220;lizardfolk no fear death #8221;  gt;ranger nods slowly  gt;sorcerer looks at barbarian  gt; #8220;you ready? #8221;  gt;barbarian nods  gt;sorcerer casts blindness/deafness at 3rd level  gt;Graves fails the save  gt;Milana doesn #8217;t  gt;barbarian runs forward, swinging his sword in a massive overhead swing  gt;Milana deflects it easily and gives an insane laugh  gt; #8220;finally! #8221;  gt;rest of party begins running away even as Graves stumbles on the rooftop, trying to clear his vision  gt;barbarian rages and swings two more times  gt;Milana blocks the first but hisses as the second cuts open her leg  gt;the cut heals and she swings her scythe  gt;barbarian barely blocks it in time  gt;she swings again, and barbarian manages to jump back before going on the attack again  gt;rest of party sprint away, leaving barbarian to give them time  gt;barbarian cuts open Milana #8217;s arm and swings again, hitting her in the chest with a lightning powered strike  gt;her hair stands on end as she #8217;s electrocuted and after the pain subsides she gives another laugh  gt;barbarian realizes just how much shit he got himself into  gt; #8220;mine has tricks too #8221; she tells him  gt;the blade of the scythe glows red hot  gt;barbarian realizes even more how much shit he got himself into  gt;Graves #8217; blindness wears off and after taking a glance at the fight below him, begins running after the rest of the party  gt;Milana swings the scythe at him and barbarian groans as the blade opens a cut on his leg and immediately cauterizes it  gt;she rolls again  gt;nat 20  gt;barbarian goes to deflect a swing, only to realize at the last second it was a feint  gt;blade hits him under the ribs, burning into his chest  gt;mfw it does 50 damage total  gt;barbarian crumples to his knees, scythe blade imbedded inside him  gt;Milana looks him in the eye and twists it  gt;barbarian;  #8220;I don #8217;t scream. This bitch isn #8217;t getting any satisfaction out of me #8221;  gt;Milana gives a nod  gt; #8220;tough son of a bitch. I respect that #8221;  gt; #8220;lizardfolk no fear death #8221;  gt;Milana smiles  gt; #8220;good #8221;  gt;with that, she removes the scythe, and with another swing, decapitates him  gt;barbarian #8217;s body crumples to the floor  gt;sword hits the ground  gt;rest of party running through streets  gt;can hear the distant sound of the fight  gt;hear it go silent  gt;accept solemnly that he lost  gt;begin hearing the sound of footsteps on tiles  gt;look up  gt;see Graves in the distance, looking for them  gt;duck into side alley  gt;Graves stops right above them  gt;ranger feels someone grab his arm  gt;turns, drawing dagger silently  gt;Tiber #8217;s eyes go wide  gt;he puts finger to lips and gestures to an open door behind him  gt;ranger beckons everyone in  gt;Graves hears a sound and sprints off  gt;game ends First game; https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/97riuv/eating_people_is_fine_so_long_as_we_all_agree_on/ Most recent; https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/9b7tx3/lizardfolk_7_things_are_going_better_than_expected/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 13:20:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry. A farewell to Hyern Tharro; lizardfolk barbarian and good friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 15:09:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>A lot of improv goes into it: i can try give an overview but that may be difficult.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 15:11:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe at a later stage</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 23:16:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>anywhere between 4 and 7 hours. I've had games in the past go for longer though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 23:20:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>The barbarian' soul went to the beastlands. As hunters and animalistic humanoids, lizardfolk are more inclined to go there.  #8203; There are death saves in my game, but i felt in this scenario, there wasn't a need.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 23:22:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>A vampire spawn cannot make someone a vampire. That power lies only with a vampire.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 00:36:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Party lvl 6 now. They are vampire spawns with some individual stats.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 00:39:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reread from the beginning maybe? It's up to you. All my posts bar 3 have been lizardfolk related for the last few weeks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 00:40:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some words may change based on imperfect memory, but I do try recite their conversations word for word. Where i mostly skip over actual words is more commonly where I can't remember what they said.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 02:30:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>No problem, i'm glad to hear it went well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 02:40:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>6 and a half</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lizardfolk 8: fallout of a fallen lizard</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 09:57:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>(no game tomorrow)  gt;be me; LizarDM  gt;be not me; lizardfolk ranger, lizardfolk fighter, lizardfolk cleric and lizardfolk sorcerer  gt;rip lizardfolk barbarian  gt;party quickly gather into room as Tiber closes door behind him  gt; #8220;are you insane? Do you actually want to die? #8221;  gt;Tiber runs his hand through his hair and groans  gt; #8220;what kind of idiot fights a Grimnar Knight after dark? Especially those two #8221;  gt;ranger;  #8220;you say no burn #8221;  gt; #8220;yeah, they don #8217;t burn during the day, but they don #8217;t heal either. They #8217;re cowards during the day. They only fight when they think they #8217;ll win #8221;  gt; #8220;we kill day #8221;  gt; #8220;no. You #8217;d be better off leaving. If you don #8217;t, they #8217;ll get at least one of you #8221;  gt;he looks around and pauses  gt; #8220;unless they already have #8221;  gt;fighter;  #8220;he stay behind. Help escape #8221;  gt; #8220;how noble of him. Well, if you #8217;re smart, you #8217;ll get out of Xanimat now. There #8217;s nothing for you here #8221;  gt;Tiber groans and looks at them with a hint of sadness  gt; #8220;you can stay here tonight. I #8217;ll give you a place to sleep #8221;  gt;party accepts  gt;as Tiber starts to cook dinner for them, cleric goes into another room  gt;after making sure no one follows him, he pulls out a small leaf from a satchel on his side and chews it  gt; #8220;my lord. Give me the knowledge I seek to know #8221;  gt;a few seconds pass before a feeling of wind brushes his face  gt;the sounds of birds chirping echo around him and the smell of the forest fills the room  gt;just as quickly as it came, the sensations disappear again  gt;cleric nods and looks at me  gt; #8220;I #8217;d like to cast spiritual weapon #8221;  gt;his bone maul appears in the air in front of him  gt;after a few seconds, it starts to shift and change  gt;finally, it stops shifting and the bone sword rests in front of him  gt;it blinks out of existence  gt;cleric takes out another leaf and chews it  gt; #8220;my lord. Please send us help. We fight for the sake of all lizardfolk. We cannot fail. Help us #8221;  gt;there is no response  gt;cleric nods and leaves room  gt;party #8217;s face when  gt;cleric returns to table in time to enjoy a hot meal  gt;Tiber sits down next to everyone, a salad in front of him  gt;party stare at him extremely weirdly  gt;he shrugs  gt; #8220;I #8217;m vegetarian #8221;  gt;fighter;  #8220;that #8217;s dumb. Fleshy no eat plant #8221;  gt;Tiber smiles  gt; #8220;this fleshy does #8221;  gt;he holds out a carrot  gt; #8220;care to try? #8221;  gt;sorcerer leans forward and grabs it  gt;he sniffs it for a moment before biting  gt;carrot pieces spray the table  gt;sorcerer drops it  gt; #8220;no good #8221;  gt;he looks at it for a moment before offering it back to Tiber  gt;Tiber reluctantly takes it, but understandably doesn #8217;t eat the mutilated vegetable  gt;party goes to sleep after dinner, vowing to make a plan in the morning  gt;as they wake, they immediately convene around the table  gt;as they talk, Tiber strums a small lute in the corner, humming a tune to himself  gt;ranger;  #8220;we shouldn #8217;t leave the city. They #8217;ll expect us to leave immediately #8221;  gt;fighter;  #8220;alternatively, they may expect us to take revenge and come for them #8221;  gt; #8220;if that #8217;s the case, they #8217;ll be on guard during the day, when they can #8217;t heal #8221;  gt;cleric;  #8220;we could lure them into a trap like with Farin #8221;  gt;sorcerer;  #8220;that probably won #8217;t work twice. If they see one of us, they #8217;ll assume the rest are waiting. We only got Farin because he thought he was catching us by surprise #8221;  gt;cleric suddenly looks over at Tiber  gt; #8220;should we be talking in front of him? We don #8217;t know his motives and he might speak draconic #8221;  gt;asks to roll insight on Tiber  gt;7  gt; #8220;you don #8217;t know if he can understand draconic but if he does he #8217;s not showing it. Or he might not understand it at all and you #8217;re being overly paranoid #8221;  gt;cleric raises eyebrow at me  gt;I give him a small smile and wave for him to continue their discussion  gt;cleric turns to rest of party  gt; #8220;either (DM) is f*cking with us or Tiber #8217;s suss. Then again, I failed my insight. Basically, I have no clue #8221;  gt;ranger;  #8220;go on the assumption he can understand us then #8221;  gt;party agrees on this  gt;they discuss for several more minutes before they #8217;re interrupted by a horrible twanging sound  gt;they turn as Tiber curses  gt;a string on his lute broke  gt;he looks up, seeing the room is now silent  gt; #8220;sorry. Do continue. I #8217;ll just need to drop into the market to get some horse hair #8221;  gt;fighter looks at him  gt; #8220;that weird #8221;  gt;Tiber frowns  gt; #8220;don #8217;t you guys eat people? #8221;  gt;fighter shrugs and turns back  gt;cleric turns to Tiber  gt; #8220;is there church? #8221;  gt; #8220;yeah, but they won #8217;t help you. Only interested in money, and as I #8217;ve noticed, you don #8217;t have any #8221;  gt;party pauses, trying to figure out if he went through their bags or he #8217;s talking about yesterday #8217;s conversation  gt;fighter;  #8220;hey DM, I #8217;m going to check if Farin #8217;s sword is still in my bag #8221;  gt;gets up from table and walks away  gt;it #8217;s still there  gt;fighter looks at sword  gt;grabs it and brings it out of the room  gt;he places it on the table and looks at the sorcerer  gt; #8220;can you do an arcana check on this? I want to know what it does #8221;  gt; #8220;it #8217;ll take an hour #8221;  gt; #8220;we #8217;ve got time #8221;  gt;fighter looks at me and raises an eyebrow  gt; #8220;we do have time don #8217;t we? #8221;  gt;I give him a smile but say nothing  gt;sorcerer rolls arcana check  gt;15  gt;he spends an hour looking at it  gt;I pass him a little note  gt;he looks at it and nods  gt; #8220;it #8217;s called Midnight. Just swarming with necrotic energy. This isn #8217;t a nice sword #8221;  gt;in actual stats: 1d8 slashing + 2d6 necrotic. 3 charges. Expend a charge to cast darkness. Gives wielder hell sight  gt;fighter sighs  gt; #8220;cool, but not super effective against undead #8221;  gt;ranger shrugs  gt; #8220;we beat Farin with little more than bones. Any weapon is better than no weapon #8221;  gt;Tiber about to leave for market  gt;sorcerer decides last minute he wants to come  gt;disguises himself as tiefling from last time  gt;Tiber and sorcerer leave for market  gt;Tiber leads him to small knick knack store first to buy some horse hair  gt;go to butcher next, pick up some meat  gt;sorcerer asks Tiber to buy a whole deer  gt;understandably, butcher doesn #8217;t sell a whole deer, and if they did, Tiber doesn #8217;t have the money to waste on it  gt;slightly disappointed, they move on  gt;as they #8217;re walking around, sorcerer sees jeweller  gt;more importantly, sees large diamond  gt;ohno.jpg  gt;he walks over and gives woman horrible smile  gt; #8220;can buy diamond? #8221;  gt; #8220;300 gp #8221;  gt;sorcerer shakes head  gt; #8220;you lie. Fake diamond #8221;  gt;woman stands up  gt; #8220;are you suggesting what I think you #8217;re suggesting, buddy? #8221;  gt;sorcerer leans in real close  gt; #8220;fake #8221;  gt;she pulls out a heavy crossbow and hands him the diamond  gt; #8220;there! Feel how real it is. Try anything and I #8217;ll splatter your brains across the opposite stall #8221;  gt;sorcerer nods, feeling weight  gt; #8220;I want to slide it into my sleeve and cast prestidigitation #8221;  gt;rolls sleight of hand  gt;19  gt;woman doesn #8217;t notice the switch  gt;he hands fake to her  gt;she takes it and places it on the counter  gt; #8220;gonna buy it? #8221;  gt;sorcerer shakes his head  gt; #8220;no money #8221;  gt;woman snorts.  #8220;f*ck off then #8221;  gt;sorcerer returns to Tiber  gt; #8220;I need to learn how to do that #8221; he comments  gt;sorcerer frowns  gt;Tiber saw what happened  gt;immediately suss  gt; #8220;we go home now #8221;  gt;Tiber nods  gt;two go to return home  gt;and bump into Milana  gt;she snarls and backs up, raising her scythe  gt;then she sees Tiber  gt; #8220;hello Milana #8221;  gt; #8220;Tiber #8221;  gt;she looks at the sorcerer  gt; #8220;another friend of yours? #8221;  gt;she gives an extremely wide grin  gt; #8220;I really did like your other ones #8221;  gt;sorcerer notices her hands  gt;hands covered by gloves made from scales  gt;Tiber steps between them before sorcerer can do anything  gt; #8220;have you got anything to say or can we just go? #8221;  gt;Milana returns her attention to him  gt;as she does, her hand lingers for a moment in front of sorcerer #8217;s mouth  gt;sorcerer;  #8220;insight check #8221;  gt;18  gt;sees her looking at him from the corner of her eye  gt;she #8217;s baiting him  gt;sorcerer doesn #8217;t bite (figuratively and literally)  gt;she takes hand away  gt; #8220;you wouldn #8217;t happen to know where your other friends are? I would oh so very much like to meet them again #8221;  gt;Tiber nods, keeping his composure  gt; #8220;try the fish market. They like to visit there when they come here #8221;  gt;Milana nods  gt; #8220;I #8217;ll do just that. Enjoy your day Tiber #8221;  gt;she looks at the sorcerer  gt;pleasure meeting you  gt;she extends a hand  gt;sorcerer doesn #8217;t take it, knowing she #8217;ll see through the illusion if she grabs it  gt;she raises an eyebrow at him  gt; #8220;someone #8217;s rude. Manners will get you far in life. You ought to learn some #8221;  gt;sorcerer doesn #8217;t say a word  gt;she grins and walks off  gt;Tiber and sorcerer return home  gt;cleric expresses an interest in visiting the church while the fighter wants to go out and find weapons  gt;Tiber agrees to take them tomorrow  gt;ranger asks me if there are any birds nearby  gt;one perception check later he sees a pigeon sitting on the window sill next door  gt; #8220;I want to quietly open the window and use  #8216;speak with animals #8217; to get it to come over #8221;  gt;pigeon obliges  gt;coos softly and bounces into his hand  gt;he tells it to wait there while he quickly ducks inside  gt;all but crashes into Tiber  gt; #8220;need cloth #8221;  gt;Tiber blinks for a second before looking in a drawer  gt;he pulls out a piece of tanned leather  gt; #8220;will this do? #8221; he asks  gt;ranger nods and takes it, running back to the pigeon  gt;creates goodberry  gt;after popping one into his mouth, he bursts another with his fingers  gt;begins writing a letter on the leather in draconic with his finger  gt;after that berry runs out of juice he proceeds to do the same to the rest of the berries until he has none left  gt;message done  gt;he feeds the pigeon a bit of squashed berry before giving it the note  gt;pigeon coos and takes it in its claws  gt;flies East out of the city, headed to the swamp  gt;game ends early because fighter and cleric had to leave First game: game:https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/97riuv/eating_people_is_fine_so_long_as_we_all_agree_on/ Previous https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/9b8ddw/lizardfolk_75_blades_in_the_night/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 12:23:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 12:26:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which bit is that? Going with Tiber? Stealing the diamond? Rolling insight?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 13:00:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, after this week, we're returning to our normal schedule of playing on Mondays and Thursdays. I typically post that night (australian night time. I don't know where you're from)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 13:01:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's that next to the cake and prawn?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 13:02:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's an amazing compliment. I really hope we can continue to entertain you as we have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 13:32:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>And the oscar goes to...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 13:57:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're awesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 23:07:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>The .5's are ones that have been broken down. But yeah, we normally play twice a week with this week being an exception</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 23:09:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's insulting because they know fleshies don't normally do it and she's sending a message. Their intent is survival. Her's is malicious intent. Also, regarding prestidigitation. We're a fan of, rule of cool. The diamond will disappear in an hour and she'll know who stole it, but for the meantime, he's in the clear</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 02:48:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>First lizardfolk post and sometime last night on this one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 02:48:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>barbarian was path of the beserker. Can't tell Cleric's Domain, he's keeping it a secret from the other players. Sorcerer also has his secret. We changed their backstories slightly in session 0 so that they could all start in the swamp. And for descriptions. Barbarian looked like a bipedal crocodile with a shorter snout, the sorcerer was a monitor lizard. The other three are based off official dnd artwork. Distinct things being, ranger has several scars and his frill (which is red) is in pieces as opposed to a full thing. Fighter is fairly large. His scales are verging on black and his frill is orange. The cleric has a red frill too, but he's quite wiry and smaller than the other lizardfolk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 08:58:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the 1 v 1, it consisted a lot of the barbarian trying to find ways to get advantage. For instance, if Milana missed, he'd say "i'd like to slip under the hit and try attack her in a blindspot". So there was a lot more dynamic fighting than two people standing opposite each other swinging weapons. For the bait, i didn't expect him to do anything. I mentioned that she had her fingers there and left it up to him if he wanted to bite. He rolled insight so i explained her motive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lizardfolk 9: Sneaking, sleep and gobby's</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 09:43:56</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;be me; LizarDM  gt;be not me; lizardfolk ranger, lizardfolk cleric, lizardfolk sorcerer, lizardfolk fighter  gt;party preparing to venture into Xanimat to retrieve more supplies so they can fight the Grimnar Knights  gt;sorcerer gives cleric stolen diamond  gt; #8220;just in case #8221;  gt;ranger wants to go out, but tells party not to leave  gt;asks Tiber to leave to buy a disguise kit  gt;Tiber begins packing up to leave  gt;fighter grabs his shoulder  gt; #8220;why help? #8221;  gt;Tiber looks at him and shrugs  gt; #8220;I help you, you help me later. Favours are worth more than money in this world #8221;  gt;he pauses for a moment  gt; #8220;money would be nice though. If you come into money, mind tossing some my way? #8221;  gt;fighter nods  gt;Tiber about to leave  gt;ranger goes to sorcerer and whispers to him  gt; #8220;wait 30 seconds after he leaves and follow him. I want to see what he does when he thinks we #8217;re not around #8221;  gt;sorcerer agrees  gt;Tiber leaves  gt;30 seconds later, sorcerer disguises himself as a tabaxi and leaves  gt;sorcerer begins following Tiber through the streets  gt;sees Tiber go up to some stores, makes small talk with store owners  gt;buys a disguise kit  gt;sorcerer content with trusting Tiber when he sees something that intrigues him  gt;Tiber sees elven woman with large bag  gt;Tiber slings lute off shoulder and walks over to her, playing a small tune  gt;sorcerer can #8217;t hear words, but Tiber seems to be singing to her  gt;elf #8217;s face relatively stern and dismissive  gt;Tiber strums the lute a little harder and his voice gets a bit louder  gt;elf turns to him, paying him more attention  gt;a smile comes across her face  gt;she sits there, just listening for a while as he finishes the song  gt;when he #8217;s done, she reaches into bag and pulls out a coin purse  gt;drops several gold coins into his hand  gt;Tiber pockets them and walks away  gt;sorcerer intrigued to say the least  gt;as sorcerer trails some more, he hears an argument from his side  gt;he turns, seeing a group of filthy young men yelling and getting in the face of someone  gt;sorcerer looks closer  gt;sees victim  gt;Graves  gt;Graves seems unfazed by the yelling and aggressive actions  gt;he talks back to the men calmly  gt;men yell at him, and one pushes Graves  gt;Graves almost seems to sigh, and then his spear flashes forward, pinning the offending man #8217;s foot to the ground  gt;the man screams as Graves leans in close and whispers something to the man  gt;the man #8217;s eyes go wide and he starts shaking  gt;Graves removes the spear and walks away  gt;none of the men follow  gt;sorcerer turns back to look at Tiber  gt;Tiber #8217;s gone  gt;rolls perception  gt;8  gt;scanning the crowd, he can #8217;t find him  gt;sorcerer reluctantly goes to return home when he bumps into a small figure  gt; #8220;oy! Watch where you #8217;re going pal or I #8217;m going to mess you up so bad you #8217;re mum ain #8217;t gonna recognize ya! #8221;  gt;sorcerer looks down  gt;sees small cloaked figure, seems gnomish  gt; #8220;go away fleshy #8221;  gt;gnome recoils  gt; #8220;fleshy? Fleshy!? Who you callin fleshy ya furry piece of shit #8221;  gt;gnome pushes him  gt;as gnome pushes him, sorcerer #8217;s disguise flickers  gt;gnome backs up  gt;gets weird grin and looks past sorcerer  gt;sees Graves  gt;gnome holds out his hand  gt; #8220;cash or I #8217;ll see if Graves wants to talk to you #8221;  gt; #8220;no fleshy #8221;  gt; #8220;comeon lizardman, I know you #8217;ve got stuff #8221;  gt;sorcerer looks around him  gt; #8220;are there any witnesses? #8221;  gt; #8220;there are some, but they might not notice #8221;  gt; #8220;I #8217;d like to use sleep at 3rd level #8221;  gt;gnome opens his mouth to speak  gt;sorcerer hits him with sleep  gt;gnome drops like a tonne of bricks  gt;as gnome hits ground, body shifts  gt;gnome becomes green and becomes scrawnier  gt;is goblin  gt;sorcerer picks up goblin  gt;party laughing their asses off  gt; #8220;what now? #8221;  gt; #8220;I uhh #8230;uhhh. Uhhh. I #8217;m going to take him home #8221;  gt;party loses their shit even more  gt;as sorcerer begins walking away, passing dwarf frowns at him  gt;sorcerer tries to think fast  gt; #8220;he trip #8221;  gt;dwarf pauses  gt; #8220;on what? #8221;  gt; #8220; #8230;bird #8221;  gt;ranger actually can #8217;t breathe at this point he #8217;s laughing so hard  gt;sorcerer rolls deception with disadvantage  gt;10  gt;dwarf raises an eyebrow and steps forward  gt; #8220;I think you should put him down, sir #8221;  gt;sorcerer panics  gt; #8220;I want to use sleep at second level on the dwarf #8221;  gt;dwarf drops  gt;party all but dying  gt;sorcerer hears voice yell out  gt;turns  gt;sees guards marching over  gt;ohfuck.jpg  gt;sorcerer starts running  gt;guards give chase  gt;sorcerer twins invisibility  gt;he and goblin go invisible  gt;guards yell orders to split up  gt;sorcerer thinks he #8217;s succeeded in escaping  gt;he turns back to face where he #8217;s going  gt;sees Graves  gt;he stops immediately  gt;Graves walks towards him, eyes slowly moving around  gt;Graves getting closer and closer  gt;sorcerer backs up slowly and leans against wall  gt;Graves looks directly at him  gt;sorcerer stops breathing  gt;Graves #8217; eyes pass over him and he begins walking away  gt;sorcerer begins to slowly creep away  gt;stealth check  gt;5  gt;kicks over a bucket  gt;Graves whirls around and throws his spear  gt;the spear flies directly past sorcerer #8217;s face and imbeds itself in a wall  gt;spear unleashes sphere of force  gt;sorcerer barely out of range  gt;spear flies past him and returns to Graves #8217; hand  gt;sorcerer creeps away with a successful stealth check  gt;makes his way back to the house  gt;he opens the door, forgetting he #8217;s invisible  gt;party draw weapons, looking for enemy  gt;sorcerer drops invisibility  gt;party relaxes  gt;sorcerer looks over at table  gt;sees Tiber tied to a chair in the corner of the room  gt;Tiber #8217;s eyes are full of fury  gt;sorcerer;  #8220;what happened? #8221;  gt;ranger;  #8220;he came back without you. We waited for a bit, but you didn #8217;t show up #8221;  gt; #8220;so you tied him up? #8221;  gt; #8220;he would #8217;ve run #8221;  gt;sorcerer shrugs and dumps goblin on the floor  gt;fighter walks over and nudges him  gt; #8220;food? #8221;  gt; #8220;he threatened to hand me in to Graves. I had to stop him somehow #8221;  gt; #8220;so you brought him here? #8221;  gt;sorcerer shrugs  gt;ranger looks over at fighter  gt; #8220;grab more rope #8221;  gt;party proceed to tie up goblin  gt;sorcerer takes away the sleep effect  gt;goblin wakes up  gt;sees himself in a room full of lizardfolk  gt;and then I ask barbarian player to join the table  gt;party losing their shit even more as they realize they kidnapped a PC  gt; #8220;why you work Graves? #8221;  gt; #8220;wha #8230;what? #8221;  gt;fighter slaps him  gt; #8220;why you work Graves? #8221;  gt; #8220;I don #8217;t work for him #8221;  gt; #8220;no lie small fleshy. You work Graves #8221;  gt;goblin frowns at them  gt; #8220;not small fleshy. I #8217;m a goblin #8221;  gt;party looks at each other  gt;fighter looks at him  gt; #8220;green fleshy #8221;  gt; #8220;goblin #8221;  gt; #8220;small, green fleshy work Graves #8221;  gt;goblin shakes his head  gt; #8220;for the last time. A) I don #8217;t work for the f*cking Grimnar Knights. B) I #8217;m a f*cking goblin! #8221;  gt;fighter pauses  gt; #8220;you gobby #8221;  gt;whole table loses their shit  gt;(context: Gobby is Australian slang for blowjob)  gt;goblin goes red  gt; #8220;I don #8217;t want to be gobby. Just let me go #8221;  gt;fighter slaps him  gt; #8220;who work for? #8217;  gt;Tiber makes some muffled sounds  gt;fighter turns and slaps him too  gt; #8220;quiet fleshy. We talk to gobby #8221;  gt;goblin sighs  gt; #8220;I don #8217;t work for anyone. I #8217;m just trying to make my way in the world. If that means a bit of underhanded shit, I #8217;ll do it. But I can assure you. I would never work with Grimnar Knights unless it meant gutting those bastards in their sleep #8221;  gt;ranger leans in  gt; #8220;why no like Grimnar Knight? #8221;  gt;goblin sniffs  gt; #8220;none of your business. We #8217;ve all got our reasons, don #8217;t we? #8221;  gt;ranger;  #8220;I roll insight on him #8221;  gt;17  gt;he sees something in the goblin #8217;s eyes  gt;it #8217;s not something he himself is familiar with, but he #8217;s seen it in others  gt;the goblin mourns. He #8217;s seen a horrible tragedy  gt; #8220;we kill Grimnar Knight #8221;  gt;goblin shakes his head  gt; #8220;don #8217;t try it. The bastards are almost impossible to kill. You #8217;ll die #8221;  gt; #8220;we kill one before #8221;  gt;goblin frowns  gt; #8220;how? #8221;  gt;fighter gives horrible smile  gt; #8220;ate him #8221;  gt;goblin pauses  gt; #8220;you #8230; you ate him? #8221;  gt;fighter holds up sword  gt; #8220;this his. He hurt us. We eat him #8221;  gt;goblin pauses before giving a small laugh  gt; #8220;that #8217;s the best f*cking thing I #8217;ve ever heard #8221;  gt; #8220;please. What did his face look like when he realized what you were doing? #8221;  gt;ranger;  #8220;scared #8221;  gt;goblin gives a grin  gt; #8220;now that #8217;s something I #8217;d like to see #8221;  gt;ranger looks at him and holds out hand  gt; #8220;we let you. Help us. We eat more together #8221;  gt;goblin looks down at the rope  gt; #8220;I #8217;d shake your hand, but I #8217;m kind of tied up right now. If you wouldn #8217;t mind #8221;  gt;party releases goblin  gt;goblin rubs his arms a bit and then holds out his hand  gt; #8220;so what do you call yourselves? #8221;  gt;party look around at each other  gt;ranger;  #8220;we no have name #8221;  gt;party hears Tiber mumbling from the side  gt;sorcerer reaches over and removes the makeshift gag the others had stuffed in his mouth  gt; #8220;are you done yet? I #8217;d rather not spend my day tied to a f*cking chair. I bought what you wanted. Let me go! #8221;  gt;ranger looks at him  gt;looks at sorcerer  gt; #8220;put the gag back in. He #8217;s whining #8221;  gt;sorcerer puts the gag back in  gt;and then party hear a knock at the door  gt; #8220;Tiber. Would you care to open the door please? #8221;  gt;the voice is immediately recognizable  gt;Milana  gt;story continued in 9.5 First game:https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/97riuv/eating_people_is_fine_so_long_as_we_all_agree_on/ Previous game:https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/9bhobb/lizardfolk_8_fallout_of_a_fallen_lizard/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 09:45:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>The next post will be in a few hours. Party can't think of a name but they've expressed interest in taking suggestions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lizardfolk 9.5: A knock at the door</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 14:01:53</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;be me; lizard  gt;be not me; lizardfolk ranger, lizardfolk cleric, lizardfolk fighter, lizardfolk sorcerer, goblin rogue  gt;voice at door is unmistakeably Milana  gt;sorcerer makes sure gag in Tiber #8217;s mouth is secure before backing up  gt;fighter points to the door and mocks swinging  gt;mouths the word ambush  gt;party nod and make their way over to stand beside the door  gt;rogue slinks in the shadows in the corner of the room, separating himself from the rest of the party  gt; #8220;Oh Tiber. Please don #8217;t make me wait out here. I #8217;m getting impatient #8221;  gt;party stay silent  gt; #8220;Tiber, if you don #8217;t open this door I #8217;ll have to break it down, and that would just be rude #8221;  gt;ranger grabs a knife from the kitchen and tosses it to the rogue before grabbing one for himself  gt;Milana sighs from behind the door  gt; #8220;you disappoint me Tiber. And here I was expecting so much from you #8221;  gt;suddenly, the head of a spear slams through the door, stopping inches in front of the fighter #8217;s eyes  gt;fighter yells at everyone to move  gt;too late  gt;everyone but rogue gets thrown across the room as a sphere of force erupts from the spear  gt;the door explodes into pieces  gt;ranger gets on his feet  gt;sees Milana standing just outside the broken doorway  gt; #8220;care to invite me in? #8221;  gt;suddenly, ranger feels rope loop around his neck and tighten  gt;strength save  gt;6  gt;ranger lets out a strangled choke as Tiber tightens his makeshift garrotte and pulls him off his feet  gt;fighter gets to his feet and sees Tiber choking ranger  gt;raises Midnight  gt;Tiber notices  gt; #8220;help! #8221;  gt;fighter barely gets a second to turn before Milana pounces on him, swinging her scythe like a maniac  gt;sorcerer launches fire bolt at Milana, barely missing her  gt;turns and sees Graves enter the building  gt;ohfuck.jpg  gt;sees rogue slink out of the shadows behind Graves and pause in the doorway  gt;sorcerer thinks he #8217;s going to run  gt;rogue appears to change his mind  gt;brings knife down into the small of Graves #8217; back  gt;Grave lets out a yell of pain and fury  gt;cleric runs forward, summoning magic weapon  gt;bone sword appears in his hand  gt;swings it  gt;sword all but shears off Graves #8217; bottom jaw  gt;ranger tries to get his feet underneath him as he #8217;s pulled away  gt;acrobatics check  gt;fail  gt; #8220;can I wrap my tail around his leg and trip him? #8221;  gt; #8220;roll a strength check #8221;  gt;rolls  gt;15  gt;Tiber falls to the ground, and for a moment, ranger can breathe again  gt;doesn #8217;t last long as Tiber plants a foot on his shoulder and arches his back, tightening the garrotte  gt;fighter swings Midnight at Milana  gt;he can #8217;t break through her defence  gt;she laughs as she cuts open his leg and then slices his cheek with her scythe  gt;sorcerer runs forward and places his hand against her stomach  gt;releases level 2 magic missile  gt;Milana is thrown across the room and into the kitchen  gt;Graves #8217; jaw begins to reform  gt;he stabs cleric in the chest  gt;the spear itself barely pierces the skin, but the cleric yells out as force damage breaks a rib  gt;tries to swing at rogue  gt;misses  gt;rogue shanks him in the side  gt; #8220;this is for Kawli! #8221;  gt;he tries to stab him in the leg  gt;Graves catches his hand  gt;cleric casts spirit guardians  gt;the room fills with the sound of the forest  gt;wind throws paper and tussles hair  gt;several ethereal bodies begin forming in the air around him  gt;lizardfolk  gt;family, comrades and friends  gt;the rest of the party recognize the ethereal form of the barbarian amongst their ranks  gt;cleric stabs with the sword  gt;nat 20  gt;he rams it into Graves #8217; chest, going all the way through  gt;Graves grabs the blade, staring with pure hatred at the cleric  gt;ranger tries to dislodge Tiber #8217;s foot  gt;manages to push it off  gt;the pressure immediately lessens  gt;ranger turns onto his stomach so the rope is on the back of his neck  gt;Tiber climbs on top and wrenches the ranger #8217;s arm behind his back  gt;fighter runs over and slams his foot into Tiber #8217;s side  gt;Tiber collapses to the ground, his breath gone  gt;fighter raises his sword and swings it down at him  gt;Tiber barely manages to roll out of the way  gt;action surge  gt;he swings again  gt;Tiber manages to roll away again  gt;on his final hit he slams the sword down  gt;Tiber yells out as Midnight impales his hand, pinning it to the floor  gt;Milana gets up from the floor of the kitchen and raises her scythe  gt;it glows red hot  gt;she runs forward and swings at the fighter  gt;he jumps back to avoid it, leaving Midnight imbedded in Tiber #8217;s hand  gt;she reaches forward and catches his arm  gt;sorcerer shoots witch bolt at her  gt;she ducks out of the way  gt;Graves tries to kick the cleric away when one of the spirits rams into him  gt;he lets out a scream of pain as his body is assaulted with radiant energy  gt;he tries to stab his spear forward but misses  gt;rogue grabs the spear and tries to yank it from his hands  gt;strength check  gt;nat 20  gt;miraculously, this tiny goblin manages to wrench the spear out of Graves #8217; hand  gt; #8220;you want this? No more spear for you! #8221;  gt;he snaps it over his knee  gt;realizes mistake a millisecond before the explosion of force energy hits him  gt;rogue is launched across the room and is slammed against the opposite wall  gt;drops from full hp to 3  gt;cleric pulls sword out of Graves #8217; chest  gt;Graves falls to his knees  gt;cleric hits him with guiding bolt second level  gt;Graves screams as radiant damage burns directly into his face  gt;he places his hands on the ground, his face all but unrecognizable  gt;cleric raises the sword and brings it down, decapitating Graves  gt;ranger grabs his knife and runs over to Milana, trying to stab her  gt;she avoids both swings  gt;party doesn #8217;t notice as Tiber removes Midnight from his hand  gt;he looks around at the room, seeing the chaos  gt;picking up Midnight, he sprints for the door  gt;the cleric tries to hit him with the sword, but Tiber avoids the strike and without a second glance back, runs off  gt;fighter looks around for a weapon  gt;he sees Tiber #8217;s lute leaning against the wall  gt;he runs over and grabs it, barely dodging a swing from Milana  gt;he runs back over and slams the lute into her face  gt;it breaks on impact  gt;so does her nose  gt;she turns to him, glaring  gt;then she looks over at the still body of Graves on the floor  gt;she hisses at the lizardfolk and turns  gt;with a smash of glass, she leaps through the window, disappearing into the night  gt;game First game: https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/97riuv/eating_people_is_fine_so_long_as_we_all_agree_on/ Previous game: https://www.reddit.com/r/DnDGreentext/comments/9c1cdq/lizardfolk_9_sneaking_sleep_and_gobbys/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 14:42:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>They distrusted him, and when he returned without the sorcerer they thought he did something. They were going to release him until Milana knocked on the door, proving their suspicions correct</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 14:44:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>someone got the reference</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 15:00:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>They tied him up because they were suspicious. In the time that the sorcerer couldn't see him, Tiber talked to Milana. The party doesn't know his reasoning yet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 02:21:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>The hungering jaws remains the same. The only change we've made is to the cunning artisan and that's because of a misread in the first game. After that we decided to keep it because we thought; Logically if you can make a rib into a dagger, what's to stop you from doing it to all of them? Edit: I'd like to clarify that the healing aspect of hungering jaws has a short rest cooldown in my campaign, but they can bite as they please</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 03:31:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>rogue</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 05:57:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a national term but it's a fairly out there thing to say. No one really says dunny or grog or Sheila. Basically, stereotypical slang</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 23:06:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a homebrew rule based on the cleric's god. I can't give anymore details beyond that for fear of spoilers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:28:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's the rogue now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>