<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject1105</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anyone remember when Deftones went the reggae (kinda) rout?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-10 01:15:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-10 06:59:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Xerxes chest rose and fell with the swelling of the seas. "My lord. We have just lost another archer ship! We must turn back! We could lose the entire fleet!" "Steadfast admiral, we push for the beaches tonight, or we die." "But my lord, the ships have just disappeared! If there are rocks ahead we will never see them coming!" "Must I remind you the consequences of questioning a god, you may ask your predecessor that question!" Xerxes voice boomed throughout the dimly lit chamber. The servants and women struggled to keep their bowels, any repulsive behavior could result in death for even his favorite maidens. The admiral left the room after receiving his bearings again. Xerxes prepared his mind for the battle ahead. The Spartans were never easy to put down, and that is exactly the kind of thinking Leonidas was counting on. Leonidas looked out at the sea, at first his men were roaring and jeering with pride and celebration when the Persians crashed on the rocks. But festivities soon turned to debates. The warriors stood at attention at the cliffs, waiting to see another Persian be claimed by the grey blue ocean. It began with a few scout boats, but then the larger ones began to disappear as well. One minute they were there, the next, it appeared the mist took them. The men stood puzzled as Leonidas shook the crumbling earth in one hand, his spear in the other, searching for answers. The men began to sense his worry as well. Picking up on the men's doubt, Leonidas's lieutenant called out to them "The gods deny the Persians victory! The might of the Spartans are so strong the Persians shiver at the thought of us!" The men regained some of their lost morale, but everyone knew something was strange. The lieutenant ushered the men back to their posts and dimly walked over to Leonidas. "What is it?" "Its not right, boats shouldn't disappear like that." "And the men know it as well, it would perhaps be best not to let the rest back at camp come to this realization." "hmph" "Could this be some kind of new trick, the Persians are indeed a slithering lot." "They aren't that clever, they know they overwhelm us and they know it. Trying to hide their ships would only show weakness, something a Xerxes wishes not to show if he wishes to continue the fiction of his godhood." "Indeed. We shall see come morning, we must gather our strength for the morning, let us return to camp." "I suppose that would be wise" grunted Leonidas, lifting his shield and using his spear as leverage. The two began down the path, the Persians would engulf their sleep. It was the dawn of the fourth day. If it were not for the occasion it would be heavenly. The summer winds blew threw the Hot Gates, passing through the last of the blooming olive trees and delivering the sweet smell of nectar from flowers buried in the nearby valley. The sweat on the brow of each Spartan reflected the glorious sun that hung hot in a sky devoid of clouds. Seabirds flocked above, catching fish in their mouths fresh from the turquoise sea. Leonidas looked down defiantly from atop a hill. Word had come that the Persians were expecting his forces to disperse. That, of course, would never come to light. But it had appeared that Xerxes waited long enough. A cooler breeze swept through the gates to the relief of the men standing in the sun. It was only a matter of time now. Xerxes had become worried now, but he did not let it show. The fleet had suffered greatly in the storm a week before, the navigators are still puzzled. However it did not matter now. Now only death was on Xerxes mind, that and the burning of Greece. The first 20,000 men were already engaged with the Spartans and the rest were on their way. As his throne reached the top of the brown mossy hill he could hear the sounds of his front infantry engaged in combat. "Impossible." he whispered. From his side, a voice called out to one of the generals. The messengers words reached Xerxes divine ears by way of his most trusted general "Your Highness, the battlefield brings news." "Speak" "My lord, we are getting reports of... beats, rising from the water." "Beasts you say?" asked Xerxes, becoming intrigued. The poor general struggled to make pace with the bulky slaves march, carrying a God is something you don't take lightly, after all. "And what do these beast look like?" "Well sir, they are a common animal, you may know them, they are said to swallow fallen sailors whole!" "What do the Beasts *look* like?" anger rising in his voice. "Well, my lord, they are, um. They're sharks my king." "Sharks? On land?" "Not just any, it has been told that they carry a device on their heads sir, it carries the power of the great sun god with..." and before the general could finish his sentence, his head seemed to disappear from his body. A bit perplexed, Xerxes stared at the headless charred body, trying to pull meaning from it, but before he could finish his thought; his throne slowed down as it came over the hill. The throne lowered suddenly, followed by a scream, and another, and another. Xerxes jumped from the falling platform and crawled up to the hill. Where were his servants? His soldiers? Had they not seen their king fall? But this soon became the least of his worries. As he gazed out over the battlefield laid before him, he could only stop and wonder. And wonder he would, until his head disappeared, just like his generals. The world went black. Leonidas watched in interest at the field before him. He could hear the calls of his lieutenant by his side, but instead he simply watched. The lieutenants wisdom would not be needed, he had seen this all before. Laser sharks. Leonidas raised his spear and shield, his red cloak flowing in the wartime breeze. "Men! Tonight we dine, in hell!" cried the King. Soon not only would the blood of Persians fill the seas, but that of Laser sharks as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-10 07:28:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks a lot! I'm more or less new to reddit so this helps a lot!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[WP]You wake up in an eerie abandoned town. You have a note next to you. It says "5 minutes"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-10 08:19:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-10 17:30:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't worry man! That's was pretty incredible writing! That was an awesome story and kinda want to hear what happens next</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-10 18:26:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw the light burn out from his eyelids. The fiery green stars collapsed under the weight of their own mass, and the vessel fell to the cool hard pavement below.A cool breeze set in as sweat evaporated from every pore of the corpse. The white hot star fire shone down to reap the flesh it had once birthed. I stood and observed this for a long while, trying to comprehend the nature of this drama. Then the ants came, and the birds circled ahead. The once breathing and frantic body was being reclaimed by nature. I stood back from all this, from the rotting flesh, the birds, and into the cool shade, where the same sun that devoured a man could not reach me. I could see its effects on his skin, which began to blister and spoil and collapse, and the smell began to set it. Why? Why did this man fall before me? I asked myself the question over and over again like a madman. I felt the cool soft shape of paper in my hand. Had the man given it to me? It certainly did not fabricate itself in my pal. I opened the paper cautiously. scrawled upon its yellow faded surface were the words One Minute Ten seconds it took to ponder. Another ten to realize. Ten seconds to run down the street. Fifteen to fear the sun. Five to fear the birds. Five to finally see another man. Five to drop dead into his arms.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[WP]There is only one bottle of alcohol left on earth. You have it. But everyone else knows you do.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-10 18:29:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-10 21:08:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Keep up the good work dude! You manage to find a way to hook a reader and immediately build a universe and a sort of mystery around everything, something very few writers can do on the fly. Anyway, great job man :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-11 20:43:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love it! I've been trying to write some of my own warframe lore myself. This is really cool! Keep up the good work man!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-12 02:29:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Three sets of lights danced around the bar. Blue red and yellow sparkled across the crystal bar. The ambiance of clinking glasses and laughter filled the musty old cantina with a sense of belonging. Waitresses made their rounds and news reports sought to suffocate the patrons fun with tales of bloody civil war and the latest galactic scandals. In vain, it seemed, as the multi species concoction stirred within the small and dim hole in the wall. Tales from miners and scouts that had returned from the belt regions swirled with the average office workers drama. The occasional rumbling of the hyper tram rattled the establishment, but rarely spilled the vetted drinkers glasses. Waitresses of all races in skimpy diner outfits buzzed around the bar like olives in Jonathan's cocktail. One of the robotic models whirred over to our table. I had to order for him, he seemed out of it, he had already bumped into a waitress before with his antlers because he wasn't careful. A million apologies and a promised payment for the glasses later he back zoning off. He wasn't himself, where had the usually sly and smooth Jon gone? He was a hit with the ladies, even for a Tarisan. Hell, one time my buddy Jon slept with a Mon Schuti, on a bet of course; no one would touch that any tentacles, except my best friend Jon. One time we were at this herb shop while Jessica was pregnant we had to pick up a medication for her morning sickness, as we were leaving he told me he forgot something in the store, I said okay and he trotted his way back in. He comes out with this slimy bottle of stuff that looked like you left floaters in someones water. He starts telling me that its supposed to increase stamina or something like that, anyway, he convinces my dumb ass to down the entire bottle. I was shitting in my pants for five days. But hey, that was Jon for you. Of course, he wasn't always an asshole. He flew me to the hospital when I tried to OD, that was before I met Jessica of course. The only reason I'm alive today alive today. But this isn't really my story, this is about Jonathan. The robotic waitress brought our order to the table. "Why the cocktail?" "Never had one" replied Jonathan in a booming voice, he put his hooves through the utensil gloves and begun to shove chowder in his mouth. "You're eating diner with a cocktail?" "I don't see the problem with it man." "Don't you have to work tomorrow?" "I guess so." "I mean Jesus man if somethings wrong you should just tell me." "Nothings wrong." "Sure?" "Sure."He said jadedly.I began to pull away at the fried coruscation on my plate, cracking the red and orange outer shell and stripping the soft gooey insides. I looked up at him, the look on his face was one of deep thought. He had begun picking at his food. "Have you even been to Esterik 9?" he asked out of the deep blue. "No I cant say I haven't. Why?" "Ive always wanted to visit there, they have lots of beaches, and the population is relatively low so there's a lot of real estate and great nature areas, i've been thinking about going there." "Would you take Tanya there?" Tanya was the given human name for his mate. I couldn't pronounce their native names, so Jon and Tanya always had to do. "Yeah, I think I would, it would be nice. Just to sit there on all those white beaches, gazing out at the small orange star, flying over the misty jungles." "You said it man." "Yeah" He stirred his chowder some more. Bits of meat and what looked to be like cabbage orbited his ladle. I drank some more ale and swirled its contents around. "*What do you got swirling around in there big man?*" I thought. "Whats it like being a father now Ben?" "What?" the question took me of guard "Being a father, whats it like?" "Well, um, I don't know." "Its okay, I don't mind, I asked anyway." He leaned forward in anticipation. I leaned back in thought. "I guess. I'm not sure. My whole life I thought I had it all. My whole life I felt like I had everything, that I needed nothing else. I had a Job, great friends, a great station to live in, and an amazing girlfriend who loved me. T believe i thought that was it. That was going to be my life, now and forever. I guess I didn't realize at the time that all I really did was settled for what I had been given. I think back to my dad sometimes man, the things he did, the things I hated him for, the feeling I felt after he died. It changed, it all changed man. I guess I realize now why my father did the things he did because he loved me. He loved me a fucking lot man, especially after I put him through all the shit I did he still loved me, no matter what. I used to think that, that, I didn't want to be anything like him. But we have Jack in out lives and, and." "And what?" "And now I don't want to be anything but my dad. I have this beautiful thing in my life now, and I'm going to love it and care for it until the end of time, because he's my son, my very own beautiful son, and I love him." "I think I understand now." he said. He got up, pushed in his chair, and looked at me. "Where are you going?" "Tanya wants to name him after you." He left. And as I finish writing this letter to you junior. You're fathers ashes are being spread on Esterik 9. He lives on through the white beaches and peaceful jungles of his new home. I hope that the day you read this letter you will be with him on those very beaches. After all, like father, like son.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-13 19:18:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where are all the colonists? Are there large cities we don't know about? There are lots of people and ships on the relays so the population must be somewhat large. Where are all those workers in the relays coming from? How did they get there? How did they become lotus operatives? Who even are these people? Why do they all wear space suits? Are they human? Are there children? Who the hell are these people?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-20 07:59:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sleep tight pupper</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-29 17:09:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm surprised more people don't use rejuvenation, helps with the ridiculous slash procs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-01 02:45:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not like any American handball that I've ever seen. The kind I used to play in school was basically hockey but with a ball. Every time you were passed the ball you had to stay in the same place where you could either pass it someone else or take a shot at the goal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-01 04:46:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Weird, maybe the name for what I'm thinking of is "team handball" otherwise it's a fun game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-01 04:50:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where is the CIA hiding all the moon cheese samples?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-03 17:01:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's kind of what I meant in the original post. It just fascinates me to think about alternate histories and the prospect that we could already be in the space age</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-04 00:52:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or, you know, he could have just not gotten sick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-04 00:53:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you get down to it, theft IS a survival skill. Humans have been doing it for thousands of yeas</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-04 05:47:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>As an Oregon resident, I can say there is HUGE Bernie support here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-05 08:58:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read it as "biotech firm wants to deliver orgasms" and I was ecstatic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dear attractive people. What are some downsides to being good looking?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-06 20:06:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-07 23:59:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>The current ruler was later executed by the very same bull when he was overthrown</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-08 00:29:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I first got into PC gaming I downloaded steam on my new computer and was looking for cheap games to play. Warframe seemed cool and was free so I hoped on in early beta, been here ever since</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[WP] You are the man who sold the world. Explain to the buyer why you did it</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-09 06:58:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-10 03:47:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! I've been playing this game since forever and I've been really craving an open battlefield esqe mission. Seeing a fully formed Tenno army on an open battlefield is something that I've dreamed of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-10 05:03:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>That night, the night that it happened. We stared into the night sky. A lay man could not tell the difference between night and day however. I gazed into the bright starry sky and and features reflected my thoughts like a moonlit pool, blurry and disfigured. I gazed into the starry night and wondered, for the first time in a long while. The luminescent velvet pushed itself in and out of the sky like a labored breath. It's vast expanses of stars and nebula's all on display for a simple creature, such as myself, to sit and gawk at. I sat and meditated in the soft sand, the light of the stars would warm its velvet touch. I let the sand envelop me like an earthly blanket, buried and bathed in endless light as well as the softest sand. The others began to worry about me, they placed their blankets around me, wondering if I had gone mad. I simply stared into the night sky as they cared for me, I smiled. I could watch the expanse forever. How something so large could appear so small baffled my primate mind. Growing up as a child my mother often showed me books of art. I stared at them with similar awe as I did the sky that night. My favorite was Van Gogh. I'm sure you could guess my favorite painting. *Starry Night.* I remember thinking that the mountains Van Gogh painted looked like tree bark, and the longer I stared the more I felt like an ant, crawling to the tip top of the bark to taste the swirling clouds. The stars swirled like these clouds, still breathing in and out, with each exhale they began to grow farther away. My eyes were sore from absorbing it all. I spared my ears over stimulation by letting them fill with sand as I rest my head against the dunes. The swirling universe before me belched, quaked, and finally began to recede back into its corners. It was all rearranged and new. When the universe settled that night there were more stars in the sky than before, they had all been scattered into new locations. I wondered where Orion's belt was now. The night was coming to a close and I could hear a rustling in the distance behind me. A miserable cloaked figure shuffled its way across the sand. Wrapped in layers of blankets like a cocoon. I recognized the brow that hid behind the blankets as my own. My daughter sat beside me and gazed into the luminescence. She curled up and wrapped her gloved hand around the crook of my arm and asked if the others had made it. I told her I didn't know. We were the only ship that landed. After a long sigh and some labored breaths into my chest she rose from the sand and shuffled across the cold dessert and into the belly of the metal wreckage. I finally rose form my perch on the dune, moisture had gathered and cooled the sand below me. I playfully stepped in the footprints of my daughter as I made my way back to the crashed ship. Small lights beaconed out of its various orifices, like fireflies in the cool desert night. I shoved my sore and tired body into one of the man sized holes. One of our friends was cooking soup in a reclaimed communications dish. Our hungry eyes circled around the fire, and our shadows danced against the flickering yellow walls. I shut my eyes for the night. When I reopened them I could see the soft blue orange light of dusk emanating from an old head sized viewing port. I lazily crawled over the other sleeping bodies of leather and nylon in the dark. Outside I saw children look into the sky. I pulled myself out from our family wreckage den and heard the talk of others. I sat down and propped my back against the hull of the ship. Sand was still slithering down our half buried tiny entrance. The awake survivors talked about the center of the universe. How it all collapsed around us. How many more stars there were. I could hear one mention leaving the desert, his friend silenced his idea, we had lost all landing craft in the crash, and besides, we couldn't transport this many people.We were lucky enough that we even made it back to the earth before it all collapsed. He was right. We would bury ourselves like beetles in the machine tomb until our deaths. I blocked the rest of their talk from my ears by burying them in the sand again. And as my head rested on the dune, I turned it to see two children on top of the tallest dune, gazing at the infinite expanse of stars. There were pointing out the black shapes of empty sky. There were so many stars, Man would no longer make constellations, it would gaze at the blackness of the sky; and from this darkness, it would be guided.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-10 17:26:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Herpes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-11 02:16:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lacera is absolutely the best elemental weapon out there imo. I recently hit 5 million damage with a radiation build on a Grineer sortie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-13 05:56:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everyone knows the star of the south is honey boo boo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My Mexican Great grandmother and my Yaqui Great grandfather [Early 1900's]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-14 02:38:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-14 19:30:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tupac</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-19 04:07:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone notice that they used pounds as the weight? I thought they used kilos. Or maybe I'm just stupid</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What song (or band) made you actually afraid?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-19 06:23:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-19 06:25:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>For me, it was Kerosene by Big Black https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HuO3wwLuF0w It always made me think of being trapped in a murder house or something. Especially around 0:45. I feel like if Big Black weren't making music they'd be off doing MUCH worse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[WP] In a world where weather men actually decide and control the weather, your weather man just announced an apocalyptic storm on your town.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-19 06:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-19 20:54:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm glad to see the world is equally fucked across the pond</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-21 08:07:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-22 02:22:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>When DE eventually decides to quit making content for the game and move on to another project, I'd imagine there'd be a system in place for user created content to keep the game alive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-22 07:48:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is he... Donald Trump?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-22 07:58:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds awful. Sorry you had to go through that man, being accused of something you can't defend yourself against is the worst and can ruin lives, I'm glad you were never put in any real trouble.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-22 08:08:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Our spices are made with hellfire</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-22 08:20:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>CALL 1-800 STEAMER STANLEY STEAMER IS YOUR HOME CLEANER</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-22 08:31:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would ruin her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-22 17:41:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>My girlfriend used to go to Catholic School as a kid. It was the pretty strict "you're a sinner and you're going to go to hell" kind of school. Apparently there was an I maintained bathroom on the top floor, and the lesbians would use it for sex, I feel like sending your kid to a religious school is the one way to guarantee your kid won't be religious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-23 03:43:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excalibur +Ivara. I want a bow that shoots lightsabers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-24 03:18:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>[](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=IQ9kQ2eSdYc) Just gonna leave this here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-24 05:43:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck the system! I don't need any of your oppressive government opinions!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-25 08:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Perfect" Courage the Cowardly Dog</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 02:07:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's Italian, check out the documentary "Reel Injun" it goes over the Hollywood perceptions of Native American culture versus actual Native Culture. It mentions Iron Eyes Cody, he was an Italian immigrant who became obsessed with Native American lifestyle, he ended up marrying a Native Girl and having a family on a reserve. He ended up adopting he culture as his own and became a spokesperson for the Natives. But he's still an Italian dude playing a native dude Edit: Iron Eyes Cody was the dude in the commercial. Wild Bill Coyote doesn't even exist</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 02:11:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Needs more jpeg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 03:17:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Robert Downey Jr. playing a black man playing Iron Eyes Cody</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 08:10:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would argue that Deftones is still pretty great</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 17:46:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>The pain</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 19:35:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>There were two screams, one from primus and another from a metal slug game. I guess if you're going to steal a scream might as well use all the ones you can</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 05:54:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will name my son mayonnaise</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 05:55:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>That mayonnaise is not an instrument</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 05:56:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pixies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 06:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy fuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 07:50:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>So people couldn't find any liberals to complain about in the US, so they started looking at Chinese commercials for them. God bullshitters are pathetic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 19:04:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't talk to me or my son ever again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 19:05:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mayonnaise</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 19:05:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rubbing my soft warm body in jars upon jars of mayonnaise</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 19:06:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mayonnaise, the game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 19:06:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mayonnaise</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 19:06:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bathe yourself in stolen mayonnaise for a clean and beautiful shine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 19:07:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not consume enough mayonnaise to please the dark lord</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 19:07:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not having mayonnaise</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 22:51:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Obviously sex Ed didn't get through to them, that just sounds like a breeding ground for oral-transmitted STD's. Poor girl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-28 00:03:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mom used to work at an HIV clinic in Downtown Portland. Lots of homeless people would mix in with the young runaways from that had been disowned by their families (often because they were gay, or had drug problems) so there was a huge AIDS and STD problem. She has all these stories about the people they would see in there. It's pretty sad because a lot of them didn't know any better because hey we're too young, mentally ill, low on money, or various other reasons.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-28 22:47:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was actually the band that lead me getting into Hum</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-29 08:37:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Totally didn't think it was a Japanese maple</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 00:53:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love Depends intensifies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>After reading/watching scary stuff, what is something that helps calm you down?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 07:36:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 08:03:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>*opens link* *see's first glimpse* *heart explodes and frantically closes tab*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 08:06:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>The soundtrack for *Samurai Showdown* on the Neo Geo was pretty badass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 08:09:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Glad to know I'm a target now :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 18:12:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fun fact, the American version of the Office and Parks and Red were actually supposed to connect. The crappy printer in the office was supposed to go through a sequence where it would be delivered to Pawnee, connecting the two universes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-31 02:06:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>As an adolescent, I can say I was pressure into doing it before it was legal, but I never ended up actually doing it. Nowadays more people are deciding just to wait till they're the legal age to do it rather than going through all the trouble of doing it illegally. Doing weed used to be cool if you're underage, but now it just looks stupid to everyone else who just waits.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-31 22:40:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shel Silverstein isn't black</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-31 22:48:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>His portrait on the back of the giving tree. When I was younger I always thought he looked like a black guy in that picture, but it turns out he was totally Jewish  #175;\_( #12484;)_/ #175;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-01 02:30:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've found the opposite. I can negotiate done a price about 10-15% when I get offered a price. From what I've learned: the first person who says a number loses, but I guess it comes down to haggling skills (should have allocated more points to charisma)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-01 03:05:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wrong, I cast Mindsight for +10 to charisma, +5 to haggling and +5 to luck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-01 07:12:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's using you for military paychecks dude</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-02 22:31:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Luke, you don't understand how much this has helped me process my emotions. Thank you so much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-03 00:38:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I need a little bit of closure, and I hope me asking this doesn't stir up any bad emotions or anything, so you don't have to answer. What happened to Brody and the Stick Guy after you left? Did they stay together (which I doubt) or did they split apart? If you could respond it would mean the world to me e/ Could you please do an AmA? I think all of us here would love it and really appreciate getting to talk to you!!! Best regards!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-03 18:17:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah! My dad got Fantastic planet at a tool concert when they opened for them! I wish I could have been there to see it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 07:12:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fucking a blender</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 07:26:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dementia is not knowing where your keys are. Alzheimer's is finding your keys but not knowing what to do with them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 22:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Portland has always been weird, now the hipsters are tagging along</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-07 07:58:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Nice!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-09 04:25:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>"The Very Old Man" by HUM. The slat vocals only make it more depressing and real</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 01:53:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Cosby show</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 02:08:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>"She was bound to win anyway"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 06:59:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope you have happiness for the rest of your life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-11 21:50:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>5763</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-13 05:35:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Except he's blowing up the same people that would perpetuate these mass shootings, the killings are justified because they help defend American lives. But no matter how many you kill, Americans will always die. His face tells the story of a man that has long come to the realization that no matter how many murderers he kills, he will still have to bear the news that more Americans have died to senseless acts of violence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-13 05:53:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a sad feeling that the very statistic you have is the reason he has gone numb. Like him or don't like him, being the president is a shitty job</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-13 05:58:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, Roosevelt was a fucking psycho</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-13 09:52:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a more 80's modern feel. I think the vapor wave guys might like it. Cool designs though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-15 17:36:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something about Memento pleased my eye. Maybe it has to do with that fact that I grew up in the early 2000's. Otherwise awesome movie (^ ^)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-16 05:03:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's so fucking fun</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-16 09:54:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought Seventh Son was based off of the rangers apprentice?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-19 09:04:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus that's crazy. How did the community react? If everyone already knew he was a scumbag I can imagine they weren't too surprised.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-19 10:10:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Banana for scale</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 02:17:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love Myanmar! I've always wanted to visit there. In 8th grade I wrote a short story for my English class set in Myanmar, I got pulled out of the room along with another kid because my teacher thought I copied it from somewhere. Nope. Just love Myanmar</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 04:44:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I'll consider it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 06:15:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a little Mcmenamins coaster collection in my room. Every time I visit one I take one of the unique coasters,still need to visit the Lincoln City Mcmenamins!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 06:35:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like Cheryl from accounting isn't getting her fucking 3 dollar snickers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 07:55:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now that I know about it, hell yeah!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 20:31:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm currently an American student, we don't really do this anymore (at least in the northwest)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-23 03:39:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wear a condom</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-23 03:40:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>*raises three hands*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-23 07:45:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Heh, same here. Author/writer hopeful club here we go</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-24 22:56:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Who doesn't get payed enough for their job?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-24 23:16:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-25 00:41:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>From what it sounds like this was more of a case of her being afraid of disappointing her parents. I'd say this is a product of poor sex education and fear of parental disapproval. Sure, she could have had mental issues. But I know from experience that when you fear your parents judgement, you can do some crazy things.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-25 01:18:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shit. I guess I'll blame it on mobile</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-25 05:42:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe she just hated hem and was acting out? I'm just throwing stuff out there now. But yeah, something was definitely wrong with her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-25 05:52:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>MAX POWER SPEED</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-25 23:05:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure if you'll read this. And I know your stance on being blindly praised. But I just wanted to say, I've been following you for a while and seeing you grow in your talent, and it's absolutely amazing. You seem to accept the fact that you are destined to be mediocre, and that you'll never reach the greatness you strive for. But I just wanted to let you know something. Never stop trying. I've tried to make this as less cheesy and shitty as possible, but whatever, if it's gonna come out that way, then it's gonna come out that way. I just wanted to let you know, that you are awesome at what you do, I've seen you grow and get better and better, and it seems the better you get, the more you beat yourself up over how great you think you'll never get. I don't know. I guess I should just put it simply, that would make it easier I guess, rather then me babbling. You're good at what you do. Don't stop doing it. Hold yourself to high standards, don't hang yourself on them. Thanks for listening to my stupid half assed rant I wrote in like a minute. Always chase greatness, because you'll never know when you reach it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-25 23:10:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>FUCK YOU BEAT ME TO IT TAKE MY UPVOTE YOU PIECE OF SHIT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-25 23:27:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sega Dreamcast</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-26 00:16:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a necessary evil, but it's not exactly an evil thing. It's just sad, but necessary for preventing more sadness</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-26 00:45:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>My idea was that they knew the general idea of what the EU was, they were just searching for more in depth information, since they don't know where to look first, the search "what is the EU" as a broad term in order to answer most of their questions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-26 01:10:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>We know we can sleep tight. But can we sleep loose? Would it be like hanging tight and hanging loose?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-26 01:43:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also how I'd describe Reddit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-26 03:57:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me and my girlfriend had a pregnancy scare not to long ago. It was a sad and scary experience, luckily she wasn't pregnant. It's just sad to think that despite all the precautions you took,it still happened, and it's really no ones fault, but you still feel like you're responsible for whatever does happen. I don't know, it's sad and scary. It also ruined the song "kids" by MGMT for me while it happened.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-26 06:19:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Biological holograms</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-27 16:33:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dammit, I needed this in my life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 03:39:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a teenager. I think sex is great. I wasn't even provided free contraception, and told to abstain from sex. Abstinence doesn't work. People are going to do the very thing they are born to do. And that's banging each other like screen doors in a hurricane.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 04:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same! I turned off operator commentary immediately because I wanted to play warframe. Not slightly smaller power ranger megazord simulator.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 07:49:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love that band!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 07:55:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fucking a blender</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 18:41:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck, my uncle Jeff is balding and has kids now, he's living off of his dad's job</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 21:16:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly, what is in the fuck?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's something/someone everyone hates, but you could care less about?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 21:27:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 21:28:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>For me, it would have to be hipsters. I see a rampant hate of anything hipster on Reddit and I honestly don't care. The fashion doesn't look that bad either. Maybe living/growing up in the birthplace of hipsterism has made me more tolerant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 21:30:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I though several was another word for seven.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the most stupid thing you have overheard?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 23:04:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 23:05:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was once lose ting in on a conversation between these two guys about music Guy A: "Do you like Bohemian Rhapsody?" Guy B: *"Nah, I don't like rap music"*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-01 18:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's funny is me and my dad were way into Sriracha years ago. When our local store stopped stocking it we just never found time to go out and buy it again. Now that it's super popular it's in stock again and we have a bountiful stash of Sriracha again. So, I'm kinda glad it's popular, it reminds me of my dad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-01 20:33:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sriracha and sweet and sour sauce is my favorite</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-01 22:05:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll admit that I get a lot of pride out of growing up with Sriracha and knowing about it before most people did</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-02 18:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am Mexican. I understand</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-02 19:22:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had a friend who went though the same thing. Two girls said that he raped them in the bathroom. Everyone treated him like shit and even the police got involved. It fucking ruined him for years, that as until one of the girls mothers intercepted a note saying it was all a prank. The two girls had to move I believe. At the time when the accusations came out I was in a different middle school (there were two that were very close to each other, so word got around) and I never knew he was the guy until high school. Finding out that your friends life could have been ruined by horrible people is infuriating</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-02 21:16:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly my thoughts, it could have ruined his life forever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-03 05:11:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Coldplay secret concert</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-03 05:11:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fucking a blender</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-04 01:21:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ugh exactly. Everyone is freaking out about these new pancakes but they look gross to me. It's just a bunch of fluff. I LOVE crispy pancakes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-04 04:27:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah Tillamook. Came from Oregon to visit family in Texas during the whole Bluebell contamination thing. They had Tillamook replace all the Bluebell on the shelves and they were always picked clean. I can remember hearing my family/locals rave about their ice cream. Now that Bluebell is back Tillamook has just disappeared. The Bluebell shelves are always full and untouched and my family is eager to visit and all they talk about is buying Tillamook shit. I'm proud of my home state!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-04 04:28:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tillamook and beer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-04 04:28:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/madlads</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-04 05:05:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>My girlfriend is an INFP just like me :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-04 15:57:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>You'd think so, but not really. We have pretty much the same energy levels and the same libido. We do tend to hang and travel around each other at parties, and a lot of times all it takes is a few glances at each other to communicate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-04 16:05:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's calling her a cunt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-05 00:30:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus I'm so sorry. It amazes me sometimes the capacity for evil that some people have</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-05 00:32:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love how convenient both usernames are In this thread</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-05 01:13:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good thing he was great for farming affinity</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-05 02:40:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blue taco</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-05 19:03:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd say it does</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-06 03:23:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-06 18:02:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>[;)](https://www.wattpad.com/218406561-flaming-hot-tips-a-gordon-ramsey-x-guy-fieri)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-08 09:18:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Grandma calls me Mr.Magoo and my Grandpa calls me Buster Brown</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Help me find the Anne Heche Barbra Walters interview where she talks about aliens</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 02:12:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 04:14:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Found!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 09:11:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. The void was the endgame for me. After doing the alerts and the Sortie, I'd pop over to the void an spend some time grinding. If I needed something really bad, I would coordinate a team to go farm with. Now who gives a foul, run into a public trash mission and play feed the extractor for a minute and a half and pop out. There's no fucking coordination anymore. Does it make far if easier? Yes. Is that a good thing? In warframe the farming and grinding IS the fun. Now most of the endgame is gone and I'm expected to use my fresh dragon nikana on the fucking solar system? What? No, if I'm gonna have a weapon that powerful it better be against something that can put up a fucking fight. Ugh. The salt is real</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 22:04:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Flaming hot tips: A Guy Fieri X Gordon Ramsay fan fiction</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 22:06:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gilbert Godfried</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 22:10:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you ever plan to visit Mt. Hood. There are some awesome cabins available near the Sandy River/Trillium Lake area. You could always go camping by Trillium lake as well! The water is beautiful and the kayaking and fishing is great</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 22:13:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Team fortress 2. It seems pretty fun but It just doesn't click for me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 22:28:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hope to have you here sometime!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 00:57:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only kind of</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 23:27:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fucking a blender</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-11 19:45:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>remindme! 2 days</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 00:09:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least you didn't fuck a blender</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 02:35:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Essentially a demon bride</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 02:50:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some dude has memory problems and kills a guy. I have no idea</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 03:00:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've never heard anyone say pop in the northwest. Probably because if they do I'll rip their goddamn throats out for not saying soda correctly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 03:08:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello Michael</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 09:37:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Buzzfeed essentially recycles tumblr posts from teenage blogs with a caption, or they just copy. Whichever they feel like. You can often see one post by a blog/account. And hen a day later see that same post reposted by buzzfeed. As much as I hate this, I'll be dammed if I don't want to find out which Disney princess I would be Source: Teenage meme librarian</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 09:41:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Checks out by me. It earns points for a possible reference, but the outdated image macro and the fact that the reference may be accidental are holding it back. 6/10</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 09:43:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a reference to a girl finding a body while playing Pokemon go. You might already know that though :/ . Still a boring meme</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 19:26:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mom worked at an HIV/AIDS clinic in downtown Portland. A lot of times the people that would come for treatment were more hurt by the stigma than the actual disease. Often times there were teenagers who had came out to their parents as being gay, and the parents disowned them. Other times it was homeless people who often couldn't get a job because of health conditions, gangrene was a common issue, as well as various liver diseases (I forget the name, but it's not pretty). But the worst us to be the mentally ill. Almost all of the mentally ill patients were homeless, and had more STD's and other disease than you could count. It's hard being a paranoid schizophrenic when everyone actively avoids you like the plague. Overall, if you had the right insurance, enough money, and good family family members you could do well. I remember vividly my mom talking about a man who had missed his time for taking his drug cocktail, and the virus changed. He had to sit on an IV pump in order to live. Yes. HIV/AIDS is bad. But the most important thing is to be supportive of the people who have it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 20:54:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Multnomah county HIV center I believe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 20:55:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely. Portland has a huge homeless and heroin problem, it was kind of a recipe for disaster :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-13 07:46:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Used to live in northeast Portland/Gresham (I was right on the border. Pretty much sounds like the kind of people I saw passing the Tri met station. I didn't get shit on though :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-13 08:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Space rock for sure [Here's one by Failure](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=alNQ84K3y5Y) [Heres one by HUM(slightly heavier) ](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=IzAxMgastXU) [Another one by HUM(little more melodic)](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=GBPWUFfbNoI) [One of HUM's radio hits](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=Rfbn3ieVUYU) [Fantastic planet by Failure(an AMAZING album)](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=o4DZ_UvMAXk) [HUM's album that had the most commercial success ](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=YvsJpV4jtms)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-13 17:00:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't want my genitals anywhere near that face thankyouverymuch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-13 17:35:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>When people say "pop" instead of soda. I swear to god I rip out your fucking throat so the the only people left in the world that can talk will be people who call soda by its fucking proper name</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-13 17:36:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me in OP's mom</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-13 17:43:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>OP's mom</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-13 17:53:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>OP's mom</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-14 19:43:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Discount George Lopez</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-14 23:03:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Art is cool and all. But it also looks like an inflamed butt hole</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-15 21:07:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>My grandpa accidentally sunk a Russian submarine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-15 21:12:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Currently a junior. Maybe one racist redneck jock in school. But that's about it, most racist encounters I've had were around older people too. I've always found my own generation to be pretty caring and polite, which I think the world needs more of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-17 00:15:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's one of those quiet successes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-18 00:22:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. My grandpa is running for a small city council position and his campaign manager is really friendly and tells us all about the business. They hop from campaign to campaign doing manager work. Typically they start with small local ones then work their way up as they gain more experience and prestige as a manager. Eventually they could help manage big ticket campaigns like presidential or congressional</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-18 05:07:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dick and a blender</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-18 05:16:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oregon forever!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-18 07:33:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know too much, but from what I've gathered it's a lot of poll analysis and secretarial work. Setting up meetings, deciding on endorsements, helping out with campaign advertisements. Pretty usual stuff. After the campaigns over I think he might work with my grandpa on a reelection campaign or work for someone else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-19 08:41:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I fucked a blender</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-19 22:07:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just add water</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-19 22:22:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone was holding the wall while getting railed from behind, they could have been on their period too. That's what I get out of this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-19 23:15:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fucking it? Sure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-20 00:04:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>REMEMBER WHEN VOLTS SPEED FUCKING WORKED FOR THE WHOLE SQUAD? THATS WAS FUCKING GREAT. I WANT TO KNOW WHO THE PUSSY BITCH MOTHERFUCKER IS THAT COMPLAINED ABOUT MORE SPEED AND GOT THAT SHIT NERFED DOWN TO A CLUNKY FUCKING PICKUP. NO MORE FUCKING VOLT SPEEDRUNS FOR EVERYONE. AND IF IT WAS SUCH A PROBLEM, YOU COULDN'T DEAL WITH A SPEED VOLT FOR ONE FUCKING SESSION?!!! NOW THE ENTIRE THING IS NERFED FOR EVERYBODY FUCK, I WANT TO FUCKING GO FAST WITH MY TEAMMATES, NOW I EITHER HAVE TO LEAVE THEM BEGIND WITH THE PICKUP IN A HORDE OF INFESTED, OR DECIDE NOT TO PLAY AS VOLT AND FUCKING BULLETJUMP-GLIDE-ROLL MY WAY AROUND THE MAP. I MIGHT AS WELL FUCKING COPTER</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-20 00:09:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should pick me because I'm cool and your cool and my flair is the opening to bee movie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-20 00:14:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>A complex cephalon algorithm coupled with stolen Grineer gene modification files on the kavats allowed the Tenno to train and produce their own breeds. At the request of the Lotus's private cephalon, all Tenno landing craft have been been updated with a streamlined tactical map of the solar system. Allowing for Tenno and on board cephalon a to more easily navigate and simplify combat data in the system.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-20 20:59:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just show him a picture of what you want, like the one someone else posted above. They get it all the time. Barbers specialize in men's hair so it should work out pretty well. Also, it would help to learn some haircut lingo too (at least if you're in my old situation), I didn't know what tapered meant or anything like that. So basically brush up on hair knowledge to get exactly what you want</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-21 00:49:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>From the synthesis lore, some have gathered that the corpus were creations of the Orokin, and Hunhow doesn't make the distinction because in his eyes they are just as evil (guilt by association and such).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-21 01:14:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Toby from the office :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-21 17:58:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>The rumor come out: Does Bruno Mars is gay?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-21 19:45:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was a twilight zone episode</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-21 19:50:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least swans are pretty. Geese are just mother fucking dicks who bite 5 year old me for teddy Graham's</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-21 21:51:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>My moms chili</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I think my girlfriend is cheating with a bowler</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-22 01:08:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me and my girlfriend we're just having out at her place. We had just ordered pizza, were watching a movie and then all of a sudden she gets really frisky. So we head to her bedroom and things get spicy and she puts her phone on the table. So as we're doing it I look over to her phone and she gets a text from this one dude asking her to go bowling. But she's going on a trip to the beach for like two weeks. Should I be concerned?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-22 01:39:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That mother fucker!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-22 10:06:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-22 10:07:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to be burned alive and then fed to lions. I'm going out fucking metal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-22 10:12:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh hey it's you. How's my girlfriend</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-22 20:27:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>A construction worker. Or in this case a *deconstruction worker*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-22 23:47:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy fuck I didn't expect to see deftones here. No one ever mentions my favorite band, but here we are</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-22 23:51:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Banana pancakes with syrup and vegan butter. Then some hashbrowns topped with scrambled egg, kale, tomato, and salmon with some ketchup on the side. And a glass of water to drink</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-24 09:41:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's called being the bull, not the cuck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-25 05:44:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn, I remember the first time I listed to that album. Changed my music taste forever</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-25 23:41:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>"[The Very Old Man](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=olzCIjdMwXk) " by HUM. Hurts every time :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-26 23:01:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Umbra Dual Dex Dragon Nikana Prime Vandel Wraiths</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-27 19:58:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I came</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-28 01:29:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Guess my dick's going back in the blender</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-28 03:57:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love avocados!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-28 23:23:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wanted to be the guy who put olives on pizza. I figured I liked olives, and I liked pizza + olives on pizza guy = free olives and pizza for the rest of my life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-28 23:25:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Monica Lewinsky wins the election by a landslide</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-29 23:44:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I always thought that the police sketch of the Zodiac Killer was chilling](https://goo.gl/images/BnONDD)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-30 07:37:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was talking to a Japanese friend at school one day. I recently read a book that took place in Shiraharma I ask my Japanese friend "have you ever heard of Shiraharma?" Except that's not what I said What I really said was "Have you ever heard of *Hiroshima*?" One awkward chuckle from my friend and 5 minutes later do I realize my mistake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-31 02:52:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's too insect-ish</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-31 06:08:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bots banning bots?! Madness!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-31 10:44:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>'Twas the saddest scene I've seen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-31 20:27:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make me cry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-31 20:33:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello! I'm u/subject1105 and I'm a 16year old from Oregon who's trying to be a writer (but not in the edgy way)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-31 20:44:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>*"You terrorist bastards! I'll let the cancer get to me before you do!* *blows up self with cancer bomb*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What are some of the funniest last words?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-31 20:46:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-31 20:50:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>My great grandfather was near the end of his days when I was much younger. He was starting to get senile in his 90+ age but he was still super stubborn. He's sitting at the diner table when he mumbles out loud *"Where's my damn eggs?"* After the words left his lips he slumped over on the table and died instantly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-31 20:52:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>F u</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Oberon Prime confirmed????</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-31 20:57:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-31 22:27:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shhhh! Don't let the Californians hear you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-01 04:20:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tried to ask my Japanese friend about this town I read about in a book called Shiraharma. We were talking like normal and I had the though to bring it up, so I asked him "have you ever heard of Shiraharma?" Except that's not what I said "Have you ever heard of *Hiroshima*?" It came off sounding like a fucking douche insult when I said it. He just kinda chuckled awkwardly and moved on with the convo. I didn't realize what I said until it was too late.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-01 09:07:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Y2K</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 03:18:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cracker jacks, bottled Coca-Cola, denim jackets (i have one that's lined with flannel on the inside), 80's- 90's music. I'm 16. Kinda sucks because people think I'm trying to be edgy. My parents are just weird</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 19:28:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds sweet, I've been waiting for music discussion on this sub. Reviving a special sub for it would be awesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 19:32:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>[koda and ledger!](https://imgur.com/a/svWqp)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 19:48:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>He should have asked you out in person man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 19:51:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck yeah similar music taste</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 19:58:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>[16](https://imgur.com/a/zgp3G)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 20:04:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>She says thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Who do you respect?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 10:25:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 10:30:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 22:41:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>[The Very Old Man- Hum](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=olzCIjdMwXk) Matt's shaky vocals, the depressing and real lyrics, and the somber sound of the song make me shut down for a while :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 22:44:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never trust a horse girl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-04 08:46:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not an expert, but if your hairline was already like that then you have nothing to worry about. Your hairline doesn't appear to be thinning</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-04 08:52:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>They both look dumb. It's not meant to be super deep I guess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-04 09:32:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-05 07:00:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-05 07:03:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got banned from a pizzeria for throwing pepperoni like ninja stars</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-06 18:59:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sort of, it depends on the reasoning behind it. Most people that were drafted were young men from poor neighborhoods, if you could afford to go to college/move to Canada or fake an injury, you could avoid the draft. The young and poor couldn't afford college or moving to another country, so they were the ones to go. So who were the people that couldn't afford to go to college or Canada? Suppressed racial minorities. The draft preference towards the poor, and ultimately the ethnic, was seen as a purposeful move by the government; by some extent it was. So if you were poor and weren't the son of someone important, then you were going to war. It comes down to reasoning. The black community at the time of the Vietnam and Korean wars didn't want to die for a country the repressed them. It wasn't a matter of blacks not being allowed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-06 19:22:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have to understand that A LOT of people were involved in BPP at the time. Those who weren't were almost certainly likeminded on certain issues but not as extreme. BPP and the NAACP represented the majority. The blacks that did want to enlist were a minority. Majorities get represented more, minority's don't. As far as the BPP was concerned they were just the loudest voice in the room. The war was already divisive, and many didn't want to fight. There were already plenty of reasons the majority of the black community didn't want to fight. The BPP (NAACP wasn't as involved as much from what I remember) brought forth even more reasons blacks and other races shouldn't fight in the war.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's the worst customer service experience you've ever had?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-06 21:56:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-07 00:22:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reminds me of my regional race a few years ago when our 200 lb guy broke his foot stretcher. Had to row the entire race with a giant deadweight. We actually almost beat another team.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-07 06:15:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wanted to be the guy who put olives on pizza. Now I want to be a writer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-07 08:32:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah! They only apply to poor people! And dirty immigrants!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-07 20:05:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>"You know who likes ass eating? Nana"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-08 05:27:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tatooine boy meets his father for the first time. You won't believe what happens next!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-08 19:39:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kilroy came from a veteran as a reference to a cartoon character I think. It was WWII I believe. I could be off, but the only thing in for sure about is that is was from a veteran</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-08 23:43:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what it was! I remember reading about it a while ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-09 08:54:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>*The Last Angry Man*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-09 10:00:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>DICKS, OUT AUTOBOTS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-09 10:10:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Middle school versus now](https://imgur.com/a/aP4fG) [Here's some more](https://imgur.com/a/phmV9) Did rowing for a couple years and lost like 30-40 pounds! I use dot be in the 165-175 range, now I'm a skinny 137-140 and slowly gaining muscle! :) [Bonus little me pics (I've got my dads Yaqui eyes lol)](https://imgur.com/a/1JsyP)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-09 21:25:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same. Im dating a white chick though :/ Maybe I'll set up Yaqui dates with my future child</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-10 06:04:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha, nice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 02:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Cellar door*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 03:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>It does however help him "sell" himself and his brand to a dedicated audience. But considering his success was so out of left field I doubt anyone would be able to convince him that it would be a successful venture</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 04:41:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>(Pssst we're pretending it doesn't exist)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-13 09:24:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was the band that got me into Hum! Still one of my favorite albums!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-13 23:25:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was one of the few movies that I actually enjoyed in 3D. Most of the time it's annoying but Avatar was a particularly cool exception.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-14 19:37:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has Jeff murdered anyone? I don't know, maybe Jeff Wood.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-14 19:55:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like and appreciate classical music. But I feel like whenever I meet someone who tells me they like classical music they end up being a pretentious asshole who tries to hard to be smart and edgy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-14 19:57:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fake it till u make it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-14 20:04:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hum-You'd prefer an astronaut.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What was the dirtiest, slimiest, most backstabbing thing you did and DON'T regret?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-14 22:27:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-15 07:58:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the kotor 2 system did it better imo. You had stances for specific scenarios. You had one for lightsaber wielding opponents One for multiple enemies. One for blaster fire. One that was aggressive towards a single enemy. One that was aggressive toward blaster working opponents (but weak against single targets) One that was a balance of all. And one that was VERY aggressive towards a single target, but had even more defensive weaknesses. Each form had their situational defensive/aggressive strengths and weaknesses. Switching between the forms and choosing a favorite was a core part of combat and key in deciding your usual combat roll. And if someone threw a curveball that countered your normal stance? You could just switch to one that countered theirs. It was really unique and added a cool layer of depth to the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-15 18:08:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh come on, he was in public, give him a break we all get antsy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-15 18:30:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>ADD here. It's hard when you pace your room every five seconds and forgot how you got there, or end up hyper focused at the wall. I'm seeing a doctor soon and hopefully getting medication or treatment :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-15 19:13:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's the secret to FTL travel?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-16 08:08:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>How did you get into that position by the way? I'm hoping to pursue a career in writing and I could use some advice on where to go after high school</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-17 03:48:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>As condom. If you need a baby daddy that is</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-17 08:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have that same map. So fuk u</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-17 09:15:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe it was a challenge?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-17 23:56:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn you Mario kart</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-18 00:04:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn you Mario kart.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-18 00:18:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>High level math is mostly just plugging shit into equations anyway. I had a math teacher who encouraged us to use a calculator for simple math just to finish the equation faster</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-18 00:23:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dad met John Cleese. Followed by David Hasselhoff outside with strippers in each arm.He was in Vegas .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-18 01:44:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Precisely</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-18 01:46:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just like mama used to make</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-19 16:58:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>He must age like fine cheese and wine before graduating to the next level</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-19 17:03:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's punishing himself for his hunger. What would be an easy drive for junk when he was fat he turned into an obstacle. He knows that he is going to have to walk six miles in order to get food. So might as well walk there and do all that work when you're actually hungry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-19 17:12:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>He has heelys so he can ride down hills faster</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-19 17:38:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jeb is a mess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-20 06:26:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do miss pre 2010 Portland though. Right before the boom</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-20 23:15:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's my girlfriend now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Welcome</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-20 23:24:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-21 07:23:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dad likes jello and cottage cheese</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-21 07:33:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't do drugs because I'm vain and I think I'm pretty good looking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-21 07:38:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus his comment history though. It's sad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-21 07:38:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hand to Gland Combat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 10:05:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>And to think, my grandpa saw her boob.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-23 23:12:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>The crew of the serenity!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-25 17:59:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>The shock from working so hard so fast at the start of the race can actually cause your muscles to consume themselves in a desperate need for energy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-25 18:12:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, if you're gonna do ecstasy, why not maintain proper dental health?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-25 19:33:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I hope he still got his rocks off with his wife.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-26 06:47:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sweet, I can get shitty pizza faster</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-26 07:28:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>My girlfriend telling me she was madly in love with me :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-26 19:11:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>With old doggo come much experience and wisdom</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-27 21:18:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I understand, in death he has a name!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is something that's wonderful about life?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-28 22:27:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-29 11:10:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Inb4 Darude sandstorm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-31 07:04:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck did u just fucking say about me, u little bitch? I #8217;ll have u know I graduated top of my class in the Navy Seals, and I #8217;ve been involved in numerous secret raids on Al-Quaeda, and I have over 300 confirmed kills. I am trained in gorilla warfare and I #8217;m the top sniper in the entire US armed forces. U are nothing to me but just another target. I will wipe u the fuck out with precision the likes of which has never been seen before on this Earth, mark my fucking words. U think you can get away with saying that shit to me over the Internet? Think again, fucker. As we speak I am contacting my secret network of spies across the USA and your IP is being traced right now so u better prepare for the storm, maggot. The storm that wipes out the pathetic little thing u call your life. Ur fucking dead, kid. I can be anywhere, anytime, and I can kill u in over seven hundred ways, and that #8217;s just with my bare hands. Not only am I extensively trained in unarmed combat, but I have access to the entire arsenal of the United States Marine Corps and I will use it to its full extent to wipe ur miserable ass off the face of the continent, u little shit. If only u could have known what unholy retribution ur little  #8220;clever #8221; comment was about to bring down upon u, maybe u would have held ur fucking tongue. But u couldn #8217;t, u didn #8217;t, and now ur paying the price, u goddamn idiot. I will shit fury all over u and u will drown in it. Ur fucking dead, kiddo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-31 07:27:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>The other day in Eugene some dickhead skinheads were trying to start shit and mosh the entire time with people we're definitely not having it. Even during slow songs. Beware of skinheads</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-31 08:35:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fucking a blender</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-31 15:13:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely, just stayed away from them for the most part. They tried to start shit but didn't get far. I got super close to the stage and nearly touched chino and saw steph up close. One of my best birthday presents! Edit: chino</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-31 15:27:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jontron was created on my birthday? Nice! I'll be 16 today AND I can celebrate Jon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-31 15:41:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mom new them in SoCal when they were just Blink. She said they were lame and pop-y. Then again she was a hardcore grunge fanatic so that might explain it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-31 15:45:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIS MY BIRTHDAY MY DUDES</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-01 02:10:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>HEY YOU GUYYYS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-02 12:01:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>FAILURE AGH SOMEONE ELSE KNOWS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-02 19:43:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bakugan???????</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-03 06:22:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was little my cousins who were younger than me started sucking each other's dicks. I still can't look at them the same.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-03 22:31:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Royal T. Funk My mom was a lactation consultant. I wonder where that kid is now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-04 21:03:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you read [Dante's Inferno](https://goo.gl/images/fnRb6b) by chance?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-05 01:40:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's the only thing he knows that brings him pleasure anymore. Sad? Drink a beer. It's so engrained into his alcohol damaged mind that even after waking up from a traumatic incident the first thing that comes to mind is the only thing that will bring him comfort. Alcohol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-05 02:04:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>He can't *function* without alcohol. The symptoms of withdrawal can only make his pain worse, and in some cases can kill you. His brain is mush already, so imagine getting him to make the decision to remove the one thing he needs to get out of bed in the morning and actually resemble a human being. Addiction takes over every single part of your being. It is the axis on which your world turns.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-05 05:12:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not saying that there's nothing people can do to help him. I'm saying that there nothing he can do to help *himself*. He needs help. He functions on alcohol and the only way he's getting clean is with the help of others</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-05 05:26:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>He can't. His brain is a mush machine seeking his next high</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-05 05:47:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, I digged through your post history out of curiosity because I'm a lurker, and I read about what happened to your mother. I'm sorry. My uncle is an alcoholic as well, so I can only partially understand what you're going through. I'm sorry. Also, I hope you saw deftones, they're my favorite band, and the live show is amazing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-05 05:55:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's good. I'm happy for you man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-05 16:50:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's my point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-05 17:49:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mexican/native/white here. I feel your pain. Luckily my Yaqui traits have pulled through and I got some good hair and a cool jawline, but other than that I'm a racially ambiguous mess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-05 18:06:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>U gotta have faith in ur buy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-05 21:30:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>[yikes](https://imgur.com/a/bkGUl)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-09 21:18:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can magically know if Bruno Mars is gay or not</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-09 21:19:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool ass books with notes from people in the 30's</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-10 03:45:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>My papa (grandfather) Dave was a submarine navigation officer on the Blueback, the submarine that was used in Red October. He accidentally crashed into a Russian sub once. He met Jimi Hendrix and he saw Janis Joplin's boob.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-10 23:25:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>As is the Japanese tradition</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-11 19:19:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Little monsters reference?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-11 19:21:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Captain mayo and his sidekick discount Dwayne Johnson</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-11 20:47:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jon Stewart is not doing anything right now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-11 21:24:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>We need to bring back presidents with beards</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-11 21:49:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>In my head it looks more like a spirit animal. Think "brother bear"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-13 17:31:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh shit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-13 20:31:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hugging my girlfriend at home</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-14 05:14:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ivara</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-14 06:57:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well fuck I live there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-15 18:37:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does Bruno mars is gay?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-15 18:41:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Myanmar</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-15 19:12:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I USED TO DO HEROIN. NOW I JUST DO STEROIDS. *RIIIIIIIIIIIIIIP*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-15 22:27:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>We had a class discussion on this the other day. Many people thought that not standing for he flag as a sign of protest was actually more patriotic. He was able to freely protest for his belief so he could make change, which I would argue is more American than anything</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-16 05:19:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Portland</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-16 05:28:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, Ebola must really suck huh?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-16 06:47:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Posted on my birthday!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-16 15:46:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-16 15:58:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Corn dogs?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-16 21:56:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I would have been your daddy, but the dog beat me over the fence."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-17 18:46:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hm, I didn't know we had flairs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-18 02:30:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Teen adventure things in general. Something like the goonies or the lost boys. I' really tired of the forced romances and cliches and I just want to go on a fun spooky adventure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-18 07:18:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>It bonds and reacts differently due to its molecular structure. Or at least that's what 1 month of my junior year biochem class has taught me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-18 07:55:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fixed, totally forgot. I mix up neutrons and electrons because I think of *neutron* which makes me think of *negative*. It's the N that gets me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-20 03:02:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe carrier could increase ammo capacity? Only by a small amount and it would keep the ammo conversion. I'm sure he heavy weapons players would love it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-21 00:12:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you ever had an experience where you thought "Shit, this is really dangerous" If so, what happened? Also, you made my teacher in think I plagiarized my short story. My mom loves you by the way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-21 02:30:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-21 02:36:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good for you. I'm circumcised and I've never and any sort of infection. My penis has always been squeaky clean and sex is great and frequent. I didn't know people were so outraged from a common medical procedure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-21 02:54:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why? There's no point in arguing with you. It's not like I'm going to change your opinion. Bedsides, I'm circumcised and I've had absolutely no problems with it, I've never had a yeast infection or a UTI. I'm not traumatized by it either. I was a baby, it's not like I remember that shit. I have a great sex life as well. But there's no point in arguing with a stranger on the internet. I respect your opinion. No amount of articles or scientific evidence from either of us is going to convince the other. So just leave it be. I'm circumcised, I have never had a problem with it, I enjoy sex and I don't remember being circumcised because I was a baby. What do you want me to say? Sorry?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-21 02:59:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>My body remembers it? What? Does my penis wake up at 3:00 in the morning screaming likes it's having a fucking Vietnam flashback?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-21 03:18:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no! Highlighted text! Listen, we can throw sources all day. But at the end of the day. My life, my SEX life, are both wonderful. Now, if you have another argument that doesn't conclude that I, a stranger on the internet, have psychological trauma from a procedure I can't even remember AND is based on what can only be perceived as the armchair psychology of a particularly self trustful redditor I would love to hear it. But if you do not have one, then I am wasting my time on nothing more than a brick wall that spent too much time watching circumcised porn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-21 03:21:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's not an argument. Do you want to tell me how my life is awful too? Go right ahead, I assure my life is wonderful. But treating me like I'm stupid is. Not going to change my mind</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-21 03:36:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Listen, as the son of a mother who worked at an HIV clinic in one of the most homeless friendly cities in America, I'm glad I was circumcised. Grown men would walk into the clinic wish strangulated penises used as a result of foreskin. The smegma from the foreskin would build up behind the tip. Nurses had to forcibly pull their foreskin forward, and then clean out the inside of their diseased dicks while they were under anesthetic. I don't know about you, but I'd like to be able to go camping without worrying about genital lesions. Okay? That's my family's reasoning, and thats my reasoning. Oh, and for my cousins sake, don't fucking compare this to being drugged and raped. You have no fucking clue what that is like.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-21 03:37:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Europe has far superior sex education.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-21 03:40:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate your politeness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-21 03:41:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>So you're saying that I was raped?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-21 03:47:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see your point. My mother saw a lot of men choose to circumcise for medical reasons while she worked in the clinic. I'm on the fence about doing it at birth. I trust my parents decision as they were both medical professionals. It just happened to work out for me, and as far as I can tell for the majority of men there doesn't seem to be that many complications. But having it as a choice is definitely important.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-21 03:52:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure, I can see that. I believe the botched ones are products of a lack of expertise/ignorance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-21 03:55:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. In this thread I learned that I was raped as a child because I had a routine medical procedure. I guess I should tell my parents that every time they took me to get a shot without my consent they were inadvertently submitting me to rape. This thread is fucking crazy. I'm out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-21 05:06:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine wasn't</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-21 05:31:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was as a baby. It worked fine. My penis is wonderful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-21 22:44:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>There was as Donnie Darko sequel?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-22 00:06:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I recently studied this, second world now classifies as a post communist reform state. So Japan Italy and Germany would be 1st world, as they reformed during the Cold War for the most part.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-22 00:07:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yikes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-22 19:13:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess we like to classify the regions of the ocean based on climate and differences surf quality</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-22 21:27:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's truthful to my perosnality</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-23 01:17:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>FUCK YEHA LOST</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-23 06:55:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-23 08:28:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's plenty of haircuts like that, this probably isn't the best representation. You could post a picture of your current hair and get some opinions:).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-24 22:17:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I swear I've heard his exact same comment before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-24 22:35:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh okay. It just seemed familiar. Thanks for clearing it up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-25 06:04:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Annie's chocolate bunnies cereal is the shit though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-26 01:33:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>*THE INCREDIBLE ADVENTURES OF DR. MORTALITY AND HIS SIDEKICK THE PASSAGE OF TIME.*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-27 23:35:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really want them to keep playing the game. I hope Arin sticks it through. It's got a cool twin peaks vibe and it's so fascinating!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-29 21:15:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stellaris</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-30 01:12:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never really considered the saw movies pure gore porn. To me it was always the suspense that put me on edge. The movies were great at putting you on the edge of your seat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-30 04:51:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just taking a shit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-30 06:09:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I in and out of Portland and I understand that there are quite a few Buddhist offices on the outside of the city as well as inside. I'm brand new to Buddhas teachings but I can try to help. If you end up finding anything I would be very happy to know! Right now I'm trying to learn the essential basics :/ .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-30 18:57:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>STOP PUTTING FUCKING CORN IN EVERYTHING. CORN ISN'T MEANT BE PUT IN CLAM CHOWDER. JUST EAT CORN BY ITSELF YOU FUCKBALLS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-30 23:06:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the book that brought me to Buddhism! Still new but it's a big help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-01 00:00:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really good rootbeer. Apparently it's rare but I wouldn't know because it's a five minute walk up the street to the corner store that has them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-01 19:45:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>She studied ballet, that's second position</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 04:22:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>My brother has dyslexia, my mother has anxiety, and I have ADHD. But hey, we're all pretty good looking. So there's that. Thanks genetics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 18:55:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It ends in childhood for some people. But others can carry it into adulthood.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-03 01:53:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dad peed next to him in vegas. He also saw David Hasselhoff in the same casino</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-03 03:20:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>16, been listening since 6th grade. Parents bonded over deftones and passed in down to me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-03 21:14:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got stung by a man of war once. Like stepping on a hot frying pan. I had it's tiny needle like injectors stuck in my foot for months without me noticing. The sting area began to cave in and form holes in the flesh. Pretty scary but it healed over in a couple days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-03 21:49:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, my best guess is that the sting got deep into the skin of the bottom of my foot, killing the lower layers. That's why it began to cave in a month or two later, as the skin was in the process of healing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-03 21:55:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fordyce spots are normal. Don't worry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-03 21:58:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Flash games, circuit city, and shit tones of PBS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-03 23:55:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Better yet, stay in California. Oregon doesn't exist</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-04 01:43:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I freaked out and thought I had an STD when I first got them in middle school. Apparently most men have them. So it's all good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-04 03:08:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, it's hard to explain. When the man of war stung me, it left its little blue nematocysts in my foot. After carefully picking out as many as I could, I assumed it was fine. About a month or two later the flesh in my foot began to cave in, dry out, and form holes. So either there were dormant nematocysts in my foot that released once more, or the venom from the initial sting dug further in than I thought which caused the dead skin underneath the top layer of skin. I dunno, it hurt and it freaked me out. I don't like my foot caving in on itself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-04 03:51:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't think you were one :). I did kind of word it weird though. It's hard to describe. Hope you're wart asshole is okay!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-04 04:54:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sadly no :( However on the same vacation I got sunburned worse then I ever had before and I threw up spaghetti. So fun times</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-04 05:14:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Plenty of pictures of stings online I'm sure! I stepped on the Man O' War so it ended up blueish. But most of the stings look similar</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-07 18:40:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, social media is pretty much open to anyone. It's not like it's a personal space, but still, teachers and students are strictly not allowed to have personal relationships outside of school</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-09 00:21:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>My great grandfather told my mother that the only thing they missed in the film was the smell. I believe him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-09 17:55:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hm, I need to start commissions then. I wrote a Guy Fieri X Gordon Ramsay homoerotic fan fiction as a joke and they said it was pretty good. I was thinking of doing Farquaad X the ginger bread man next</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-10 03:21:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bill Clinton isn't running for president. Hillary is, why the fuck does he keep bringing him up? He doesn't fucking matter</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-10 04:12:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course. But I don't see how attacking him is attacking Hillary. Despite the shit that he may or may not have done at the end of the day he not the president anymore. He holds very little power and it just seems cheap to attack Hillary through bill</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-10 17:33:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.wattpad.com/218406561-flaming-hot-tips-a-gordon-ramsey-x-guy-fieri Beware, I wrote this as a relatively new writer, and only for a few friends as an inside joke. I tired to be over dramatic and stuff. I hope you like this monstrosity</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-11 19:13:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>West linn represent. Emerick is still a horrible Econ teacher and I'm sitting in her class</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-11 21:59:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's my first time having her, she keeps forgetting her own due dates and she has a no late work policy. Half the class is fucked</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-11 22:45:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Second period? Is her name Mary?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-11 23:13:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wasn't there for that, but the whole Mr.Peachy thing was also a major incident. I always kinda figured he was creepy though, it didn't surprise me he was a pedo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-12 00:42:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>More or less, ever since the weed linn bust and the legalization people have just been a little more careful about handing it out. There's more casual pot smokers now and people tend to form groups around it, I have some friend who are in these groups. There's a pretty big alcohol problem but the school is relaxed about it as long as West Linn keeps its good grade reputation, I'm pretty sure that's what they care about the most now anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-12 00:56:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Molly not so much. There's a few heroin people here and there but either no ones really doing hard drugs, or everyone learned to shut up about it. I know there's a coke dealer somewhere in west linn that sells to white suburban families and their kids without either party knowing, shits fucked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-12 03:25:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's okay, doesn't matter too much. I'm fucking rocking market watch though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-12 04:28:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess I'll keep my trade secrets even more... secrety</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-12 04:54:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh shit. I have a D in her class right now because of her late policy and the fact that she can't decide on due dates</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-13 17:17:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>HOKY FUCK FUCKIN STAR WARS *A NEW STAR WARS* FUCK ME UP TAKE SOME LIQUIFIED STARWARS AND SHOVE IT IN MY ASSHOLE FUCK GUYS STAR WARS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-14 00:09:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>My grandfather was that Lt. Commander and navigator of the *Blueback* the same submarine that was used in the hunt for Red October! I love hearing submarine stories</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-14 19:22:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I played timpani and bass drum, my band teacher always told us that bass drum gets payed the most. I guess I covered both my bases in case I don't get a career in writing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-15 01:03:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>His point was that the bass drummer keeps the entire rhythm of the band. But this was also pep band, so...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-15 02:22:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always assumed it wasn't the water, but some earth exclusive impurity in the water that killed them. The aliens knew there was water on the planet, but were unfamiliar with whatever impurity was in the water. Thus, to their surprise, it killed them. That's why the invasion was able to be stopped. At first invading and taking the natural resources makes sense, but when those resources kill you on touch, why continue the invasion?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-15 04:29:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude, you're literally making the argument that your shit doesn't stink. Or in this case, your trash. Don't actualize a metaphor</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-15 04:33:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>We do refer to them by numbers. We use 9th 10th 11th 12th and freshmen sophomore junior senior interchangeably</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-15 04:35:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've only had to in elementary school. I think it's mostly for us to memorize it rather than brainwash us. It's always good to memorize the pledge of your own country. After elementary school they stopped making us do it. Also, in elementary the only time they made us do it was during the weekly assembly, not at the start of class.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-15 04:36:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-15 06:30:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>True</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-15 10:07:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can rumble, and roll my eyebrows</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 09:05:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Part your hair on the opposite side</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 09:09:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>T H E B O N E Z O N E</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 18:20:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It good go well either way. You have good hair and it would look good long because of the way it curls. Short hair is hard the mess up. Either way it's going to look good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-17 02:03:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>This fucked me up when I figured it out for myself. I felt so smart.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-18 07:20:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dad and his friend would play "smear the queer" when they were little. Looking back on it he feels really bad. Even though it was just keep away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-18 22:29:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>One day, my papa (grandpa) and a few friends decided to head downtown to a Jimi Hendrix concert. The show was completely packed, no way of getting in right? So it's no big deal, they park outside with a bunch of people and listen to the music coming from inside the stadium. My papa decided to take a walk around the stadium to get away from the BBQ/hippy stench. By now he concert is ending and things are winding down. He walks to the back of the stadium to see if he can catch a glimpse of he entourage. But out of a small little side door comes out the one and only, Jimi Hendrix. "Hey, you're Jimi Hendrix!" "Yeah man." Jimi walked away, no entourage, nothing. He boarded a greyhound bus and left. Another time my Papa was in a tattoo shoppe (also in the 60's it turns out that the artist there was really famous, I forgot his name). Inside he saw Janis Joplin's boob, apparently she was getting a tattoo on her chest. My papa ended up joining the navy and working on submarines. Eventually becoming a Navigation officer. The submarine was the Blueback. The same one they used in The Hunt for Red October.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-18 22:30:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>The USS *Blueback* submarine. My grandfather was the navigator on it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-18 23:55:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/outside</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-18 23:59:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess every Asian person on earth will disappear</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-19 00:01:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meet with my dad, who worked in Home Depot. And convince him to kill one of the terrorists. Apparently one of them returned something to the Home Depot he worked at before the attacks. He was dumbfounded</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-19 00:59:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice! Fun fact, the civilian entrance way the built into the sub for tourists was actually where my Papa's quarters were! He was kinda pissed but it's alright now, he plans to do tours soon as he is one of the only members nearby for the commute. Also, being high ranking helps</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-20 17:03:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/threadkillers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 00:45:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dad ended up watching it backwards. He was a party and he fell asleep during the first half, and only caught the second half. He was really pissed so went out and bought the movie just so he could watch the first half and find out what's going on</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 07:05:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dang, I heard Arizona and I thought you'd be a Yaqui :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 07:50:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>[My personal favorite from the randomizer](https://imgur.com/a/KoBFH)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 17:15:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pascua Yaqui tends to yield more search results</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 17:24:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hear a lot about Seattle in this thread. But how will the earthquake affect the city of Portland?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 17:47:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Patrick Stewart as Professor X</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 18:38:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Do not dwell on the past or imagined futures"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 18:39:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>The giant fucking earthquake that's set to happen in my lifetime in the Pacific Northwest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 18:54:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>It hasn't happened yet, but it's set to be bigger than San Andreas</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-22 06:20:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha nerd. Look at this nerd everyone. So smart. And successful. Go back to your high paying job dork. Am I right guys? Guys?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-22 10:18:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty much. They go to meeting and talk about current events. Most of them are old dudes. It's basically and old timey union. Source: grandpa was a Freemason</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-22 10:23:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>To stop thinking about how everyone I love will die one day</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-22 10:42:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>It'll be okay! I went through something similar. It worked out in the end. But sometimes it's better to move on. There's always something better to be found around every corner in life!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-22 20:53:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, Grandpa is an atheist. But nah, they're just a really old club with a cool name</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-25 08:52:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Writing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Who amongst your high school graduating class had the most successful life?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-26 01:43:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-27 01:09:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm kind of a jerk. People say I'm actually really nice. So maybe I'm just really self deprecating. I mostly just keep it around because it sounds cool and the name wasn't taken. It's started as my Instagram handle :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 04:15:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>*"M'lady"* *"Did you just assume my gender?"*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 05:53:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>The better not fucking come back here. Everyone I know is pissed off beyond all belief</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 05:28:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay but actually Holy fuck. He just He just Fucking grabbed it Like "Here it is!" Like holy fuck He just chased down a goddamn giant bird emu and just Hugged it? Holy fuck man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 08:41:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Day of the dead jat kittag skin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 08:42:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Halloween promotion, you get free stuff</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 22:23:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mom was a lactation consultant. Royal T. Funk was her favorite</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-01 07:17:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like r/thalassophobia is the place for you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-01 07:41:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my teachers once made the point that WARS being new medical technologies. Effectively sacrificing thousands to save millions Ex: the ambulance in WWI</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-01 17:35:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup. We have one here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-01 21:22:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/eyeshakers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-01 22:13:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/accidentalrockwell</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 02:40:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>*"Is only game. Why you have to be mad?"*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 08:21:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone else think that the Alabama pipeline explosion is going to cause a dawg towards the protesters side?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 16:41:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>God, and I thought the ads in Oregon were getting bad with all measure 97 ads every two seconds. I can't begin to imagine having presidential ads on top of it :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 16:44:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jokes on them, the democratic garden is flourishing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 17:15:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good luck fellow forest dweller :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 21:21:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll start work on a Doug fir fortress</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A sad kid in a sweater</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-03 17:13:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 18:51:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still don't see them as nu metal. They're like the Radiohead of metal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 22:57:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought deception was awesome! The music in that game is so sweet! The whole thing felt super dark and brutal, like mortal kombat should be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 03:52:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Totally! Sub zero and scorpion looked badass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 10:09:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>That depends, personally their early stuff is really good. Sadly it kinda got bunched up as nu metal because they came out at the same time and from the same general area. My favorites from their first album are [Fireal](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=GSQuY74s7rU) and [Bored](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=rkChWhA6vQ8) The second album they keep a lot of their heaviness but get more technical. Around the fur is one of my favorites. My favorite track would probably be [My own Summer](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=9IdYLvd7OsU) As for White Pony, it's considered the quintessential deftones album by many. It's really where they started to deviate from the mainstream. Personally I recommend just playing it and seeing what you like, since there's a lot to listen too. (Also, back to school (mini maggit) is a faster rapped version of pink maggit, essentially their label forced them to do a catchy rap song to sell some more, a lot of people like it but I find it super cheesy and it doesn't fit he tone of the record at all.) The self titled don't album is one of my favorites as well, but it kinda gets overlooked. It's pretty dark at some parts but I find it pretty sweet, a good starting place. [Needles and Pins is one of my favorites](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=Ye-frzA7N0E) Next comes Saturday Night Wrist and Diamond Eyes. Both super solid imo. I recommend just starting on Saturday Night Wrist if you're into softer stuff, I consider it their softest, it has a special place in my heart  lt;3. Diamond eyes is much heavier but not dark. Its definitely got heavier instrumentals. Their newer stuff is GREAT to start out with. Depending on what you like of course. I could write a ton but it wouldn't do them enough respect. Honestly, just give a few tracks a listen and see what you like. TL;DR: Deftones changes their sound constantly. So the best thing I can recommend is shifting through their discography and seeing what sticks, then follow that feeling and let the rest come naturally. I started out loving their heavier stuff years ago but I ended up finding their softer songs much better than I originally thought. The one thing I will say though, is that it's very easy to spot a deftones song, they change up their sound, but they keep a consistently good style. Also, come visit us on r/Deftones :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 22:38:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I kinda like it. You remind me of [Inigo Montoya ](https://pbs.twimg.com/profile_images/469498101/inigo1.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-08 06:32:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Giving alcohol to kids who he invite to his house. Then touching one of them. He was married too. He was considered the fun and easy Spanish teacher.he's in prison out there I believe, so fuck Mr. Peachy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-08 22:13:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you have to be especially good at acting to be a part of it? Is thee an incentive to be as convincing as possible or simply get your character alliance across to the trainees so they can continue doing their thing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 08:20:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's sad that people have begun to fight *with* social justice, rather than fight *for* it. Using social justice as a means to be prejudice, and a means to make a point will never work. In order to attain the goal of equality one must push the cause, not drag it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 22:30:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't worry, American background checks are shit. We'll get our guns</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 23:45:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course, I forgot that guns don't exist in the west. Silly me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-10 00:00:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Colorizebot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-10 04:27:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pandas. I mean, they are bears. Don't forget that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-10 22:01:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nigel. Duh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-12 11:04:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>He made a fucking rib shield. So he's in college right? Getting his medical degree young along with others and they end up working on a cadaver one day. He never went into specifics on what they were trying to do, but the entire thing was pretty relaxed as they were all pretty far along in the year. The professor just kid of sits in the corner/ move in and out of the room while the students do whatever they want to do. Well my dad being my dad sees a wonderful opportunity. He was able to saw incisions around the cadavers ribs. One of his friends managed to take a bone from he arm. Before you know it, my dad and his friend are locked in a skeletal duel with my dad cheering "RIB SHIELD!!!" He ended up graduating with an doctorate and becoming an amazing chiropractor. Turns out the business was inflated so he now works at a clinic for schizophrenics/criminally insane. Fun fact: It's the same building that they used in the one who flew over the cuckoos nest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-13 20:15:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>My theory was that there was originally one queen, who was cloned as part of an experiment. However the new queen was cloned from birth, so there was an older one and a younger one. When one dies a new one was cloned, this one would be younger than the previous clone. This happened over generations, thus leaving an eternal cycle of one older queen to teach, and a younger one to learn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-15 01:12:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Grunge is back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 06:02:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, I never thought of it that way, but they kind of are. Huh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 07:27:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, but how often do you read the newspaper? Most webcomics nowadays are non political, even online newspapers don't really have comics that are anywhere near influential as they used to be. Memes reach an incredibly large audience, and they can be altered to have countless different meanings surrounding the same basic joke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 07:29:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Memes are great :) and it's good you read the newspaper!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-17 22:52:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm on bug I guess, had the same happen to me. You can revive them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-17 22:53:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't forget tomatoes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 09:42:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>One can be a Buddhist and an atheist. Siddhartha was a real historical person, who we even have mummified pieces of. Following his teachings does not mean I believe in a god, simply in a way of life. While some sects of the Buddhist faith (generally the pure land sect) believe in life after death, most Buddhists believe in either reincarnation or are simply atheist on the matter. Buddha it's a god, but simply a teacher who sought to bring happiness to the world :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 20:26:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Archwing 2.0</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-22 02:25:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/outside</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-22 07:43:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Similar thing for the Pascua Yaqui. Apparently we adopted Christianity form the spaniards as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-22 21:33:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see you with that deftones  #128064;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-23 21:29:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck yeah I'm going left wing, it looks like a fucking party. I don't want to hang out with a bunch of creeps in the cold ass snow and woods</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-24 00:31:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like a reverse Oreo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-24 01:50:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depends of the severity of the year has. But technically if it's heavy duty stuff that's currently being used it could fall under the classification of a chemical weapon by the 1925 Geneva Protocol. Source: Model UN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 19:05:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought it was finally labeled as a suicide? He had made phone calls to family members beforehand concerning his daughters. They said he was crying and distraught, the coroner later said that he was also under the influence of drugs at the time of his death.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 05:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a bitch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-28 02:58:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're still flying half a ship.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-28 03:29:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>My grandpa was a Freemason. From what he described it was just a hangout club where they organized events and projects for the community, as well as some workers rights stuff. Essentially the freemasons were like a pre-union. My grandpa has since left because he just didn't have time for the meetings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-28 06:17:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Doesn't surprise me honestly. The higher the position, the higher the secrecy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-28 07:51:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would definitely recommend cleaning up the sides and growing out your top a little more. It will help your face seem less round and more long. After that the finer details on what specific style are up to you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-28 17:32:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right now it's a little more round, but face shape isn't exactly set in stone, outside factors (especially your hair) can completely change the way your face looks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 20:33:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>My 11 year old brother found one not to long ago, they're still around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 21:14:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>A Farewell to Arms. Hopefully they like nihilism.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 23:46:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's be like if Tumblr only made posts about r/incels</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 05:09:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Branron" This is gonna be a hard play through.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 18:01:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reddit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 21:15:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey. I'm only *kind of* a dick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 23:28:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-04 04:38:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Baron will use to the throne, execute and suppress the loyalist faction lead by his older brothers. Then either take Ivanka as a bride (to preserve the bloodline) or have a royal form a neighboring nation marry into the Trump family. Melania will take the crown until Baron comes of age. We're back to the 1600's everyone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-04 04:58:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>But isn't Taiwan technically separate form china? China doesn't recognize them but that doesn't mean they aren't independent. China can't do fuck all to Taiwan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-04 22:52:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, the political status of Taiwan is ambiguous, in the San Francisco treaty of 1951, Japan renounced its right to Taiwan without explicitly stating the sovereignty status of it. In modern day, 90% of people living there identify as "Taiwanese" rather than Chinese. When given the option between unification and independence, 65.9% of Taiwanese supported independence (according to Forbes, aei.org, and various sources on Wikipedia).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 01:37:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did an experiment just like this! managed to increase he productivity of solar panels without completely melting it. Also melted some plastic soldiers afterword, super fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 04:31:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well my experiment focused on improving the power productivity of solar panels, I used basically the same method in this video, except on a smaller scale, and got about a 10-20% increase depending on the time of day/weather etc. my idea for the long run was to develop a lens that could be placed over a panel like a film, improving power output. Like the other comment, there are some plants that use this method. I know of one (it may be the one the other comment is mentioning) that uses fresnel lenses to boil a water tower, producing energy. I might be a little biased, but I think that the future of solar panel productivity lies in fresnel lenses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 15:49:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>It essentially works like a magnifying glass, I have my drawing somewhere that go into more detail but I think I might have lost them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 16:32:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sadly, my experiment didn't stretch that far, we had plans a) a film that would redirect incoming light b) a moving platform above the panel that would focus light downward c) a solar box Our experiment was just to see if it worked, which it did :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 17:48:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Our idea was a fresnel lens placed over the solar cell that would be slightly larger than the cell itself, the lens essentially works like a magnifying glass, collecting normally dispersed light and redirecting it to the center of the cell. As the lens would have a slightly larger surface area, more light could be directed to the cell. This wasn't the focus of our experiment however, our job was just to see if a fresnel lens could work without melting the cell into oblivion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 22:01:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright, what reputable source are you using? Why should I believe your poll? When did I saw that all other democracies are dictatorships? Isn't that your point? The Taiwanese president was clearly elected democratically, of course you wouldn't know that because you didn't believe that Taiwan was its own independent state. What's your point?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 22:10:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>My grandpa was the Lt. Commander on it, the civilian entrance they use for tours used to be his quarters. After he retires he plans of giving tours there :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 22:33:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely! He's a super quiet guy but he has the coolest stories, some of my favorites are about celebrities.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 22:54:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>*I USED TO DO HEROIN. NOW I JUST DO STEROIDS* *RIIIIIIIIIIIP*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 23:06:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>If 5% of it is salt, that means that Warframe is still more salty than the ocean.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-06 17:57:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>DE is good at buffing, not so much at nerfing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-06 21:49:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>People like you are the reason I almost killed my self. Just fucking leave us alone. Not everything is a fucking moon landing conspiracy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 04:36:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was clever. Have an upvote!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 04:41:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Back in my day we called them picture shows.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Literally just a normal fucking picture of jontron that will get downvoted because it's not a shitpost.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 06:06:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-10 20:37:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is a difference between fighting *for* social justice, and fighting *with* social justice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-10 22:00:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>If Dutch was her first, then maybe she's more used to expressing emotion more clearly in that language? Whereas in English she would have to think harder about it, and think it through more. Just a theory though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-11 08:50:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you a Chinese Christian man in his late twenties/ early thirties with 2.4 children? If not then you're not average in the way you think you are :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-12 18:28:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have one named Clint</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-13 17:34:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>"You have the moral backbone of a chocolate eclair."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-14 22:12:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>ITT: 95% people saying this thread is going to get locked because of bad comments and 5% actual bad comments</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-16 01:59:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Colorizebot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-16 01:59:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Colorizebot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-16 02:03:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You tried</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-16 02:14:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope, many are abused and treated poorly. Tourist don't know any better though. Poor elephants :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-16 08:09:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Minesweeper coach</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-16 09:54:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but you won't get sweet karma that way though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-17 04:38:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>So your teacher was Danny divito?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-18 06:36:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Savanna or Sierra</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 02:40:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>My Ign is courior Thank you!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 08:50:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're thinking of puta. If I remember correctly from abuela Puto means "dot" as in "12:00 on the dot". I suppose it could also be used as an insult too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 08:54:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah right, now I remember. I get my P words in Spanish mixed up all the time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 21:12:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>W.I Semen, M.D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-24 01:36:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yikes, I'm a curves man myself but fucking a tetherball would be rough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-24 09:38:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate sand, it's coarse and rough and gets everywhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-26 01:08:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>You better watch your mouth, before we know it a new weapon will require 50,000 gallium for research</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ANTI-DRUG BRAVE BRIGHT MAKE SCHOOL brains good STRONG CHOICES CONTROL SMART SAY 'no'</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 05:06:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 09:56:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm picturing Ellen Ripley's cargo lifter from Alien</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 20:25:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/bandnames</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-06 18:36:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>They can't be vaginas, he would have clawed his eyes out trying to grab them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 03:20:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I wish they would take more inspiration from Mortal Kombat IMO](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=6f_WZuEd0xw)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 03:08:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>The names aren't unique at all, they're stereotypical faux unique upper class names. That's the joke</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 03:20:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, it's a bit specific. There's been an upturn in parents trying to make their kids names "unique" but they all end up sounding he same or not being unique at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 19:46:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friends dad was the lead writer on the game. I'll pass along the compliment!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 18:31:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was actually pretty good! The lead singer is awesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 06:20:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, meta already, I think this might be a new record</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 06:28:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Goddamnit not this fucking meme again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 10:04:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-19 08:08:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah,I still remember meth, eth, prop, but. Organic chemistry is boring as hell sometimes, but other times it's really cool</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 19:17:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hue hue hue</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-21 18:46:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Protests are designed to disrupt and make life miserable for everyone, until the only option becomes making the change they request. Protesting in a library is super disruptive, it's also incredibly easy to makes your presence knows. Protesting in a library also as some symbolic significance. If I was trying to make a change, and I'm pissed off and no ones listening, then you're goddamned right I'd protest in a library</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 06:33:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't be embarrassed to show off your poetry man! I've deleted poetry posts too, but feedback really helps!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 21:58:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/gallery/T1kbk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 21:45:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 07:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literal bologna</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 01:39:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Fashion Calling](https://imgur.com/a/dPG6m)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 17:46:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Totally! Your hair looks super nice though. Also, holy fuck your skin looks smooth, good job on moisturizing man!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-05 08:42:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right? Like I'm pretty lenient when it comes to physical differences but holy shit the guy looks like a fucking alien</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Off Topic] Nidus and Nova are terrifying</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 05:45:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was running Nidus in today's sortie, my Slowva Prime buddy popped molecular prime all over the map, while I spammed larva. It's kinda fucked up when you think about it. I mean, basically your enemies have to face these giant swirling masses of flesh filled with their friends, that explode in a chain reaction like a giant antimatter meat grenade. So pro tip: throw your spinny meat trap all over the place and watch it explode.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 00:52:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could try asking r/Deftones</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 00:08:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-19 00:04:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly, my brain feels like mush.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-21 23:45:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 19:59:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's nuts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-25 10:19:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still a virgin but those eyes say you cry after sex.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 02:39:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pansexual essentially means you're attracted to everyone, regardless of gender or sex. Source: GF is pan, dated some girls and had a crush on a transgender person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 08:29:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I missed my chance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 17:52:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually uh, my hair is just like that. Mine Is really a grown out undercut. I have curly hair so it can get really long but still stay somewhat manageable if you're vigilant. Anyway, after the shower I dry my hair with a towel and then dry it with the space heater in my room (I don't have a hairdryer, but hey I got a shit ton of compliments on my hair so I guess it works). TLDR: curly hair and dry it with hot hair</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-28 05:58:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe they didn't want to bring down the mood? Idk, i'd hate to be in the middle of a concert and then remember that one of your favorite artists is dead. But that's just me :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-28 08:14:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, that clears it up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-01 05:46:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>They left plenty, not much has survived the change however.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-01 06:59:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Native American culture is a rich and vibrant one. However, most of the stories, the techniques, and the ways of Native Americans were passed through oral tradition. Many did not have written languages, as close tribal ties and alternate forms of communication (smoke signals for example) rendered written language useless. You were either close enough to others to simply talk to one another, or too far away to yell at each other. However this lack of written culture made Natives vulnerable. It started with the instigation of tribal conflicts, European settlers pitting tribes against each other, sometimes aiding the more helpful ones with guns and craft goods. This also opened the gateway to western indoctrination and religious persecution. Those Native American tribes that conformed to Christian Ideals survived (most of the time). The tribe I descend from, the Pascua Yaqui, were one of the tribes to do this. We were persuaded into religious conformity by the Spanish, through this conformity many of our oral traditions survived, but they still had been twisted to also include a Christian aspect. Hell, [just look at our flag.](http://www.crwflags.com/fotw/images/x/xa-pasqua.gif) It essentially came down to this, smaller tribes were absorbed by stronger cooperative ones, and in turn those tribes became the subjects of European influence, and eventually domination. [Indian boarding schools](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_Indian_boarding_schools) are an example of this. Native Americans who were not killed by disease, who conformed to European ideals, and who weren't massacred by the thousands survived. Native Americans left plenty of culture, but what wasn't erased by a tide of European imperialism was slowly choked out through old age and the indoctrination of Indian youth. It all came to this: Native Americans were stepping stones for the Europeans, those that were shaky and troublesome were removed, and the ones that stood still and obeyed were kept in place, but still stepped all over; above all this, culture came second for the Europeans. Edit: aww, thanks for the gold! I hoped my next gilding would be a funny joke, but it always comes back to genocide :p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-01 07:01:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Precisely</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-01 08:52:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>You misunderstand, what I meant was that written language rarely developed among Native Americans because it was sparsely needed in our way of life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-01 09:01:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand. If I was any more Yaqui my life would be drastically different. It's mind boggling that this cultural destruction continued so far into the present. I'm sparsely proud of my country.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 18:18:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's such a shorty sentiment too. Like, since when do I "owe" you grandkids? At the very end of things, the parents are going to have to take care of the children, and the grandparents only get to see them at their best, kinda like pets. I've seen and handful of friends have kids/ get married before they were ready and the parents wonder why they're children are depressed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 23:41:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which was the basis for the name of the Deftones album *Saturday Night Wrist*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[WP] You wake up in your apartment with tattoos all over your body like Memento, they read "fuck Dave" and "Avacado Ranch".</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-05 02:10:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-05 03:34:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like you had a hunch and went for it, in surprised no one else caught on to the clothes and stuff. Sharp eye!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-06 21:00:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly the main appeal to me and my friends is that they're so ridiculous and over the top that it's enjoyable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-06 23:18:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is pretty much the plot of All Tomorrows. Genetic meddling of the defeated until they become nothing but animals unaware of their past for millions of years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-06 23:20:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, if you cheat level up past 63 the game freaks out and the scaling increases dramatically, which is how you get hands of thousands of bandits</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-06 23:53:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least you can high five someone without them running away</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 07:24:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a few others out there that deal with the same topic, Evolution by Stephen Baxter comes to mind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 17:28:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me to thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 17:28:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me to thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 05:34:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Not paying taxes makes me a good business man" -Donald Trump So what is it now Donald?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-16 07:11:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I doubt they hated each other or anything, It was mostly Jon wanting to do his own thing. Also it doesn't seem like Jontron had visited Stormfront territory around that time, it all seems so recent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-16 21:53:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same here! The letters in my words also connect too, it's probably a holdover from cursive class in 3rd grade, now I write in this weird half print half cursive font</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 03:53:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/dadjokes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 05:29:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Woah I didn't catch that. That's clever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 07:31:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually kind of like this one. Like there's no penalty for not upvoting. Just he prospects of cozy good sleeps and no "you'll never sleep comfortably again" or something.thus is how these should be done Edit: I mean me too thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-21 07:34:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll always upvote drake and Josh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 18:44:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>A surprise to be sure, but a welcome one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 04:59:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is this from? Edit: Jesus Christ guys I just want to know if it's real or fake</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 07:30:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>The best part of waking up is folgers in your cup</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 07:32:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's embedded in my mind over here in Oregon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 21:06:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I figured as much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-30 19:07:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>My grandpa met him once, it's kind of a long story so if anyone wants to hear about it just ask, there's also one about Janis Joplin Edit: alright here it's goes So my grandpa loved our near San Francisco in a town called Petaluma not far from the city. San Fran being the busy city it is, got a lot of foot traffic from the 60's movements and plenty of famous bands of that era. My Papa (I call him papa) and his navy buddies heard that the one and only Jimi motherfucking Hendrix was in town. My papa was psyched, he was a super fan of what he called "acid rock". He was really into Blue Ouster Cult, Janis Joplin, Bread, The Eagles, you name it. So my Papa and his navy buddies arrive at the concert in downtown San Fran and the place is PACKED. They can't even get into the place. "Alright, whatever." They all say. For a while they all decide to just hang around the stadium and listen to the music from the outside in their cars, and when it all wrapped up they would go home. You see my Papa got kinda bored of this, he told his buddies he was gonna take a walk around the stadium for a while, see if he could catch the entourage or something. He reaches the back end of the stadium and he ends up behind the lot near this side door exit. The concert is beginning to wind down and he decides to start heading back. That is until he starts hearing the door open. He goes over to investigate and lo and behold, in all his glory, it's Jimi Hendrix, rock god. No entourage, no girls, no band, just him walking out of the door with his guitar and some gear. My Papa is freaking out! There's no one else around, everyone's packing up and leaving, but here he is with Jimi Hendrix right in front of him. My Papa runs up to him and says: "Hey! You're Jimi Hendrix!" And Jimi looks back at him and gives him a smile. "Yeah man." Then Jimi gets on a greyhound bus and leaves all by himself. Edit 2: okay the Janis Joplin one isn't as exiting but it's still kinda cool. Basically my Papa was trying to get this tattoo for the navy (the tattoo artist ended up becoming pretty famous in the San Fran area too, but I forgot his name). Anyway he walks into this tattoo parlor and on one of the seat sitting there is Janis Joplin. She was getting this tattoo on her shoulder/chest area. My Papa can safely say that he saw Janis Joplin's boob.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-30 19:47:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I dunno, I've told it a lot online and it never really got traction or visibility. I'm on mobile too so it takes way longer to type out a big story so I wanted to make sure people would actually want to read it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-30 22:11:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds familiar! I'll have to check in with Papa</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 09:03:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>You look pretty sick with it in a pony tail imo. But I'd definitely go with what the others are saying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 22:07:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think she would be sweet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-01 05:38:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn, this is some r/bestof material, really insightful. Thank you so much for sharing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-02 16:26:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>WHYDOPUTHEKIDSHOPONTHETABLE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 17:55:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Herpes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Jontron if he was a form of memory</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-04 22:12:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Issa me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-04 22:16:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 03:19:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Teen here. They're tacky and there advertising is annoying. Especially in my city where they've bought up a ton of ad space.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 07:24:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly I loved every chapter that had nothing to do with the Joads. The turtle was a great representation of the hopelessness and suffering of the era. I also loved the chapter with the car salesman. His rapid thoughts and dwindling, trying to keep his only lifeline alive. The Joads were well written, but super boring.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 00:46:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perhaps you could spend influence on a cover up of your atrocities so that the galaxy never knows. This could start an event chain on the cover up, or on the opposite side, an event chain where you uncover and investigate the cover up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 01:26:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>YouTube</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 03:55:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you at least keep the boss's number after your gf broke up with you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 21:36:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idk Se #241;or taco is pretty good. They make tongue just like abuella used too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-08 21:18:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apparently he was later diagnosed with bipolar disorder as well as an increased vulnerability to drug addiction. He was more or less suicidal for a good part of his life. I don't believe that he really valued his life al that much in the first place</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-10 18:34:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>My grandpa used to work on helicopters in the marines. One time a guy was working on a rotor and got his ring stuck on the machinery. It pulled his finger off, along with all the tendon and meat and bone from the inside of his arm/finger. During training they took it out of formaldehyde and showed it to the new recruits. Needless to say, don't wear rings when working on machinery.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 02:54:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like a bad series of bugs or something. Usually the game isn't like this. Something probably broke with the AI in your game and has caused this. You should probably start a new game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What was the British popular opinion during the period of the American Civil war? How did they react?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 22:00:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 22:03:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, a failure reference, it's been a while actually.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 07:45:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Push it forward or maybe go a little more messy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 05:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought you said ransom notes and I was very confused.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 21:02:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go for it, you have he face shape for it too, plus that awesome beard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 18:52:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, there IS the end of the cycle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 18:55:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>The ISB mod has some sweet super weapons, planet destroyers, star destroyers, planet eaters, extinction level event super weapons. One of my favorite mods.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 19:07:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup! At least in my experience. I tended to be ahead of the curb when it came to try so I didn't get to see them use a lot of the planet destroying stuff (a lot were xenophiles) but they used all the ships in the tech tree</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 04:17:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any idea what period he was involved in? You could start from there and work your way into the types of weapons used. For example, many healthy soldiers were struck with the after effects of Agent Orange post-Vietnam.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 04:23:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dexter did it well, it was kept consistent and there was a solid reason every time it was absent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 05:59:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wanted to be the guy who put olives on pizza. It didn't pan out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 06:59:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe she got abducted  #128125;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 16:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, I was glad they at least kept it the focus of the show for a reasonable period of time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 23:03:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 19:40:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Integer overflow. It stops counting after awhile</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 00:23:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>^^^</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 23:51:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah, it's all good reb</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 00:07:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Asking the real questions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 06:52:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought I was in r/crappydesign at first but then I realized it was a completely different language. Either way congrats</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 16:10:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh yikes my bad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 19:56:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wrong sub dude</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 01:42:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Quintin Tarantino foot fetish</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 08:27:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wrong sub it looks like</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 05:03:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please... I need my meme fill.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-12 02:25:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>This has more upvotes than the actual post. I hope you're proud</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-12 08:01:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friends dad was the screenwriter/ storyboard guy for Gun. I hear it's pretty good?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 22:10:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Triggered much?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 22:13:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, that was easy lmao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 22:14:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah, in pretty fine actually. You're the one who doesn't have to respond</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 22:18:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-19 06:54:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't forget Dave Grohl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-19 16:32:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah you're right. I consider him a part of it because of his role in nirvana. But as a frontmen he didn't get to shine way later. Still he's an absolutely awesome guy and I'd hate to see him go. For now though it seems he's doing alright :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-22 22:10:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>So no preexisting conditions then?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 00:02:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure I want a trail of organs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 01:03:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I crushed on her for years until one day we walked through a park and went down on each other. We've been together almost two years now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 01:30:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like the idea of some ex Microsoft employee thinking "Finally, I can get rid of this stupid ugly hat" that he got at a work formal. Little did he know that years later it would be posted on Reddit for sweet karma because of it's A E S T H E T I C</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 20:19:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>It reminds me of an E.E Cummings poem</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 23:54:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's another available job for a person who might not otherwise find one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 00:52:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right? I see a lot of bashing on gas pumpers in this thread. It's just another cheap easy job, and I don't see how more jobs that improve quality of life and don't actually affect much else are that bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 09:04:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like they took it from some other page and were too innocent to figure out what it meant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 09:07:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which makes me worried, because I love the Crow, but I hope people don't think I'm going as a juggalo for Halloween this coming October</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 01:09:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's a fairly interesting dilemma. Despite the damage Trump could do, he's a weak politician that's failed to live up to many of his promises if he gets the boot we're stuck with Pence. Pence is an established politician with plenty of party loyalty. He could very effectively execute whatever the GOP has in store for America. So the question is, do we prefer a gridlocked and incapable leading party? Or one that can swiftly and effectively achieve its goals. I'm not entirely sold on either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 01:56:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>My one question about pence is whether or not he would be in on the Russia operation. I wonder if he would continue communication or go strict instead. He's been staying out of the media spotlight for now, which can gives me the idea that he either doesn't want the media to know what he's doing, or he wants to separate himself from trump in the event that he is impeached.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-01 06:02:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dad works there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-01 06:03:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>His daughter is the superintendent there now, my dad works under her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-01 09:08:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, it all kinda depends on how your hair acts or moves. It looks like you hair is pretty darn straight. As far as thickness goes I'd say you're somewhere in the middle. Essentially there is a lot you could do here. If you wanted to keep your long glorious mane but change it up you could go for he man bun look, but it's kinda falling out of style and it gets perceived as kinda hipsterish. So that leaves us with chopping your hair off. I would start with maybe six inches? Enough that it covers your eyes. From there you can see what you can work with. You want to leave room for mistakes and experimenting, so that's why you leave a bit more hair than you'd be comfortable with. Once you've got the general idea down start cutting and chopping yo your specifications or you could skip all this and head to your local barber for advice/ a cut. Your hair seems pretty straight so I'd invest in a bit of hair product. I tend to prefer matte pomaded because they look natural and have a good strong hold without clipping your hair up for getting it shiny and greasy. Just remember to play it safe and find out what you're comfortable with. You've got plenty of hair to experiment on :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 18:15:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>HEAD LIKE A HOLE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 18:31:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>BOW DOWN BEFORE THE ONE YOU SERVE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 01:18:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>From what we can tell the chick in the video is homeless and does porn for money. She must have gotten pretty cleaned up before the video because she was actually pretty good looking. Anyway, they get to fucking and the guy behind the camera asks if she has anything in there. She says it might be the anal beads. They pull out the beads and they have shit on the very end of them. So that's gross. He let's her get cleaned up and they try for a round 2. Apparently it still feels like there's something in there. He puts a finger in and low and behold, an entire condom deep inside her vagina. He remarks that, well, no wonder her vagina has been hurting, there's a condom in their and she might have a yeast infection/toxic shock. She is at a loss for words as to how it got there. The guy is done, he pays her for the video, and they clean off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-06 08:23:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought that was outed as a hoax to discredit him? Someone correct me if I'm wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-06 08:37:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you. Currently in high school with averageish body (actually getting some muscle here and there, still working on it). I used to be a pretty chubby awkward guy in middle school which created a lot of confidence issues throughout the rest of my life. Even after getting the girl I always crushed on since 7th grade, losing 40+ pounds from joining rowing (not doing that anymore, trying to get back progress), and turning my habits and body chemistry around. I still feel pretty inadequate. I know I shouldn't worry, in fact I've been feeling a lot better in the past year or two. I grew into my body a bit better, I'm relatively attractive now, and I've been tying to keep a positive attitude. But every once and awhile that fat depressed kid from middle school comes back and makes me feel like I'm not good enough again. It's honestly why I started following this sub, I thought I needed motivation. It's motivated me for sure. For a while it was for all the wrong reasons. Now, I'm a little bit healthier about it. I don't know where this is going or where it came from. But I appreciate people like you, who remind vulnerable young guys like me that it's okay to not be a fucking muscle on muscle dinosaur of a man yet. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-06 08:38:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right, I remember reading a TIL about how he donated to Jewish community funds and programs also. Seemed he was a pretty alright guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-06 18:08:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Freud?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-07 09:06:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bio ware is losing its grip a bit. I could still see them recovering in the future perhaps. Bungie seems to be on a good track now for destiny 2. The first destiny seems pretty rushed by publishing (IMO it was probably activision, the lore of destiny was fairly deep) but I feel like they can really pull through on the second one if they are left alone. Not sure about valve at this point</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-07 19:34:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Down with the false Brendan!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 19:24:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's sounds like a desperate and lonely person. Seems like you won in the end there. Just ignore her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 23:25:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The year is 2054 We have long abandoned insults through primitive sound vibrations. All insults are passed through smell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-09 17:42:47</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128293; #128680;HOLD UP #128680; #128293;  #128064; #128166;and get ready for DADDIES mummy CUMMIES #128166; #128064;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 18:43:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Looks like we don't have to end up dying in a jungle. But you guys can go die in a desert though, don't worry, it's for WMDs."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 19:03:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depends on what they mean. Oregon has long been a refuge for white nationalists. Partly due to the lack of African Americans/other races in the area since Oregon straight up banned blacks from entering during the civil war.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 19:05:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>"We learn from the past, to understand the present, to make a better future."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 19:13:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least he's cute.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-13 01:36:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have those same plates... and I ate grilled cheese on them today...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-15 04:18:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't say that!! Never give up!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 00:10:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also communism memes are funny to anyone on any political side of the spectrum. Whether you believe in it or not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 04:14:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it me or does skeet look like Morrissey</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 20:27:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is no content</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-25 04:54:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Their shells are in fact the carapace of a wormhole generator. You can tell because swirl=portal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-25 05:16:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Common misconception. Snails are worms that are bred for their spacetime altering properties. Rookie mistake</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-25 11:37:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I hate Yemen stealing whores."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-26 01:09:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Moreso galactic multiple personality disorder</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-26 17:46:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>The very old man- Hum Shits fucked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-26 17:53:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>"He doesn't talk to me anymore. I worry."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-26 17:54:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>It gets better over time. The first time is never good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-26 21:54:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>hush bb. es ok</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 06:46:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you think we should be able to play AS Waluigi? Or perhaps we're a young buccaneer learning the ropes from our eccentric captain Waluigi?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 06:47:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also, i'm more than willing to help with writing for the game!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 07:48:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/seaofgreed join us</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hi</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 20:07:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 22:24:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>no</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 22:25:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>wait yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 23:07:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>no</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 23:07:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>wait yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 23:12:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>no</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 23:12:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>wait yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 19:27:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same here with Oregon except we also have AIDS and disappointed Californians.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 23:39:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can we talk about how cool Ballas looks? It's nothing like I expected but it looks so fucking awesome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-09 00:03:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here you go](https://twitter.com/captaindumac/status/883726670791888896)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-09 00:44:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>ALL ABOARD THE HYPE TRAIN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-09 07:32:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think your buddy was messing with you. No one buys the starter packs. All the "premium" currency can be traded in game. You buy literally everything without spending any real world money.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 00:17:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>He looks like some kind of God, which is what was somewhat implied through all the orokin lore. Hedonistic and fantastical displays of power culminating in an eccentric and power worshiping empire.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 03:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>It wasn't about physical pain. As other commenters said, it was more about the souls disconnect from God and their ironic cruel punishments.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 08:51:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's he saying?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 08:54:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are enemies that can do some instadeath/massive damage if you're not careful. Corpus techs come to mind. Especially once you get to high levels support builds down to buffing, debugging, and healing/energy regain. So yes, there is a spot for support, it just depends on how you play, where you're playing, and what the objective is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 10:30:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well my name is Brandon so this meme belongs to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 15:43:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>We form the B R A N D O N C O L L E C T I V E</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 15:43:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>See other reply</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 15:43:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey I'll have you know my mother loves me very much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 16:45:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like I need to go to prison.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 21:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Moms white and dads half white/ Yaqui Mexican. Can confirm most poor folk do this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 07:40:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always say it. Grew up in Oregon but was born in California and raised by Cali parents up here. I idiot call it Devils Night because of The Crow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 11:15:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn we really need new failure content</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 09:20:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you got any uh... spare Saryn Prime Neuroptics... hit me up...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 20:07:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, RNG hasn't been kind to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 23:23:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use a cheap wireless Logitech controller. I find controllers are better for movement in warframe. You can find them at your local Best Buy, Target, or any other outlet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 15:09:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like the idea, but I worry about losing the freedom to pick and craft the empire that I desire simply because I don't want to deal with ethics attraction being an issue. It might lock people into certain builds or even create a sort of meta build that people strive for. But this is all just my opinion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 16:00:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I typed kind of a long winded response to this, but I thought it would make sense if I just cut it short. I want to play how I want to play. I don't want to have to micromanage my civics. Because if repression in this game has taught me anything, it's that it does nothing. That spiritualist faction isn't going anywhere. Until we can have more options to control factions, I'm not in favor of having my governing ethics challenged so early in the game, especially since I'm playing as an authoritarian/xenophobic/militarist star empire. I'm already forced to micromanage my ethics attraction because of how hard it is to get rid of factions; and yes, I've tried appeasing them, however xenophilia isn't exactly my top priority when cleansing xeno home worlds. Listen, I love Stellaris because it offers immense freedom to create your own story and form your own fun little headcanon. Don't get me wrong, I admire difficulty. But it's so easy for people like me to fall into another micromanaging min/maxing trap. It's just that, I don't really see a need for this. It feels like something unnecessary. Edit: Don't get me wrong, I understand the point of the mod, but I would much prefer this to be a toggle-able feature that one could turn on and off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 16:09:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah it make me feel pretty awful reading this thread. My dad was a chiropractor, and a flamed good one at that. He never practiced on infants and never spouted any healing bullshit. He'd help people with nerve issues (he got a lot of truckers with nerve damage) back issues, and muscle problems. I always saw Chiropractic as a more practical form of medicine, but he always made sure that if someone needed medication, they got it. Does chiropractics cure cancer? No. I have, and he never has believed this. There are benefits however, and chiropractics have heir merits in solving everyday muscle and bone issues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 01:20:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's the fail here? It just looks like a nice picture.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 07:30:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>The dude in the back looks like he's about to knock out the dude in the front.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 01:36:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pacers is amazing. I have three separate loaodouts for pure rad/mag/corrosive damage. Each one works like a charm and the damage snowballing is incredible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 18:00:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's good the first time too. It's very exiting. Just don't hype up losing your virginity. The best thing you can do is to have fun with it, and have it with someone you can trust.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 01:17:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>By not jacking ourselves off about it on the internet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 09:53:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Increased accuracy while aiming" How did I not hear about this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 08:15:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lord strong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 08:52:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>what do I win</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 08:57:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry I suck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 09:03:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey my names Brandon and I was born in August</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 09:08:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/memeframe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 02:55:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god. It's too late for you. Run.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 19:07:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same thing happened to me over a summer. She was a psycho bitch. A hoes a hoe my man. Best thing you can do is forget about her completely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-05 09:08:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>You absolutely should tell your boyfriend. Also, alert the local authorities and your schools authorities. I recommend you get a rape kit down immediately. I'm so sorry this happened to you and if you need anyone to talk to we are all here to support you. Edit: it doesn't matter who this guy is, if he has raped you, that doesn't make him a good person. Remember that. You're not a slut and please don't listen to whatever he has threatened.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-08 00:37:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's the various companies present in both films. In the background lots of cloverfield a medical research company (tagruato I believe) was drilling for a certain substance at the bottom of the ocean. In 10 cloverfield lane the logo/name of this company or one of its subsidiaries can be seen on a letter in the bunker</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-08 00:39:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It wasn't the satellite, there is a lot of background lore going on in cloverfield that circles around a shady company preforming deep ocean drilling operations</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-08 04:39:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wanna pull a Kenobi and drop down with a nice "hello there"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Title suggesting interesting content</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 02:02:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Statement humorously opposed to the title that you were left to believe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 05:25:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or maybe he's just a chill guy who warns people of dangers in the road Maybe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 06:22:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to give him a hug</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 18:42:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>You look like the daughter of Keanu Reeves. That's not a bad thing though, trust me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 21:23:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm nearly a thousand hours in the game and I'm only MR 12. I've been playing since early beta. It's all about what you want from a game. I wanted fun</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-17 04:13:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't most parents know the sex of the child beforehand through ultrasound?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-17 04:16:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, interesting!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 07:33:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wrong sub, damn failure needs to put out another album</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We need some regular content guys.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 07:36:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>This sub was created for the band Failure. But this is sub is so dang inactive that people have just started positing fail pictures on here, oblivious to the fact that this is a band subreddit. We could use a mod change or some mentions on the music sub's or ANYTHING. Just something to get the blood pumping in here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 18:04:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember it getting stuck into a wall once and it was actually a saw blade looking thing. I guess they changed it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 21:29:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right? It's so painfully obvious it's satire.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 23:39:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>We could start a new sub, something like r/failureband ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 01:00:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds good. We'll see how it goes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 04:27:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ammo drum is a super common/cheap mod that's barely used on any builds. So I'm pretty sure he's joking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 23:57:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>My great grandfathers last words were "Where's my damn eggs?" He died instantly from either a heart attack or stroke I believe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 19:31:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>"So, you come here often?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 00:22:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks pretty good actually. You might want a matte hair gel for a more uniform look. If you're looking for slick I'd recommend normal gel or a tiny bit of coconut oil to moisturize.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 02:12:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>GROFIT UNTO THE VOID</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 21:55:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>They tried that. It didn't work because people would realize they were in a simulation, thus the matrix wouldn't work and people would attempt to break free. So they created a world just like they one they knew before and it works almost perfectly. There is a long running fan theory that the matrix is actually multi leveled. Essentially the matrix we see in the movie works for most, but for members of the resistance, the 'real world' as we are lead to believe is actually another level of believable simulation in order to contain those who resist the main matrix simulation. Basically the whole time, Neo and the gang were living in another sim. Still, it's just a fan theory, but fun none the less.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-25 11:47:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well fuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 19:57:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>[My money's on Mayweather ](https://imgur.com/gallery/nqQK6)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 01:13:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reminds me of e.e Cummings. I wrote poetry too and took a lot of inspiration from him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 03:56:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the beach, Oregon has lots of flora/grasslands leading up to the sand</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 18:11:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, she can't be a flawless demigod though. Her loneliness and isolation is a part of her character that she overcomes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 21:56:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you think of color? Do things have different shades when you visualize things? Sorry if it's a silly question.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 22:01:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same exact situation over here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 17:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait, but how do they know which mans penis will open up to accept the other mans penis?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 00:00:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Remindme!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 01:34:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>This changes everything</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 23:56:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can get frost prime free with twitch prime I believe. Unless it's not going on anymore</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 01:41:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>We didn't start the fire!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 04:43:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That reminds me of that episode of the office where Andy got punched by a 5th grade girl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 09:12:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>People would rather off themselves than hang out with me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-11 22:08:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lee farms?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 18:01:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a solid, reliable gun that will take you far. It'll get the job done for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 18:09:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, it has great status and crit, but it take a a bit of forms and dedication to get to super-endgame levels. It's a great gun but it takes a bit of dedication</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 03:48:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Regina Spektor is awesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 19:03:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>*jazz for your soul*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 07:50:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>WTC?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 04:00:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>My grandpa went in to get a tattoo when he was younger. I believe it was something kind of dumb, but he had just gotten into the navy. He walks in and he sees Janis Joplin being worked on, somewhere around her chest area, with a boob or two hanging out. Better yet, the tattoo artist was Lyle Tuttle, a famous artist in San Fran at the time. So it was kind of a two in one. I always found it funny, because the tattoo he got was something stupid like a dagger, that he eventually got partially removed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 22:12:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd recommend losing the pony tail. Your face is already a good shape but the ponytail makes it look a bit elongated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 23:08:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have a lot of hair to work with so you have quite a few options. [Something like this](http://gto-live.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/04/Easy-cool-blonde-hairstyles-for-teen-guys-or-college-student.jpg) maybe. At the end of the day it's up to you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 04:04:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dad calls it the pendejo. Typically some at parties. It's everything you can find on the counter mixed together in one drink. Never again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 04:46:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Royal T. Funk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 10:42:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always believed that Gordon's last name was an on the nose nod to his role in the story. He is the emancipator of man. Gordon Free-Man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 19:13:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fucking accurate. I had a teacher who dressed exactly like this, all she ever would do is gossip with other teacher and popular students. I'm glad I don't have her anymore, ugh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 21:29:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a drawing, but the model actually looks like that when you look at his page. It's insane</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 10:04:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Almost makes me regret writing homoerotic porn between him and Gordon Ramsay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 20:24:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The return of the king</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 23:57:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 09:26:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I like weed, but fuck poor people."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 22:31:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>They hath crucified the lord. His suffering for our sins will be forever remembered.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 11:25:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/incels</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 12:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're missing a bit of your bottom lip, but otherwise I think it's pretty great!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 23:51:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/nocontext</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 06:20:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, if I bought art from an artist, then I own the art. However, I can't go around saying that I created it, and take all the credit. Makes sense to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>JOY DIVISION-BACK AGAIN (xpost r/nocontextpics)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 05:23:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 22:39:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same. Most of my friends are girls.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 23:50:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>"**DEATH IS A PREFERABLE ALTERNATIVE TO COMMUNISM**"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 07:55:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>For real though Jim Croce is great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 23:51:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're either super cool or total creeps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 02:35:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's kinda fucked that my very first thought was "Oh, three people. That's not that bad." I hate being desensitized.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 06:26:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like a shithead. But people like that never make it around normal people in the world. Whether he likes it or not, people aren't going to put up with his Shit anymore at some point. It's already happening actually, as you mentioned he is angered by having to pay for his own items and things. Life if going to kick him in the butt eventually, and if you really want to get back at him, just let him be. He's a dumb kid. You're an adult, no matter how low you may think of yourself. It's best to just treat him the way he is, a dumb kid. You have your other brother, and you seem like a much better person, and that's what makes you strong. Who knows? Perhaps he'll grow out of it. Or maybe he'll stay that way, and end up miserable. Either way, things will get better for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 06:42:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe you do have feelings for her, but your guilt gets in the way of things? She has some deep feelings for you. You seem to have some for her too. Maybe try giving it another chance for a little while. Perhaps things will be better? Perhaps worse? But the important thing is that you know. You wont be left with a life of "what if?".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 06:45:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should talk to your friend about it. Start with her talking to you first, and move to you getting feelings for her. Just be honest. Because it's hard to fault someone for that. It might even help him get over a love that was unrequited in the first place.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 06:54:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Confidence is key. At the risk of sounding cheesy, you've got to believe in yourself! You gotta get out there and make something of yourself. Live your life, have some experiences! Most guys who think they're ugly are a haircut and a gym membership away from being total studs. Remember that, because besides those two things, confidence is the crown jewel that ties the stud machine together. Like what the other guy said above, you gotta get out there and start talking. It's gonna be awkward, it's gonna suck, but you know what else sucks? Crippling loneliness. Best of luck to you my man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 07:07:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Sociopaths almost ever believe they have anything wrong with them/ that what they've done is wrong. 2. Narcissists never even raise the question in the first place. We've established that you aren't either of those because you're here. You were a kid deprived of love and support, who grew up around jealously and a rocky marriage. You coped through others. You needed validation, love, support. Things you believed were lacking from your family life. Stuff like this is incredibly common. Hell, one could say you have mommy/daddy issues. Which isn't something that you should be ashamed of. Because it's not your fault. You're coming to terms with it now, and that's good. The best thing you can do is spend some time making others happy. Give a homeless person some money. Send a few anonymous PM's to people who need them. Offer support to those who need it. Trust me. Making others feel happy is one of the best feelings in the world. It is leagues healthier than manipulating others for validation. I'm proud of you for coming forward and talking about this man. Because that's the first step. You've done it all by yourself! Stages your own intervention. Now, what are you going to do about it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 07:09:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ride the wave man! Enjoy love! I'm really happy for you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 07:13:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>On the other hand, you might die. Drugs are a slippery slope man. I mm sure you've the spiel before. No ones gonna stop you. But you have people who care about you, who love you, who don't want to see you get hurt. At the end of the day it's up to you. What matters more? People who love you? Or Xanax? I've seen a lot of people I know start on prescription meds and get worse. But your decision is YOUR decision. Just be careful out there man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 16:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds like a good plan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 20:16:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I knew a guy named *Spirithawk.* He had a long ponytail and worked with heavy machinery all day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 07:31:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It had some sense of balance to it. All warframe sand weapons would start at level zero. As the game went on you would rapidly increase in level, unlocking your abilities and mods that you previously had on. At the end of the round, players had all their mods and levels up and that's when things started to get a bit unbalanced. But the gradual ramping up of the chaos was super fun for me at least.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 18:52:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not gay if it's a three way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 06:59:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>In my game the khergits have nearly wiped out the sarranids.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 08:03:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>People play him as this fanatic egotistical drug maniac or something. I think the doors movie has a play in that, as it portrayed him as a total dick. He was a shy, bookish, misunderstood person who's only outlet was music.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 08:16:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ian Curtis. I don't think he would have become a worse person per say, but his epilepsy and other issues were already on track to reduce him to a husk. It's tragic the way his life went.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 23:49:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idk hitler is kinda up there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 04:01:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm always afraid of falling into this stereotype. Mom's white but my dad's half Mexican/Yaqui from my grandma. I inherited a lot of the traits from that side of the family (dark curly hair, cheekbones, almond eyes, tan really fast and dark, etc,)and I grew up around a lot of Mexican culture since my mother was adopted. However, where I live there isn't too much sun so I end up getting pale. Sometimes people thought I was totally white, but other times they thought I was something else, I never really felt like I fit into either category. Heck, I don't even think I fit into a mixed race category. I'm kind of just stuck in this weird place where I was never white enough for white kids but never ethnic enough for ethnic kids. I just started telling people I'm mixed since it's too much of a bother to explain all this weird internal racial identity crises stuff going on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 10:33:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Stay tuned" low key getting the feeling that she might call out Tarantino soon, that or someone else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 04:23:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>[your resident S I C K B O Y E calling in](https://imgur.com/a/NaHq8)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 06:55:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>West Linn?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 19:08:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>- Jaden Smith</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 05:06:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Genma Onimusha?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 05:16:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's more so about there being a combination of numbers required to unlock it; not referring to the mathematical term.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 05:19:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it just takes cash</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 06:07:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Part time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 06:21:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/a/G9vnk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 23:09:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your hairs gusty? As in like a gust of wind?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 08:06:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ugh good strawberries are amazing when oh find them. Soft enough to bite through without effort, but too soft like they've been getting old for a while. That and the perfect level of sweetness. When I was a kid I used to dip strawberries in sugar; whenever I find good strawberries I can forgo the sugar all together.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 09:46:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>On many ancient statues, yes, the eyes were painted on. Through time and age much of the paint was worn away. This is roughly how they would've looked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 02:05:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Out of curiosity, what did you have for lunch?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 02:11:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pepperoni taco? Is that just stack shell with, like, pizza toppings in it? Or is it a sandwich with crunched up taco shell and pepperoni in it? I may have found my next recipe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 08:58:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>He died of pneumonia I believe. That or something related. He gave an extended inauguration speech lasting something like 5 hours, then apparently died of the ensuing sickness he acquired from it. Or that's how the story goes at least.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 04:47:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, the same thing happened to Luke in the OT. There's was very little training for how skilled he was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 08:15:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shoutout to Vice President Jumbo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 21:07:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this and e.e. cummings poem?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:10:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's like PEMDAS it's okay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 18:34:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your hair is pretty rockin' right now. But I could totally see the Dev Patel haircut looking good on you. Sick jacket by the way!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 23:34:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 23:36:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can see the way I want to go back to my house and I'm just not sure what to do with my life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 03:32:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>F</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 09:23:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same old faux "genetic proof" and bullshit statistics they pump out to subtly prove how superior the white race is. What really gets me is that oftentimes people point to developing countries as proof of how low and stupid other races are, nevermind the fact that those very countries have been raped and pillaged by Europeans for for centuries at a time. It's a cesspool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 08:22:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>The reaction kinda depends on the person. I was stung by one in Hawaii awhile back. I stepped on it while waking in the beach so it got some good contact on my foot. I remember it feeling like stepping on a hot frying pan. My leg felt fine but I could see blue streaks which I'm pretty sure we're my veins and capillaries up and down my leg. There was also remembers of the toxic "darts" that they lodge into your skin on my foot. Besides some sensitivity and swelling it turned out fine. However a few months later I remember these "holes" of dead skin showing up in my foot around where it was stung. It looked like someone had straight up cored tiny bits of my foot like one does a tree. So I guess I just had some dead flesh or something hanging around in there. You'll probably live, and a graze while swimming probably hurts like a bee stings but maybe worse. You're not likely to die unless you have an allergic reaction on some type. 3/10 would not recommend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 07:34:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bot spotted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 08:01:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your account was created four hours ago and you've reposted the same story to two unrelated threads, and another story to two serrated threads as well. If you're not a bot, it's just an account running on a script to farm karma that you check every once in a while to make sure no one is suspicious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 21:38:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idris Elba lookin like a snacc</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 07:17:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>When we talk about racism/sexism, we often talk about it as a force that only disadvantages others. Whereas, in truth, it advances and advantages the dominant class (in America, straight white males). So while you aren't actively oppressing anyone, not caring, not listening, and so on and so forth is you living comfortably in the world privilege has given you. I don't think your racist or anything, but the issue is that people don't feel comfortable, or feel downright angry, when someone points out that they may have an advantage. People don't like admitting they have it easy sometimes. I'll give you a not-so-mentioned example. Black dolls. I knew a woman who was trying to find a black doll for her mixed race child. She went to six different stores, nearly every doll was white (this was a few years ago). When she mentioned this to a friend, her friend responded "Just go on amazon, it's easy." And that's privilege and comfort in action. It's dismissive. It's not a matter of availability, it's more so a matter of principle. She shouldn't HAVE to go to six different stores to find one single doll that isn't white. So while someone can not be racist, they can be unaware of what makes heir lives so much easier and comfortable than someone of another race, gender, religion, etc. As for safe spaces, I don't necessarily believe in them. They exist because people can't be adults and not be assholes. When people start being assholes to other groups of people, folks group up and talk inward amongst themselves. This isn't productive, but neither is being an asshole. What needs to happen is that people need to learn how to engage one another respectfully, or engage a disrespectful person in a disarming manor. Things like racism are invented institutions that have no bearing on the natural world, and this shouldn't matter in the first place. If we lived in a perfect world, we wouldn't talk about race because race wouldn't matter. But because those in charge, and those who would seek to gain power through racism seek to hurt and disenfranchise others, we must talk about race/gender/sexism etc. and continue to have these conversations, because for now they do have an impact on our lives. These are just my thoughts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 07:42:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>And yet, that's an assumption, isn't it? I don't much like my role as a mixed person. I don't like getting into arguments and confrontations about it with people. Are there people out there who like playing the victim? Sure. There's always going to be a vocal minority in any issue that likes to make things about themselves, or say the most inflammatory thing. What you have to remember is that the 5% doesn't represent the 95. Not all white people are racist, and not all "SJWs" are men hating neo-gender fascists. Most of what people want, in my experience, can be gained by just being kind all around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 16:39:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree. Before I came to my current thoughts on the matter I was quite the men's rights activist, and adamant about the things that disadvantage men in the world. I'm a bit more educated now, but many of my initial thoughts remain the same in light of the facts that prove them correct. Yes. Men have a harder time in family court. Yes. White men can be poor Yes. Universities/employers often times employ minorities for the sake of being diverse. That last point is something that irks me. Because while it's not exactly true in every respect (these scholarships are actually more difficult to achieve than one might think I.e affirmative action) the whole "we must employ minorities to appear diverse" thing is counterintuitive. It feeds into the exact reason why you're angry, it creates a resentment towards minorities when in fact the situation doesn't happen as often as you might think. It's also sort of degrading in a way. "Yes, I, the gracious white man, will of course hire this downtrodden brown person!" It's racist and shitty in it's own way, and I don't support hiring every minority just because you need to appear diverse. As for the whole black doll thing, I was giving an example of just every day privilege, not outright oppression. My friend in that story was white, and was rather concerned about the fact that her children won't grow up with at least a basic damn doll that looks like them, and rightfully angry at the dismissiveness and vitriol when she lamented about this to another. She just wants a damn doll. But if you need another example, I can give you another one. I'm sorry I can't finish this response, because I have to get going. But I'd absolutely love to keep talking about this with you. Because you seem like a well-to-do guy and you have a lot of opinions on the matter, is love to share with you some information that might change your mind. As well as some of my own personal experience. Because that's what it really comes down too. I can't every know completely what your life is like. And you can't do the same to mine. There's just the numbers, the facts, and the personal testimonies. If you need any reading, I highly recommend Te-Nahsi Cotes "Between the world and me". It's better than any of the other race books I have ever read, because it's essentially just personal experience. Cotes is an absolutely beautiful writer as well. I'll probably respond later, and when I'm not on mobile. Thanks for taking the time to respond though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 19:20:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Sins of summer sisters"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 09:21:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mexicans are multi ethnic people. Comprised of Iberian peninsula colonists and Native Americans (in most cases). Over time and with population growth the lines begin to blur over generations. In my case one of my relatives was a full blooded Native American, who married a Mexican. So in a sense I'm part Mexican, but more so Mexican/Native? I tend to go with the latter. Genealogy is fascinating stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 17:35:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get that. It's about a clean 50/50 for Native and "Mexican" for that side. I'm actually have a lot of white European in me (Mom is mostly Irish, dad is half European mutt) but since I look Mexican/Native and I was raised more Mexican I tend to go by mixed race. My dad and grandmother get mistaken for Polynesian and Asian a lot funnily enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 17:40:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, what I was trying to say is that the Native American genetics are more recent on my side, so me or my family never really considered ourselves fully Mexican in that sense, somewhere in between. You're correct on the cultural thing though, my Native relative was adopted from a young age, and never grew up around Yaqui/indigenous culture. Still, I passively research what's there and continue to support rights for Natives, considering my ancestors were actively exterminated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 23:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>They got rid of the genetic degradation of the kubrows I believe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 06:34:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dad processed this guy and the schizophrenic clinic he works at.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 06:45:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>The tunnels are more less real, and shanghai-omg occasionally took place, however it was not nearly as common as tour guides want you to think. They were mostly old shipping tunnels.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Renowned physicist Steven Hawking has died at 76.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 04:58:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 01:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Talking head and Ariel pink</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 05:07:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>-ee cummings</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 09:30:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>He definitely was one of the few in my option who could pull it off right. It never came across as heavy handed or unnecessary, the poetry and words itself are beautiful but the structure itself serves a purpose as a guide for the reader. I could talk about Cummings all day, he's absolutely one of my favorite poets.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 04:41:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy cow! I thought my great grandpa was the only one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Eyeofbaphomet</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 19:24:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 08:51:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>You called.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 19:46:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>We do have one! "Epicaricacy, deriving pleasure from the misfortunes of others"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 05:27:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually have a strain of local sativa that smells weirdly nice. Like pine almost, it's really helped out with smoking outside.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 08:20:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/unethicallifeprotips : start cutting yourself to get a sweet deal on new tattoos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 17:39:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Happened with me an XCOM. I had dreams which were actually fairly normal, however I and everything else could ONLY move in the XCOM tiles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 18:37:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chummy He #8217;s a gay receptionist my mom knows. He #8217;s perfectly normal. Just decided to change his name to chummy one day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 21:48:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still wouldn #8217;t be able to pay off student loans</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 22:48:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Optimal browning. Plentiful cheese. Diagonal slice. This one checks out boys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 11:18:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>In middle school, our yearbook (which was put together by faculty, contrary to high school) had  #8220;Blablah middle Shcool #8221; written on the side. Might have a picture somewhere. Still regret not ordering one, best way to end middle school ever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 18:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seconded</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 22:18:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>And they #8217;ll often end up losing a match because of it. I #8217;ve had people be the last person alive and only one other person. They #8217;ll take a solid minute looking at weapon skins and then get shot in the head from behind. Just play the game guys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 19:15:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>For legal states it #8217;s pretty much just over 21. I assume the normal no smoking areas apply to joints as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 23:42:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s a joke</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 17:03:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apparently, my great grandfathers last words were  #8220;Where #8217;s my damn eggs?! #8221; Before slumping into his chair and dying right there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 18:33:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Graduating, actually. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 09:27:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought I was the only one! My elementary school class took a field trip there once and at the reveal it was nothing but laughter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 19:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>The band got their name from a book about a section of a concentration camp called  #8220;joy division #8221;. Might be the same story you #8217;re thinking of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 21:21:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>If the movie had been excellent, would you still criticize the choice to move it to China? Imagine if it were an amazing movie, people would be lauding the setting change with praise as unique and genius. These kind of criticisms are baseless and highly dependent on the other qualities of the movie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 22:58:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, I was just assuming they made a movie about the book and that #8217;s what you saw</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 04:28:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which is why the point is redundant. It #8217;s not important to the quality of the movie, and obviously not an important enough of an issue in the video. So why complain about it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 02:24:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>What edit: what</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 08:10:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I understood the joke. But this video felt like it was made by an AI.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 08:53:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 03:15:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, if you don #8217;t want to see them you can leave if you want. You don #8217;t have to ask us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 22:27:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>You called</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anyone just wish to be a kid again?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 23:58:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just completely innocent, still loved and adored by everyone. Everything is new and incredible and your heart is so full of love. I miss it a lot, I feel like I missed out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 00:04:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Happed to me too, GF of three years. She was my absolute world. She wants a break, and she #8217;s open to being together in the future. But the issue is, when is that? It #8217;s a feeling based thing, not a precise date, and its killing me. I feel like I #8217;m just passing time and trying to make things go by as fast as possible so I can go back to her. I #8217;ve resorted to just drinking and smoking grass all night just to avoid crying myself to sleep every night. I haven #8217;t cried in a long time. I feel a physical pain, like my organs are slowly eating themselves up. Anyone else get this? Everything seems so pointless now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anyone else hit themselves?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 00:09:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tend to hit/punch myself, or throw myself against walls. The vast majority of people cut and there isn #8217;t a lot of advice on hitting. Last night I took a belt and whipped myself until my back was red. I was wondering if anyone is experiencing the same thing? Any advice? Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>