<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject8062</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 23:59:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hoping for braids or crochet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 22:42:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. While it's true that depression is a long term illness, the severity changes. That's why people can feel more depressed one week than another. I know that for me, a really bad day can easily trigger me into a depressive slump that takes ages to (partially) recover from. For those who aren't professionally diagnosed (for whatever reason), or are having a hard time coming to terms with their diagnosis/the fact that they have a mental health concern, reading comments like yours can quite easily stop them from seeking help, speaking about their experience, or continuing treatment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 10:31:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just pointing out that a lot of the language you use in this post is transphobic. Trans women *are* women, and you should probably back up your own words and remember/respect that in the language you use.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is this real? What do i do?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 12:27:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone, I found this Reddit (or subreddit) about a week ago and it's been super helpful. Im looking for advice/encouragement, so please help if you can. I'm posting here because my biggest concern is what my family will think, and I think/hope someone here will understand. I've spent the past 3 or so years trying to define my sexuality. In my third year of uni I started to feel more than friendship for a lot of the girls I knew and it was really hard to come to terms with that. I kept telling myself that it only happened when I was drunk, or that I don't fit the "mold" of what bisexual women were like. But time kept passing and I kept feeling the same way. I still feel that I'm trying to be someone I'm not, and that really this is all just me tricking myself into liking women (for what reason I have no idea lol). But another, more rational part of me says that it's okay and that it will be easier for me to just accept who I'm attracted to and find a way to live my life authentically. So here's the problem; I think a big reason that I feel so insecure in this is that I've only told people who don't really matter in the grand scheme of things. I've told a few friends and they've all been super accepting. But if they weren't, I know that I can always make new friends, you know? But I can't make a new family. I'm scared what when/if I tell them, they won't speak to me anymore, and that I might do serious damage to our family. We're already going through some tough stuff, and I don't want to add to the problem. Also my parents are super super Christian and I know the backlash will be terrible for me to deal with. This is such a source of anxiety and stress for me. I've fallen into bad patterns, and I want to stop. I have a feeling that being comfortable enough with myself to own my sexuality will help me in so many areas of my life, and I want to be open with my family because I love them, but I have no idea if it's the right thing to do. And what if I really am just making this all up in my head? Is exploring the truth worth hurting my parents? I'm sorry if this makes no sense, I really appreciate anything that anyone has to say. Tldr; I'm pretty sure I'm bi (but I also think I'm making it up lol), I'm tired of feeling like I'm hiding a part of myself and want to be honest with myself/fam, but I'm scared that things won't end well, and that I'm making a mistake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Im a bit confused...and worried. Looking for advice n</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 04:17:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone, I found this Reddit (or subreddit) about a week ago and it's been super helpful. Im looking for advice/encouragement, so please help if you can. I'm posting here because my biggest concern is what my family will think, and I think/hope someone here will understand. I've spent the past 3 or so years trying to define my sexuality. In my third year of uni I started to feel more than friendship for a lot of the girls I knew and it was really hard to come to terms with that. I kept telling myself that it only happened when I was drunk, or that I don't fit the "mold" of what bisexual women were like. But time kept passing and I kept feeling the same way. I still feel that I'm trying to be someone I'm not, and that really this is all just me tricking myself into liking women (for what reason I have no idea lol). But another, more rational part of me says that it's okay and that it will be easier for me to just accept who I'm attracted to and find a way to live my life authentically. So here's the problem; I think a big reason that I feel so insecure in this is that I've only told people who don't really matter in the grand scheme of things. I've told a few friends and they've all been super accepting. But if they weren't, I know that I can always make new friends, you know? But I can't make a new family. I'm scared what when/if I tell them, they won't speak to me anymore, and that I might do serious damage to our family. We're already going through some tough stuff, and I don't want to add to the problem. Also my parents are super super Christian and I know the backlash will be terrible for me to deal with. This is such a source of anxiety and stress for me. I've fallen into bad patterns, and I want to stop. I have a feeling that being comfortable enough with myself to own my sexuality will help me in so many areas of my life, and I want to be open with my family because I love them, but I have no idea if it's the right thing to do. And what if I really am just making this all up in my head? Is exploring the truth worth hurting my parents? I'm sorry if this makes no sense, I really appreciate anything that anyone has to say. Tldr; I'm pretty sure I'm bi (but I also think I'm making it up lol), I'm tired of feeling like I'm hiding a part of myself and want to be honest with myself/fam, but I'm scared that things won't end well, and that I'm making a mistake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 02:08:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe don't put what school you go to and your year on the internet if your shoving people's faces into beehives. Just a tip.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 20:32:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's no harm in taking the job, sticking it out for 6 months, and then moving on if you find something you're more interested in. Also you never know if this might be the job that works for you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 20:55:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>As long as you're not happy about the fact that she has a terminal illness, I think you're okay. We can't help but find joy in other people's misfortune sometimes, and that doesn't mean we're not good people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why are people like this? Thoughts on the Snape discourse?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 21:47:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I found this while scrolling though tumblr and im actually at a loss for words. I think people have forgotten that this is *fiction* and that maybe comparing characters from a book to actual Nazis is disrespectful/kinda overboard. Anyway, I'd love to hear thoughts about the extreme (read: sometimes irrational) hate people have for Snape. Also can we acknowledge that some of the points are literally made up and do not exist in the books/movies at all? From the post: "his first fucking thought was to go for a slur. that #8217;s like if a black person were to walk up, defend you while you #8217;re being bullying, and your go-to would be to call him the n-word, not #160; #8220;fuck off, #8221; #160; #8220;piss off, #8221; any of the alternatives. you #8217;re suggesting that in times of great stress, it #8217;s perfectly excusable to call someone n #8212;-r, f #8212;-t, k #8211;e, j-w, any number of slurs you can think of. it #8217;s inexusable. But i love how far y #8217;all go to defend a fucking racist, purist prick who might as well be a kkk member because he thinks it #8217;s cool and is wondering why he #8217;s getting bullied. #160; if i remember rightly, it was just kid stuff, pranks, rivalry, whatever, up until snape started getting into the dark arts and decided he was going to join the nazis. the #160; #8220;bullying #8221; by the marauders was probably just them being intolerant of this intolerant fuck they hated anyway. Nazis deserve to be bullied, ostracized, hated. Snape was willingly deciding to basically join the nazis. if he was a real person and a muggle, i would have gladly done everything james did and more to stop him from becoming powerful and MURDERING PEOPLE. is it #160; #8220;good #8221; is it #160; #8220;pure #8221;? no. but sometimes you gotta bust your knuckles to punch a fucking nazi so fuck off with this shit. sincerly, #160; an american who is literally dealing with nazi  amp; white supremicist neighbors and government right fucking now. the more y #8217;all defend snape, the more i fucking realize how fucking personal it is why i fucking hate him. He is everything i despise and yall, and JK ROWLING HERSELF, continue to APOLOGIZE for this motherfucker, and EXCUSE HIS ACTIONS, and your defense was #160; #8220;he was bullied! #8221; and #160; #8220;Lily wouldn #8217;t sleep with him! #8221; and #160; #8220;He only wanted to protect harry! #8221; when the only reason he did so was because he wanted to sleep with fucking lily. You know what, *I* was fucking bullied, *i #8217;ve* had people that wouldn #8217;t love me that i was desperately in love with, and you don #8217;t see me joining the fucking KKK so FUCK OFF with this nonsense because snape is a metaphor for everything evil in the world. #160; He is complacency. He is white-boy entitlement. He is Incel. He is Misogyny. He would have fucking drugged lily and raped her if he got the chance (we know so little about what really happened that he actually MIGHT HAVE). We already know he would have let her family die if he could #8217;ve just had the opportunity to fucking rape her and kidnap her. (what did you think he had in mind when he asked the dark lord to spare her? That he was going to invite her round for tea? No. Voldemort would have kidnapped her, drugged her with a love potion, and probably imprisoned her in fucking malfoy #8217;s basement or some shit after killing her HUSBAND AND CHILD), and y #8217;all just WILL. NOT. STOP. DEFENDING. THIS. CREEP."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 00:51:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thats fair; here's the post in its entirety. To be honest, im pretty sure poster 3 was being entirely serious, and that's what I find concerning. Clearly this topic can rile people up, but I think there's a big issue with people in this fandom going overboard with their responses (sarcasm or not). I wonder how these people are able to have healthy discussions off the internet :/ anyway, here's the post! Poster 1: I hate when people say the bullying was 4 on one with Snape. Last I checked, 2 people didn #8217;t equal 4. James and Sirius were the bullies, Remus and Peter didn #8217;t bully Snape. They were friends with the bullies but at best they were bystanders. Poster 2:I mean one person bullying another is still one too many but that is true. How bout nobody bully nobody? Poster 3: Nobody ever wants to talk about how Snape still managed to bully Lily though even with his underpants hanging out Poster 4: OH fuck off with this bullshit fanom. Snape didn #8217;t bully Lily. He called her a slur out of rage and shame of having his underwear exposed and bullied but I guess you would act like a cute flower and wouldn #8217;t be angry/ashamed in that situation. You wanna talk about #160; #8220;misoginy #8221;, how about the marauders sexually assaulting Snape in that scene? Because I can #8217;t find another word to removing your pants off in front of a whole school and being made fun of it. But how dare Snape get mad and angry for being bullied and having his underwear exposed, he should behave like a good victim and stay quiet! Poster 3: see text in main post</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 01:50:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel exactly the same way. It's almost scary how accurate this is. I know it's a platitude, but you're not alone. And I guess that means there's hope that someone has been through this and knows how to get better. For now, try being a bit more open with your therapist. They're there to help, and they can't really do much if you're not honest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 03:25:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>30 to 3 kills! How embarassing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 22:43:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im in physical pain. Saya pls they're already dead</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 23:11:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>3 team fights, 3 team kills. Feeling kinda bad for Florida</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 23:20:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty sure no one on Florida is gonna have a job next season</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 23:23:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, *no one but saya*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Feeling guilty about not pursuing engineering after graduation?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 02:35:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone, thanks for reading in advance. I graduated just over a year ago, and since then have been working in a field that is 100% different from engineering. I have a real talent in this field, and it's something I could see myself being really happy/successful in. My issue is that from time to time I feel overwhelmingly guilty about wasting my degree. My major was biomedical, and while I loved doing my degree, I think that I wouldn't be happy working as an engineer, nor would I excel. People are always asking me what I'm doing now, or where I'm working, and I feel as though im letting everyone down when they hear it's not engineering. I guess I'm wondering if anyone has been in a similar situation, and what they've done about it. Thanks for reading/responding!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Feeling guilty about not pursing engineering after grad?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 02:48:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone, thanks for reading in advance. I graduated just over a year ago, and since then have been working in a field that 100% different from engineering. I have a real talent in this field, and it's something I could see myself being really happy/successful in. My issue is that from time to time I feel overwhelmingly guilty about wasting my degree. My major was biomedical, and while I loved doing my degree, I think that I wouldn't be happy working as an engineer, nor would I excel. People are always asking me what I'm doing now, or where I'm working, and I feel as though im letting everyone down when they hear it's not engineering. I guess I'm wondering if anyone has been in a similar situation, and what they've done about it. Thanks for reading!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 03:57:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for responding! I feel like that would be true regardless of what I pursue. If I work in a new field, heading back to engineering will be difficult. And if I transition back to engineering now, if I want to leave, it will be difficult to start a new career in my desired field (I'd need to go back to school, etc). What would you suggest?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 03:58:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the encouragement! I'm trying to focus on what makes me happy (and what I'm good at), but dealing with other people's expectations is hard as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 20:21:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>353</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 01:56:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>K so who else thinks ny was just chilling? There's no way they were taking the game seriously, especially with pine literally not caring on gibraltar</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 02:15:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol not trying to take anything away! Just expressing an opinion. (Also no need to get super defensive, I don't actually care who won either way/you don't need to convince people that Val won. We saw the score lol)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 04:17:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could this be the day? Could the losing streak be over?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 04:47:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last I heard, they were still having communication issues which made it hard for geguri to use zarya at her best.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 05:05:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>My heart literally can't take this. Shanghai why</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 02:43:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Philly was outclassed that whole game. Props to Houston</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I was forced/guilted into showing my wounds</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 22:39:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've had a tense relationship with my sister for a while, but I'm normally the one asking if she's okay and listening to her when she's sad. Lately it's like I've been doing everything wrong in her eyes and when I try to explain how I'm feeling, she ignores me or shuts me down and makes it about her. Anyway, today she came to visit (I live with our parents), and she was guilting me the whole time saying things like "I shared with you, why aren't you telling me anything. That's so unfair." "The things I said we're hard but I did it" and "I'm making things worse I guess I'll shut up" when I was crying. And it just kept getting so bad and I felt so miserable and tired so I showed her. I wasn't in my best state and I regret it so much. But I wasnt ready to show anyone (and she even asked to see more of them), or to explain how I did it (when I told her she did this like half gasp half laugh thing which obviously made me feel worse). And she is forcing me to go to the hospital on Tuesday "can you just go for me" even though I've been 3 times this week and they don't take me seriously. I wish I was strong enough to avoid her. I feel 10 times worse and I know I'll probably cut again to get over this. Fuck nosy, gaslighting sisters. She's in the house now and she's just laughing and hanging out with everyone as if what I told her meant nothing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>