<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject747</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-13 00:28:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>.senoJ_drageruaeB,  #233;hcuoT.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-13 21:09:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>That makes sense to me. I couldn't figure out how it worked unless there was at least *some* possibility of a payout (albeit years off, maybe).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-18 19:04:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>A Foundation Series movie, or several. They'd probably make a hash of it, but I'd love to see someone try. (Past attempts have fizzled from what I understand.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nothing to see here.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-09 00:46:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-15 06:08:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Looks REALLY familiar.](http://www.reddit.com/r/Jokes/comments/214rxe/women_are_like_hurricanes/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The U.S. Supreme Court is set to decide whether a fish tossed over the side of a boat is covered by the evidence-shredding provision of Sarbanes-Oxley.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-17 00:27:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-17 20:50:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, but O'Connor is no longer the swing vote #8212;Kennedy is. And he's a bit of a wild card with reproductive health. Example: Kennedy was the decisive vote in Gonzales v. Carhart (2007) which upheld a partial birth ban that was almost indistinguishable from one the court had struck down seven years earlier (Stenberg v. Carhart (2000), in which O'Connor was the swing vote). That said, Kennedy signed onto the Casey plurality that struck down the spousal notification requirement, so hopefully he'd do the same here. But who knows?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The South Fork Shenandoah River From 35,000 feet.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-05 23:04:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Spotted this "book" in the library. The inside is an empty cardboard box.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-13 00:05:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-09 08:30:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>April foo #8212; [BOOM!]</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Another smooth delivery by UPS.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-13 07:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-13 07:54:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, that's definitely on my agenda.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Every single Office update, without fail, is labeled critical.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-07 08:06:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-19 07:17:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm reminded of Archelaus cards, a staple of many a holiday in my family: http://www.archelaus-cards.com/retail/index.php?main_page=index amp;cPath=1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Uber faces lawsuit over 'greedy and creepy' plans to track users not running app</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-22 16:31:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just a little weather experiment.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-06 06:13:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-28 01:14:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm on the too-perfect-to-be-true train. Wouldn't your natural reaction be to wipe away some of that dust when you exposed the safe rather than leaving it undisturbed? Feels staged #8212;like someone is trying to show us how "unexpected" a discovery it was. Also, where did the dust and debris come from? Did they take an hour to rip out dry wall and lighting fixtures over the safe before they thought to try the combination? Not to mention a couple of the comments in the captions ("It's cute" and "I'm still laughing at that one") feel super contrived. Of course, that could just be garden variety internet posturing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-14 18:46:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Primal fear is responsible for our species of meat-covered skeletons making it this far. So thanks, but I'll go ahead and maintain an appropriate level of mortal terror.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-08 09:12:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's one hell of a lead image for an article about accounting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I submit to you the Rule 34 Rule 34 hypothesis: someone, somewhere has shot a porno about "Producing Documents, Electronically Stored Information, and Tangible Things, or Entering onto Land, for Inspection and Other Purposes."</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-15 03:05:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Hey baby, I'm an attorney and I'm here to inspect, measure, survey, photograph, test, or sample your property or any designated object or operation on it. Mind if I... *come in?*" *Cf.* Fed. R. Civ. P. 34; *Rule 34*, Urban Dictionary (Mar. 30, 2006), http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=Rule+34.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ten years of boozin', and this to show for it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-29 22:21:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-07 18:38:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was a surprisingly contentious debate in my family over the holidays.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-07 18:41:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometimes, yeah. But other sets will have 1-3 holes in one shaker and 3-5 holes in the other. We've got an opaque pair like this at home, which prompted the debate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-07 18:43:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>The question "why" isn't open-ended enough? Weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-07 18:47:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>True. But isn't that the case with most family arguments?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-07 19:47:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a discussion with many different opinions and no right or wrong answers, as my Christmas dinner confirmed. But oh well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-07 20:59:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Why?" in this context clearly asks for both opinions and reasons (not that there's a bright-line distinction between the two anyway). If I likewise ask "Which way should the toilet paper be hung and why?," it's obvious that I'm asking for preferences and explanations of those preferences #8212;not a research report. My fellow Redditors didn't struggle with the meaning of the prompt, as evidenced by their comments. Nor did you when asked "why?" in the following AskReddit threads from the past 48 hours: * ["How many times have you scratched you balls today, oh.... and why are you awake?"](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/3zutth/how_many_times_have_you_scratched_you_balls_today/) * ["[Serious] Why didn't you get a flu shot?"](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/3zmit0/serious_why_didnt_you_get_a_flu_shot/) * ["After the events in Cologne, why should anyone even visit Europe?"](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/3zmk0y/after_the_events_in_cologne_why_should_anyone/) * ["Do you want kids? Why or why not?"](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/3zmsl3/do_you_want_kids_why_or_why_not/) * ["Why doesn't the U.S. or U.N. crush North Korea and displace the regime in control?"](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/3zmsl3/do_you_want_kids_why_or_why_not/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-07 21:19:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hm... very well. I still don't think there's a right or wrong answer to this question (or that my phrasing insinuates that there is one), whereas your http example has a single, authoritative explanation. But I concede it's grey enough for reasonable minds to disagree. Thanks for going four rounds on this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-07 21:04:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man, Portal 3 looks awesome!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>More Thoughts on Speed-Adjusted DELOCK Music</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-25 05:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I spent a while listening the [speed/pitch-adjusted version](http://vocaroo.com/i/s17jQUt3w4p9) of the DELOCK music courtesy of [/u/Thick-McRunFast](https://reddit.com/u/Thick-McRunFast). I don't think it's circus or merry-go-round music, even though it sounds like there's a calliope in the recording. It seems too uptempo for the circus, or at least it feels to me like it *should* be played at a tempo faster than circus music (though maybe not quite as fast as the adjusted version). Also, it lacks the lilting, up-and-down quality that I expect of the genre. My next thought was that the structure of the piece reminded me of ragtime, which [/u/TheSkeletonWhoWalks](https://reddit.com/u/TheSkeletonWhoWalks) [suggested previously](https://www.reddit.com/r/UnfavorableSemicircle/comments/46s7d7/pretty_interesting_find_by_uthickmcrunfast/d07lgug). For example: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0anGlEIlTaQ But it also sounds a bit like jug band music: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zUF7hu-edRw And boogie woogie: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=08jyOwx96Ig And the Cantina theme (which itself draws on Benny Goodman/swing music): https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kCGPt3XFxJk Also, the instrumentation #8212;and to a lesser extent the tune #8212;sound a lot like this: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jlh2WLrkqiw To be clear, I'm not suggesting any of these *are* the piece in DELOCK. But the structure definitely reminds me of these genres. Can anyone with more knowledge of music help zero in this search a bit more?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-25 06:57:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I may be wrong, but I think the calliope is giving a false impression of carousel music. It doesn't seem to have the short, up-and-down phrases that I associate with a merry-go-round.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-25 06:58:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Interesting point about the distortion #8212;maybe I'll reach back a little further time-wise. Good luck with spotify.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-26 17:32:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>The thought had occurred to me, but does YouTube really allow a username to be reclaimed that quickly after suspension?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-26 17:37:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aha, that would explain it. False alarm everyone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-25 18:06:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>All 44 U.S. presidents (or 43, depending on what you do with Grover "Nonconsecutive Terms" Cleveland). Checked [this book](http://www.amazon.com/Yo-Millard-Fillmore-those-Presidents/dp/1935212419) out of the library in the mid-90s and learned the mnemonics. Eventually got to know the sequence so well that I could just rattle it off without thinking. Still can!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-21 18:35:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok, it's a car. We've invented the Pontiac Aztek.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-23 04:09:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>He has a definite Artful Dodger look about him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-03 17:26:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>The fact that opaque cups in movies/TV shows don't have any liquid in them. Actors swish cups of "hot coffee" around like they're singing a pirate shanty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-23 07:26:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/gifsthatstarttoolate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 06:35:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>[My thoughts exactly.](http://imgur.com/gallery/QGpMZay)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 06:43:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Relevancy." You keep using that word. I do not think it means what you think it means.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 15:05:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mhmm. https://www.reddit.com/r/gameofthrones/comments/26x0mj/ https://www.reddit.com/r/gameofthrones/comments/1fc4c4/no_spoilers_i_found_who_looks_like_beric/ https://www.reddit.com/r/gameofthrones/comments/28hdbr/no_spoilers_stannis_totally_looks_like_napoleon/ https://www.reddit.com/r/gameofthrones/comments/ua1fd/is_it_just_me_or_has_anyone_else_noticed_this/ https://www.reddit.com/r/gameofthrones/comments/t0wdw/the_first_person_i_thought_of_when_i_saw_pyat_pree/ https://www.reddit.com/r/gameofthrones/comments/24smua/s4e5_any_downton_abbey_watchers_here_did_this/ https://www.reddit.com/r/gameofthrones/comments/uw76d/ https://www.reddit.com/r/gameofthrones/comments/t1hal/what_jaqen_reminds_me_of_the_elder_scrolls_related/ https://www.reddit.com/r/gameofthrones/comments/23ir39/no_spoilers_does_jack_gleesons_portrayal_of/ https://www.reddit.com/r/gameofthrones/comments/sa1u7/little_finger_reminds_me_of_this_guy/ https://www.reddit.com/r/gameofthrones/comments/se2yf/is_it_just_me_or_does_grand_maester_pycelle/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This 1980s ad for Circus Fun Cereal is slightly terrifying.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-30 18:24:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-30 18:45:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Interesting #8212;the ad sort of leaves the impression that it's made of modeling clay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-03 15:16:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>[circumbendibus](https://en.wiktionary.org/wiki/circumbendibus)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL that it's unconstitutional to be tried for a murder conceived and committed in the Idaho section of Yellowstone National Park.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 17:17:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 17:18:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>The key passage:  gt; Say that you are in the Idaho portion of Yellowstone, and you decide to spice up your vacation by going on a crime spree. You make some moonshine, you poach some wildlife, you strangle some people and steal their picnic baskets. You are arrested, arraigned in the park, and bound over for trial in Cheyenne, Wyoming before a jury drawn from the Cheyenne area. 21 But Article III, Section 2 plainly requires that the trial be held in Idaho, the state in which the crime was committed. Perhaps if you fuss convincingly enough about it, the case would be sent to Idaho. But the Sixth Amendment then requires that the jury be from the state (Idaho) and the district (Wyoming) in which the crime was committed. In other words, the jury would have to be drawn from the Idaho portion of Yellowstone National Park, which, according to the 2000 Census, has a population of precisely zero. 22 (The Montana portion-should you choose to rampage there--has an adult population of a few dozen, which might nevertheless present Sixth Amendment problems as well. 23) The Constitution entitles you to a jury trial and an impartial jury of inhabitants of the state and district where the crime was committed. The U.S. Code steps on the rusty nail; it makes it impossible to satisfy both provisions in the case of the Yellowstone State-Line Strangler. Assuming that you do not feel like consenting to trial in Cheyenne, you should go free.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 17:29:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Normally yeah. Federal park land is under exclusive federal jurisdiction, so you'd be tried for [federal murder](https://www.law.cornell.edu/uscode/text/18/1111). The point is that there are two conflicting constitutional provisions which appear to make that impossible in this tiny section of Yellowstone, thanks to a mismatch between state and federal district borders. To try the crime elsewhere, they'd have to prove that there was some sort of interstate nexus to the crime. But that wouldn't be the case for a murder that was purely conceived and committed on that land.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 18:19:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn't say it was the point of the article; was just underscoring the limitations of the loophole. If some element of the crime took place in another state #8212;for example, a conspiracy that began in the Wyoming section of Yellowstone and continued into the Idaho section #8212;you could be constitutionally tried in Wyoming. But Congress having drawn the district of Wyoming the way it did, it's not constitutional (at the moment) to be tried for a crime that was exclusively confined to the Idaho section of the park.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 18:59:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right you are. I just went with murder in the title 'cuz it's sexy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-14 08:29:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Game of Throne'd!](http://imgur.com/nnIEmWw)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-26 15:23:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>And that barn's name? Albert Einstein.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-07 05:34:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I interpreted the Jon/Davos/Missandei exchange as a hint that something happened in the cave (possibly affecting Jon's title): Missandei: Ser Davos. Lord Snow.  #160; Davos: King Snow, isn't it? No, that doesn't sound right. King Jon?  #160; Jon: It doesn't matter. But maybe that's reading too much into it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[EVERYTHING] The music in that final scene.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-08 14:39:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just wanted to say how excellent the score was in the loot train attack. Really raised my heart rate (as did damn near everything in that scene)! It was particularly cool to hear the interaction of the different leitmotifs. I don #8217;t think the Rains of Castamere and the Dothraki themes have ever featured in the same scene before. My not-all-that-musically-savvy breakdown of the motifs: * Drogon parts the clouds  #8212; **Dracarys theme** * Drogon incinerates the center of the line  #8212; **rapidly descending strings from Dracarys** * Dothraki archers charge  #8212; **Vaes Dothrak theme** * Drogon strafes the loot train from the side  #8212; **Dracarys** * Drogon strafes the loot train again (right after the arrows bounce off)  #8212; **Dracarys** * Jaime sends Bronn away and turns to face Dothraki head on  #8212; **Rains of Castemere** * Bronn charges toward Dothraki rider en route to Scorpion  #8212; **Vaes Dothrak theme** * Tyrion and Jaime both look across the burning battlefield  #8212; **Rains of Castamere** * Drogon makes a low pass over the water  #8212; **Dracarys** * Jaime charges at Daenerys  #8212; This sounds to me like the first couple of notes of Rains of Castamere on loop, but sung by the same indistinct voices from Dracarys. So maybe a hybrid of the two motifs? Hats off to Ramin Djawadi et al!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 05:46:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could be, but I don't think the Hound-like figure in the trailer looks or moves like a wight. He seems fully intact and draws his sword in a smooth motion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 05:54:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hm, I had the opposite reaction. His hand looks like a normal human color and his armor looks intact. Also, would a wight bother to keep a sword in a scabbard?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 06:03:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aren't those pants? They look fabric to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 05:31:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's an awful lot of fire in the last shot of the second S7 trailer (the scene where Jon strikes down a single wight). Also, the wights in the background seem to be keeping their distance from Jon in a weird way. Could there be a dragon standing behind him maybe? (Of course the fire could also come from Beric's sword.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[EVERYTHING] Guess he warmed up to the stuff after all.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 06:02:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 21:36:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fireworks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 17:11:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Um, okay. Then you'll need to remove these front page posts as well: https://www.reddit.com/r/gameofthrones/comments/6wgp8p/everything_rhaegars_hair/ https://www.reddit.com/r/gameofthrones/comments/6wgh2s/main_spoilers_now_we_know_the_truth_about_theon/ https://www.reddit.com/r/gameofthrones/comments/6wgkl4/everything_littlefingers_actor/ https://www.reddit.com/r/gameofthrones/comments/6wgj7y/everything_lena_headey_appreciation/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 17:20:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Isn't it V**ise**rion? http://gameofthrones.wikia.com/wiki/Viserion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 17:33:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha, whoops, I just now picked up on the pun. D'oh!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 23:45:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>FFS, this is sitting on the front page right now: https://www.reddit.com/r/gameofthrones/comments/6wk3k8/main_spoilers_viserions_roar/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Random pile of cubed ham leaves Baltimore internet, Downtown Partnership fascinated</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 17:19:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 16:36:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>For anyone who prefers the opposite default (i.e., sound on but with a quick way to mute a noisy tab), you can also go to chrome://flags and enable "Tab audio muting UI control." Then just click on the sound icon at the top of a particular tab to mute/unmute it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 04:01:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>[But that's none of my business](https://i.imgur.com/L1dQKKQ.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 04:03:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Augh, and just as I finished my !@#$% submission.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 17:05:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically this, where every month is a single column: https://img.etsystatic.com/il/71be1b/1358969729/il_570xN.1358969729_gjub.jpg My grandparents had a wall calendar similar to this when I was little, and the image always stuck with me. I haven't seen this format very often, though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 16:40:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, that headline is pretty damned misleading. Like, technically accurate insofar as the people who found the mics were employed by the U.S. government. But they were defense attorneys *being spied on by the U.S.*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 18:10:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't always love the showrunners' execution of the Arya-Sansa feud, but I think it's more plausible than many folks give it credit for. Recall a few things: * Arya is like 17 years old(?) at this point in the show #8212;not yet a grown adult. * Arya had a pretty contentious relationship with Sansa *before the show even began*, and it certainly wasn't helped by Arya's impression (fair or not) that Sansa had collaborated with her captors in King's Landing. * Arya's been living on the fringes of civilization for YEARS at this point, unable to trust anyone for fear of getting murdered by soldiers or bandits or occult face-stealing assassins. * This is the first time Arya has been back at Winterfell since the slaying of her parents and eldest brother #8212;hardly surprising that she's squicked out by seeing her frenemy sister in charge of her childhood home. * Sansa, of course, does not help matters with her own machinations and questionable tolerance of Littlefinger. That's not to say Arya's behavior toward Sansa was entirely logical or self-aware or ideal under the circumstances. But it makes sense that an angsty teenager who's been to hell and back would have a less-than-seamless reintroduction to life at Winterfell. I have no trouble believing that a person in that situation might rebel against authority in irrational and counterproductive ways. (Fortunately she and Sansa came to an understanding before we ended up with more dead Starks.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 20:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>All good points. I think you're right about the inspiration and aim of Arya's tactics. I was mostly responding to the argument that the sisters' feud was inherently pointless (i.e., "for no god damned logical reason at all"). That's true in a sense #8212;Arya probably could have saved a lot of trouble by having a calm, adult conversation with Sansa about the Littlefinger threat. But people who are emotionally broken and (understandably) paranoid don't always handle things in the most sensible way. They seethe, they scheme, they lash out, they recriminate. In other words: they do what Arya did. What's that GRRM says about the human heart in conflict with itself?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 20:29:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right? It's almost as though there are no universal absolutes in the workload distribution of human endeavors! Every task is a little different.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 23:52:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>As several commenters have noted, this isn't 100% true. For example, the IRS recently launched a [private debt collection program](https://www.irs.gov/businesses/small-businesses-self-employed/private-debt-collection) for "accounts where taxpayers owe money, but the IRS is no longer actively working their accounts." Approved firms are [allowed to call taxpayers](https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/columnist/tompor/2017/04/14/irs-turns-debt-collectors-call-unpaid-taxes/100483162/) to recoup outstanding debts. In theory this program only applies people who have already been notified of outstanding debts by letter. But it certainly has the potential to muddy the waters, which is why it's been [widely criticized](http://www.slate.com/articles/business/moneybox/2017/04/the_irs_is_using_private_debt_collectors_again_that_s_a_problem.html). Also Pioneer, one of the approved firms, was [ditched by the Department of Education](https://www.ed.gov/news/press-releases/us-department-education-end-contracts-several-private-collection-agencies) and [sued by the CFPB](https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2017/03/31/the-irs-has-hired-a-debt-collector-that-is-being-sued-by-the-government.html) for placing misleading debt collection calls. So there's that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 16:14:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Relevant New Yorker cartoon: https://images.fineartamerica.com/images-medium-large-5/bad-drawing-david-sipress.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 01:27:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Listen to recordings of U.S. Supreme Court arguments. Supreme court litigators are incredibly good at what they do and can turn even a boring bankruptcy case into a compelling story. It also gives you a great sense of how the different justices think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 02:44:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't recommend nonprofit legal work highly enough. Certainly there are trade-offs compared to private law (lower pay, a tight job market, and the potential for some really emotionally draining casework). But if you can get past those drawbacks, it's great. It allows you to work a semi-normal schedule and to feel like a human being while you're doing it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 07:24:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or ride around shirtless on an ancient dirt bike in the back yard of the house that you bought while two flamboyantly gay construction workers look on from the fire pit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A star is born</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 06:14:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So long then!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 14:15:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 14:17:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good call #8212;shoulda tried this when his health was already depleted. (I swear you could nuke these things from orbit and still only take out half their HP.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 14:22:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lit a bunch of fires in the house of that one Tarrey Town family (while their daughter was sleeping) to see how they'd react. They took it pretty well, all things considered.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 21:02:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sadly for the bokoblin, it looks like he was alive through that whole hellish plunge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Chuchu takes a bullet + Lightning-powered parry</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 05:34:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 16:32:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Counterpoint: https://assets3.thrillist.com/v1/image/2695213/size/gn-gift_guide_variable_c.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ajit Pai: Next FCC meeting will be "our own version of 'Avengers: Infinity War.'"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 22:03:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 22:09:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right? Not sure that's a comparison he wants to invite. Or maybe it is, who knows. Would kinda be on brand for him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do the Hyrule Shake</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 05:40:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 19:51:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fellow DMVer here. Tbh the motorcades have never felt like that big a hassle. I work in building that that gets periodic Trump  amp; Pence motorcades whipping by, but I'm rarely delayed in traffic more than a few minutes. Mildly frustrating at times, but eh, that's the price of living in DC. It's the big events on the Mall that tend to wreak more havoc with my life. (Of course it all depends on where you work/live/play.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 23:06:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depends on what you mean by outsource. They don't offshore, but the IRS [has begun using private debt collectors](https://www.irs.gov/businesses/small-businesses-self-employed/private-debt-collection) for certain overdue debts, and those collectors are permitted to call taxpayers. Fortunately you'll probably receive multiple letters before your account reaches a private collector. But it was still a dumb move on Congress's/the IRS's part to open the gates to private call centers. It just muddies the waters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 16:32:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sadly Comcast's corporate personhood will be a short-lived blessing. Your case will immediately be diverted to individualized arbitration (per the terms of your contract), which will cost you more than you can possibly recover anyway. You will die sad and penniless, cursing Comcast with your last breath.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 17:02:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, but that's the cost of arbitration process #8212;not your own legal fees. In all but the most extreme cases, it'll cost more to hire a lawyer to represent you through arbitration than you'll ever recover. And because Comcast's agreement mandates *individualized* arbitration, there's no chance of a class action (which would otherwise be good mechanism for enforcing common violations of the customer agreement).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 17:11:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reasonable minds (including 4/9ths of the Supreme Court) will disagree. The truth is that the Court has gone out of its way for a decade+ to read the Federal Arbitration Act in the most expansive way possible. So now suddenly a 1925 law encouraging the enforcement of arbitration agreements supersedes the 1935 National Labor Relations Act. I agree that the law has to change. But yesterday's decision was not an impartial and inevitable reading of current law. (See Ginsburg's 30-page dissent on the subject: https://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/17pdf/16-285_q8l1.pdf#page=32)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 17:30:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Arbitration can easily cost more than ordinary litigation ([e.g.](https://www.citizen.org/our-work/government-reform/cost-arbitration-executive-summary)) #8212;it depends on the case and the particulars of the contract. Plus there are other downsides: no option of a jury, no right of appeal, arbitrators and procedures that tend to favor companies over consumers. But yeah, individualization is the real killer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 18:16:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well as I said, it depends on the case. Taking the Comcast contract as an example, arbitration could certainly cost more if your claim is for more than $75,000 (since under AAA rules you may end up footing the bill). If your claim is for less than that (and is not found "frivolous or brought for an improper purpose"), that same Public Citizen report finds that transaction costs ("witness fees, attorney fees, [and] discovery costs") can still be higher:  gt; The oft-cited benefits that arbitration can offer in exchange for higher fees will seldom benefit consumer litigants. Not only is there is no evidence that arbitration reduces the overall transaction costs of litigation (e.g. witness fees, attorney fees, discovery costs), but nobody has expounded a coherent theory to explain how arbitration could reduce such costs except in a few categories of cases. Indeed, Public Citizen's careful examination of the cost savings claim demonstrates that in the vast majority of cases, arbitration will necessarily increase the transaction costs of litigation. I don't mean to say that arbitration is *always* more expensive. I think there are plenty of legitimate uses for ADR. But mandatory arbitration clauses force legit consumer cases out of the courtroom even when there's good reason to keep them there. And of course companies like Comcast put arbitration clauses into consumer contracts for a reason: on balance, arbitration is more favorable to their interests (whether or not it happens to be cheaper for the parties in a given case).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 19:12:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well this isn't a constitutional case; it's about how to read two interlocking statutes passed at different times. But even if you accept that  #8220;laws are dead as they are written, #8221; that doesn #8217;t tell you how to deduce the  #8220;dead #8221; meaning of the text. Do you focus on the original public meaning (and if so, how do you ascertain what that was)? Do you look ambiguous terms up in dictionaries (and if so, which ones)? Do you place emphasis on canons of statutory interpretation (which can be helpful but aren #8217;t exactly law themselves)? Do you look at how Congress has used the the same language in other statutes? Do you take into account the legislative process and historical context that led to the enactment of the statute (which may be ambiguous but can also provide crucial insight into what Congress was thinking)? The Court mixes and matches these methods depending on the case and the justice writing the opinion. But in tough cases (like this one), these different interpretive tools don #8217;t usually point to a single unambiguous meaning. Gorsuch is disingenuous to suggest otherwise. Take this case, for example. On the one hand you have the Federal Arbitration Act (FAA), which requires courts to enforce arbitration clauses except  #8220;upon such grounds as exist at law or in equity for the revocation of any contract. #8221; On the other hand you have the National Labor Relations Act (NLRA), which prohibits  #8220;interfer[ing] with, restrain[ing], or coerc[ing] employees in the exercise of the rights guaranteed #8221; under the NLRA. One of the rights guaranteed by the NLRA is the right of employees to engage in  #8220;concerted activities #8221; for the purpose of  #8220;mutual aid or protection. #8221; So the question is: if you have a clause that prohibits employees from pursuing work-related claims on a collective (class action) basis, does that unlawfully interfere with their right to engage in concerted activities (which, in turn, would exempt the contract from the FAA)? Or does the FAA require that clause to be enforced? The majority said no, the right to engage in  #8220;concerted activities #8221; only extends to traditional union organization #8212;not collective legal action #8212;which means the FAA requires enforcement of the clause. Ginsburg #8217;s dissent says yes,  #8220;concerted activities #8221; include joint legal action, so the FAA doesn #8217;t apply to this contract. Both opinions go through lengthy statutory analysis to reach those conclusions. I'd argue Ginsburg's is much more coherent and in sync with the context in which the NLRA was passed, but others may disagree. Bottom line, though: Gorsuch #8217;s opinion doesn #8217;t have any special claim on the  #8220;true meaning #8221; of the FAA  amp; NLRA. It's just one of several possible readings that garnered the necessary five votes. (It's also another example of the conservative majority going out of its way to extend the reach of the FAA and give corporations the upper hand in litigation.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 20:17:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>* EPIC Systems is binding precedent, yes, but that doesn #8217;t make it the one  #8220;true interpretation #8221; of the NLRA  amp; FAA. Dredd Scott, Plessy, and Bowers were all the law of the land until the Court overturned them as wrongly decided. The Supreme Court screws up sometimes, as it did here. * I agree that  #8220;the law should be interpreted as it is written, #8221; but (as I said above) that does virtually nothing to explain how a case like this should be decided. The entire crux of this case was a dispute about what the FAA  amp; NRLA meant "as written." Two groups of justices came to polar opposite conclusions on that question. * Many words and phrases are susceptible to multiple valid interpretations; courts are often forced to choose between several alternative readings. Often laws don't carry one unambiguous meaning. * Courts make law every time they interpret a statute or the constitution. That #8217;s what precedent is. They don #8217;t write statutes, no, but they certainly make law. * If Scalia were still alive and wrote the opinion Gorsuch did, he'd be wrong too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 21:05:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>And just because you and five justices agree with it doesn't make it the correct interpretation. Your point?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 21:25:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apologies, I took your last response in the wrong way. It sounds like we're in furious agreement on this point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 06:34:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Elon Musk and SpaceX are welcome to ask for certain concessions in exchange for granting an interview (e.g., limiting the scope of questions), but they should know that most serious journalists won't agree to things like prepublication review. That's usually an ethical red line, as it apparently was for Sharon Weinberger. And in any case, the burden is on SpaceX not to reveal protected information to a third party (or to accept the consequences if they do). You don't get to conscript journalists into correcting your fuckups after the fact #8212;that's not how an independent press is supposed to operate. I don't know the ins and outs of ITAR, but the Supreme Court was pretty clear in Bartnicki v. Vopper that the First Amendment protects the publication of matters of public concern by a third party (e.g., a journalist), even if the original source of that information broke the law in disclosing it. So no, no jailtime for journalists in Weinberger's shoes (unless perhaps they actively encouraged someone to leak classified info). Bottom line, Elon's sanctimony/sass is a bit much here. And also he's apparently [just wrong](https://www.reddit.com/r/quityourbullshit/comments/8lxboj/elon_has_been_on_a_roll_lately/dzj91db/) on the facts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 07:15:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Former journalist here. Prepublication review is definitely not the industry standard. Some publications and reporters do it on the margins, but for most serious journos, it's an ethical red line. Bear in mind that fact-checking (i.e., verifying the factual assertions in the story) is different than turning over an article wholesale to a source before it's published. The former is good practice; the latter gives your sources an inside line on the story and opens you up to haggling and editorial manipulation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 07:33:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>If SpaceX reveals protected information to someone who isn't authorized to have it (e.g., a third-party journalist), that's their own fault. They don't have the right to claw back information after the fact (unless the journalist agreed to those terms in advance, which most serious journos would not). And even if SpaceX *could* claw the information back, they'd still be on the hook for leaking to the journalist in the first place, which presumably violates their ITAR obligations. As you say, the First Amendment protects your right to publish information, even if the original source of that information broke the law by obtaining it or sharing it with you (see [Bartnicki v. Vopper](https://www.oyez.org/cases/2000/99-1687)). So Elon Musk and SpaceX aren #8217;t actually protecting the journalist from any liability, they #8217;re just trying to protect the company. And while I certainly get that impulse, Musk shouldn't act surprised when a journalist balks at SpaceX's request. She doesn't work for them; it's not her job or legal duty to protect their secrets. I'm all for fact-checking, but sources don't get to go through with a red pen and take out parts of articles they'd rather keep quiet (even if they contain classified info).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 08:33:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the more obvious option was to refuse to submit to prepublication review at all. Which, if I understand Weinberger correctly, is what she did. (Also I don't see why her retelling that story is "manufactured drama" #8212;it seems entirely relevant to Musk's recent comments about the press.) Bartnicki still looks pretty on point to me. The statute in that case also imposed an undifferentiated obligation on the public not to disclose certain information (the contents of an unlawfully intercepted phone call). The Court said that just because a *different* party had broken the law by intercepting a phone call didn't mean that the government could punish the public at large for republishing the contents of the call. Content-based restrictions of that sort are almost always struck down as unconstitutional (see also [Smith v. Daily Mail Publishing](https://www.oyez.org/cases/1978/78-482), [Florida Star v. B. J. F.](https://www.oyez.org/cases/1988/87-329)). So even if the ITAR regs prohibit all U.S. persons from republishing certain information, the First Amendment would appear to bar enforcement of that regulation. I am not aware of any First Amendment cases that distinguish between dissemination to U.S. persons and dissemination to non-U.S. persons #8212;both would seem equally protected. I think the Court is unlikely to recognize a distinction like that, too, particularly in the internet era.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 05:18:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>The explanation may not be *malice*, exactly, but I don't think it's stupidity either. If it really wanted to, YouTube could crack down more aggressively on channels and users that try to scam and exploit young viewers. But it doesn't, because (in part) it's financially incentivized not to. So while there may not be a mustache-twirling villain at the controls, YouTube passively benefits from some pretty sketchy shit. At some point that's not just "screwing up" #8212;that's a pattern of negligent acquiescence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 07:34:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>If Ford has the ability to fix certain defects in its vehicles that contribute to road deaths, yet refuses to fix those defects, the blame lies (at least in part) with Ford. And depending on the circumstances, Ford may be held to account through a product liability suit or even criminal charges. So no, it's really not that unfair to say that YouTube bears part of the blame.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 10:40:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm all for requiring vaccines, but conditioning basic social safety net programs on child immunization is a bad idea. We'll just end up revictimizing kids who already had the misfortune to grow up without proper medical treatment (either because parents are anti-vaxxers or because our healthcare system has failed them).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not a good time, I guess</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 23:39:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 06:05:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Toh Yahsa Shrine: https://www.zeldadungeon.net/wiki/Toh_Yahsa_Shrine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 05:03:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/WtWFotMJaJtRAtCaB/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>...please don't judge me.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 02:30:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ow.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 01:20:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 01:25:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>"It is my plea... what the shit dude?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>HEBRA CALLS FOR AID</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 05:11:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>HYRULE CALLS FOR AID</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 15:41:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 15:56:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Raises my heart rate every time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 02:39:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah this is riiiight on the edge of the allowable range. Five feet farther and it would've blinked out of existence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>THE BEACONS OF HYRULE ARE LIT</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:30:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:19:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Denethor (best I could do).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>