<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject4527</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 23:57:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kind of annoyed with Tay's Inner Circle. I do believe they now have Her, Acting Like A Boy, Nashville and plenty of demos. I do happen to own a rare piano demo of We Were Happy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Unreleased Songs</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 23:59:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, does anyone have super rare songs? Ones that are not currently in circulation? Kind of annoyed with Taylor's Inner Circle for never sharing. I think it's hypocritical to gain an unreleased song but tell other people it's wrong. Just up for discussion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 01:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you show me a list?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 01:57:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you have any at all?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 01:57:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which I wouldn't leak but I'd be happy to share within the true fan community</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 02:26:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay! Post a list whenever</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 02:26:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay okay maybe I can help?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 02:26:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure man! PM me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 03:11:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>That I do know and I have all the ones in circulation. I'm just upset that there are a few that have surfaced that some fans say other fans can't listen to, ya know?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 04:38:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. I have everything in circulation but I was talking about the rare stuff that few people have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 12:44:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, you have everything I do and then some. Here's my list: Taylor Swift Song Trade- Acoustic Demos- All Night Diner Angelina Beautiful Eyes Being With My Baby Brand New World By The Way Can I Go With You? Check Out This View Closest To A Cowboy Cross My Heart Didn't They Don't Hate Me For Loving You Fall Back On You Fearless Firefly I'm Alright I Wished On A Plane Look At You Like That Love They Haven't Thought Of Yet Love To Lose Made Up You Matches Me And Britany My Cure Our Last Night Our Song Perfect Have I Loved Picture To Burn Rain Song Shake It Off Stupid Boy Superstar Sweet Tea And God's Graces Tell Me Ten Dollars And A Six Pack (Demo) Ten Dollars And A Six Pack (Studio) That's When Thinking About You Tied Together With A Smile Til Brad Pitt Comes Along Tim McGraw Under My Head We Were Happy (Piano) When You Think Tim McGraw (Original Tim McGraw Piano Recording) You Do Your Anything Volume 2- 4 U (For You) American Boy Honey Baby In The Pouring Rain I Use To Fly Live For The Little Things Mandolin My Turn To Be Me Never Fade Point Of View Same Girl Spinning Around Sugar Tennessee That's Life This Here Guitar Studio Unreleased- American Girl Am I Ready For Love? Baby, Don't You Break My Heart Slow Being With My Baby Better Off Breathless Brought Up This Way Dark Blue Tennessee Diary Of Me Hold On (feat.Jack Ingram) I Know What I Want (Ain't You) I'm Every Woman Just South Of Knowing Why (Drive All Night) Long Time Coming (Long Time Going) Lucky You Making Up For Lost Love My Cure Need You Now Never Mind (Country) Never Mind (Pop) One Thing Permanent Marker R-E-V-E-N-G-E Riptide Smokey Black Nights Sweet Tea And God's Graces Tell Me Thirteen Blocks (Can't Call It Love) This Is Really Happening Wait For Me Welcome Distraction We Were Happy What Do You Say What To Wear White Blank Page Who I've Always Been Writing Songs About You You All Over Me You Don't Have To Call Me Your Face Original Demo Recording- A Perfectly Good Heart A Place In This World Beautiful Eyes Christmases When You Were Mine Cold As You (Version 2) Come In With The Rain Crazier (Version 1) Crazier (Version 2) I Heart ? Invisible Mary's Song (Oh My My My) Picture To Burn Teardrops On My Guitar The Outside</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 12:45:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm well aware. They must have some pretty close connections.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 12:46:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yessir. Those would be the ones and I know they don't share. My only hope is that someday these songs will surface  #128591; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 12:48:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand them wanting to protect these songs from a major leak and I know they have a right to not share because they obtained these songs from their own sources but having them say that circulating songs is wrong is like a thief telling another thief it's wrong to steal. I would gladly circulate songs to fans who want them. Obviously not leakers but you know what I mean.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 12:49:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate the offer but I did end up obtaining it. Thank you though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 13:01:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't know for sure what their reasoning is. All I know is that it's kind of condescending to make posts about songs while telling other people they're not gonna get to listen to them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 04:25:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some of them are. Here's my list. Acoustic Demos and Volume 2 sound scratchy and sometime are hard to hear and show the earliest versions of Taylor's song writing abilities. Studio unreleased were songs officially recorded in a studio and were at some point probably considered to be on an album. Original demo recordings are first takes on songs that were eventually put out: Taylor Swift Song Trade- Acoustic Demos- All Night Diner Angelina Beautiful Eyes Being With My Baby Brand New World By The Way Can I Go With You? Check Out This View Closest To A Cowboy Cross My Heart Didn't They Don't Hate Me For Loving You Fall Back On You Fearless Firefly I'm Alright I Wished On A Plane Look At You Like That Love They Haven't Thought Of Yet Love To Lose Made Up You Matches Me And Britany My Cure Our Last Night Our Song Perfect Have I Loved Picture To Burn Rain Song Shake It Off Stupid Boy Superstar Sweet Tea And God's Graces Tell Me Ten Dollars And A Six Pack (Demo) Ten Dollars And A Six Pack (Studio) That's When Thinking About You Tied Together With A Smile Til Brad Pitt Comes Along Tim McGraw Under My Head We Were Happy (Piano) When You Think Tim McGraw (Original Tim McGraw Piano Recording) You Do Your Anything Volume 2- 4 U (For You) American Boy Honey Baby In The Pouring Rain I Use To Fly Live For The Little Things Mandolin My Turn To Be Me Never Fade Point Of View Same Girl Spinning Around Sugar Tennessee That's Life This Here Guitar Studio Unreleased- American Girl Am I Ready For Love? Baby, Don't You Break My Heart Slow Being With My Baby Better Off Breathless Brought Up This Way Dark Blue Tennessee Diary Of Me Hold On (feat.Jack Ingram) I Know What I Want (Ain't You) I'm Every Woman Just South Of Knowing Why (Drive All Night) Long Time Coming (Long Time Going) Lucky You Making Up For Lost Love My Cure Need You Now Never Mind (Country) Never Mind (Pop) One Thing Permanent Marker R-E-V-E-N-G-E Riptide Smokey Black Nights Sweet Tea And God's Graces Tell Me Thirteen Blocks (Can't Call It Love) This Is Really Happening Wait For Me Welcome Distraction We Were Happy What Do You Say What To Wear White Blank Page Who I've Always Been Writing Songs About You You All Over Me You Don't Have To Call Me Your Face Original Demo Recording- A Perfectly Good Heart A Place In This World Beautiful Eyes Christmases When You Were Mine Cold As You (Version 2) Come In With The Rain Crazier (Version 1) Crazier (Version 2) I Heart ? Invisible Mary's Song (Oh My My My) Picture To Burn Teardrops On My Guitar The Outside</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 05:37:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you need?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 05:56:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah man. Message me anytime if you need anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 16:40:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. Do you want me to email it to you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 23:39:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree. I don't support them and there really shouldn't be a middle ground.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 23:41:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>And as much as I hate it, there's really nothing we CAN do. We can not support them but they're still gonna have and keep getting these songs. In regards to us who aren't as privileged enough to be in the IC, we won't get to listen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In regards to LWYMMD music video...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 05:23:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a question for Swifities who love Taylor across all eras. Did anyone else get kinda sad when she was kicking down the past versions of her? When she kicked the one from You Belong With Me I went back and watched that music video and it made me kinda sad. I don't know. I'm just curious how other people felt. Also, what Taylor's other than the obvious ones did you notice? I noticed one from 22  #128513;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 05:38:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right?! It was just a taint of sadness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 05:57:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like that! That makes me feel better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 14:30:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know! When she's holding her guitar while falling...It made me sad but it was a pretty cool shot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's okay to not be okay</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 16:17:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to think that feeling sad or mad or depressed or any other emotion one would consider "negative" was a bad thing. I always felt that by allowing yourself to feel that way after someone hurt you, it was giving them the upper hand and that drove me crazy so I would try my hardest to smile and just skip right to the part where I'm "over" the situation but someone just told me that there's no such thing as a negative emotion. It's okay to feel pain after someone hurt you. It's okay to cry and be mad and feel depressed as long as you don't let it consume you. I guess what that all means is it's okay to not be okay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sims 2 digital download?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 01:00:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where can I buy a digital copy of Sims 2 to download?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Please save me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 01:56:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please save me. I struggle horrible with BPD, depression, and anxiety and it all stems from things that happened to me as a child. I'm in therapy and I take medication but I feel like I'm drowning. I feel like I'm dying, I already made two attempts on my life in the past. I don't know why I'm posting this but I'm having a depressive episode. Please somebody save me..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Unreleased/Rare Taylor Swift songs?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 02:02:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s 2018 and this time last year, You All Over Me has leaked. Has anything else leaked since then? And I don #8217;t meant in WIAB or the IC because they really only care about their elitist title. I meant something that has leaked entirely</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 03:09:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not a troll. Lemme run this down for you and you can look it up. There #8217;s a whole list of unreleased Taylor Swift songs, album cuts, and demos that have leaked and are traded among an underground of fans. It #8217;s called the Taylor Swift Song trade. Here #8217;s the list of songs I currently have: Taylor Swift Song Trade- Acoustic Demos- All Night Diner Angelina Beautiful Eyes Being With My Baby Brand New World By The Way Can I Go With You? Check Out This View Closest To A Cowboy Cross My Heart Didn't They Don't Hate Me For Loving You Fall Back On You Fearless Firefly I'm Alright I Wished On A Plane Look At You Like That Love They Haven't Thought Of Yet Love To Lose Made Up You Matches Me And Britany My Cure Our Last Night Our Song Perfect Have I Loved Picture To Burn Rain Song Shake It Off Stupid Boy Superstar Sweet Tea And God's Graces Tell Me Ten Dollars And A Six Pack (Demo) Ten Dollars And A Six Pack (Studio) That's When Thinking About You Tied Together With A Smile Til Brad Pitt Comes Along Tim McGraw Under My Head We Were Happy (Piano) When You Think Tim McGraw (Original Tim McGraw Piano Recording) You Do Your Anything Volume 2- 4 U (For You) American Boy Honey Baby In The Pouring Rain I Use To Fly Live For The Little Things Mandolin My Turn To Be Me Never Fade Point Of View Same Girl Spinning Around Sugar Tennessee That's Life This Here Guitar Studio Unreleased- American Girl Am I Ready For Love? Baby, Don't You Break My Heart Slow Being With My Baby Better Off Breathless Brought Up That Way Dark Blue Tennessee Dark Blue Tennessee (Piano) Diary Of Me Hold On (feat.Jack Ingram) I Know What I Want (Ain't You) I'm Every Woman Just South Of Knowing Why (Drive All Night) Long Time Coming (Long Time Going) Lucky You Making Up For Lost Love My Cure Need You Now Never Mind (Country) Never Mind (Pop) One Thing Permanent Marker R-E-V-E-N-G-E Riptide Smokey Black Nights Sweet Tea And God's Graces Tell Me Thirteen Blocks (Can't Call It Love) This Is Really Happening Wait For Me Welcome Distraction We Were Happy What Do You Say What To Wear White Blank Page Who I've Always Been Writing Songs About You You All Over Me You Don't Have To Call Me Your Face Original Demo Recording- A Perfectly Good Heart A Place In This World Beautiful Eyes Christmases When You Were Mine Cold As You (Version 2) Come In With The Rain Crazier (Version 1) Crazier (Version 2) I Heart ? Invisible Mary's Song (Oh My My My) Picture To Burn Teardrops On My Guitar The Outside</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 03:12:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Acoustic demos have a scratchy sound and were just recorded by a simple recorder with Taylor and her guitar/piano. Studio songs are songs that were recorded for Taylor Swift/ Fearless and were cut for one reason or another. For example, Dark Blue Tennessee was meant to go in Fearless but was cut in favor of White Horse Volume 2 was a studio acoustic album that Taylor went door to door hanging out before her fame. Demos are songs that have been finalized and released but these versions are their earliest stages and have gone through lyric/ instrument changes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 03:24:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>For instance, the song  #8220;Tell Me #8221; was a song that was meant to be included in either Taylor Swift or Fearless and was recorded and finalized but was cut from the final album. It #8217;s a song about lack of communication at the end of a relationship and I consider it one of the best songs she #8217;s ever written. The chorus goes:  #8220;Could ya tell me, what did I do? Because it can #8217;t be we #8217;re already through. Did you sell me out for a fool after you held me? Is that just what you do? #8221; The song trade is a circulation of unreleased songs for diehard fans to enjoy. You obtain a song and trade it so another song trader for one you don #8217;t have but leaking a song to an entire community is frowned upon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 13:18:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, most of the songs are online. I have and am willing to hand out songs. I #8217;m just not willing to leak it massively.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 13:19:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. I need to fix that but the idea is he same.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 13:20:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most can be found online. Some people (such as myself) am willing to share a few to help get people stated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 13:20:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>The IC and DBT really is horrible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 13:22:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can send you some.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 13:24:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>And I hope you #8217;re not referring to me as a horrible person. I #8217;ve sent people songs they didn #8217;t have many times when they had nothing to offer. I just don #8217;t post download links or anything like that but yeah, I #8217;m pretty bitter about the IC or WIAB</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 13:27:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay for everyone that commented that #8217;s curious you can message me and I #8217;ll help you with a few songs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 16:12:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha! I bet so! You should totally share sometimes. It #8217;s nice to have someone else to bitch about them  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 16:17:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>My rarest is a piano demo of a song called  #8220;We Were Happy #8221; We Were Happy is a song probably meant for Taylor Swift. It was finalized and it #8217;s a beautiful song and it #8217;s one of the most common ones but I also happen to own the very original demo recording of it. It #8217;s hard to find a demo of a released song let alone an unreleased one. These horrible websites are definitely not the only places to trade them. These two websites are run by a group of people that have someone obtained songs that nobody else has. They also won #8217;t hand them out under any circumstances. They claim its to protect Taylor #8217;s privacy but really, it #8217;s just to protect their own rare status:  #8220;We have something you don #8217;t but we #8217;re not gonna let you hear it but we #8217;re gonna post how awesome they are #8221; There is one song I would kill for. It #8217;s called  #8220;Nashville #8221; and it #8217;s not to be confused with the live cover she did on the Speak Now Tour. Nashville is regarded by those who have heard it as the best and most beautiful song ever and every trader is hunting for it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 16:19:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn #8217;t Steve like stalk her or something or am I thinking of someone else?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 17:58:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I read that somewhere before but I #8217;m in slight denial and I like to pretend it #8217;s authentic  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 17:58:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>DM me and I #8217;ll send it to you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 18:00:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t know why! It #8217;s so good. I remember I was dating my ex whenever I first heard You All Over Me and I remember thinking  #8220;I bet this is the song I #8217;m gonna cry over when he leaves me #8221; and it is  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 18:02:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know she had some super stalker that stalked her in her early years and I could #8217;ve sworn I saw the name Steve but I #8217;m not sure. In any event, I can #8217;t particularly agree with his methods. I just think having a website where he boasts about the songs nobody else has is salt in the wound but I can #8217;t judge his character for certain.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 18:23:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay! So I #8217;m not crazy! That actually did happen!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 19:45:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or, and this is just a thought, I assumed only people who knew about the trades would comment because that #8217;s who this post was directed at</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 05:05:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly! It #8217;s one thing to have a song that nobody else has but it #8217;s another to make a blog bragging about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:08:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>DM Me and I will!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My dog doesn #8217;t love me anymore?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 07:15:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dog doesn #8217;t like me anymore. We used to be best friends and he #8217;d never leave my room or my side. I moved out of my parents house and in with two of my best friends. This has of course become financially difficult so I picked up a second job on top of being in school. My dog latched onto one of my roommates. He always hangs with him and sleeps with him. My dog doesn #8217;t even get excited anymore to see me. He doesn #8217;t listen to me anymore. My roommate actually rubs it in my face too by making comments like  #8220;guess I #8217;m your favorite human now! #8221; whenever they are playing and not to get personal but I #8217;m already in a crippling depression and this is really making me feel even worse. Advice? Thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Reputation tour set list?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 17:08:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want your dream set lists Personally, I want a Getaway Car/ IKYWT mash up  #128513;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tips for hiding self harm scars?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 14:53:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi! I recently got invited to go the beach with my boyfriend and his family for next month. I haven #8217;t been seen without my shirt in public in years but I also haven #8217;t been to the beach in years and it #8217;s my favorite place to be. I use to self harm a lot when I struggled really bad with depression. There are many scars on my upper left arm that are always hidden by my shirt sleeve. My boyfriend has obviously seen them and knows about it but I wanted to know if there was anything I could do to cover them up while I #8217;m there in front of his family or just the rest of the beach goers in general? Thank you  #128158;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>