<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7326</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Weak wifi?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-29 03:58:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-29 04:16:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is anyone else having these abysmal speeds? I have 200mbps/down and tested it with 3 other devices that confirm it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-29 05:12:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, exactly. I'm wondering if it's a bad radio in some of these early units</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-29 05:23:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Restarted the router, restarted the modem and nothing. Tested wifi on the note 4, 5 and Microsoft surface, and all are getting excellent speeds</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-29 05:50:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the feedback! I think that's what I'll do</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do you prefer to record in 1080p 60fps or 4k? And why?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-03 03:49:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Did anyone try to calibrate their display?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-03 15:04:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-03 16:12:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you try adjusting via manual mode?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-03 17:34:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>So many complain about it not being an Amoled display, I figured maybe this can help with saturation</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-06 00:30:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had that happen a few times. Try activating the Bluetooth before starting the vehicle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-08 01:54:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is going to sound funny but put your mouth over the headphone port and suck IN really really hard. Do that a couple of times</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-08 02:14:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try this... Plug in your #160;headphones, power down the #160;phone, power on the #160;phone #160;then remove the #160;headphones</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>He found the camera</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 01:07:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 14:25:29</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128522; you would be surprised how inexpensive it actually is</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 14:49:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is why it's hard becoming a vegetarian  #128522; #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 21:20:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably angry cause T-Mobile Tuesday only gave him 1 free small frosty from Wendy's</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 22:04:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tahini sauce would go great with this  #129316;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is my screen F'd?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-06 02:07:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Phone connected to LTE Band 1?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 05:09:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 05:27:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're right, it was wrong. Showing B4 with signalcheck. Thank you!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 05:38:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, but I'm guessing it had something to do with the phone being updated to android 7.0 just prior to that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 05:56:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the information. I was just worried that the update may have disabled band 4, being as it's an unlocked Sprint phone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 01:03:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha yeah</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Very sad news  #128546;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 16:41:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>As an adult, I'm not eating nearly as much Ice cream as 10 year old me though I would</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 20:56:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Don't you hate it when you're driving along smoking a cigarette, you flick it out the window and you drive for a couple more miles and smell something funny and you look over onto the back seat and sure enough..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 21:49:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Grandma's fingering herself again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 14:13:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>To all, I am not trying to pass this joke as OC. I found this online and thought it was funny, so I thought I'd share it here. I did not know who Doug Benson was until you started mentioning him in the comments. I apologize!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 18:49:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol nah New York native</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 19:26:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ohh snap I thought I posted this to the speedtest megathread. How do I move this in there?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 19:39:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brooklyn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 23:47:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was Arnold Schwarzenegger a cool dude to work with?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>School starts next month</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 17:25:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 18:25:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Movies is Top Secret! Though, not a Mel Brooks film</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Breitling Chronomat 44 B01] My favorite in my collection</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 21:49:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 22:00:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Breitling #8217;s flagship model Known for its functional design and outstanding precision, the Breitling Chronomat is a world classic amongst aviation watches. It's striking bezel with four rider tabs is considered to be one of the trademarks of the Breitling collection. The history of this unique wristwatch is far from boring since the Chronomat has been reinvented and reinterpreted countless times. Today #8217;s Chronomat (Ref. AB014012 or Ref. AB011610) bears hardly any resemblance to the original model of the collection (Ref. 769). In the 1940s, Breitling created a sensational watch that offered not only a time display and a chronograph function, but also an integrated slide rule. This allowed the wearer to perform various calculations by simply rotating the bezel. The manual-wind chronograph was named  #8220;Chronomat #8221;, pointing out the chronograph function as well as the mathematical function of the watch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Deadbolt won't lock with key?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 01:49:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have no issues unlocking with key and no issues with locking or unlocking from the inside. What could be the problem? Thanks in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fascinating!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 03:18:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 18:05:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>May be someone you know and no limit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 14:29:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>What resolution are you recording in?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 18:36:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, at this point with the lg v30 being announced next week, I'd wait. LG V30 will superior almost in every way (minus removable battery and IR blaster)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 18:49:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah it'll be $800+ If you do decide to purchase the LG V20, make sure it's carrier branded, because I believe the unlocked varient is no longer supported by LG for future updates/patches</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Difficult decision</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 20:57:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>90% of being married is just shouting "what" from other rooms...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 00:19:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'd rather take a razor scooter to the ankle 55 times than tell the class a fun fact about myself</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 16:10:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>For everything else there's Mastercard</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 00:41:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I hate it when these porn movie plots never finish. Did the pool get cleaned? Did the pizza get cold? Did the baby sitter get paid?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 16:05:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>On the next episode of McGregor VS.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 20:14:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you've been working hard for 1 hour and you're still not a millionaire</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 14:35:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Live footage of Joel Osteen while on top of the Lakewood Church during Hurricane Harvey</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 14:56:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Lincoln penny</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 20:54:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bunny kisses</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 22:59:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Belly tickles</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 00:56:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wakey Wakey cat cat</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 14:10:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mornings summed up</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 15:07:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 21:11:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had something similar happen when I was unlocking a Sprint note 5. The UICC unlock option should be somewhere in the settings menu, try to go to About phone. Or search in the setting for UICC. At least that's how it was with the note 5. But sprint has to unlock it and it usually takes 1-2 days to be "unlocked"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 21:40:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look for the phone on swappa.com you'll find a great deal there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MRW my friend doesn't know where the rave is</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 03:01:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MRW my friend doesn't know where the rave is</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 19:28:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 19:41:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's playing just fine on my phone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>For previous Note 7 owner</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 21:28:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>As per Samsung FAQs, it says, "You will get UP to $425 off Galaxy Note8 with trade-in of eligible phone on Samsung.com or the Shop Samsung app." Then is says "We will evaluate your device when we receive it, and if it does not meet the conditions described above, or if it is a device that is not eligible for trade in under this promotion then Samsung will value it at twenty five dollars ($25.00) and charge you the trade-In credit that was applied to the purchase of the Galaxy Note8 minus the twenty-five dollar ($25.00) value ( #8220;Device Condition or Ineligible Device Charge"). Please note that your old device cannot be returned to you. So does this mean is they value your trade in at less and you'll be responsible for the rest? Sorry if this question has be answered already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 21:35:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right, but if the device meets their criteria can they still value it at less? Because no where does it say it's automatically $425 off, it's says up to $425</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Jackie Channing Tatum</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 04:45:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Eat your f*cking cereal, Leo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 14:57:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 15:14:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I taking credit for this as original? Do you see it say [OC] anywhere?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 15:17:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>And BTW, here a link to what happens in the real film https://youtu.be/DV6EGCZeMOA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 15:22:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>But I do see your point. Someone made it into a trailer and it's not a combined gif</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Solid knitting skills</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 18:54:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Player 3 has entered the game</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 22:46:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Brain melt</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 14:44:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A$$hole Monkey!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 17:11:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Save the skateboard!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 02:37:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A$$hole Monkey!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 05:06:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>But all the cool kids are doing it</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 16:06:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stunning!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 16:08:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 22:25:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ive ordered from Samsung in the past (not cell phones) and on more than one occasion the item would arrive on my door step, while online said pre-order or preparing for shipment. Hopefully this doesn't happen with the note 8 though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MRW my German relatives ask if I speak German</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 21:53:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are you ready for the new IT movie?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 21:56:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are you ready for the new IT movie?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 22:00:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Remember to opt out of arbitration within 30 days</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 22:23:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Found this on the android central forum: In case you weren't aware, Samsung has an arbitration only clause ( no lawsuits, no class action). You can opt out within 30 days of purchase by following these instructions: "You may opt out of this Agreement by providing notice to Samsung no later than 30 calendar days from the date of the first consumer purchaser #8217;s purchase of the Product. To opt out, you must send notice by e-mail to optout@sea.samsung.com, with the subject line:  #8220;Arbitration Opt Out. #8221; You must include in the opt-out email (a) your name and address; (b) the date on which the Product was purchased; (c) the Product model name or model number; and (d) the IMEI or MEID or Serial Number, as applicable, if you have it (the IMEI or MEID or Serial Number can be found (i) on the Product box; (ii) on the Product information screen which can be found under  #8220;Settings; #8221; (iii) on a label on the back of the Product beneath the battery, if the battery is removable; and (iv) on the outside of the Product if the battery is not removable)." This is an excerpt of Samsung arbitration clause: "YOU AND SAMSUNG EACH AGREE THAT ALL DISPUTES BETWEEN YOU AND SAMSUNG RELATING IN ANY WAY TO OR ARISING IN ANY WAY FROM THE STANDARD LIMITED WARRANTY OR THE SALE, CONDITION OR PERFORMANCE OF THE PRODUCT SHALL BE RESOLVED EXCLUSIVELY THROUGH FINAL AND BINDING ARBITRATION, AND NOT BY A COURT OR JURY. ANY SUCH DISPUTE SHALL NOT BE COMBINED OR CONSOLIDATED WITH A DISPUTE INVOLVING ANY OTHER PERSON #8217;S OR ENTITY #8217;S PRODUCT OR CLAIM, AND SPECIFICALLY, WITHOUT LIMITATION OF THE FOREGOING, SHALL NOT UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES PROCEED AS PART OF A CLASS ACTION. THE ARBITRATION SHALL BE CONDUCTED BEFORE A SINGLE ARBITRATOR, WHOSE AWARD MAY NOT EXCEED, IN FORM OR AMOUNT, THE RELIEF ALLOWED BY THE APPLICABLE LAW. " http://forums.androidcentral.com/e?l...token=rbkTak1J</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-08 15:07:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Turn off quick charge when charging overnight</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>PsBattle: This well dressed male model</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-08 18:18:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-08 21:16:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hulu has a show based on this book, titled 11.22.63. Pretty damn good show</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Situation in Florida</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 20:44:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Report live from hurricane Irma...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 20:53:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does the Note 8 still have a 5 minute record limitation in 4K resolution?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-11 22:39:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 01:08:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just like GTA</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 16:18:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is there an option to turn on VoLTE or is on by default? (for Tmobile version)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 21:48:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 21:54:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Understood. I asked because the lg v20 had the option to turn on /off volte, so I thought I was missing something. Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Story time with Danny</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 15:16:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Met an older woman at a bar last night.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 14:21:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>She wasn't bad for 57, we drank and flirted a bit, then she asked if I'd ever had a mother and daughter combo? I said no. We drank a bit more, then she says that tonight is my lucky night. I went back to her place. She put the hall light on and shouted upstairs: "Mom, you still awake?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A man left for work one Friday afternoon.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 14:32:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>But it was payday, so instead of going home, he stayed out the entire weekend partying with the boys and spending his entire pay check. When he finally appeared at home on Sunday night, he was confronted by his angry wife and was barraged for nearly two hours with a tirade befitting his actions. Finally his wife stopped the nagging and said to him, "How would you like it if you didn't see me for two or three days?" He replied, "That would be fine with me." Monday went by and he didn't see his wife. Tuesday and Wednesday came and went with the same results. But on Thursday, the swelling went down just enough where he could see her a little out of the corner of his left eye</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MRW my girlfriend says my hand smells bad but I don't smell anything</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 17:57:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The length of time toddlers stare at each other on the playground would get you stabbed if you did that shit as an adult.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 21:22:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>PsBattle: This contortionist pointing at a bar chart</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 22:52:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Damn you Newton!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 17:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>NSA getting excited</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 22:31:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Make a smart decision</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 14:37:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've never seen a chicken with curly feathers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-24 13:44:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>PsBattle: This chicken with curly feathers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-24 15:57:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Desktop of greatness, back in the day</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-24 16:55:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What the monsters of Doom actually saw</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 23:13:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You can't see him</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 14:50:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Whipped</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 03:34:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does this hernia make me look fat?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 06:43:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How I imagine kindergarten teachers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 06:55:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hello October</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-02 16:25:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Squirrel stealing a pumpkin</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-02 18:11:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's how the pros do it</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 01:42:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guy catches his chicken sleeping on the job</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 01:57:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thank you good human</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 04:05:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'd eat you but I can't get up</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 01:51:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You know those sex houses, the little wooden houses with the hole for your dick that people hang in trees?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 21:22:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apparently those are for birds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is your take on higher job title vs higher salary?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 22:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"I know Kung Fu"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 21:40:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Didn't know this was legal?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 22:22:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Game names taken literally</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 14:54:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can't we all just get along?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-30 13:14:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What are some things you can say to your dog but not your girlfriend?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 14:30:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you were younger, what cartoon/show did you watch after coming home from school?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 15:41:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What was the hardest interview question you were ever asked?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 17:05:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's your interpretation of wealthy vs rich?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 20:51:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What world event happened on your date of birth?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 03:38:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is it like to be poor in a rich group of friends?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 22:27:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the biggest culture shock you ever faced?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 01:12:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If you had to watch one movie repeatedly for 24 hrs, what movie would you watch?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 04:03:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Harvey Weinstein sexually assaulting young aspiring actress.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 18:23:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>All we hear is Radio Gaga!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 18:36:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sooo fluffy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:30:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Terry Crews is talented AF!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 15:45:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"I Dropped My Hot Pocket"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 03:47:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is something you pretend to understand, but really don't?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 18:18:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What are you afraid of?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 13:30:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Plot twist</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 03:20:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Such a majestic horse</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 21:45:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Destroying wine glass with laser pointer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 21:50:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Seiko TV Watch</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 04:54:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Baby wants ice cream</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 05:08:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Don't mess with Jesus</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 02:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My feels weren't ready for this</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 16:22:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fake news</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 21:52:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What sentence could use during sex and also a family dinner?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 02:05:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You should see my view</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 21:13:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is your wealth accumulation strategy?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 17:06:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What piece of pop culture did your parents ban when you were younger?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 13:44:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"Warren G ft. Nate Dogg  amp; Michael Mcdonald - Regulate (Remix)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 01:25:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nostalgia - GEARS OF WAR- (Mad World Trailer)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 00:54:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>5 Second Rule with Sofia Vergara</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 03:01:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Of all the things that you have lost in your entire life, what would you reclaim (if it could be anything), and why?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 04:23:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Name a petty reason why you won't date someone?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 04:21:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Death wish...but employed!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 23:57:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ok third place it is</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 03:50:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Confused criminal</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 18:41:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Give back my kid!!!!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 15:24:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ass crack violation</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 16:30:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fishy tricks</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 02:53:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The unbeatable Martial Arts technique</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 02:24:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What Star Wars quote to shout out during sex?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 21:46:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Once in a lifetime shot</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 21:56:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pro Level 1000</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 22:00:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thumb job</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 07:37:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's wrong with our society today?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 03:57:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Life hack for mobile FPS games</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 02:08:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Neon Lights</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 18:38:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's your game?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 04:32:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Leg cramp</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 14:37:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 21:59:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Found the original source https://youtu.be/6jV3F52XMhA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>LSPD and their disregard of public safety</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 19:52:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Could it be true?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 00:26:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do I have to do everything myself?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 21:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>At the gates of Hell</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 15:32:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>GPU Turbo update not coming to US</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:09:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Where to even begin...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:54:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What are some random facts about yourself?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 05:43:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>At least he's wearing a hard hat</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 14:44:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fahaka puffer feeding</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 19:52:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>THAT feeling</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 02:31:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>To do a jumping jack</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 01:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yogurt, anyone?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 14:57:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stay for the end</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 15:38:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to refill your lighter</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 01:52:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Must be a delicious sandwic.... Ohh WTF!!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:12:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Smell this picture</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 04:16:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>To impress the judges</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 15:38:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>He gonna die tonight</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 16:38:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fuck! What do I do now???</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 17:51:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>