<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject8233</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-11 21:29:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>No revenge and the OP used WAAAYYY too many parentheses. That 4th paragraph was just fuckery and nearly impossible to read. Then it just sucks to get to the end, realise the post sucks and that re-reading that parentheses garbage to try to make sense of it was just an even bigger waste of time. Downvote fo show.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 01:21:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>American Starbursts are way better. The ones here are mingin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Most creative uses of cantrips</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 01:53:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a fairly new player, I love reading about interesting and creative uses for minor spells and cantrips. What are the most creative ways you've used cantrips and spells, especially those involving trickery and cunning? Specifically shouting out things like minor illusion, prestidigitation, thaumaturgy, and things like that that have endless possibilities. Edit: if there are numerous posts already like this, please link me to them. I'm also fairly new to reddit (this is my first post) and would be more than happy to be linked up instead of having to try and search for this kind of thread specifically.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 02:08:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've done something similar with my Tiefling and his innate darkness. Useful indeed, though I've tripped once with a bad roll, as I couldn't see. That time, it didn't help much (read, at all) because by the time I was back up and running, they had just gone around my darkness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 02:24:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I LOVE catapult! I have used it to throw flasks of oil at enemies.. Then I use firebolt on my next turn to set them ablaze. They then burn for ages until they are dead, from my experience. I will have to focus on dropped weapons more.. I like the idea of dealing extra damage somehow with this spell. I have also used it to throw an Alchemist's fire and acid at an enemy, but sadly, the fire missed the only time I tried it and that was a waste of 50g.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 02:26:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very sneaky indeed!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 02:28:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like this one, especially if anything makes you barf. On the other end of this is causing NPC's to soil themselves when they annoy you. You raise the price on this item? Well fine then, but you sir.. Have just soiled yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 03:28:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Noice. I have used it to avoid fights as well. Enemies were trying to light something on fire. Used minor illusion to make it look like they succeeded,and had a back-up minor illusion caster create fire sounds. The enemies left having thought they succeeded. Otherwise it would have been a nasty fight. I've also used minor illusion to hide my gnome in a crate, convince npc's we're there to help them by recreating an image of the person they trust that sent us, lure people out of houses with a bit of deceit about somebody dying and then adding a blood-curdling scream for help, and more. I'm always down to hear more uses and even more creative ways of using this nifty lil cantrip.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 18:50:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like that idea! I've only used it in its proper way, but this is creative indeed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 01:28:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. Having cancer gets you fuck all. So glad okkokk has also had cancer and is down to earth and realised that they're dying just like everyone else. Except for the part where they have cancer and could die much quicker. Like seriously.. If having cancer isnt an excuse for throwing up, what is? Wish i could downvote okkokk's reply more than once.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 01:29:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree! You should edit the story to include this sensational news!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 16:16:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm still fairly new to reddit. Had no idea downvote trolls were a thing...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found in Edinburgh</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 02:30:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Don't be tryin to charge me for a few extra black olives Subway!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 19:37:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I rarely get Subway, but every time I have had it, I've never once had a problem with getting a bit more veg if I asked. This was not the case once in a Memphis location nearest the city bus station. I have only recently gotten more creative with my orders, but before this, my order would always be the exact same: oven baked chicken breast on honey oat with lettuce, pickles and black olives. I think that employees must think that people don't like black olives much so they rarely put more than a sprinkle on. I've always had to ask for just a bit more, please. As I'm only ever getting three veg choices out of the many, many different options, I never feel too bad about asking for a bit more as I think this is pretty reasonable. On this particular occasion, I order my regular and when it comes time for the black olives, my artist (the only person seemingly working at the time) literally puts 6 black olives on it. I ask for more, and on goes maybe 4 additional olives. In my politest voice, I ask if she could put some more on as they are my favourite topping. She says, "I can put more on but I'll have to charge you X amount for extra toppings." I'm dumbfounded for a second. I've literally never been told that asking for a bit more would cost extra at any Subway I've ever been to or any I've been to since then. After a quick second of thought, I say, "No worries. I don't need more. Can I just get the works now please?" The works, if you're unfamiliar, is everything (or almost everything) they have to offer on the free veg side. She obliges and proceeds to fill it up with everything on offer. I then ask for about 4 different sauces and then watch her as she tries to wrap up this disgusting, saucy, packed sub. As she's about to put it through the till, I simply say, "I've changed my mind. I think I would have just been satisfied with a decent portion of black olives at no extra charge." Cue my immediate exit as she's speechless with mouth agape. Tl;dr Subway worker tries to make me pay for a few extra olives so I make her add EVERYTHING and then leave without a sandwich or paying. Edit: This seems to be a very polarising post as it's getting nearly as many downvotes as upvotes. While this doesn't bother me, I do just want to clarify a few things. At no point was I anything but polite to this girl. I realise she is just doing her job and never once degraded her, raised my voice, or cursed. Whether she is just that dedicated or whether it was a strict branch, I understand that she is just doing it the way she was shown. At the end of the day, when her boss checks as to why she had to throw away a sandwhich, she will simply say she was following protocol and that the customer chose not to purchase it do to an extra charge. This should only ensure she gets a pat on the back for doing her job to a T. However, I'd like to think that if enough people walked out after being charged extra for a lil veg, they'd be forced to rethink their policies at this particular location. In the end, this will only barely hurt either the massive corporation of Subway or a franchise owner who is stingier than ANY other Subway I've ever been to across the world. I'm fine with that. This was posted in petty revenge after all..?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 21:10:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>As stated, she was working alone. Either she was the dickwad manager, or she just was strict herself. I mean.. It's not as if he manager has counted the olives and knows when she gives out 10 too many. She chose to charge extra when there was nobody there micromanaging her. If it had been like the situation you experienced, I still would have been this petty and made my parting remark directly to the micromanager. Also remember, she barely put any on in the first place. I was not requesting some insane, unreasonable amount of free toppings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 23:26:40</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128514; I'm new to reddit. Had the app for like a month. This is my 3rd post ever. Don't know what story is similar but I can assure you that I barely know what karma is or how it works and could give a fuck less. You do you though. Ps. I actually AM gay and calling something gay as a derogatory thing was never really acceptable, but even less so in 2017. You might wanna work on that...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 23:39:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>A lil bit, though it was only due to my homosexuality. Gotta love small farming community high schools!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 23:44:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are always policies. I think this may be one of those things that is in the books but followed on only the rarest of occasions by the strictest of locations. I don't blame employees for the policies by any means. In every service job I've had there have always been some things that are the corporate-correct way to do it and then the way that everyone actually does it. This just seems to be one of those things for Subway. Thank you for recognising that 6 olives is a bit ridiculous! You were one of the good ones.  #128076;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 23:51:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yaas!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 00:58:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know this may seem like 1st-world-entitlement, but I already wasn't going to pay more for something that didn't match the same standard as every other Subway I've ever been to. That's just consumerism. I shared this because it is a petty revenge story against a giant corporation who wastes way more food on a nightly basis than my lonely lil sub, and this was only because, at one of their locations, they tried to jack the prices unexpectedly. My manner in everything is polite which is defined as "having or showing behaviour that is respectful and considerate of other people." The definition of polite doesn't seem to say you have to buy something that is at an unreasonable price just so you don't waste food. The only "person" harmed from this experience was the corporation or a stingy owner. Soo Yeah. I stand by the fact that I was politely protesting in my own way the injustice of being told to pay extra at one of several dozen Subways I've ever been to just for a few extra olives. If I'm paying for something, I expect some quality. Soz if that makes me awful. Soo to recap, the major opinion I see here is your opinion on what is considered polite and my "opinion" on what is polite by dictionary standards.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 01:17:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I merely deleted that comment because it seemed to take away from where the general thread was going. Still new to reddit. Just doin my part and sharing what I believe to be a decent petty revenge story. To add, this was about 1 and half hours to closing, and I was the only person in shop. I wasn't holding up other customers. I would argue my time was wasted as well because I wasn't going to pay extra at a chain restaurant when I've never encountered that before. An eye for an eye? Sounds petty and deserving enough of this thread.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 03:04:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>No no. He called me a twat and said all this before he knew I was actually slightly bullied for being gay. Thanks for sticking up for victims, but I'm gonna make sure that this dudes post is only seen as him disagreeing with me by way of HS jokes and not homophobia. Ps. Retarded is no longer really acceptable to use as a derogatory statement, especially in 2017. Thanks for kind of having my back but you should still work on the ways you use that word.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 08:59:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great job reading the part where it literally spells it out how this could never actually affect this girl's job. Thumbs up friend! I was on a cross country bus trip and was never going to be there again. I certainly wasn't going above and beyond in my efforts to change this shitty Memphis locations policy. My time had been wasted enough. I needed to find something else to eat and quick before my next bus left.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 09:07:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair enough.. I had been having a drink at that point. Entirely fair assumption that I missed a point. Still don't like the word retarded being thrown around. Seems like a person who hates bullying so much would understand why that's a hurtful word in and of itself. Even more hurtful when you use it in a derogatory way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 12:53:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shit that I get free at every single other Subway I've ever been to. Also.. Fuck you too random person..? Is that how reddit works? We just fruitlessly tell each other to fuck off? At least say something original that's going to make me "change my ways." Your comment is lacking finesse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 12:57:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like I'm on repeat here. This was a single location out of dozens and dozens I've been to. This has happened once in my 29 years. When you've spent 29 years paying the same amount for something, you're not suddenly gonna pay more because of some strict stores policy. Hopefully if people did this a few times, they would stop skimping and start being like literally EVERY SINGLE OTHER SUBWAY EVER. And to recap, I didn't treat the worker like a dick in any way for her doing her job. I would never belittle a fast food worker.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 13:01:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You literally used the word literally 6 times within 4 small paragraphs. Literally think you should get yourself a thesaurus.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 13:01:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheers! So many haters!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 13:02:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 13:03:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Asshole OR cunt? Well which is it?! I'm on the edge of my seat here..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 13:27:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That username haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 13:32:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>As I've said previously to a since deleted comment, I've only been on reddit for a month, this is my third post ever, and I could give a fuck less about karma as I'm not even fully aware how it works. I have 0 motivation to make shit up. The guy in your story sounds like a dick as well. I was nowhere near that devious and I would never purposefully try to make a service worker cry. Good job, though, on finding a barely similar story about a guy who also went to a Subway. Thumbs up!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 13:37:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used plenty of other words as well. I honestly just thought you were a touch damaged. The follow up comment does not dispel this notion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 14:15:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love these!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 14:40:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just fairly over it all in general. Can't be bothered arguing the same points again and again. And yeah.. When you sound like a crazy person, I'll call you crazy. I wouldn't say it's my go to, just that you earned it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 14:56:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just as nasty as somebody who goes around calling strangers nasty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 15:02:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I keep making the same points because people keep saying the same things. In the end, it's got slightly more upvotes than downvotes so it seems the slight majority agree with me that this was an ok act of petty revenge. Carry on thinking whatever you want of me. I could LITERALLY give less fucks about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 15:11:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>There was no mistreatment. Did I accidentally put a paragraph in my story where I said that I went on a rant and called this artist a cunt and then punched her in the face? She makes sandwiches. I had her make me a sandwich and then left because I wasn't satisfied with that locations policies. I just fail to see how this is mistreatment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 16:25:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel no need to repeat, again, all of my rebuttals to what amounts to be the same comment over and over again. I feel even less of a need to justify it to somebody who makes light of rape of any kind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 16:28:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think it was out of spite either. I just wanted to cause waste to show them that charging extra for more than 10 olives on a 12 inch sub was actually going to cause them to lose money rather than make the extra amount of whatever the extra veg charge was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 16:50:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just have to repeat myself because people don't want to take a few minutes to see that their unoriginal thought has been posted many times previously. I don't consider this petty revenge rude in the least. Also.. Yeah. You still suck rape dude. Your opinion literally means less than dirt to me. Go be a terrible person somewhere else where rape is somehow ok to joke about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 17:21:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your remark to him wins Reddit for today</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 22:12:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had never been there before and I'll never be there again. It was while I was waiting for a second bus during a pit stop in Memphis. She seemed dead set on the extra charge so I wasn't even going to try.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 23:39:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>This would make me wanna die more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 00:02:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cha cha now y'all</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 00:11:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't lost my virginity until 19. Don't rush it. Mine was with a dude who's name I can't even remember. Also, I was a huge slut after that and more than made up for it over the next few years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 00:38:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I made the same pact with myself. I'll be 29 in a few months and have basically been depressed and fucked up since my teenage years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 00:54:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wtf page did I just look at?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 01:16:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why exactly would she get in trouble? For following the rules and not letting me have extra? Did you not even read the whole post? I've covered this already. Surely she will only get praise for being strict if that's how they like her to be. You make no sense lady....siren.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 01:17:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. I really don't blame her. Just wanted the manager to know how stupid policies can actually cost more money than he saves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 01:26:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a smallish dick. I'm not really worried or embarrassed about it but when I was a pre-teen and began maturating, I was scared that I was jerking out all the testosterone that was suppose to make my cock bigger. For a long time, I thought my dick was below average because I couldn't stop wanking. I've never told anybody this dumb misconception because I'd have to bring up my penis size and that's just awkward.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 02:53:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's the comment? Read the thread. Spooky af. But i can't be reading 5,000 comments to find the one you considered creepy.. Is the story i just read the comment and I'm still too new to reddit to realise it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 05:51:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>So many questions... And so little time to educate your ignorance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 06:29:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I almost always hate things like this. Your video.. Was no exception. Haha jk! I surprisingly liked this all the way through. Congrats!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 18:38:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Poor lil snowflake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 19:30:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Typical snowflake response</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 09:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once had a guy offer to pay me $100 to complete a fantasy for him. I'm no prostitute, but I heard him out in case it was something easy where I wouldn't have to actually do anything sexual. Just for the record, I'm a gay male. He wanted me to go out into the woods with him "deep enough that nobody would ever hear us." Immediate alarm bells just from the first sentence and it gets way, way worse. He continues that he wants me to wear the same pair of socks for 3 days straight and bring them with us into the woods. He then wants me to get completely naked and suck him off all while he's smelling my dirty socks. After he gets off, he wants me to beat the shit out of him. He wants me to really lay into him until hes cut and bleeding from being pummled by my fists. Bear in mind that this dude is like late 60's and I'm only 21 at the time. I'm already thinking I could end up killing him. Anyway.. After his beating comes the cherry on top. He wants me to finish by pissing all over him and into his bleeding wounds. He asked if I could try to hold my piss in all morning so that is was "dark yellow and would be steamy in the cool temperature of the woods. It's important that your piss steam up out of my bleeding wounds." I really needed the money for rent so I agreed. I told him to pick me up from a nearby apartment complex that I didn't actually live in. Asked for the money up front, walked around to behind the building and got on my bike I had stashed there. Took off and never heard from him again. I'm still fairly certain one of us would have died had I gone into the woods with him. (I realise this last part makes me the bad guy as well. I was young and dumb and strapped for cash. Soz.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's something you absolutely hate that everyone else seems to love?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 11:53:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 11:54:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>For me, it's avocados. Gross, slimy shite that tastes like wet, mowed grass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 11:56:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>You've actually tried to watch it? How far did you get?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 12:05:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was lacking fo show.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 12:07:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate medieval shit too. Somebody basically forced me to watch a few episodes and I am now a devoted fan. I'd say this is one of those things you definitely have to try before saying you HATE it. Maybe just describe as refusing to watch it because you don't like that genre?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 12:08:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>And repetitive af. Snooze.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 12:22:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you hate Halloween too? Or is this like specifically anime cosplay or..?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 12:25:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>whoops. Nope. My bad. I was thinking of john oliver.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 12:29:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Across the board? Not even like babies in your family?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 12:37:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh. Well yeah. I've fantasised about smothering a few wailing babies I've been forced to be around. That's the worst.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 12:42:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is this abomination of which you speak?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 12:49:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel ya on this. The season never seems to fucking end. Like maybe 2 months a year of sweet, football-free bliss.. Unless it's the world cup or some other bs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 12:59:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh fair enough if it's cultural. Sounded like some awful fad thing started in the heart of california.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 13:02:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Poor frankie muniz. I was reading recently how his multiple strokes and medical condition have basically made him forget all the years and experiences he had making malcom in the middle. Like half a decade or more just wiped out and he's only in his young 30's</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 13:04:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you'll find this is 50/50 ish. Fuckin nasty, soapy shite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 13:06:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>My husband and I only got into after season 6 was finished. Literally watched all 6 seasons TWICE in a month and a half.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 13:22:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>What?! Which episode did you watch?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 13:24:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sunny side up? With like the white bits still being a bit embryotic and jelly-ish? That's the worst.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 13:29:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ass fuck is not one I've heard a lot but I will say I'm happy that "on fleek" has mostly disappeared. That was just dumb. Literally didn't mean anything other than on point and it wasn't even shortening the phrase in any way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 13:39:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe OP is referring to just a random person in their lives which I find quite amusing for this thread. They've got my upvote.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 13:40:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe so and she's annoying af.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 13:41:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you also hate frenching?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 13:47:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm guessing you much prefer Fake News instead? Oops. Meant Fox News.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 14:12:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you hear that on Fox?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 14:24:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>How many episodes have you seen?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 15:11:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah.. No thanks. I'd rather not pay an extra 2 bucks just to have avocado mush ruin my burrito.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 15:12:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you a m or f? I think this makes a difference.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 15:13:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well.. You tried.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 15:28:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hanging up on somebody without saying goodbye. Everyone answering phones on the first ring. Those ridiculous 30 course breakfasts that always seemed to be made by moms and then immediately skipped by everyone else. And of course, just the perfect looking people. The character will have just gotten out of the rain, they'll be in prison or a post-apocolyptic world, exploring alien planets or deep beneath the earth in some cave but I'll be damned if their hair and make-up aren't always absolutely perfect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 15:31:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why would you read it twice?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 15:54:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got wayy too drunk at a high school party and was sitting still kind of swaying back and forth, really out of it. My best friend threw a mcdonalds bbq sauce at me to try to "wake me up" but instead it got me square on the nose. I had been swimming a lot lately and my nose was raw from the chlorine. As soon as the packet hit my nose, blood just came bursting out. I was way too drunk to deal with it so my best friend is just holding paper towel after paper towel against my face. I saw it the next morning and we're talking like 8 paper towels full of blood. Anyway.. It was actually my best mates party so she called it off after this and started telling people to go home. There were loads of people still arriving at the time who could see me plain as day bleeding and what i thought would be very obviously drunk. The rumor that started was that my best mate and I were huge cokeheads and doing tons of cocaine at this high school party. Like, for literal years people thought we were cokeheads. I had dodgier people in school I barely knew trying to get me to score for them etc until the end of my high school career. This always just seemed really dumb to me. People who are on too much cocaine would not look the same as a person who had had too much to drink.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 16:00:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>How many people groan after making a pun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 16:14:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>As are straight men. I think this one we can just leave at "people are weird sometimes."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 16:27:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Should check out British tv shows. They usually like to keep them short and sweet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 16:31:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've heard of many people not liking the taste but love the smell. At least you're consistent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 16:36:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly! I can confirm that flamin hot cheetos encrusted chicken is fucking awesome. Tonight I'm actually making homemade mozzarella sticks with flamin hot cheeto breading. Should be noice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 16:49:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've actually heard a ton of variations of this kind of thing, but honestly.. It never gets old. Have the upvote simply because of how hard it is to learn a second language.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 16:50:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I think I talk better than I right" hahaha I can guarantee this as it would have been correct had you spoken this sentence. (It's write, not right.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 16:58:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha I think if I knew you in any way, I would have known it was irony. As it stands, there are plenty of people who suck at spelling that this mistake is not competely out of the realm of possibilities.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 17:01:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>?? Could you link to the story about his drug issues? From what I always knew, he was famously not into drugs and was never caught up with that scene. The strokes and seizures are purely from a rare medical condition. He even has a tat of the word zero which means, for him, zero tolerance for alcohol or drugs. I'm curious to see what you can come up with though...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 17:08:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to send asshole customers to the queue line for the spanish helpline. They would only get hold music for absolute ages and then come on the line to find out they were with people who only speak spanish. Many of the spanish people can also speak English but it was required by my company that they had to be put back through to the english line so they could never lie and say something was wrong with their account because they weren't understood.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 17:27:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>No probs! Literally mixed up some celebs myself on this post. Confused jamie oliver for john oliver. Haha. It happens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 17:37:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Saaame. My sister in law says it's one of her favourite movies so we inevitably watch it every. Fucking. Christmas. Nobody wants to ever watch A Christmas Story though which is mine.. (To be fair, I'm american and living in England. Having married into an English family I understand why they dont have the same nostalgia for my movie. It was never a thing here.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 17:39:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll give this a try sometime</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 17:39:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Runny yoke = yum Runny white bits = fuck off and die.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 18:26:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah.. Gonna try this.. Though I always cook mine with butter so going with the butter spooning suggestion that was made a bit ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 18:27:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>The show? The person in your life? The name itself?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 18:28:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Smite!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 18:28:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 18:30:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eggs take like 2 minutes to make. How long you fryin these mo fuckers? I'm captain holt when it comes to egg making.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 18:35:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've never read it. Always meant to because of the hype.. I really just wish it had been required in my high school so it would have killed two birds.. Had to learn and read something I've meant to read for 15 years as well. Regardless of how awful it is, it couldn't have been worse than Lord of the Flies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 18:36:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>As in.. Everybody Loves Raymond?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 18:36:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Winner</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 18:38:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha the British.. Are you European by chance? I live in England but I'm American so.. I kind of get it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 18:40:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I respect your feelings but I just don't stop believing that it's a good song.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 18:42:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a gay man, I can say that anal sex can be quite pleasurable to a man. Some dicks can hit that spot in your bum where it rubs against your prostate and can make for an amazing, intense organism. For women.. I'm really not sure what the appeal is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 18:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha. So many dumb terms for things. And yeah.. Just to let you know.. That fake British advent that people do. Only about 5% of British people sound like that. British people have different British accents that vary from city to city. It's similar to how Americans can sound different of they're from the south, north, brooklyn, boston, cali.. Etc. There's LOADS of British accents and the weird part is that most of them can tell exactly which city a fellow brit is from based on a few sentences. It's bizarre.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 18:49:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>All the upvotes! Winter is king! No bugs. No heat. Beautiful snow. Love everything about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 19:27:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you a veggie?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 19:29:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. Thank you. After half a bottle of wine, I didn't understand that, but obviously me and the OP worked it out in the end. Maybe read the comments next time?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 19:30:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wasn't so much forgetting as being a bit drunk and letting my swype text do its thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 19:32:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is. Frozen didn't suck but ya. Tangled is better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 19:33:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Booooo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 19:37:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I personally like dressing up for Halloween. I've never done it otherwise unless it was a Fancy Dress party. I think it's fun and I can see why a lot of people have fun dressing up and pretending to be characters for a day. I'm sure it's a bit of a release for them from the mundane while their surrounded by other people who feel the same. I won't knock other people having fun in the non-harmful way they choose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 20:11:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm too drunk to care or tell. I'm hoping this is more sarcasm. If so, have an upvote! Otherwise.. Have an upvote because again.. I'm too drunk and tired to care</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 20:12:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Def.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 20:18:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have soo many things to say to this. But I'm drunk. So yeah don't listen to me say that Bernie didn't march with black people decades ago when it was unpopular. Bernie never stood for gay rights even though he spoke vehemently about it in the 90s. Bernie doesnt care about the middle class even though he cared so much about that demographic that he refused to take donations from big corporations and their lobbyists.. What a terrible advocate for the actual real people living in America.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 20:47:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never watched it but have had a similar experience with other shows.. Does it not feel like they ended it on a good note so viewers would be happy? Instead of dragging it out for 11 seasons or so when even die hard fans hate the show.. Watch "You, Me, and the Apocalypse" it's amazing of course but ended too soon. The britsh do that. If the second series won't be as good, it's over. I highly recommend Catastrophe and Him  amp; Her as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 20:49:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>But Drumf is better because..?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 22:06:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can anybody walk me through the steps of posting pictures? I'm new to reddit..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 22:33:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>No.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 09:14:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha. Gotta love swypes autofill. Was too drunk to even notice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 06:50:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Petty. I approve.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 19:32:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are underrepresented AND they never get fully naked seemingly. What are they hiding?!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>That sickening crunch when you've stepped on yet another snail..  #129314;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 22:04:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 19:53:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I fucked that dude. Was a good lay. And yeah. Waited until he was an adult naturally.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 14:09:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. Now I'm extra thirsty</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 20:32:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice body. Dunno if it's because of the way you're holding your phone or the way it seems like you're pushing your head forward, but your head looks almost like photoshopped and too big for your body. Haha I'm trying to unsee this but I can't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 00:43:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sexy af. Loved the old posts as well. Deffo reppin the underrepresented asians well!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 03:17:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've got freckles on mine too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 03:21:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah man. I love the body hair. Would be keen to see you shirtless</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 03:50:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>That boy is adorable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 04:13:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly one of the most perfect dicks I've ever seen and I've seen a lot!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 16:00:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking recent ones, but you do you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 16:03:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>For me, its the long lumberjack beards. I've always hated them and I wish they'd just go away already. The hipsters that go above and beyond awful by incorporating flowers, braids, bells, dyes or other dumb things into their beard also just Need. To. Stop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 16:04:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oo Yeah. And i saw once that live baby turtles in a necklace were popular in asia.. Just awful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 16:06:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a good one! The current version includes people tattooing a specific meme on themselves. Like memes don't even stay popular for a few months, let alone years. What are you doing to your body?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 20:24:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Noice. Good thickness.. Love the colour!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 18:29:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hot af</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 18:32:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn dude. So much cum. This is my new fave vid on reddit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 18:41:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know who that dude is but I can already tell that I would fucking hate him if I ever met him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 00:43:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perfect is definitely not some word to throw around. It should only be used to describe truly spectacular things like this dude's body.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #128514;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 19:49:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 02:10:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>A need for refrigeration and upvotes?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just shave it bro.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 14:16:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 14:18:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try Heinz 57.. It's been a long time since I've had it, but I remember it tasting very similar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 10:45:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meh. Whatever. Dumb subreddit. I'll just unfollow instead.  #128077;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pretty much.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 21:40:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 21:27:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is it. The dumbest thing I'll read today. That's really saying something considering how long and dumb this "prorevenge" story was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found on Plenty of Fish by a friend. She didn't go for it...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 13:57:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 11:28:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's pretty hot to be honest..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Kimmel's always comin for the smack down.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 08:15:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 13:03:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>My bad. I did a quick look to see if it had been posted before but I didn't see it. Guess it's for all the people that missed it like I did!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 16:05:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sweet parenting skills</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 13:56:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 17:20:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This took me quite a minute.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 20:13:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"The floor has to get cleaned somehow"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 20:52:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 16:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha maybe. Just for the record. This was only in my fb newsfeed. I'm not the first OP.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 16:56:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey now! I'm from Indiana and that is just completely and totally uncal.. Accurate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 16:59:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in England now! Got far, far away from that shite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 17:02:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mmhmmm. Just sucks because now i rarely get to visit the cool places in America I still wanna see. Feel like everytime i come back, i gotta go back to hoosierville to see people. Ah well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 17:03:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very very nice! Would like to see a fuller body pic if you're so inclined to post one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 17:06:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah.. And not somewhere you want to spend  #163;2500 and use up some of your vacation days to go visit. That's more what I'm getting at. Visiting home is so expensive. Could go to Amsterdam, Paris, Italy, Greece etc you name it and it still wouldn't cost as much as a trip back to small town indiana does.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 17:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice! I'll shall check back soon!  #128513;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 17:12:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oo was it nice? Debating about going to berlin in march. I've not been yet but think I'd probably rather go other places instead. My husband is all for it though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 17:15:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm I'll let him "win" this one then. I was on the fence anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 17:17:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice cock AND youre hot af too! Lucky bro.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 17:18:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just saw. Very nice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 17:19:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol. Did I imply somewhere that I'm rich? I think just the one place is good enough. I'll be going to a few other countries next year as well soo gotta save accordingly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 18:53:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/therewasanattempt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 01:19:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll have to check it out. Just apprehensive because trains in this country of England are ridiculously priced..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 11:40:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol. No. Kokomo is also an island off of Florida. The beach boys were not relaxing in Kokomo, Indiana.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 11:45:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still wanna see that dick. You haven't shown it yet. Don't be scared!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 11:49:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's in manchester.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Even UK tv shows are roasting Roy Moore.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 21:22:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 01:16:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was born in the first place to live and work in the UK.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 18:44:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sings, "I'm my own grandpa!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 21:09:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yaaass queen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ramsay likes your spelling.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 10:49:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The handicap bathroom is conveniently located down this stairwell.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 19:27:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Don't rip off the penis!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:42:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 12:14:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Terry from the marketing department.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The castle in Edinburgh on a lovely day in Scotland.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 19:45:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 20:26:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>All of Edinburgh is beautiful! Definitely check it out!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 01:18:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>How long does it last between charges?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 02:51:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>So straight men move their hips like that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 18:54:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once, during the summer, I spent two straight weeks at my best friends house without letting my mom know or even calling her. When I realised that half a month had gone by, I gave her a lil ring and just let her know I was still alive and at my mate's house. She said, "I figured that. You didn't need to trouble yourself with calling. Love you." I was 12.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 14:43:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate everything about this guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Don't be a fun sucker.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 19:44:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>2meirl4meirl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 12:30:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 12:48:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spoiler! I'm going to have to unsubscribe from this subreddit until AS3 is over... :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 11:55:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Repost.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 10:40:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Way back when I was religious, i definitely remember the bible also saying that you have to follow the laws of the land where you live. Forced sex is rape and is illegal, married or not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 13:16:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're cute, prefect sized cock and it's aesthetically pleasing. Don't worry about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 00:23:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Labrynth. Maybe I just don't see the appeal because I didn't watch it as a kid but I don't understand why everybody thinks it's the best movie ever, even after rewatching it as an adult.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 15:10:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Keep it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 15:52:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try shrooms</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 16:13:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>This one wins.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 17:14:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meh. Only /r/mildlyinteresting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 14:26:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Flappy Bird</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 19:08:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>We play weekly! Used to twice a month and we all decided we needed more. Been playing as a group for over a year now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 19:18:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh right. We are all fairly close to each other. Where we play is within walking distance from where i work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 19:26:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's some serious dedication! Ever considered roll20? I here that's good for groups in your situation</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 22:45:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 00:04:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is pretty damn amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 02:31:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems like only the guy who started it should be the one who gets fired. If somebody slams my head into something, I'm gonna defend myself and retaliate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 04:15:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I say that sexy will cover it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 04:16:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wheres the pic of it hard? :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 05:08:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I chuckled for two minutes straight and I have no idea why.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 05:30:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've just spent ages reading about ball lightning. Thanks for sparking that! They're quite fascinating!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 06:08:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Hag Syndrome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 00:18:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boo get naked</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 18:43:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cat?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 20:40:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Downvoting simply because OP is trash. Check out his other postings....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 20:56:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>A</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 15:18:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Minors</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 00:59:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Better get the poop knife.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 08:16:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>C</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 08:17:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eat like a fat piece of shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 08:17:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Goodbye</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 08:21:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Screaming Infidelities by Dashboard Confessionals Haligh, Haligh, A Lie, Haligh by Bright Eyes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 08:26:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>A</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 09:52:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>P</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 09:52:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>T</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 10:01:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Satan, is that you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 10:04:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's why she's amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 10:05:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Piper Chapman in Orange is the New Black. So glad she's been basically knocked down to a side character in later seasons.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 11:04:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>F</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 11:11:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>A</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 08:55:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>O</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Who even is this "rape" guy..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 12:22:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>and why does every chick I have sex with scream his name?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 18:34:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>10: Magician 18: Paranormal Investigator Now: Bookie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 15:56:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you delete somebody else's post?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 16:06:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>As</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 18:50:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Motherfucking</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 06:16:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 19:26:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so curious how these old people find the background colour function of Facebook but still have no clue what they're doing..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 19:29:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 19:30:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Smoke</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 19:32:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Came here to say this, but unfortunately, I never came..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 11:17:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/WatchPeopleDieInside</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>2meirl2meirl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 17:30:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 01:10:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you use a spoop knife?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 12:54:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>my</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 13:26:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here for my tick. Cheers!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 14:23:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've only lost Ticket to Ride once. And that was the very first time I ever played. And I only loss by like 4 points. My husband hates that game now...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stop the violence!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 14:53:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 14:56:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/unexpected</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 15:12:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 16:10:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/unpopularopinion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 11:33:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>All the "y's" are different...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 11:39:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lawnmower</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 11:39:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>11/10</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why has he kept this?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 16:17:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 17:18:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/farpeoplehate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 19:29:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm gay so I don't swing that way. In fact, it doesn't swing any which way cause my dicks too small. Spot on mate.  #128076;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 19:33:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wouldn't that just look like I got sucked off by a Smurf? I guess it works because my dick is Smurf sized..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 03:39:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just for the record, I do not know this dude. I just care very little about karma or what random people think of my penis size. The actual person in the picture is my best friends boyfriend who did not want me to take a picture of his manbun, but he knows i posted this picture for laughs cause I took it when he was least expecting it. He is also very, very vegan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 00:27:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/trashy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 00:28:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you American OP?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 00:33:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like the fact that they're Indian is completely unnecessary to this entire rant. Just rant about people cheating. Who cares what nationality they are? Plenty of cheaters are from your home country as well..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 00:38:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>What nationality are you OP?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 00:56:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let's see some research showing that. Cheers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 01:00:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your personal anecdote about your personal college is not enough for you to just start putting ALL Indian and Chinese foreign exchange students on blast.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 01:02:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you start making blanket statements based on a few experiences, that's called racism, for the record.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 10:50:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's probably why. I'm American living in the UK. It's not an unpopular opinion here. It's pretty normal for the Brits to hate on Herseys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 11:32:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agree to disagree. You telling people to fuck off back to their own country for doing the same thing that millions of Americans also do seems racist to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 12:05:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your kids are going to form their own political opinions as they age. Yes, you influence them, but they aren't just clones of their parents. I think taking place in a protrst when they're young can be a good thing. They learn about activism and standing up for what you believe in. The first amendment is amazing and kids should get to learn how it works first hand. Not every country gets the opportunity to protest, so being taught to take advantage of it when it's warranted is good thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 12:54:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like to see people stumbling over their words, sneezing, farting, burping or coughing randomly for no reason related to the plot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 13:44:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah. You just didn't grow up with it is all. It's not as good as Cadbury's, but it's not awful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 15:16:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/2meirl4meirl there ya go bud.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 15:21:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally just google "beauty is in the eye of the bee holder joke" and you will get like 50 results with the exact same punchline. As soon as I read the end of the third paragraph, I stopped immediately because I knew the punchline.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 15:23:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/scriptedasiangifs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 15:34:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Annnd stay out. Cheers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 19:54:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>If my race was continually treated as being second class, I think I'd naturally feel some camaraderie and solidarity with fellow members of my race just because they also know what is like to be treated differently just for the colour of your skin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 20:11:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is this so funny?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 05:52:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good bot You've brought a slight bit of context to this since deleted comment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 05:52:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's a hottie! Get it gurl!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 11:45:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait. Why Cat-Dog?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 11:59:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Powerpuff Girls had crossdressing satan Will and Grace had the gays Harry Potter and Sabrina had witchcraft Spongebob was too effeminate Simpsons, Beavis and Butthead, Family Guy or any other adult cartoons because of adult themes Jumanji was too scary (boy sucked into the board in the first 10 minutes. I remember going to the theater and then them walking out with me after that scene. Watched it everyday at my mums though and loved it!) Basically anything with excessive violence, cursing, sex, blasphemy, gays, or magic was a no go. There are many other shows and movies, but these are the ones I can think of off the top. To top it all off, my parents had something that I think was called a Guardian Angel (or something similar). Basically this device that plugged into the TV and would cut out the sound on live tv everytime somebody said a curse word. It would then put the caption of the sentence at the bottom and replace the curse word with something similar. Ass became Tail, Shit became Shoot, etc. It was super annoying to watch 3rd Rock from the Sun because the character Dick would constantly get changed to Jerk. I don't speak to my dad or step-mum anymore. They only ever want to save my soul and see if my "gay phase" is over yet. Seeing as I've been married to a man 4 and a half years and have been out of the closet for 16 years, I think it's safe to say it's not a phase.. I feel better without their negatively in my life anyway!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I was raping this chick the other day and she screamed, "Please! Think about my children!"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 12:18:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>God, what a kinky bitch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 16:26:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh shite. Just heard it from a friend the other day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 18:13:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Grandmas name is Floyd. Weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 21:12:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 22:00:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/justfuckmyshitup</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 22:03:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/trashy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 10:30:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>scab</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 10:42:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Upvoting for "Thank Satan"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The people who need to spend 5 minutes talking to the bus driver or have to spend forever looking through their purse for change are ALWAYS the first to board the bus.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 11:45:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you know you're going to be taking a minute to get your ticket, go to the end of the queue and let people who already have tickets or cards go through first. It's called being considerate and British people are supposedly suppose to be good at it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 01:30:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/nottheonion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 01:38:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally just got the chills. I HATE praying mantises. This is terrifying af.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 02:15:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/trashy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 02:18:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That show wouldn't work as well in some other countries. Over half of their pranks rely on people being overly nice and helpful. #OnlyInCanada</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 02:27:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man. This guy is such an idiot I was almost hoping this was r/watchpeopledie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I wish I had context for this one..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 13:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 18:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>wombs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 11:44:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>It wasn't bad enough to remove curse words from the middle of words, but was still annoying af. And my mum was the compete opposite. She used to let watch anything I wanted, even, tbf, some wildly inappropriate scary movies. I learned all the curse words (and character names) at her house.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 18:11:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>E</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not sure if this has made its way to this subreddit yet, but I had to share as I love this reasoning.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 13:47:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 15:20:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tiny lil jump in the gif so only 98% perfect loop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 15:49:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did try to scroll through and check! After looking through a month of posts, I grew weary and just decided to post it. Sorry if it's a repost!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 15:56:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/tiresaretheenemy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 15:56:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/tiresaretheenemy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 16:28:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/unexpected</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 16:36:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you do that? I'm still not a reddit savant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 17:08:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheers! I will look at this next time!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 20:09:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just wanted to make it clear that I wasn't looking for karma or to repost. I just hadn't seen it before so I thought I'd share. People are insinuating I'm a karma whore. Haha. I thought the title was clear about my intentions and that's all I tried to go for.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 21:51:56</DATE>
    <TEXT> #129335; #8205; #9792; #65039; I'm pretty shocked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do you finger a Jewish chick?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 11:38:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Two in the pink, one in the gas chamber.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Beware! The slime man is coming home!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 11:40:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 11:42:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>This has been posted on this subreddit like 5 times at least.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 16:42:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just wondering where you work that serves food dirt cheap! Kid got mac and cheese, chocolate milk and toast, parents both presumably got at least an app or side and drinks.. And all this was only $12.78??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 17:49:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh yes. I had forgotten the gift card. Makes more sense now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 17:50:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh yes. I was forgetting the gift card. Makes so much more sense now!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 00:05:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vein</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 00:07:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Foods that make your butthole itchy"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 14:27:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/wowthanksimcured</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 14:28:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>A light sprinkle can be cute sometimes for sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 16:00:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/holdmycosmo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 18:09:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Licked</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 00:39:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>My post was almost two weeks ago. I have literally ceased all amount of caring I could give to this cause.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 00:42:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can we get OP to ask why Trump's diet hasn't given him a heart attack yet?!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 15:28:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've just gotten a dachshund pup and I'm not getting him neutered. He will be studded out and I have no doubts that he will enjoy this as well as the fact that we will get some of the money back used to purchase him. I just don't see the need to removed them after he's been studded a few times. He'll be used to having them and his behaviour will be just as good as it would be without them by that point. I think it's ultimately the decision of the pet owners. Unless their dog is going around impregnating random dogs on the street, I don't see what your problem is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 15:37:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Farm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 18:01:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>SPOILERS! We are still playing the Rise of Tiamat so please don't spoil anything for me. I'm not the DM, but we threw him off completely by climbing into a chest that would teleport to the well of dragons. We then killed the captive who would activate said teleportation which basically meant we skipped the end of the first book. He was not prepared for that. We (luckily) finished the night on that idea so he was able to prepare thr next bit. He said he couldn't find anyone else online who had used that approach so perhaps we're just clever?  #129335; #8205; #9792; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 15:38:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Goodbye.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've wanted a puppy my entire life. At nearly 30, my dream has finally become a reality and I couldn't be happier! Please say hello to Gavroche!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 19:13:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 19:56:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who is this? Any vids or links?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 07:59:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 08:00:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aww that poor pup. People are garbage. Thanks for the niceties!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 09:22:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've always thought that was a guy..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 12:26:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mate said this exact thing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 12:59:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shit.. You got through that many games in 5 hours?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 13:16:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>This particular performer happened to be Mexican. He says, "I shall now disappear on the count of 3" "Uno" "Dos" *POOF* He disappeared without a Tres.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 13:41:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>7 wonders took longer to play when we tried it. Was unfamiliar with coup. And i didn't really consider how fast betrayal would be if the haunt happened quickly. My bad my bad. I get it now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 14:40:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/nobodyasked</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 15:00:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Snape was an ass.. Always. Awesome work though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 15:26:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/untrustworthypoptarts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 15:36:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Neat but I'm gonna have to call r/DiWHY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 17:32:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg! I loved that game! Really wish I could get a copy but it's like  #163;100 since its so old.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 17:36:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>True. Tbf. I tell the OG joke and the one I told together. I always make the Si speaker Spanish in my version. Then I'll use Mexican in the next joke so as not to be too repetitive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 15:29:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I missed this paper towel. Context? Link?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 16:01:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought that person had a really hairy ankle until I zoomed in..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 18:48:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where do you live?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 19:55:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check out couchsurfing.org for meet ups in your area. There are many places that have regular meetings in bars where you can go and meet new people. Even if you don't make a local friend, there's always tourists and such who are just passing through who would make good company for an evening.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>They definitely did not cut a little hole and then shove their straw through.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 16:39:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 17:05:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wouldn't be hard to do with a pen. I feel like the cup would have tipped over from the force of trying to get a blunt straw through plastic. I just don't see how she did this without at least even realising there was a massive amount of resistance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 17:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>the</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 22:35:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm honestly not sure what is happening here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 00:16:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's the title from?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 00:50:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are common in like mini juice cups. There's many things I can think of that have foil that would be similar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 00:50:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Classic. No peeing on it to keep it warm then? I think I saw that in a movie once.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 00:51:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love the front. Might we see the back in your next post?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 00:53:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed again. You only get half a second to even notice they are asian and this one seems genuine to me. It's nowhere ckose to the one where they are playing pool that was literally probably filmed half a dozen times before posting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 01:14:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha no man. I meant pissing on the bag, not into the wine itself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 01:15:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the point of the sub.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 01:23:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair enough. I think I saw it on the terrible movie Let's Go to Prison. They were keeping it warm I believe. Never made hooch. Didn't realise how easy it was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 01:25:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>That seems way more likely than this. I never discredit posts where they say they bought a ridiculous amount of something because I have personally also experienced being drunk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 01:28:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's actually exactly what I was looking for! I wanna know the hacks that made life better or easier to survive. Yours is pretty hardcore. Never would have thought of this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 03:39:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has she also never had a coffee or to-go drink in her life?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found on r/facepalm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 10:03:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 10:42:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>This isn't an unpopularopinion, just a shitty one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 10:58:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it was on my lap, it'd be dead. Don't know what it is otherwise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 11:09:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Indeed. That's where I thought this post was going when I first read it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 12:50:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was actually thinking about this place when I made the post! Didn't see anything, but it felt creepy and I still really, really enjoyed it. I lucked out on my tour. It was only me and the tour guide so it was especially creepy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 13:21:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is very beautiful! Been there a couple times. Amsterdam and Venice beat it for prettiest, but it's up there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 13:24:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 14:23:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>All the "Christian" holidays were hijacked by the church from other religions. So regardless of how the question is worded, it's still wrong to begin with as they aren't originally Christian holidays.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 14:58:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I rewatched them all about 2 years ago. I'm nearly 30.  #129335; #8205; #9792; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>She likes to pretend she does sometimes, but I'd be willing to be anything that she NEVER tips. Her edited-in soundcloud link for the rapper she manages just solidifies her as trash to me.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 15:11:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 15:21:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>It wasnt bad. Of course I didn't like it as much as when I was younger but I was glad to finally see all the storylines *in order* and knowing that I didn't miss any episodes. I'd happily watch it if I were babysitting or with my own kids (if I had them) but I don't think I'll be watching them again on my own. Was still a good trip down memory lane.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 15:26:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree that servers should be paid a fair wage to begin with. However, this is not the servers decision and taking it out on them by not tipping is not sticking it to anyone except that server. You know how tipping works by now and that servers *depend* on tips to survive in America. Just avoid restaurants with servers if you're not going to tip. Plenty of other places to eat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Her edited-in soundcloud link for the rapper she manages just solidifies the cringe for this human garbage.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 15:27:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The edited-in soundcloud link for the rapper she manages just solidifies the cringe for this human garbage.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 15:37:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 17:48:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>In those instances, the workers are being paid at least minimum wage so it's not necessary.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 17:49:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>There was definitely continuity. You just gotta watch the in the right order which is pretty difficult when you're only catching ransom episodes here and there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 18:48:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>This. Exactly this. Like write to your senators to get them to change the national law so servers can't be underpaid on their hourly wage. If you are such an anti-tipping crusader, direct your complaints at the level where it can actually change things. Stiffing your server because you don't like tipping is NOT the way to effect change.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 19:13:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>It truly depends. If the place is a pickup only shop, that means the workers are making at least minimum wage and their children aren't going hungry because you don't tip. However, if it's a nicer sit down place and you've put in a large order for pick up, it's most likely the case that your server is getting the food to put into bags and making sure all of your stuff is correct and that you get the appropriate sauces, napkins etc. This takes them away from their tables where their main focus is because this is where they make their money. In this kind of instance, a small tip is appropriate. This worker isn't making fair wages without tips, she has to prepapre your order to go which takes away from her tipping customers, and I think this entitles them to at least give 10 percent. I don't think a full tip is necessary as they are not having to actually wait on you, but they did put work into your order and they deserve more than the 40 cents they probably made doing that for you. If it's a delivery driver, tip them! Even if they are making minimum wage, many employers require you to cover the gas to make deliveries in your own personal car. This isn't even considering the cost of regular car upkeep which becomes pricier when you drive it constantly. If it's a bartender, pick a single bartender and tip a lil almost everytime. This mostly just ensures that you get drinks almost immediately when you come to the bar. Just make eye contact with them and you'll be served next. And naturally.. No matter the industry or the person providing service, if you think they've went above and beyond and appreciate that, flash a wee bit o' cash. This has been my full breakdown of when to tip. Haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 07:42:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not talking about burger king in my example. I'm more referring to like a pick-up order from like a Texas Steakhouse, Applebee's, etc. An actual restaurant where the server has to sort the to-go orders out in addition to dealing with their tables. These servers are not making minimum wage. I specifically said, in fact, that tipping isn't necessary for places that are to-go only. Again, those people are making minimum wage. And yes. Again, I agree that tipping these restaurant servers shouldn't have to break the bank when you're picking up a to-go order. Again, I specifically said a *small tip* such as 10% instead of 20%, especially if it's a large order.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 08:07:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't kill any and all spiders just for existing, but if a big one that I don't recognise is in my lap, I'm going to kill it before it bites me. I am not trying to get a poisonous spider bite in exchange for a spider's life. Sorry to the downvoters, but my health and safety is more important to me than a single spider.  #129335; #8205; #9792; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 08:09:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about it? What does that have to do with effecting change in other states that don't have this in place? If it's a state where servers can make a decent wage without tips, then tip or don't tip.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 09:05:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could watch this all day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 09:34:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is this so funny and realistic?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 09:55:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perhaps even a lil r/nobodyasked</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 11:44:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/theydidthemonstermath</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 11:45:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let's rotate the board!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Saying transgender people are just mentally ill and need help, not acceptance or surgery, is not an unpopular opinion.. It's just a shitty one.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 12:54:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>When your "unpopularopinion" is posted to this page on a weekly basis, it's obviously not unpopular. This applies to all of the regular reposts, but the transgender one just irks me the most. It's just the same echoed misconceptions that could easily be put to bed by *actually talking to a real transgendered person.*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 13:05:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Disagree. Just because it's less popular, it's not unpopular. If hundreds of millions of people share the same opinion, I wouldn't say that's unpopular. The majority of people don't watch sporting events. By your logic, this means sports aren't popular.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 13:09:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Liberals don't like gay people? That's news to me, a gay liberal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 13:18:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would personally say somewhere around 5-10% of the population or less. That's just me though. Perhaps that's *an* unpopular opinion.  #129335; #8205; #9792; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 13:19:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>What does somebody wishing they were a different sexuality have to do with conversion therapy? I didn't make that leap in my head.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 13:36:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you're only thinking of the first world. It's really only a minority of people in developed, semi-liberal countries and that's just BARELY the minority. I think you'll find that the majority of people in the second and third world not very accepting of gay or transgendered people. There are too many places in the world where it's illegal and places where they will flat out just kill you for it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 13:38:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think i may have just read your initial statement wrong. I see what you're saying now. My bad!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 14:06:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah. Ketchup is good in ice cream? Sounds gross but I don't think it's shitty. Acne is cute? It's definitely unpopular, but I don't think it's shitty. You liked/hated that particular film? I may not agree but I wouldn't say you're shitty. Your opinion oppresses, belittles and perpetuates falsehoods about a particular group of people? You're shitty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 14:37:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some of your questions have been addressed in other comments. As far as the trans mental illness questions go, I don't have the time or energy at the moment to hash it out with you. I'm sure the folks at r/lgbt will educate you if you ask about it. Otherwise, r/changemyview might prove helpful instead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 14:42:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because I'm not a bigot and don't need my view changed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 14:46:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Link me to some places that share your bias." God forbid you actually talked to real transgender people about the realities of being transgender. Clearly, all non-transgendered people know better than the people actually living with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 14:49:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>You do you. (The same way transgendered people will continue to do them.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 14:57:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think that we're making headway either way here and I've spent more than enough time on this topic. You do you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 14:58:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>You seem unsure about quite a lot of things tbf.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 14:59:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Transgendered people are the same as people who want to eat shit. Nice sentiment. And you say you're not a bigot?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 15:23:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unless it's a *large* order as I've specified several times. https://www.google.co.uk/amp/amp.wptv.com/2491498066/server-stiffed-on-tip-by-local-mega-church-posts-on-facebook-gets-fired.html You can continue to goad me if you like, but I'm truly done now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 14:48:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/thalassophobia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 15:17:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm glad I came to see the only comment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 18:07:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>They aren't allegations. He has confirmed it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 18:08:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/comedycemetery</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 18:30:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Racism.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 00:35:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It wasn't great, but it was definitely culturally acceptable. That's all I meant. But by all means, downvote away!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm a bit drunk and I just blew a raspberry on my new pup's little tummy while we were play wrestling. He seems confused.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 01:58:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 02:41:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/drunk but have realised how crazy it is for the OG sculptor to have maybe a slight bit of recognition while alive, but somebody can post their work on reddit like 300 years later and get literal worldwide recognition and approval in less than a day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 12:25:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me. I take them waayy too often even though I pay monthly for a bus ticket..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 13:10:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/thingsforants</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 08:45:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's one of those rare posts that's r/iamverysmart r/ihavesex and r/nobodyasked all at once.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 09:39:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/frugal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 15:50:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you need a poop knife?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 16:36:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought the title was going to be about using the toilet. Not the best OP. Cute vid though. Still got my upvote.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 10:54:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>God damn. Y'all are dickheads. I had a cute, drunken thought before bed because I was talking with a lovely girl on wakie who was saying she had nearly given up on apps because of all the unsolicited dick pics and creepy guys hitting on her. If you continually send nudes without asking, thats wrong and you should be banned from that app. So fuck y'all. Downvote if you want. Don't give a fuck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 10:56:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Downvoted because you think that everyone gives a shit about karma as much as you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 16:43:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/diWHY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 19:10:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/wowthanksimcured</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 21:16:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/thingsforants</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 15:43:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/justneckbeardthings</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 15:45:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/wowthanksimcured</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 18:23:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Obama was a better president on his worst day than Trump is on his best day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 19:19:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>A sausage, bean and cheese pasty from Greggs in the UK.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 04:44:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>think you'd get more traction on his over at r/dontputyourdickinthat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 13:20:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 09:50:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's one of my favourite packs!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 10:21:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Been watching The Good Place?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>No homo.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 11:15:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 22:48:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's very common in the uk for chavs to stand about literally with both hands down the front of their pants as you first described. It's not something i ever saw in America before moving here. I'd be willing to bet op is british and referring to this chav behaviour.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 16:30:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ticket to ride. Save every card and only play them when you need to. Basically connect all your routes in your head and work on collecting the cards you need for said routes. Play cards if somebody else is near your route of choice and you think they will go there next. If somebody takes a route of choice because you were saving cards, it's easy to reroute when you've not been laying trains down. Only go to lay down when you have 80% of the cards you need. After competing, if there's time, get new tickets. If you have completed the long route, at least one new ticket will be a route you've already completed or easy to get to. I have played this game well over a dozen times and have only ever lost once, and that was the very first time I played. I only lost by less than ten points. Normally i win by 30-40 points minimum. The downside is that nobody wants to play anymore cause i always win.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 16:49:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean honestly.. Who tf actually likes chicken?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 16:53:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/whatcouldgowrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 17:33:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was being sarcastic. r/woooosh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 17:45:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was merely commenting to further add proof to the fact this is a fake text. Most people don't assume others don't like chicken so it seems weird that he would have to ask. Continue to downvote either way. Not bothered  #129335; #8205; #9792; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 17:57:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>If i were bothered, i'd delete my comments to prevent further downvotes. I was merely explaining my sarcasm.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 18:01:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't really feel like I've been a dick about it but apologies if anything I said went too far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 20:07:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm only talking about my personal experiences with friends on our own actual board game. Not saying I'm the best ever. Just that this strategy has not failed me yet in my personal experience. Not really keen on digital games. Much prefer playing people in person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 23:16:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did not. However, by commenting this, I'm basically inviting everyone who doesn't know my intentions of the original comment to downvote yet another comment to hell. Would be quite troublesome if I was a user concerned about karma.. Ah well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 00:13:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah man. Chicken is awesome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 08:40:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tbf, I've only played the american one once at a mates. We own the europe version and that's the one i play the most.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 12:24:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/humblebrag</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 12:23:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha you're right. I was havin a drink at the time. Ahh well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 14:09:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I realise this is satire. Just thought it was a funny fit for the sub.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 11:28:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also the jaw line. Danny had lots of good shit goin on</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 11:30:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>She just had a kind of glow about her..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 11:39:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had a huge crush on Peter Pan in the live action 2003 version. Those cute af crooked teeth and fantasies of flying away to a magical island was enough to get me going.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A guy finds a $1 hooker in a dark alley.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 00:34:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's cheap so he goes for it. He's thrusting away and honestly, it's some of the worst sex he's ever had. It's super dry down there and feels awful on his cock. After a few minutes, he complains. The hooker says that she can make it better if he's willing to pay an extra dollar. The man agrees. She takes the extra dollar and goes further down the alley out of sight. She returns and announces that she's ready. The man is tentative, but goes for it again. This time, it's amazing! She's so wet and his dick is just being hugged by a perfectly warm, flowing pussy. He finishes in record time. As he's zipping up, he curiously asks, "So what exactly did you go and do with that extra dollar?" She says, "The extra dollar was just how much I charge to pick the scabs off."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 16:50:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Be sure to check out the vaults! They are creepy and the tour is great!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 21:23:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah.. Always go for more tickets if you have the time. You may pick some up you've already completed and if not, completing new ones gets you points for laying down as well as the eventual points for completing the ticket.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 13:50:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ugh. Thought Gallowboob fucked off..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 23:52:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/mildlyvandalised</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 08:32:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>More like r/badfaketexts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I think braces ruin teeth. I much prefer janky smiles.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 01:21:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not gross, unlooked after teeth. I'm not talking about black, rotting, meth teeth. I love unique, uneven teeth: crooked teeth, overbites, slight gaps, a tooth growing over a tooth, underbites, very sharp, and generally irregular teeth. I like those unnaturally wide smiles, people who have slanty-inward facing front teeth with average spaced canines, those people who have what some would call "horse teeth" and people who have lil Chicklet teeth. I think braces ruin smiles. Braces seem like a bad choice, except when it's absolutely medically necessary. Unless it causes you pain, or you can't emotionally handle it, please keep your teeth the way they are! Your bitemark is practically as unique as your thumbprint. Don't change to fit the standard just for the sake of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 01:23:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry. Noted. Still getting the hang of reddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 01:36:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>And don't forget to use your poop knife afterwards.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 12:51:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok.. I did. And? I did only reference "slight gaps." If Evil Knievel wouldn't jump the gap, it's probably best getting that attended to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 12:53:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think it's that goofball-ish. It's better than yet another post about how people think Trans people are only mentally ill. Like.. We get it. There have been a hundred posts about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 13:22:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I only came to the comments to see who else thought he was fit af.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 09:52:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who's driving this boat? Caitlyn Jenner?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 19:34:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's a shame everyone is going straight for the fat jokes. She's also extremely unattractive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 20:46:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wonderfalls. It was amazing. Cancelled after 4 episodes, but fans made them release the whole of the first season on dvd as it was already finished.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 03:24:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm jealous that you have seen ticks so infrequently in your life that you failed to recognise it. I had to deal with the bastards all the time growing up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found on r/CasualUK</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 00:29:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 20:59:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Head on over to r/CasualUK for the OP. The poster seemed like a regular lad. Just thought a lot of people might not be on that sub that could enjoy it here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 21:03:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Found the link boss. r/notmyjob</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 11:58:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was a post on r/confessions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 14:40:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/untrustworthypoptarts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 06:49:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least there is r/gaypornhunters if you're into dudes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 17:41:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure, but I'd definitely partner up with Madeline McCann!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>2meirl4meirl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 16:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 16:52:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/suddenlygay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 17:02:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I've got to use the ATM machine."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 17:05:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Daredevil. I actually liked the movie way more than the current Netflix series.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You definitely didn't just order a water and say your name is Beautiful just for upvotes.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 18:56:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 23:20:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Woof! You're a hot chick!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 23:46:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That could be true for literally any post on this sub. However, you'll find the OP on r/humblebrag</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 23:49:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm ashamed to admit that I don't know how to do that.. I'm a newer, basic redditor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 01:35:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I only use the app. Does that make a difference? I'll try this next time though. Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 01:45:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah right. Nice one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I started watching RWBY again because of this sub and I couldn't be happier!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 17:31:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>When this show was still in its first volume, a friend introduced me and I absolutely loved it! I stayed caught up and watched volume 2 as well. Tragically, that's when Monty Oum died and I was sure that I had read that the series was going to be cancelled. Apart from re-watching the first 2 volumes again when they were on Netflix, I never looked into the show again. That all changed earlier this week when somebody posted a comment from this sub to r/nocontext . Found this sub and of course saw all this amazing artwork for characters I had never seen. I immediately got goosebumps and rushed to the rooster teeth website to find that there were THREE more volumes! I've binged them now and have already begun a second watch through. I LOVE this show! Thanks r/RWBY for being around as I'm not sure I would have ever looked into this show again without y'all!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 17:50:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really do! Already looking into getting some merchandise for my flat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 18:26:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha so much! I've only just binged it all in about 3 days. I'm still processing. I will reflect and get back to you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 19:50:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheers! Love the fan art here so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 20:33:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/glitchinthematrix</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 22:23:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was in relation to Ice Cream. It said something like "I never thought cannibalism could be so cute." She was eating ice cream in the picture. I didn't recognise her. Came to the page.. Didn't recognise loads of other characters and hence the dawning of the fact that there were more episodes made. Honestly.. So thankful that happened.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 22:31:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still haven't thought of all of these but i did immediately come to the conclusion that the best guy is Sun Wukong. He's fit and his weapon of choice is one of my absolute favourites. I also want Yang to be a lesbian. Perhaps ship her with Ilia as we already know she likes chicks? I'm lame and just gonna have to go with Ruby as best female character. She's awesome and is only made more awesome by the fact that she's got extra silver eyed powers. Jury is still out on best volume. Gotta rewatch them all until i decide. Hope I didn't disappoint!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 00:08:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool cool. Can i get all of yours? Same question posed. Would like to hear these from a long time fan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 01:14:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought of blake and yang as well.. But i just love Yun.. He is sexy and has continuously been there for her.. I don't want to take away Blake from him....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 13:47:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 17:06:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>O</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 20:39:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe it's lies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 01:06:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's still a bit meh. He still kind of sucks in battle and his semblance was predictable. His healing poweres are even super slow. He's a meh for me. As soon as the dream of shipping him with Pyrrha was literally dead, I pushed him to the back burner.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 11:28:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/animalsbeingbros</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 21:43:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/fellowkids</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The best of this meme so far.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 21:26:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 00:34:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don't get to see many cute pussies on this sub. Well done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 00:42:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's so perfect. Disappointed that you only have 4 pics! Need more perfect dick pics in my life.. For the record, I've only commented something like this on less than 5 posts..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 00:45:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could always try r/dirtyr4r</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 00:45:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Otherwise, craigslist is your friend for hookups (especially gay ones)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 11:00:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/notkenm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 12:32:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work in a bookies. I've seen this happen about a dozen times. It's always quite amusing if I'm being honest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 12:59:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amusing in that they think it'll hurt the company when in actuality, it surely does way more damage to their person. We have plenty of resourses available such as gambling addiction hotlines, they can self exclude from a shop and we'll kick them out if we see them come in, and of course, the staff personally go out and talk to people if we see somebody spending loads but getting more and more upset. After all of that, if you're still a rage monster and want to punch a machine and injure yourself, go ahead. Here's a hint.. It's never good guys that do this kind of thing. It's always the douchebags who threaten to wait outside and stab you when your shift is over.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 15:46:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Worked at Build-A-Bear for a few years. If you're unfamiliar, at one point, the bear builder will get the child to "bring a heart to life" which then goes in their bear. I would always have the kids kiss the heart and give it lots of love. I would then have mummy and daddy or brothers and sisters kiss their heart as well for extra love. Had this one little girl come up with her sister. I had the girl kiss the heart and then asked her to let her little sister kiss the heart to give it extra love. She holds it out for her sister and her sister misses and kisses the girls fingers instead. She laughs and says, "(Sister) kissed my fingers and gave them love! I've never had *finger love* before!!" Had me dying but I couldn't laugh too hard as I didn't want her parents to think I was a creep. If you're out there little one, please just wait until you're older for any finger loving!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 15:56:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well.. I do live in the UK so there's nationalised healthcare. They just seem to think that breaking the machine will make us lose out on loads of money when, in actuality, my shop makes enough profit in a single day to fix all the machines 2 times over. If they are smashed anytime during the day, they are literally fixed within an hour and making money again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 16:03:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope there weren't any asians around! If so, this would be a good post for r/accidentalracism</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 17:49:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/fakehistoryporn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 18:22:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>The machines themselves are pretty expensive. Replacing the screens is super cheap. Not to mention they are heavy bastards. Miss me with carting about that shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 20:31:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>The machines get fixed within an hour unless it's late in the evening. It's very easy for them to replace broken screens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 12:28:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I must work for a better company.. Also, my shop in particular makes more money on our machines than anybody else in the region which is about 40 shops so they prioritise it when it does happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 16:05:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lorna Morello, is that you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha thank you! Not only is this funny, but (I think) it answered my question. This lady is Australian, right? I'm not the best at accents and I can't find any news story about it so I was relying on comments to point me toward the country of origin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 20:32:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. Krushems are in the UK as well. I'm an American expat living in the UK. Constantly trying to figure out different accents. That's why I wanted to make sure this was Australian and not some random UK city accent. Edit: Thanks for the insight from a true Australian though. I'm 80% sure she's Australian. I only wanted to know if my accent guess was right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 20:51:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah! I missed that important slight difference that clears it all up. And yeah man. I have been here for over 4 years. At one point, I was just overwhelmed with accents and I just tuned them out. I've mistaken Brazilians for British, I've fucked up and asked British Uber drivers where they're from, and I had even reached a point where, several times, I failed to recognise an American accent. I'm actively trying to recognise accents now. It's a very British thing to do. I only have about a year before I can apply for citizenship and say I'm British too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 07:05:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same. But judging by the above answers, I get it a little bit more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 07:06:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL the term Reddiquette. Cheers!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 18:59:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>This deserves so many more upvotes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 23:04:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm still all about Norway. It was so ridiculous!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 21:46:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Indeed! I don't want to say who I work for, but we're the best!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 17:52:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uk mountain dew sucks and is nothing like the American original. Source : am American living in Manchester.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 23:19:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 23:21:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good bot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 23:23:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Untrustworthy seems to more about staged photographs while thathappened features written far-fetched stories.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 15:18:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tooken was the original title for the series before they changed it to what it is now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 16:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>And kelsey</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 16:46:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish there were more scenes with her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 18:29:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely. We needed more than just a single fight scene from her..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 21:40:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tbh.. Until user r/Darkrell said it was her semblance, I just assumed it was her weapon box thingy making all the weapons.. Because it's her semblance, it drains her aura to use it so it indeed makes sense that she's the kind of "last resort."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 22:17:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ohhh! Thank you! That makes so much sense! I didn't fully understand her. Sorry. I'm fairly new to volumes 3-5 of RWBY.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 12:20:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a very fucking weird movie but I'd watch it again..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 12:35:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>OP is just an angry, hate filled little shit. Check out some of this persons other crazy rants. They are clearly delusional and far too judgemental of other people. Fuck your opinions OP. You are human garbage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 13:03:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not a burnout, so thank YOU for proving my point that you're a judgemental bitch. I'm not basing this off of a single post. I've looked at your other anecdotal posts about lesbians and LGBT etc. You're just a shitty person who literally makes broad blanket statements about entire groups of people worldwide just because you've personally experienced a few different things. Making broad statements about billions of people is the exact same as racism. You just suck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 13:46:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm gay married. And yeah.. You're definitely just a garbage person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 13:57:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Again.. You're judging me based on your own skewed opinions. You don't know me. You know nothing about my lifestyle or values. This is just as bad as being like, "oh, you're black? You must be a gangmember and deal drugs." You shouldn't assume anything about anyone based on a single fact about them. When you do, you're just being a piece of shit. Grow up, yeah?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 14:10:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're judging me based on my sexuality. I'm judging you based on the way you seem to come to snap conclusions about everyone and everything based on almost nothing. You have a lot of growing up to do kiddo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 17:52:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>This bitch again...  #128580; Human garbage and not because of your opinions about weed. Can't you just fuck off and be a terrible person somewhere else? You are not improving reddit in any way with your judgemental, bigoted opinions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 17:55:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just in case you want to know why OP is garbage.. https://www.reddit.com/r/unpopularopinion/comments/8k0dpf/comment/dz4ga0z?st=JHAPTPMJ amp;sh=e7f30e6a</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 18:20:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check out her other posts. OP is one of the most judgemental pieces of shit I've ever come across. Also.. I literally said "and not because of your opinions on weed."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 21:26:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>So other LGBT people agree with you that bisexuals should not be stereotyped against.. So you're proving my point that not everybody thinks the same. I personally also don't think bi's should be discriminated against, yet you made the snap judgement that I think all these things just because I'm gay. How can you say all LGBT think a certain way and then also say you know LGBT that don't think that way in the same breath? You're literally contradicting yourself. Just fucking stop judging people you don't even know based on your own fucked up, bigoted opinions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 00:16:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 17:19:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 17:51:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oo that would have been good!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 18:01:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know! I knew immediately who I wanted to go as as soon as my mate said what her birthday theme was. Sadly, not very many people knew who I was though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 01:21:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just disney! Although there was the Shadow Man and Cruella Devil there...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 04:41:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought so.. People all night didn't know who I was so I had to show them pictures so they understood my boobs were *suppose* to be saggy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 12:08:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>They were just socks shaped and taped strategically into place below my own lil moobs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 12:10:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aww shucks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 12:14:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's acceptable. I mean, if your server is straight up being rude to you and your table, then that's not good service and they are probably in the wrong industry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 04:03:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was really neat! I only just now got around to watching it but it absolutely made me realise why she has always stuck out for me in my mind. They did an excellent job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Here is my heart, Gavroche!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 14:05:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 16:10:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really liked the film. I had never seen the series before and I loved the movie so much that I actually went and watched the original series. Would never have been a fan without that movie..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 17:16:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Saaame. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 10:45:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't like that this GIF makes you assume he can't do it. The full video shows him getting it in the box.. [See here.](https://youtu.be/9zOuVZ97318)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 11:25:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 11:25:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>For sure!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm sure your local FB garage sale page is the best place to start looking.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 16:18:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Roses are red, there's been an attack,</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 16:20:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does every Dachshund do this, or is mine the only that burrows himself within our head pillows?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 23:12:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 00:10:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheers all! I assumed he was only doing his natural burrowing as I know they originally were bred to hunt badgers. Just doesn't realise this applied to pillows..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 10:20:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a sucker for people with poliosis. It's that condition where people get random white patches of hair. I don't know why I find it so sexy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 21:00:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm less than a year into Reddit, but I'm absolutely obsessed. My job allows me to be on Reddit 70% of the time and then I go home and literally still stay on Reddit for hours with background shows on tv that I've seen before. I've never been a mod and I'm mostly a mobile user. I'm not sure how to be a mod, but I take direction well. I will easily pick it up and be vigilant on posts. I've been subscribed to r/needamod since I was first on reddit basically. I think it would be awesome to be a mod and I would enjoy it greatly! I've not once asked to be a mod for any other subreddits yet as I wasn't a big enough fan of the subreddit to throw in my hat. However, I love r/HoldMyKibble because I'm an extreme dog lover. I also am a recent dog owner as an adult, as evidenced by previous posts. I have had dogs all through growing up and am happy to say, I've finally got my very own as an adult! I would be thrilled to be considered. If you find my lack of experience off-putting, I completely understand. Again, I'd just love just even being considered for such a thing. Just a little after-the-fact fact, I'm an American expat living in the UK so I am in the GMT zone, though, at the moment, it's currently called the BST zone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 22:30:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate America.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 19:51:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh please tell me what this is from. I feel like I have heard/read it before and it's bugging me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 20:07:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh yes. I have seen it before in full. I just couldn't remember if it was some inside joke from a different thread or what. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 20:39:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey now.. This isn't r/roastme head over there if you wanna open the library.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 20:40:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats man! I escaped christianity and will never turn back. Also.. Absolutely fantastic smile you got there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm almost 30 and have been in so many various retail type jobs in my life looking to find a place where I could grow. I didn't ever find it and have never even been promoted to a supervisor before. Today, however, I was just promoted to a store manager position. I'm absolutely buzzing!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 21:08:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 21:09:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely. But there's a time and place. If somebody is feeling happy about something and sharing their happiness, I feel like it's in poor taste to crap on them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 22:13:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>This deserves way more upvotes. It's one that that you can actually say out-loud to a person and they can understand it. That's really hard for r/wordavalanches</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 23:53:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah? Why does that matter?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It looks like he's jumping and landing awkwardly</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 02:44:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I can never get a good video of these two playing. When I try, they just give me this look.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 01:31:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 13:18:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do this, but then I end up setting the alarm for when I absolutely need to be up for anyway. And then I'll lay there still for 15 minutes and just be late for whatever it was I needed to be up for. I suck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 13:34:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/nothingeverhappens</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 00:46:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could offer any crazy amouny you want. As soon as she's in love with you, it should be easy to convince her that she doesn't need the money so long as she has you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 22:27:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with OP.. Never have I ever had a bag with this few "munches" in it... Definitely untrustworthy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 21:07:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice tats!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 17:51:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've never seen a pure black one before! Gorgeous!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 23:47:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tbf it looks like she had literally just finished doing the thing where you spin around a bat with your forehead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 23:48:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>This would be fun for Dungeons and Dragons</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 00:21:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm always the first to call r/untrustworthypoptarts but when it comes to Trump supporters, I genuinely believe they are that stupid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 23:16:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Best one by far!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[NO SPOILERS] I don't know the artist, but I love Renly, so I had to share.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 23:02:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 23:53:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. Well spotted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 01:58:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>"With just a bit of grime" Him ashing in the peach was enough to haunt me my entire life...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 02:01:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice pic but I had to downvote over the use of love heart smileys on your own headline. Downvote away. Had to share my opinion..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 02:02:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/enoughinternet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 02:05:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine is a quarter chihuahua.. It's actually,better for these sweet peas to be crossbred as they tend to have a lot of back problems growing up. Crossbredding is best in order to keep the pure-bred babies from growing up with health problems.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 04:07:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same. Still one of the hardest things to swallow about the show.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 04:52:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't read of Stannis's death yet, but I'm partway through A Feast For Crows, and I still strongly dislike Stannis. He has zero charisma.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 12:04:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd think that you'd have to know the show well to understand the the importance of that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 12:07:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh thank you! Was hoping somebody would be able to credit the artist. I love the Loras one, but Dany was looking a bit manly there..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 12:22:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>How can you tell she's banned as opposed to having just deleted her account?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 12:36:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Interesting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 12:39:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did not. It was shared by a friend on Facebook and I wasn't near a computer at the time. I'm sure there's a way to search on mobile, but it seems like it would be a right faff. Luckily, somebody else has already commented about who the artist is and has given them the credit they deserve.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 15:14:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so happy this sub exists.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 22:28:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>For sure. He's sexy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 22:29:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know it bro.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 22:49:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can somebody please get a mirror? It's not available in my country..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 22:50:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would expect nothing less from a cooter shooter</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Complete with pictures.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 12:05:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 14:59:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Got a spammy phone call. We get them constantly. Guy was like, if you give me just one minute of time, we will never call again. I said, alright go. I've started the timer. He starts asking me all these questions. Like my address, full name, etc. I just said, you asked for a minute of my time, not my life story. I'm not answering any of your questions. By the way, you've got 30 more seconds. He just thanked me and hung up. Use to get these calls almost daily, but haven't heard from them since!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 16:01:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>You must do a r/masterreturns video when you're back!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 16:21:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 17:28:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd try it in this scenario. Why not?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 18:35:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah.. I wouldn't be able to do that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 02:04:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/enoughinternet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 18:45:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could watch this all day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 20:09:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree. I've actually read this story somewhere before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 02:08:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely. Came here to say that. Seems to be a recent trend...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 02:11:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>This makes me feel older than I should because I immediately thought of Mr. Limpet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 02:23:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I enjoy them. I'm not saying they aren't entertaining. I subscribe to that subreddit for a reason. While entertaining, you can't tell me you think it's unscripted. That's the point of that subreddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 03:56:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>So what? I'm not saying I even believe this until you can provide a legitimate source, but you're getting angry just like the people did when Rosa Parks sat in the front of the bus. Do you think that Susan B. Anthony should have just shut up and not protested? Martin Luther King Jr. started a movement that saw thousands of minorities fighting against oppression. When there are people who are openly discriminating against a minority, it should be met with opposition. The fight for equality in the eyes of all mankind is still far from over.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 03:57:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 11:55:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>That last guy wasn't even close. He clearly did that on purpose</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 12:11:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>They may have done several takes and one where it was done correctly, but on this particular take, I think he purposefully messed up the flip. Btw. Nice username. Animorphs reference?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 12:15:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Noice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What a close family.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 15:42:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 18:10:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah.. A karma whore already reposted it there 30 minutes ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 18:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>They had the same last name before I blurred it out. I'm guessing father/son? Would be even worse if it's uncle/nephew.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 18:20:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is already over the line, but if it were dad/daughter, I would definitely need some r/eyebleach</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 18:24:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I marked it as such when I originally posted it on a different sub.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 18:35:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah fair enough. I looked around for it but i didn't see it. A friend sent it to me through fb.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 18:37:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Father/son</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>She deserved it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 18:51:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 18:54:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're the man-best</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 20:14:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was sent it by a friend on facebook. The names were unblurred. I poked around for it on reddit but didn't see it anywhere. Assumed it hadn't made it from fb yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 20:42:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>She didn't seem to mind much tbf.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 21:14:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm still fairly new to reddit. I'll get there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 21:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/forwardsfromklandma</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dogs aren't horses you stupid little shit.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 21:16:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 23:27:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Snowball. Nope nope nope. I hate that shit and he knew it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 23:28:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>You play with fire, you're gonna get burned.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 23:51:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you clink your beer on top of somebody elses beer (glass bottle), it causes it to foam up and spill over. Pay close attention to the bottle right after she clinks it. You can see it fizzing up and that's why he puts his mouth over it. All that foam then goes directly into her face. Edit: Apparently, it can shatter it as well. I've never seen it happen IRL, but have definitely seen people do the foam clink. It's probably a matter of force involved.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 02:24:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amazing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found in a small town newspaper. Is he looking for a girlfriend or a chauffeur?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 12:17:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 13:13:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't care, had sex.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 13:34:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>"This nigga throwin beans!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 14:26:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Came in his mouth, he kissed me after and pushed my own cum back into my mouth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Drama over the ethics of clinking somebody's beer devolves into childish insults, your mom jokes, and talk of mass shootings.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 15:47:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 16:27:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mmhmm. I punched him. And he made the mistake of getting me off first. I was done and he finished in the bathroom by himself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 17:28:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I looked, but couldn't find it on this sub. Can you link me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 17:30:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's amazing. Saw him live recently. One of the best comedy shows I've ever been to</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 17:51:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Username checks out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Such tiny tweezers..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 20:21:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 22:55:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>It says you CAN stop time when you're sleeping. Doesn't say time stops when you're sleeping. Presumably, you don't have to stop time every time you go to bed. I think it would be a great power for when you're hungover or just need those few extra hours of sleep in the morning before work. Or maybe you would be missing the party of the year because you have to wake up at 6 for work. You could still go and just freeze time to sleep. Sure, you age a little faster, but I'd rather have a good quality of life and not have to drag myself around hungover just so I age the same as everyone else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 23:24:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair. I actually overlooked the first comment because circadian rhythm caught my eye. I'll acknowledge that i posted that comment on the wrong that considering what the first comment was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 23:27:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>What was the last gif from of the guy floating in mid-air?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Such tiny tweezers..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 11:54:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just one of those mornings...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 16:57:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 22:06:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>5e. I forgot to mention that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 22:28:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't want to multiclass. This is just something our dm has put forth for us to have an opportunity to come up with our own spell or ability. I have multi classed with a different character. Didn't really like it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 23:21:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oo that's a good idea. Maybe the ability to cast 2 single action spells at once once per long rest or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 23:25:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>He would want to make his own ruling on the use of the spell slots involved.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 00:02:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good idea. I've actually thought of something cool and creative for once though! I'm just waiting on the dm vote. Will update if it's approved</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 00:06:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh right. I like the way you think. He's just particular</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 00:24:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>And where might we find pictures of this OSHA compliant penis? For science.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 00:28:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a 5... Apparently. I'd have thought I was a 6 but I just took the lil test.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Baby's First Tea</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 02:55:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 04:08:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boo. I'm not very active on this sub, but mostly because only a few stories every now and then are extremely interesting and provoke serious thought. That was one of only maybe a dozen posts (besides top all time) I have read and loved since I've subscribed. Definitely revise your rules because if something gets almost 900 upvotes in a day on *this* sub, you should be encouraging it, not locking it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 04:09:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like somebody needs to make r/GITMforkids or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 01:11:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It sucks caring about it. But I've upvoted all of yours as well. Here's to fake self esteem!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 01:22:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think so.. And most of it is bs cross-posting. I wish it was more about the things I've said or [oc]</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 01:27:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is actually solid advice. I spend a lot of my day on reddit now. My job allows me to be on my phone about 70% of the time, and then I get home and watch tv in the background while playing with my phone. I have been sucked into reddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 01:30:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Again.. Mostly cross-posting.. Once, I posted a pic of me in cosplay as Madame Medusa, from The Rescuers. It was shite and cheap but when it got 1.2k, I was stoked. Way more excited than when I was x-posting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 01:32:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Top ten what?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 02:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I take my dog, Gavroche, out throughout the day. We luckily live across the street from a park. I maaybe might be on my phone half the time..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 02:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm on antidepressants. Just started a different kind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 02:54:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fake Internet points for posts or comments that get a lot of upvotes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>*squirrel noises*</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 11:38:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 12:54:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will OP ever shave that shit off his face? RemindMe!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 21:58:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn dude. You sexy af</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 03:10:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>It had the absolute most wormwood allowed for for absinthe in that country. I can assure you, at 95%, i was way more drunk than I was ever feeling any psychedelic effects. Edit.. The green fairy sadly seems like a myth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 15:42:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>That smile at the end is adorable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 16:28:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 16:43:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm really not sure what's happening there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 17:49:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 07:48:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool. Yeah. Saw this sign on fb. Didn't realise it was on reddit. I've also said this before in this thread. Sorry it was a repost. You don't have to get on your high horse about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 00:58:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who was that kid, you ask? It was a young Albert Einstein.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 01:12:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Obviously because the dog has been trained and the op wanted upvotes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 03:18:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It had not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 12:30:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Clapped that ass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Gotta love small town news</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 15:26:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 16:13:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought that's where i was at for a second. No way this is real.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 22:52:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Small town boredom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 22:52:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds fun! Do you remember any of the best ones?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any advice?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 11:22:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 15:06:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/shittylifeprotips</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 17:18:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually posted it to born simultaneously. Soz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 21:22:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's my kitty!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 21:30:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Beautiful. Who is he?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any potential here?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 20:34:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 21:06:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd guess the first bit is just ashleigh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 00:33:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha I'll get right on that!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 00:35:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's basically my life. Thanks for the kind words!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 00:37:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This ](https://www.reddit.com/r/Dachshund/comments/8ks79u/here_is_my_heart_gavroche/?st=JIUUD9BO amp;sh=071a0777) is probably the most adorable pic I've got of him if you wanted to see non-flopped ears.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 00:40:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's my first dog as an adult and I'm nearly 30. The struggle is real until you finally get to that point. Someday you will!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 00:43:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sexy af. Looked through your few other posts (definitely need way more) and realised you also have such gorgeous eyes! Make sure to get it all in one pic next time!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 00:44:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will do. And yeah, I get that completely though I've always preferred lil dogs, especially dachshunds. Good luck mate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 01:05:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like honestly. Do you just not like penises? This is a pretty perfect dick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 02:56:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>He actually is a chiweenie! He's 1/4 chihuahua. His big sad face won me over instantly. I feel like he's the perfect combo of the two.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 04:38:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love it. This is the direction I hoped it would take.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 04:40:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aww thanks! I'd love if you linked me to your sister's pup!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 04:45:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shucks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rare toddler edition</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 09:54:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 13:05:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn't notice that. Had to watch 5 more times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 17:00:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>[original post on r/confusingperspective](https://www.reddit.com/r/confusing_perspective/comments/8u4jx6/thats_not_a_slope_on_a_snowy_mountain/?st=JIX8XMAG amp;sh=350b95a8)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 17:02:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought it was a smooth enough recovery to warrent posting it here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 19:24:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sad I had to scroll this far down in the top comments to find this answer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 19:28:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hooked up with a guy and later found out he was one of the lost boys in that film. I can no longer watch it. It's off-putting to watch a child when you can't help but to think of a time when you did sexy times with them as an adult.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 08:25:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pockets I think was his name in the movie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 02:36:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like you might benefit from a sit and a cup of.. mate?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Infinity health bars</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 19:03:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just signing "things"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 22:36:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 22:24:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe we are playing with the first 3 expansions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 22:27:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh ok. Yeah. By 3rd expansion, it must mean the second one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 22:28:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also thanks. I'll pass that along to the group</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 22:34:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Solid. This will be my game plan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 22:39:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>It takes how long now?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 23:22:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Geez. My group is definitely optimistic in thinking it would only take 4-5 hours...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 23:29:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Take my upvote sir, you'd earned it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 23:30:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheers for advice mate. I'll take any and all of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 23:40:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheers man. Thanks for making me be realistic. Our group is now coming to terms with that fact that this will be a two-nighter game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 23:43:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cray. I've honestly never played something like this in my life. Will be quite an experience.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Probably caused by a sugar high</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 23:27:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 00:13:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/quityourbullshit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 14:31:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>The sleeping dude was cute af though so it redeems the gif a bit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 16:26:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same. That smile is perfect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What tf did I just read?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 15:01:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 15:54:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry. Don't mean to shit post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[W] sitting on the toilet and looking at memes for so long that your shitty asshole goes crusty.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 16:53:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 19:55:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>1400 plus on her downline?!? I mean, obviously I know MLMs are a scam and that almost noone actually makes even min wage from it, but even I would think somebody with over a thousand people in their downline would be at least earning a living wage. Anybody got any numbers on how much somebody with 1400 people below them could earn? I'm not asking cause im interested in joining, obvs, just curious. Never heard of somebody actually achieving numbers like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 20:05:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>She only left you with an emotional scar. At least she didn't leave something physical like those crater-face scars you got from teenaged acne.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 20:09:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tbf.. I would gladly be one of the first couple thousand to join an mlm. If they take off, fuck it. At least you'd be getting some dough. I'm more surprised that she would end a genuine 20 year friendship because you didn't want to buy her stuff. Like dude. You got 2700 people making money for you.. Do you really need to disown a genuine friend over a single penny in the bucket?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 12:14:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>A green chick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 22:35:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha for real. Just for the record though, Miranda Sings is actually [quite pretty.](https://www.pinterest.co.uk/pin/437201076304072353/?amp_client_id=g-nGZbYayDk8LHdj27ikLFw9sL22G2khCSIQU2kJoncXt8ktFgL-iuxY5vy2__yv amp;mweb_unauth_id=228fd5cc02591b46d31c63c594a6414f)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 19:21:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any updates on sentencing, op?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 01:21:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>If she threw away her ice cream, then why is she trying to eat his? She was done. He clearly doesn't feel the same way about his ice cream being too much to eat, but now he has to share?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 02:40:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>This effect will always remind of Disney Channel's That's So Weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 02:41:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey! I'm random! And I survived..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 15:22:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hannah Baker is the worst.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 16:20:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean.. Honestly. She made a bunch of tapes that told a very one-sided story and put everyone on blast, a number of whom honestly didn't deserve it. These tapes drove one person to try to commit suicide, another person to heavily consider it, and sent yet another person on a downward spiral that could have ended up with a lot of people's deaths on her hands. She's manipulative, dramatic and moody as hell. I'm not saying she deserved anything that happened to her, but a number of her experiences are stuff that most kids deal with while growing up. Losing friends, boyfriends, waiting for your crush to ask you out, etc. She villianises her fellow classmates for doing stuff that is just a normal part of life. She's the worst. And for the record, I'm a feminist and believe in equality. I think it's disgusting that you would try to invalidate my opinion based solely on my sex.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 17:17:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>She encouraged the bullying by asking people to throw rocks through his windows. Not even her rapist got any retaliation that bad. Yes, I've seen the second season which is why I noted that she told a one-sided, heavily edited story. The whole Zach tape was fairly bullshit. After having slept with him all summer, his comment to her in the cafeteria should easily have been taken as genuine instead of her flipping out on him like she did. Alex would have never connected the two incidents without those tapes, so she is still at fault. So to recap, a bullied girl asks people to bully somebody else back in retaliation, she dramatically turns a simple, nice comment from a former lover into drama and then blasts him on the tapes without even mentioning any of his good sides, and she targeted a Alex for not being her friend anymore which is just a part of life. This targeting of him for no good reason leads to him nearly killing himself and now he is left with permanent disabilities all because of Hannah Baker and her bad decision to hang out at a rapists house, by herself, late at night. I'm not trying to victim blame with that last statement, but I mean come on. Hannah is a smart girl and should have made a better judgment call on whether she should hang out at a rapists' house all alone. It's still on Bryce and does not give him the excuse or reason to do what he did, but if Hannah had been more responsible in her judgement, the entire show wouldn't exist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 17:49:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>This just proves how manipulative and dramatic Hannah was. Yes, she needed help. Instead of seeking help, she dragged others down to her level causing many of her peers to end up with their own problems. This is a very selfish personality trait. If you have problems, you shouldn't have the "if I'm going down, you're going down with me" kind of mentality. Mental illness is a serious thing, but just because you have one, all of your actions are not automatically excused. You still need to take responsibility for the way your condition can affect others. Not everything about Zach is black and white. However, it's very black and white that she painted him as this douchebag who was trying to lower her self-esteem when she no doubt hurt him just as badly by making a scene over a nice, genuine compliment that she must've absolutely known wasn't to be taken the way she took it. She chose not to mention on the tapes about how he was amazing to her all summer long and that's black and white. She made the conscious decision to make him look as bad as possible by only telling a small part of a larger story. And of course, I agree that's it's not her fault. It's never a victims fault. However, if you know somebody gets violently drunk, you shouldn't be around that person when he drinks. If you can't swim, you shouldn't dive into the deep end when you're alone. If you don't want to be mauled to death, don't hang out in a lion's den. These things are common sense. Your instincts should tell you not to put yourself in a situation you know could be potentially dangerous. If the abusive drunk punches you, he's still at fault for assault and he's not off the hook, but had you used your instincts and better judgement, you wouldn't have put yourself in that situation that you knew was dangerous in the first place.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 06:24:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. It's not harmless as you can see from other peoples comments, if done hard enough, she could have knocked the bottom of his beer out resulting in broken glass and possible injury. And also.. Just don't be a dick, ya know? I don't like to be covered in beer, do you? She certainly got covered..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 06:24:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I indeed fell for that sub</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 07:06:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>WTF, man?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 13:00:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 11:16:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't either. This post is over a month old. I certainly don't care anymore and there's little chance of very many others seeing your comment soo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mad lad gets a Sonic shake</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 11:12:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Megamind</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 11:39:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 13:26:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Og post link?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 22:23:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tbh.. I didn't realise it was a little person. Either way.. If you're fine with poking fun at non-little people with big foreheads, then it's kind of biased. I make fun of everybody equally. I'm just a good person like that. When you start to pick and choose who to make fun of/treat extra nicely/treat differently based solely on somebodys disabilities or their minority status, then you're still being biased and treating others differently based on things they can't help. Call me what you will.. Downvote me to hell.. But yeah.. I treat everyone the same. If I will make fun of one person with a big forehead, nobody else is going to be immune because I'm not going to treat anybody differently. I choose not to be prejudiced in that way..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 01:03:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once, I was in a youth group and it was just a huge room with tons of bouncy balls. People were just throwing them around at each other. One girl was a bit unpopular and had leg braces. Absolutely nobody would throw a ball at her. I said fuck it. She was clearly being left out. I nailed her like 4-5 times. She fell down quite a few times. Got up smiling and threw balls back at me. I could see some people looking at me a bit shocked when I would throw the ball hard enough that she would wobble and fall over. Idgaf. She seemed to love being treated like everyone else. I personally just think that if you treat people with disabilities and minorities the same way that you treat everyone else, they appreciate it more. They already feel like outsiders the way it is. You don't need to tip-toe around them and their feelings. That's practically as alienating as being ostracised. I do want to clarify that I would never tease somebody who doesn't have the mental capacity to understand what's happening. This is more about minorities and disabilities, definitely not people with conditions that affect their brain function.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 02:00:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I rip on my friends constantly. It's a big part of my culture to make fun of your friends and shit. It's a way of bonding and being able to laugh about your flaws. I do this with people I like regardless of their afflictions. You do you as well. I just choose not to alienate people. In this particular instance with this post, I would never take it down now because I found out she's a little person. I wouldn't have taken it down for anybody else and I'm not going to jump to change that just because somebody doesn't fit the "norm."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 02:03:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe, as other people have mentioned, that she may be a little person. I didn't realise this at first, but I stand by posting this here either way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 02:39:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any term can become something people hate if it's used in a derogatory way. Over 50 years ago, saying somebody has mental retardation was commonplace and not offensive. Since then, the word retarded has been used in a negative way giving it a whole new level of connotation far beyond the original definition. Humans will see "new" derogatory words rise and fall as time goes on. Mix up some context and connotation with a bit of time and you've got yourself a new slur.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 09:16:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe that rabbit is flipping people off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 09:29:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Downvoted as it seems you're well past 2500 and I want to keep the balance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 17:07:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's very little logic to the entire thing. Don't overthink it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 18:40:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I dunno why, but I hate this fucking video and the song and just everything about it. I wish it would disappear forever instead of being reposted every other year. Honestly it's so old and annoying and yeah. Fuck this video and people who repost it. Downvote away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 18:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You do you. I might have enjoyed it the first time.. Over 5 years ago when it was first posted. Why do people upload garbage that is clearly old af as if they think it's never been on reddit before? Lame ass shit imo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 19:14:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Super unpopular opinion, but I actually liked the 3rd Maguire movie far more than the second one. At least he wasn't a powerless pussy douche in the 3rd one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 19:30:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just stating my opinion. I know it's unpopular, but I felt it needed saying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 19:46:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I delivered my opinion in the way I wanted to. I was intentionally being condescending. This video is fucking old and stupid and I wanted to make sure OP knew that in the most blunt way possible. Shame on OP for sharing old garbage that was barely amusing in the first place. It's so fuckin old the dog in the video isn't even still alive. So yeah. I stand by it all and my delivery. I rarely do things like this so when I think it's deserved, I don't hold back. I just really, really hate this video. Sorry, not sorry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 20:31:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>No more than it cares what you think, so why bother commenting at all?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any Drag Race fans?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 20:58:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 19:27:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>The vaults are awesome! I really enjoyed my tour down there. Just google Edinburgh vaults for more info.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 22:48:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you're reading to far into it..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 22:51:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was never suggesting drag queens should be part of the harry potter canon. If you realise it's a joke, then why try to read further into it? You must be fun at parties.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 22:52:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm the one who wrote them..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 22:55:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was only combining HP and Drag Race quotes. You know.. Like how the picture is of a drag queen that resembles Umbridge and they made puns about it mixing the two. I'm not sure what you're failing to understand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 07:01:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shut up, Meg.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anybody know where I can find a printable Cleric spell list similar to this Druid list? Specifically a Tempest Cleric if possible, but I'll take what I can get.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 11:03:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 14:23:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll have a google. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 14:53:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>The idea that pedo's are trying to gain acceptance by joining the LGBT community is nothing but a plot by the alt-right to drag the LGBT community through the mud by making it seem that gays and lesbians etc are just as bad and belong in the same group as pedophiles. It's right wing propaganda that you've obviously fallen for. Way to stay woke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>R Kelly releases "I Admit," a 19-minute song discussing how he's not actually a pedophile.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 21:25:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 22:50:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>["Clovergender" is one example ](https://www.snopes.com/fact-check/are-people-identifying-as-clovergender/) [Yet another example of the Alt-Right pushing this bullshit](https://www.snopes.com/fact-check/lgbtp-adding-letter/) Snopes is pretty easy to use dude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 00:19:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once, I was dreaming and I think I heard a noise. I semi-woke up but must've been lucid dreaming a bit. I thought the noise was our apartment door opening and that I could see a man entering our bedroom. I face the door in the bed I share with my husband. I hatched a plan to pretend to be sleeping and keep my eyes barely peeping at the intruder while he crept closer. When he was within range, I let out a loud yell and just started sleepily slapping the crap out of my husband. It dawned on me that I had never actually opened my eyes or seen anyone. I knew this because I was laying facing my partner and had my back to the door the whole time. It was a strange experience. Dreaming and then "waking up" but still in a lighter dream that I'm in bed. My husband was fine and just laughs about it now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 06:25:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah no problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"You'll just feel a scratch." The words said to me at the hospital before drawing blood from my hand. Still got this a week later.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 13:53:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 17:08:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would be if he wasn't a weebo who has been to jail for meth possession.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 18:16:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is that subreddit? I don't get the premise..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's so great when I can be a jerk to my man and he just sits there and takes it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 15:03:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 18:32:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah.. I dont get it. Do people not like her?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 10:21:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. It's delicious if you've never had it..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 09:51:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yaaas. Besides Deathly Hallows, GOF was my favourite book. They completely ruinded the movie though and I think it's easily the worst film of the series. Such a damn shame.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The worst kind of "OopsDidntMeanTo"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 23:26:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 18:41:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>i</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 19:36:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An explosive device used to cause avalanches</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 12:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Be careful!! Oh.. Wait.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 16:33:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 17:59:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Remember me~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 18:00:56</DATE>
    <TEXT> #129335; #8205; #9792; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Posting this to a FB singles dating page is pretty trashy imo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 18:46:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 18:53:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha i wondered the same thing! I was going to put something like that in the but it got long. Like a friend of hers had to tie her up like this and take the photos</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Was trying to get a good picture of his sleepy time blep, but I got caught.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 11:41:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 15:47:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Au/titletoimagebot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 18:11:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know! My phone was on silent. There wasn't even a click or anything</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 22:20:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah! Mine likes to bury himself in our head pillows [like this,](https://www.reddit.com/r/Dachshund/comments/8lw7to/does_every_dachshund_do_this_or_is_mine_the_only/?st=JK8PWA85 amp;sh=8aa9f401)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sweet, sweet vindication</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 11:52:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 15:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure what you think I've faked. I took a screenshot of my fb feed. I didn't make the original post about the roses. Fair enough, the roses are photoshopped, but since u/Naspbeats has nicely pointed out that the are a number of real green flowers (not to mention actual green roses though they don't look like this) I believe that my friends original point stands and I'd call it a win.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 15:58:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>In his second comment, he is seemingly attacking me directly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 16:37:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah good. I wanted to be amused by this but I couldn't knowing all the birds probably died. Now there's no guilt. Solid stunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 17:19:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/reallifewins</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 17:35:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was waiting for this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 18:17:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>OP? Aka my friend in real life? Is that you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 20:27:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome! Welcome to Reddit! Here's some good subs to try out: r/trashy r/nosleep if you like spooky stories r/idontworkherelady usually has plenty of entitled bitches being put in their place r/pettyrevenge r/prorevenge and r/maliciouscompliance are all pretty self explanatory and good content r/dankmemes r/kidsarefuckingstupid r/shittydadreflexes r/childrenfallingover Any reddits starting with r/holdmy are usually pretty good r/awfuleyebrows r/murderedbywords r/instantkarma r/idiotsfightingthings r/justiceserved r/crappydesign There are just so so so many. You can do a search on any kind of fandom you belong to and you'll no doubt find a thriving subreddit for it. When you go to a new subreddit, you can change the tab that says "Hot" to "Top" and then "All time" and it gives you the best of the best and gives you a great example of what kind of content the sub has. Enjoy Reddit! If any random redditors want to add to this list, please feel free!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 21:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know! And you get to avoid all the bullshit pyramid schemes! Speaking of which, r/antimlm is pretty funny as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 23:13:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for sharing. If it gets less than 100 upvotes in 24 hours, I'll gladly delete it as I'll realise then that it's not a good fit for sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 23:16:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everybody has their own reasoning for their system of posting on reddit. That's just how i roll.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 00:04:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/subsyoufellfor</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 00:12:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Done. Didn't know that was a thing! I'll be moving my post there instead. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm looking for a subreddit that shows police violence but ONLY after its been concluded and the cop was sufficiently punished for their corruption. Something similar to bad_cop_no_donut but again, only when the cop actually faces charges or is otherwise punished.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 00:27:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've looked several times, but i can't seem to come up with anything. I love when I see cops get justice for their cruel ways, but it leaves me seething and unable to have a good day when i see one of the thousands of videos of police abuse and know they just got away with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 00:40:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amazing! I've only just discovered this findasub reddit and I'm impressed now! I'm going to have a look through them with a bit of leisure so I'm going to leave this post up for a lil while. Unless there was one not covered by u/boxscape everyone can consider this one answered!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 01:21:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 01:41:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>[this is the original post I made that inspired this question.](https://www.reddit.com/r/facebookwins/comments/93d3wy/sweet_sweet_vindication/?st=JKACH0C4 amp;sh=df9c4abd) There are already numerous responses by people in that thread which could belong here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 01:42:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Verified. This is the real OP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nice build up</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 10:45:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 11:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've never seen it before and thought it was amazing. My husband and I pretty much live online so when neither of us had seen it before, I thought fuck it. It's a year old but redditors need this in their lives. Sorry if it's extremely old, but hopefully, it reaches a bunch of new people like myself, who's lives will be momentarily made better by what I can only say, is simply the best angry note I've ever seen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 15:06:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 15:15:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I dream about my dead mom a lot. She died nearly 3 years ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 15:43:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheers bro</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 18:48:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Super ULPT: do this anywhere for anytime you're hungover. If anybody asks about it months later, garner further sympathy for the miscarriage you had.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 19:57:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Politcal activism is also very much a part of history, culture and heritage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 23:54:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>u/titletoimagebot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 09:35:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. Like. We may not have loads of money and are approximately lower middle class, but at least we wouldn't abuse the kids physically and emotionally. We'd probably have to jump through a hundred hoops anyway as we're a married gay couple. That is, if we'd even be allowed to at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 11:20:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Underrated comment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 12:07:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You'd be surprised how many people think that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 15:45:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds shite that you go through that and you're not even a girl.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Catching up with an old friend and had this convo. I think it speaks for itself. Let's lift up EVERY member of our community!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 19:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 20:07:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well it's certainly not the whole community, obviously. But it's certainly enough that I feel attention needs to be brought to it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 20:09:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. It's this attitude that needs to be left in the past. Definitely no reason to be thinking like this in 2018.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 20:31:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like somebody making contact with an infinity some.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 22:11:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Optimism had never been my strong suit. I'd love to be more of an activist, but, as I'm fairly poor, the most I could ever do would be protesting somewhere within reasonable travel. Unfortunately, my pessimism just convinces me this won't do much anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 23:57:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess I just don't see much change that these campaigns have effected in recent years...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 10:12:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just don't care that much who has it. I've got pics of my pets up that could be used to dox me if people really cared. I post what I post with pride and 0 fucks given. Also.. I don't care much about Karma.. Over 60,000 in less than a year. If I cared that much, I feel like I could reach that again with a new account.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 10:37:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>No because it's not true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 10:38:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bad bot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 10:47:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Failed to see any adults kissing children in that video. So you mad that some kids kissed each other at a gay pride? Would you be mad if it were hetero kids at a birthday party playing spin the bottle? I've certainly done that as a kid that couldn't have been any older than those kids. Looking for any excuse to be mad. Smdh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 11:10:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I knew you were being funny, just felt like sharing my thoughts on it either way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 13:35:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>What video did you watch? I saw a few light kisses. Maybe a couple lingering ones. I failed to see any "making out"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 13:50:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You never played spin the bottle? 7 minutes in heaven? These are OLD SCHOOL games soo.. I dunno. When were kids innocent? The 1800s? Cause you certainly can't say that games like haven't been being played for quite some time now. You can be against children innocently kissing each other all you want, but using this footage to try to tie the LGBT to pedophiles is just straight up bullshit and you know it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 14:25:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then why bother commenting at all? You literally didn't watch the video, you're not on topic in any way, like.. What were you adding to the conversation? Kids making out has literally nothing to do with anything that was said so just go back to sleep.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 22:43:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait a second.. Sears is *running*??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Whatever works</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 15:45:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 16:43:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I need to see more of this guys videos.. For science.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 23:34:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dear god. I hope people take the plunge and click this added link. It will haunt me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 23:36:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>The speed at which that croc springs into the water and then when it swims toward the woman is simply terrifying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My pup was scared of a soccer ball that somebody left in our backyard. We live in an apartment building, and this was about 11 pm, so you'll hear me shushing his barks.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 00:22:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 01:13:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shiiiit. I'm an idiot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 01:29:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know what you mean. This was a customer who was so unfamiliar with those kind of cartoons that he immediately tried to make me seem like a kid because I watch cartoons. How do you break through that cultural barrier about a cartoon that's made for adults, but you can't just describe the things in Archer that are inapropes? My wording to him could have been better, for sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 01:39:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did try to bring up Family Guy, South Park, and American Dad but he didn't know of any of those. He was unfamiliar with cartoons that are aimed at an older audience. I could be wrong, but I assumed this particular lack of knowledge was just cultural so I noted that he was African.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 03:24:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in the UK. The dude was legit African from Africa.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 07:21:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha yass. That must be it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>After all that..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 13:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not Ken M on this guy's woooosh</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 15:53:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 16:01:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a step in the right direction. Keep it up man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 16:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not. I've just never been into other people who were 15% French, 25% Irish, 20% Dutch, 25% Scotish and 15% other. Call me a dick or whatever, but it's just my preference.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 16:16:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Friends. Food. Drugs. And the crazy liquor. Everytime I go back to America, there's some new flavour of vodka or some delicious root beer thats actually beer or something. British people just don't get creative. And yeah.. Lots more recreational drugs available in America though you can find some decent ones here for cheap if you know where to look.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 16:17:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>The lotto numbers for the next big payout. Pretty obvs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 16:20:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, but I'm wearing this vomit on my sweater already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It only took two panels</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 16:24:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 16:39:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Got absolutely shit faced with Charlotte Crosby at a company day out. Ended up getting arrested and spent the night in jail for causing a disturbance after getting kicked out of the venue. It's not her fault, but honestly.. Who plays beer pong with wine? I got pretty fucked, pretty fast.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 16:39:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ligma</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 16:43:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>E</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 17:34:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/iamverysmart</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 17:41:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/findasubreddit might know of one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 23:37:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another classic #DaddyofFive upload</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 00:03:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>What green and smells like yellow paint? Green paint.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 09:53:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually tried to. You can see from my post history they I would normally xpost. It just wouldn't allow me at the time I saw it. Didn't see this subreddit in my subreddit list.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wat.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 05:51:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I just never know the right thing to say lol</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 12:52:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 23:22:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not just an unpopular opinion, but if opinions could be wrong, this is the most erroneous opinion of them all. Have my upvote.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 23:26:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've sprinkled a bit of mint into a spliff once and it was delightful. However, I've never tried to replace the tobacco with just mint full stop. I think that could possibly end up harsh af.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 00:51:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 00:54:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can weigh in on both sides. As an American who has lived in the UK for nearly 5 years, I gotta say.. Spliffs all the way. Once you start smoking them, it's nearly impossible to go back to pure weed hits. I nearly died the last time I visited home and kept having to smoke bowls and bongs etc. I kind of wish this weren't the case, but i still have 0 regrets about smoking spliffs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 03:15:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>After you sing the line "I just want to tell you all to go fuck yourselves."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 03:18:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Goodbye</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 03:20:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. I don't get it either.. It's late and I looked at this for so long, I started to wonder if it was loss. Way to do that to me OP.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 06:22:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>My little sister, who was old enough at the time to know better asked, " Bubby, do we have two hearts? One in our chest and one in our neck, cause I can feel one in there too."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 08:43:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>u/titletoimagebot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 08:47:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's something incredibly adorable about this guy that I can't quite put my finger on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 09:18:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't read it as the kid saying "this is my scientific evidence" but rather that that's how his dad described the findings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 09:29:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>[take your own advice?](https://www.reddit.com/user/inonimi/comments/8us2b1/hong_kong_beauty19201200/?st=JKTDZF77 amp;sh=ad9116fe)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 17:25:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>u/titletoimagebot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 00:32:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol honestly. Why did I even bother clicking on that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 04:34:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah. This is just a picture of crisis actors lounging on their break. /s In all seriousness, this is inspiring af. Gonna seize that day tomorrow!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This definitely happened organically</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 09:48:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I hate this but it's so well done that I just don't know</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 10:03:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 10:07:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>France. Sorry. Should have noted it was a xpost from r/evilbuildings Couldn't xpost directly for some reason.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 10:09:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>[original post in r/evilbuildings ](https://www.reddit.com/r/evilbuildings/comments/978xno/polygone_riviera_france/?st=JKUUTL2J amp;sh=afb8cdfd)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 10:23:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Polygon Riviera</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 10:42:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well shit. I'm gonna have words with him. In the comments he says he's a lovely boy. This might get posted later to r/quityourbullshit Who fakes something like this for Facebook likes? You don't even get karma... [original post by friend on Facebook ](https://imgur.com/wSHh1nU)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 10:44:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also I'll be removing in a minute after you have seen these comments. Thanks for letting me know!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 10:45:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perhaps because people haven't seen it before? I've certainly never come across it and I've never intentionally reposted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 10:46:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's seemingly paper towel and soap dispensers attached to the wall in front of the mirror.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 10:52:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay dokie. I was only going off the og post in r/evilbuildings which I have linked to in another comment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 14:43:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 14:43:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please don't make me imagine that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Old Fb profile pic of a friend posted with permission. Took her 40 minutes to do this and she doesn't even have cats..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 14:59:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 15:07:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Y'all need to stop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 15:08:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely more time on your hands than I have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 17:02:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can confirm. It was MS paint. After I was done cry laughing, I asked why she put in so much effort. Apparently, she thought it would make her look cool</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 09:03:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>And get along with each other.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An appropriate response to those kinds of people</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:37:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>10/10 clap back</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 13:21:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 13:54:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Downvoted to help you out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 13:57:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>A</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Don't help, just take a picture for upvotes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 14:07:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 14:48:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Obligatory the Harry Potter series.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 14:50:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go for it. You miss 100% of the shots you don't take.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 14:51:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> #129335; #8205; #9792; #65039; living with awkwardness is better than living with regret imo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 15:01:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Goodbye</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 15:01:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>K</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 15:35:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've read this before... By in the wild, do you mean on reddit?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 16:51:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah.. Getting sent something by a friend isn't really what I'd describe as "finding something in the wild," but you do you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've been in the hospital for nearly a week and just had my gallbladder removed yesterday. Been asking my husband to send me daily pics of my puppy and I got this sneaky one today.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 19:40:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 20:07:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 13:05:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>King James Version by Harvey Danger</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 16:26:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gavroche constantly causes and drags fluff around the house. We literally vacuum 3 times a week ir more. We just can't keep up with him. Don't know where he even gets it from!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 16:31:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah yeah. He's gonna be doing everything for the next week or so fo show.. And thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's lasted quite awhile, but I think he is finally going to destroy the toughest toy we've gotten him yet.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 18:25:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 18:49:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know! Yes destroyed at least  #163;50 worth of toys in the 6 months we've had him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you've already snapped, but she's still on your stones.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 19:58:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 20:42:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mysterious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 17:21:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Feep like this might be better on r/whatisthisthing or r/nostupidquestions as it's not really a question that's going to inspire varying answers with good thread discussions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 17:49:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>This. I've never met a bad dog, just bad owners.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 17:54:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/boneappletea</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 19:32:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry. I can't remember where it was posted for the first time. It had a title attached to the image that I cropped off and then uploaded it here. Edit. It was an actual post though. I didn't see it in a comment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 22:17:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gallstones do not generally pass like that. Source: am currently in the hospital as I've just had my gallbladder removed on Friday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 22:49:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was that am electric skateboard? If not, how did he get that much momentum from that tiny jump?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 22:52:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gave you an upvote, but i would have started the wasted part when he's falling back, just as his eyes get really big.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 22:53:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for that nightmares!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 23:09:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh nice spot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 00:15:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh yeah. Painful leading up to it if you go through an attack whilst waiting. Also, very painful if you have any stones left behind in your bile duct after your gallbladder is removed. They had to do an endoscopy today and then, using that camera for visuals, cut me from the inside and squeeze the last of the stones out of this duct so that my body would pass them. Felt pretty great within hours of that. If you don't have to worry about either of these things, then you'd likely be able to go home the next day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 02:27:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep, hence why I said it was pretty rare. They almost always get stuck in the bile duct before making it into your intestines which is pain city. Nobody said anything about peeing one out? If you were just adding extra clarification, no probs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 02:29:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks and yeah.. I feel ya. I'm hoping I'm going to be able to eat like a fat piece of shit again one day. Gonna be well sad if my body can't handle it ever again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 02:35:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair enough. I'm half asleep. It seemed as if they were implying that I said you could pee them out. Probably just read too far into it with my sleep-deprived mind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 04:24:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks pal!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 06:02:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm so funny after a bit of sugar!  #128514; #129315; #128514;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 08:12:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 11:14:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay? Sad to see you go?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 11:19:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you referring to the sarcastic laughing smileys?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 11:43:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh gotcha. Yeah.. You definitely need to have a strong stomach to handle all the cringe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 11:54:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't. Tbf.. I'm not entirely sure what's even happening there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 12:56:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's gotten loads better! I moved to England about 5 years ago though, so that'd be why.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 13:12:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ant-Man won't be in it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 13:36:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some ketamine and a spliff usually do it if I'm desperate to fall asleep quickly. Typically, I just lay there for a few hours until I eventually drift off</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 13:39:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sweet! He's one of my favourites. Just assumed with the ending of Ant-Man and the Wasp that they wouldn't be making an appearance in Avengers 4</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 13:55:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>You miss out on all the great threads and comments though? I like browsing new about 25% of the time, but I think I would get bored of reddit if that's the only way I ever browsed.. Adk Reddit would be particularly boring if you never saw the posts that took off...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 14:27:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If you can't handle a girlfriend who flips out over dumb shit, then you deserve a hoe!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 15:50:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 16:16:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw it on r/nothowdrugswork and double checked that it wasn't on this subreddit within the same time period. Might not have gone back far enough though. Sorry mate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 16:54:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>She is implying that she's going to start fights about little things that don't need fighting about just because she likes to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 16:56:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have seen it and the after credit scene. It was because of that that I assumed he wouldn't be in the next one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 17:05:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't think about him making it out on his own tbf. Figured he'd just be stuck in there until everyone got snapped back into existence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 17:06:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's my favourite way to do it. (:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 17:20:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wasn't but hey. You do you. You clearly just have way more time on your hands than I do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 19:28:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry! Didn't see it here before I shared it. You actually know this person?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 19:28:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 19:35:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha you must have loads of OC from this person then! I genuinely thought it was only shared to r/nothowdrugswork I never repost intentionally. I am a fan of xposting though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 21:41:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Arnold Schwarzenegger</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 21:48:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been in the hospital since last Monday because I needed surgery to get my gallbladder removed. Was supposed to go home yesterday, then today, and now it won't be until tomorrow or possibly Thursday. My puppy has been stressed out without me. He's chewing through everything and apparently runs to the door every single time he hears the main door to the flat building opening. I miss him loads and just want to get back home to him already!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:17:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well.. There used to be craigslist, but they've removed the personals. Not sure where you can easily sell yourself on the Internet anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 11:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you post a pic of your baby? Perhaps gone, but never forgotten. Sorry for your loss OP.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 11:51:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd wash up with a spurt of Davy Gravy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 12:33:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check out Prey if you haven't read that one. Seems to be one of his less popular books, but it's amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 14:11:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>F</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 17:13:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>What. The. Fuck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 17:38:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Steal posts" It's clearly been crossposted from another subreddit. Never claimed it was my own OC and anybody who wants to can go right to the original post and upvote it there. Do you honestly think every crosspost is "stealing content?" The whole purpose of that feature is for people to share content to other pages where they think it might be more suitable. Do apologise about not recognising it's a boy. Looked like a girl to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 17:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Way to steal content.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 17:42:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow. Stealing content are we?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 17:51:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tis true. I did say lady. I'm soo soo sorry to have offended you by my mislabeling. Just thought this was a neat gif that fits in this subreddit. Sue me. I'm in the hospital on loads of painkillers after having just had my gallbladder removed. Sorry my love of reddit and slight loopyness when it came to making a title is causing you such distress, but I could honestly care less. Downvote away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 17:56:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. My bad. Was half asleep on painkillers when I crossposted this. Got deleted by the mods for not having a descriptive enough title. In my efforts to add a better description, I made a mistake. That's all on me. Soz.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 18:03:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apparently. The ironic thing is is that the last two posts by this crumpets person are crossposts. Edit: crumpets originally stated that I was stealing content despite the fact that this is clearly a crosspost. Now they are just trolling and have edited their original statement to make them seem like less of a tool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not being a pedophile means you're a Nazi (reposting because I forgot to censor this insane person)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 18:58:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 19:45:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Deleted. Sorry. I had never seen it before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 20:30:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't downvote all *3* of your posts. Just mearly calling you out for being a hypocite on two of them. Such an exaggerating troll. I, for one, have never been that sad or even considered such a thing. Have fun downvoting all my posts for the next few hours though. Whatever tickles the fancy in your sad life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 20:31:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/nononono is a YouTube channel? Are you being this much of a troll on the original post?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 20:42:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perhaps when you edit things, you should state that they're edited if you're going to change the context. Got a few downvotes so you had to edit your post to make it seem like you're not a douche. Haha so sad. Now, begone troll! This was amusing for a minute but I'm over it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 20:44:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly.. I'm stuck in the hospital. I've got nothing better to do. You're just this much of a shitty person that you are happily wasting your life to be a troll. Hope that's fulfilling for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Surely there is great potential here. Let me know of any investments that pay off!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 07:47:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pedaling your essential oils scam on a post about kids committing suicide</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 12:51:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>NSFL guy describes his smegma build up hardening and how it could stink up a room</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 09:07:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 21:14:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>The shade!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 22:05:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha that is.. Very specific.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 22:06:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Btw. If anybody is at the Manchester Pride Festival and spots Adore, she'd probably be more than happy to take a picture. Apparently, not many people have asked because people don't know what she looks like outside of drag.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 22:11:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least you took him to the hospital. Now stop drinking and driving ya dope. Just do it at home amd ruin your own families life like all the other alcoholics do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 00:53:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 00:56:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is needed to know. This post is going nowhere fast without the actual context or reveal of the rain he's a mad lad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Kicking your 13 year-old daughter out of the house because she was "disrespecting your man"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 09:20:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 09:44:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not in the UK ):</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 11:14:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dachshund for life. Their little paws and long bodies melt my heart.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 11:18:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Laying around and recovering from gallbladder removal surgery. I have to miss the Manchester Gay Pride festival this weekend even though I've had tickets for months. ):</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 11:22:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a rescue cat with one eye that we named Dumpster Baby or D.B. for short. IASIP reference</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 14:35:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus christ. This is no longer r/casualchildabuse</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 05:12:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah yeah.. I tried posting that here a few days ago.. It didn't go anywhere so I deleted it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 14:35:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's [mine.](https://imgur.com/a/7dM8RE1) It's been my background for almost 4 years. Basically ever since I owned by first iPhone. No plans to change it soon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm sure he's fine</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 11:00:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So many variations of the same fake text. Do people still find this funny?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 12:20:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 12:36:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's like candy cane.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Reddit ads are getting ridiculous. Just counted 6 ads per 4 posts on my feed, including several that were back to back the *exact same ad.*</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 13:11:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>There has been a ridiculous amount of ads on reddit lately. I've just counted 6 ads for only 4 posts, and several of them were back to back ads that were the EXACT same.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 14:32:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 15:05:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually know somebody who does that irl. It's fucking annoying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 19:21:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bye Felicia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 20:29:34</DATE>
    <TEXT> #163;100</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 03:10:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/fuckyouKaren</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 09:25:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was from 172d ago. No lesson has been learned or anything will be learned by this point, but thanks for playing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 10:02:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anytime.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The piece of turkey is stuck to the underside of the glass. Strap in cause it takes him several minutes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 12:21:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 13:05:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Megamind irl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 20:12:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I find that, with too tight of a crop, you can end up with a thumbnail thats cutting words off, forcing you to click it in order to read it. If the letters are big enough and the whole post is included in the thumbnail, it's nice to be able to read it directly from the homepage without clicking through.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 00:55:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always thought it was 2 or more. I guess it's just more than 2, but not much more. I tried.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 05:43:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is indeed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 09:53:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>The best cider there is, hands down. It's just soo sweet though. Can only have a couple before I turn to Westens instead</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Socks on the floor!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 11:13:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 13:31:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't try to actually present facts to these people. They have willfully ignored these things for years now. You'll just end up driving yourself crazy trying to reason with an idiot who refuses to acknowledge anything outside of their delusional lil bubble.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 13:52:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just don't care about any of the characters. I'm not invested in them in the least. Feels thrown together from a shitty comedy recipe instead of actual group of main characters who have chemistry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 14:08:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just be confident when you shower</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wildly testicle and also one of the most uncomfortable things I've ever seen</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 17:14:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yee-haw!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 20:51:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 20:54:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's a crazy ex-boyfriend, he's so broken inside..!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 22:28:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>This should have been uploaded as a gif since i had to click rewatch button approximately 17 times..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 22:51:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! Did much better there! I have been subbed to r/OSHA for ages so it's nice to finally contribute.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 23:49:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep! 3.2k so far</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 00:08:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why did I click that? I know better...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 01:06:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aww that's cute. Wish i could edit the title now..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 07:43:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you do that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:06:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>You guys look like the kind of couple you'd find in magazines. Congrats!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 11:46:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Being gay and having a crush on Jonathan Taylor Thomas instead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Did you hear that random noise? Must be food!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 23:23:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 23:52:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never read the article as it's one of those bs ones you have to click through 30 times to read it all. Wish I could give you context. Was only looking at the comments hoping for a clickbait saviour to explain what I was seeing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 23:59:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice. Not heard of that sub before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 00:31:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sucks mate. Try to stay positive! You're a young, good looking chap and if you handle all your problems this well, you'll make a great husband to somebody else someday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 00:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>With the lanes going the directions they are, this is a country with a left-sided driver. So yes, the person recording is also definitely the person driving the car as well. This makes them an idiotincar as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 00:47:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Friar Tuck? Is that you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'll just get in a high speed car chase with my baby in the backseat</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 01:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 01:20:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/hardcorechildabuse</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:25:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because there are terrible parents in the world I suppose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:34:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>And just like irl, this person is lying about how much karma/how many followers they *actually* have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:55:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats on the weight loss. You're an inspiration!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 08:03:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are still too many places in the world where the LGBT actually ARE victims. Where they are disowned, imprisoned, or straight up killed for being LGBT. Until this isn't the case, you can bet your ass I'm going to be fighting for equality as loudly and proudly as I can because we are still far from equal friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 08:12:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Been watching Paradise PD? Haha. Just saw the first episode myself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 08:16:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Were you pissed? Did you ever get revenge somehow?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 08:27:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah. I like seeing beefcakes walkin about with no shirts on. While I'm gay and not invested in such, I actually think it's only fair that women get to walk around with no shirt on as well. If we could get this kind of equality and society could get over a topless woman, we'd finally be able to leave public nursing women alone and everyone could move on with their lives instead of freakin out about some *boooobs*.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 08:34:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>What fruit/vegatables are these? Why are they mixed? Is one just peeled and the other isn't? I don't think I'm going to be able to sleep until I get answers..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 08:38:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 08:53:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I realise that.. It almost looked like oniona or something though where some have been peeled and others hadn't. I just honestly had no idea what they were</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>