<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7678</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 16:05:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have to read the graphic novel to get an understanding of both of these questions and the alternative realities they might be living in. I don #8217;t want to give out too much, but... [We find out at the end of the novel that it very well might have all been a dream because he could just be in a comatose state *or* still in the process of dying. Time in the subconscious (and unconscious) world works differently.  #8220;Dying #8221; at the end could very well be true death.] (/spoiler)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 16:09:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, The parent did by being so goddamn stupid that they couldn #8217;t run this by his pediatrician first. Or researching what asthma actually *is.*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 03:52:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>100%. I do this all the time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 03:53:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do not recommend that. Say it after, but don #8217;t let it be a consideration of your qualifications.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 15:04:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t you mean  #8220;Mechokeme. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 04:49:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>*I BELIEVE I CAN FLYYY*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 16:54:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>23.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 20:08:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>wrong movie  #127871; I think you meant to say *Wade* dies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 05:22:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha the regeneration process for him is always the disturbing and potentially upsetting (not to mention *disappointing*  #128514;) part.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 01:38:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s a very detailed kinetic sand creature.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 23:16:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Along with the possibility of being killed by the Campbell #8217;s in doing so, Sam was more *logical* without a soul. Drinking Demon Blood, while useful to the task at hand, isn #8217;t logical. Besides, soulless Sam never felt the emotional/mental *need* for demon blood because addiction doesn #8217;t effect those without emotion. It was his emotions that drove him to drink it (a incessant need for power and control over his life), which were waned down significantly without a soul. The demon blood gave soulful Sam control over his life where all else seemed hopeless and helpless to him. It gave him a rush. He loved  #8220;the feeling of it #8221; and couldn #8217;t stop thinking about it, even without usage for long periods of time. Without a soul, he no longer felt the emotional baggage of a shifty upbringing and absent parents, the loss of Jessica and other loved ones he #8217;d lost no longer bothered him. He also no longer felt so inclined to put himself in danger in order to save others. This might be a reason he didn #8217;t want his soul back. Logically, he *was* better off without it; but he wasn #8217;t *really* Sam without it. [With his soul back and even so many years later, I do believe he still struggles with the mental/emotional need for demon blood as there have been small hints throughout the series, as well as implications of still having demon blood inside him. I #8217;d like to see more on that in Season 14, as well as him talking about and showing his struggle with Lucifer #8217;s torture and, quite possibly,  #8220;Hallucifer #8221; as he never stated he stopped seeing him, he only asked Castiel if *he* still saw him.](/spoiler).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 23:33:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>U</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 23:42:04</DATE>
    <TEXT> #220;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 23:42:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>K</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 23:52:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nooo don #8217;t name the person, you #8217;ll just confirm it to them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 05:21:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good bot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 04:34:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. For me, it #8217;s caused by a co-occurring wheat allergy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 05:09:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>C</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 06:21:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>N</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 06:44:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damnit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 18:21:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 18:39:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not every possession, just the things you held especially close to your heart that created energy strong enough to attach your spirit to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 21:12:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>All the time wondering,  #8220;was that one breadcrumb worth it? #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 05:08:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who ever heard of a *bad* french fry? Ludicrous!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 05:17:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Technically, fancy pants, I #8217;m only *six* months older than I am. :P</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>23 Year Old Transman Needs 2 Hip Replacements</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 17:21:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 05:36:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;d think  #8220;*oculus reparo* #8221; **would** have fixed his eyesight. What if it was intended to but the spell casted back against the glass of the lenses??  #8220;*Spectacle amendo* #8221; sounds more like it #8217;d *just* fix glasses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 01:17:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>True. I #8217;ve never met dumber, more ignorant people than the people who believe they #8217;re the smartest and most intelligent beings in the room.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 01:43:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder how this is going to pan out in terms of getting insurance coverage for much-needed transitional surgeries and HRT. I feel like it could make things harder because there would be no medical basis? Not that I think trans people are mentally ill, but I believe it having a diagnosis (one that can only effect mentality and does not immediately effect physical condition. Hopefully that made sense.) helps get insurance coverage?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Theory] Sam  amp; Crowley #8217;s Addiction</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 02:07:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>So everyone who #8217;s seen the show up to its 5th season knows Sam #8217;s DNA and blood-line has been infected with demon blood. The eradication of such has never been confirmed, and Jared Padalecki ( #8220;Sam Winchester #8221;) is a firm believer that Sam still has demon blood in him to this day (which, coming from basically Sam himself, makes it canon to me). Demon blood is nothing but human blood that comes from a possessed human vessel. Sam injected Crowley at the end of S8 with *his own blood* in order to not only close the gates of Hell but also to  #8220;purify #8221; himself due to the contamination of demon blood and the subsequent ramifications it caused throughout (mostly) the first five seasons. Crowley shows up in Season 9 addicted to human blood, but unlike Sam, cannot drink demon blood because he is one. They both have a similar mental effect (euphoria) but opposing physical effect (strong emotions and possibly other undisclosed effects). He also injects the blood as opposed to drinking it. I #8217;m wondering if Sam #8217;s blood *caused* a blood addiction in Crowley. It #8217;s *all* a form of human blood at the end of the day. Sam obviously can #8217;t drink human blood for the same reason Crowley can #8217;t drink demon blood. They would biologically *have* to drink opposing forms of human blood to achieve effect, but the addiction itself could be coming from the blood of Azazel (who #8217;s blood *might* be able to effect Crowley because he #8217;s a higher form of demonic presence). Thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 23:03:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s DLC.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 23:16:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Explain.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 16:40:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>He never finished the trials to do so because it would have killed him. He tried to finish it but Dean stopped him. Crowley never turned 100% human, as the demon Father Thompson cured had.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 22:09:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sam said  #8220;Not anymore, I don #8217;t think. #8221; That leaves a lot of room for bringing it back or leaving it. Lucifer still wanted his vessel in like, what was it, S11.E10. That shows there #8217;s still something *there,* no matter how suppressed it may be. When the BMOL mentally tortured him in Season 12, he started having a hallucinogenic fit (which may have been suppressed psychic abilities haunting him for his mistakes all at once, as if you recall, he gets really bad headaches as well).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 23:35:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did it though? Or am I mistaken? I thought he had to *finish* the trials for it to purify him?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 23:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god these are not mental images I needed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 23:38:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I heard our heart skips a beat when we sneeze, and for just a half second, you kinda are dead. Or something like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 00:28:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>/gasp/ *I #8217;ve been deceived.*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 03:16:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Um... hmm.... I know my great great grandmother got chopped up and thrown into a well, where my great grandmother found her and subsequently had issues for the rest of her life and had a very strained, mostly estranged, relationship with my grandmother and my grandmothers sisters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:13:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Such as? I don #8217;t really have much more information. My great grandmother found her mother chopped up in the bottom of a well as a child, then she practically abandoned her kids in her adulthood (eventually complete estrangement). My grandma is 80 and hasn #8217;t heard from her mother since like 1970 where she pretty much told her mother to suck dirt and die. My grandma, even as a child, became a sort of  #8220;mother #8221; to her siblings, doing her best to raise them. She married my grandpa at like 16. Had my dad at 17 (she was almost 18) then 3 more sons after him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 14:15:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, right. Forgot to add: Some guy murdered her. I think he also raped her, but I can #8217;t remember. I #8217;ll have to ask my grandma. He was black and she was white but we have no idea if she said something or did something to provoke him. It was the 1920 #8217;s, after all, so she very well could #8217;ve.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 16:16:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, indeed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 01:07:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It still wouldn #8217;t be 1 whole day; it would be 2 days divided by 24 hours.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 22:58:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everything I ever bought at Toys R Us as a kid was extremely overpriced, so I can #8217;t say I didn #8217;t see it coming. *Karma is a bitch, Jeffrey.*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 10:54:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. The prices were *definitely* part of the problem; public to private probably was part of it, too. However, there #8217;s been a huge decline in Toys R Us shoppers in the last 15 years. People would rather get their kids something at Walmart or Target because it #8217;s more affordable and, to be honest, there #8217;s a chance the toy will get broken either way (and it #8217;s not like we can honestly say Toys R Us made quality toys). Why pay $50-60 on a toy you can get for $25-35? On top of that, we have a magical place called *Amazon* now, where if something breaks within a few days or whathaveyou, they #8217;ll [usually] replace or refund it without any attitude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 16:06:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahahaha. *Geoffrey* didn #8217;t deserve respect! He certainly didn #8217;t respect *us* by displaying these unrealistically priced toys in arms reach, our dying wish for that $250 plastic game, nor last but certainly not least, our parents wallets.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 23:44:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>They #8217;re not much more freaky looking than Hermit Crabs *without their shells*.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 18:32:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>u/Endopl4st I hope not. That #8217;d mean I #8217;m a robot at this point. You are your brain and your nervous system, which is a long stringy bundle of nerve receptors and shit connected to your brain.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 20:45:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Found the middle class who #8217;s never had to *cut that shit open to find the remaining, hidden sliver*.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 23:51:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Time is always killing you, so that #8217;s kind of redundant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 15:07:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Big Bang reference.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 15:12:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>* #8221;Yes, it does, old man! #8221;* Signed, A 23 Year Old</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 16:11:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Forget storing water in the tea jugs! Arizona Tea is the real world Nuka-Cola!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 18:05:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>... You weren #8217;t even born in or before 2000!  #128514; You can #8217;t genuinely remember anything from that year...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 18:06:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>