<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7238</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My first Lolita skirt! What works best?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 03:01:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello all! I have been really interested in Lolita fashion for a few years now and have finally decided to create my very first outfit. I'm sewing everything so I decided it would be best to start with a skirt and purchase a blouse. I'm not sewing as a way to save money, but I just really like to sew! I have a few concerns however and would like some help answering basic questions. 1) Should I do a high waisted or gathered skirt? My body type is rectangle so I'm not sure which would be best for my type. I'd prefer to do a cupcake style skirt either way. 2) Does anyone know where I can find good patterns? Whether purchased or free, I'd like to have a few different choices preferably. I appreciate any help I can get! Thank you  lt;3  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 10:03:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really like Brave New World and Catcher in The Rye</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's your most effective coping mechanism when you feel really anxious?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 03:21:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Will I ever be good at art?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 06:15:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like doing digital art, but I constantly have to use references because I always forget the details of everything I draw. I have to stare at something long enough to put the description into words to be able to remember it and it's just too time consuming. I'm also garbage with proportions because I can't see them in my head. Does anyone have any tips? Or should I give up?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>People to play with?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 06:19:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really want people to play DST with and it's kinda hard to find people as interested as I am. My server or yours, doesn't matter. I have discord but I'd prefer to not VC until I know you better. Any skill level is okay with me because I'm not the greatest in all honesty. Please message and ask for my discord or steam if you're interested! Maybe we can set something up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 14:26:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, I fell asleep. I'll message you with my steam name if you wanna maybe play later</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 15:56:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I added the right account, but lemme know if it worked when you can</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Re-entering an abusive relationship?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 03:29:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got out of a relationship about a year ago because he did some kinda crappy things to me sexually, even if it doesn't qualify as r**e. No matter what it's described as, it gave me a fear response to him for the longest time. But I'm starting to think that maybe my relationship with him wasn't so bad after all. He was really sweet and loved to make me laugh and was just always there for me. I really miss him and I wanna maybe try and mend our relationship because I really love him, but my sister keeps reminding me of what he did to me. I know the things I told her about really did happen but I don't really remember it. It's more like I'm reading the events in a story book or something. If I can't even remember it vividly or have a very big fear response anymore then surely it wasn't bad enough to break up, right? I dunno what to do...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 23:26:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! This comment really helped me actually</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 03:30:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Constantly. If I'm too stressed or anxious, I feel really sick and can't eat at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Help] Individual components of Ciel Phantomhive Ciel in Wonderland Cosplay?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 05:29:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I realized I could very easily make this whole cosplay myself in time for Mecha con if I could just find the right light blue shirt and shorts. Apron should be easy enough to make/find. Any ideas?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just self harmed and I don't care</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 03:40:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm prone to have really violent thoughts and I relapsed worse that I normally do. Usually, I just scratch my skin but this time I took a box cutter to my arm. It bled a lot and it almost bled through my long sleeve. I've just been so empty lately that I don't even really care. So what? I hurt myself. Why does it even matter? Does anyone else feel this way?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>