<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject855</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>American Football pedalboards (Summerhall, Edinburgh - 3rd Sept. 2017)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 11:51:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 18:17:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>From memory, the pedal after the ditto looper on the middle board (Mike's) is an A/B box. No idea what the big pedal after the boss tuner on the far left board (Nate's) is though. It might be some kind of looper.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 16:56:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I made my money the old fashioned way... I got run over by a Lexus.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tips on coming out to parents?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 22:07:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm confident that they will be fine with my sexuality. However, I'm not 100% sure how I should actually tell them. Also, I've been struggling with depression and anxiety for a while and I'm worried they might think it's related to me being bi/pan, even if I tell them it's not (because it's totally not, my sexuality is like the one thing about myself that I'm comfortable with). So to sum up, what's a nice, non-awkward way of coming out to my parents, and how can I reassure them that my mental health problems aren't a result of my sexual orientation?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-02 23:50:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Why Bilbo Baggins? Perhaps it is because I am afraid... and he gives me courage".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Honestly, I just wish I was braver</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 23:35:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish I was brave enough to reach out to the people I want to be friends with. I wish I was brave enough to show my true personality, instead of this facade I've constructed because I'm afraid of what others think. I feel that the only thing holding me back from improving my life is the fact that I'm so freaking scared of everyone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 23:55:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe bravery wasn't the right word, I guess I just meant that I wish I could stop my anxiety from dominating my life so much. Thanks for taking the time to comment in any case, I guess I agree with your point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 23:48:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel the same, if I've interpreted what you meant by that correctly. Some nights I sit awake in my room trying so hard to cry and let everything out, and wanting nothing more than for the tears to come, but nothing happens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What was the song that got you into this genre?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 23:59:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apologies if this has been asked a million times before. Mine was Tracy by Mogwai.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 07:56:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>That story is a beautiful testament to the power that music can have. Thank you for sharing it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 22:01:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha, no, it wasn't a skate video (I'm not cool enough for that). A link to the album version was included in an article about how to make ambient guitar sounds. I clicked that link and fell into another world.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Everybody says 'just be yourself' but I'm ashamed of who I am</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 17:45:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>And equally, I hate the person I turn into when I try to pretend I'm OK.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wow, these songs hit hard</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 00:44:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't seen the show. I don't know that much about musicals (being someone who for the most part listens to pretentious, depressing alternative rock). But I just listened to the DEH original cast recording, and here I am sitting on my bedroom floor in the dark, an emotional wreck. These songs touched my heart in a way unlike anything else in a long time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 15:31:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because I'm awkward, uptight and boring. I'm really sensitive and too scared to create relationships with people. Whenever I try to fake having confidence I always over compensate, and talk way too much. Consequently, the people who I actually want to be friends with only ever see the over confident version of me. Basically, who I am is just really good at fucking up my own life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 17:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much. This was really comforting to read. When I feel ready, I'll try to begin taking your advice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Absolutely terrified of the future</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 01:49:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whenever I think about it, the future just seems hopeless. Like I'll always be unhappy, like I'll never feel comfortable with myself/my life and I'll always be scared of what's going to happen next. Honestly, sometimes it gets to the point when I don't want to live anymore because I can't stand the thought of going on like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 21:05:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I watched the bootleg recently (not too proud of watching it for free, but I live a long way from New York and have zero money so it's better than nothing). I really enjoyed the story/dialogue in between the songs, it's both heart-wrenching and hilarious. I might still buy the script though, so I have something more lasting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When your friend opens up to you about feeling depressed and you sit them down to talk about it</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 23:39:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Recommend me some bands that use clean guitars with scream vocals?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 23:46:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>No particular reason, just a sound I've been chasing lately. The mathier the better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I just came out to my parents</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 23:25:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>They were ok with it. I feel super weird about having actually told them, but also pretty glad that I did so it kind of balances out I guess. I have no idea what to do next, but I'd just like to thank this sub for helping to give me the confidence to take this step. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 22:05:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>This makes me so gosh-darned happy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you're proud of something you worked hard on and then somebody compliments you on it</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 23:44:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 07:56:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your comment made me smile. :) I guess pride isn't always a good thing, but being proud of yourself is necessary sometimes (even though it can be hard).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Advice on setting up a home studio?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 00:01:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>So as the title says, I'm looking to get some equipment together in my bedroom to record the music I write. What I'm hoping this community will be able to help me with is: 1- Telling me what I will need. 2- Recommending me particular products/software/etc, keeping in mind that I'll be on a pretty tight budget and would prefer for costs to be kept down where possible. 3- Offering any additional advice or tips that you think will be helpful. If it's relevant, I mainly create ambient/electronic post-rock stuff (like Mogwai, Tycho etc.) and write mostly on guitar and keyboard. Thank you in advance if you reply.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When people say you can't be the Senate but you're not going to let negative opinions stop you from being yourself</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 23:22:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 00:19:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh man, Mark Hamill...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I want to come out, but I'm scared</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 00:47:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>So far I am out to my parents and one girl I know (she is gay, so coming out to her was fairly easy and she promised to keep it a secret). I'd like to just let everybody know and not hide who I am anymore, but I am kind of afraid of what people's reactions will be. People at my school aren't actively homophobic/biphobic but sometimes I feel that there is kind of a stigma about it (such as people being uncomfortable with it, and certain homophobic words getting slung around with little regard to what they mean). My year is pretty small, and although I'm not popular on any level word would get around quickly. I only have a few months left until I graduate so I guess I could just wait, but at the same time I'd kind of like to spend those last few months at ease with myself and feeling more prepared to come out to people in later life. This post was partly just to rant in all honesty but I would still really appreciate any advice that this community may have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 00:55:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Mouse Rat version of The Way You Look Tonight is absolute awesomesauce.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 09:43:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know. I could talk to people more? But then I would get all panicked and then go home and hate myself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guitarists, any advice for someone trying to get the tapping thing down?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 10:22:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I kind of know how to tap, but I don't really know how to do it in a math rock context. Right now I can only really do it on one string at a time (and pretty slowly as well). Can you recommend any practice techniques, or even just random things that helped you get to grips with it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 23:30:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>My coming out story is pretty boring. I just sat down and told my parents one evening, and then we kept watching tv. But to be honest, that was all I wanted. However, maybe I'll do something more extravagant when I come out to everybody else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 23:40:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Remember that you have the right to feel happy about who you are. It's perfectly fine to be confused about something like this, because it's a very confusing thing. Just take some time to think things over, and keep in mind that even if everything is not ok right now, it will be one day. If your boyfriend loves you just as you love him, then he'll understand. Go get that haircut :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you're feeling sad so you go on r/wholesomeprequelmemes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 23:32:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 23:52:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello. I'm in a similar situation to you, being a mostly closeted bi male high school student who's never been in a relationship. What I'm doing right now is starting small by coming out to certain individuals I know who I trust not to judge me or tell anyone else, and seeing where I can go from there (advice I got from this sub actually... r/bisexual is a marvel). I don't know if this helps or not, but if you think that you want to come out (and you don't have to if you don't want to) doing this is working ok for me right now. It's also worth remembering that one day you'll figure everything out, and things will get better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 23:53:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know that this is hard, but you're stronger than you think you are, I promise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 01:12:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someday... someday I will be ok. Someday we will all be ok.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 01:16:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would have followed you, my brother... my captain... my king. Ok nevermind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 01:17:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're not a fake, or a weirdo. The fact that you still feel an attraction to men through your positive experiences with women shows that you are indeed bi. If identifying yourself as bi feels right to you, then that's who you are. You have had some unfortunate experiences that have given you some confusing feelings, but that dosen't mean that you will always feel this way. Ultimately, one day you'll find someone (if this is what you want) who you can be happy with, whatever gender they may be, and while these feelings are confusing now you'll eventually figure everything out and embrace yourself as the wonderful person that I'm sure you are. P.S. I don't know where you live, but it's just turned midnight where I am. I hope you have a wonderful 2018.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 02:57:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Glad that I could help. Be nice to yourself in your search for yourself, you have a right to feel happy about who you are. Also, it might be kind of weird to mention this but it's nice to see someone else from the UK on this sub. Maybe there's more of us than I realised.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 14:48:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I thought you were my friend. I THOUGHT YOU WERE MY FRIEND"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Latency issue in ableton - any help?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 18:38:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>So like the title says, I'm having an issue with latency in ableton live 9 lite. I get a pretty severe delay between the note played and the note detected. I have the sample rate as high as it will go (96000) but I still get static upon trying to set the latency any lower than around 40 - 50 ms. Ableton's preferences menu has a slider for setting Input buffer size and another slider for setting Output buffer size. This layout is different to instructional videos I have seen, where there is just one slider for selecting overall buffer size. I am new to home recording, and would greatly appreciate any advice this sub may have on how to fix the issue. P.S. if it's relevant, I'm using a focusrite Scarlett 2i2 interface and a Windows 10 pc. EDIT: So I changed the driver in ableton's preferences menu and that seems to have fixed the problem, at least for now. Thanks for your responses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 00:53:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>IN ONE MORE HOUR, I WILL BE GONE Whatever the genre, this album is awesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do you consider Julien Baker emo?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 00:55:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen a few individual posts regarding her on this sub but am curious to know what the general opinion is. I love her music either way though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Songs in FACGCE tuning that aren't Never Meant?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 00:59:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Title says it all. I use this tuning alot when writing, but don't know any other songs that use it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 23:21:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never seen her comedy before, but this is genuinely hilarious! Thanks for posting!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:23:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit. It's worth remembering that the Daily Mail should not be taken seriously (it's basically just a campaign of hate against tolerance and diversity in society), but you cannot make this shit up. It's almost like a parody of anti-lgbt propaganda. But stay strong friend. These people are just a minority that shout louder than everyone else. We're all behind you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:32:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is Bob Ross the patron saint of wholesomeness?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 19:59:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Breathtakingly beautiful, and also comforting in a way. Reminds me of the drawings of J.R.R. Tolkien himself, but with their own unique feel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>High school has fucking ruined my teenage years</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 23:28:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nothing else makes me as miserable as it. Nothing else has made me want to die as much as it. Nothing else can suck the life and joy from my soul quite as much as it can. It has made me question whether life will actually get any better. Will I just be stuck in a never-ending cycle of fake friends, spirit-breaking routines, awful people, anger, sadness, cynicism, isolation and anxiety forever when eventually it spits me out into the real world? Every night I come home physically, mentally and emotionally exhausted and every morning I hear the alarm clock ring and contemplate the fact that I have fucking nothing worth getting up for. I have like 4-5 months left until I graduate but it may as well be 4-5 years (shit, I don't even think I should joke about something like that). I guess I'll just have to keep fighting until then. But the worst part is it has taken my teenage years, a significant part of my life, away from me. That's not including all the time that I imagine it will take me to recover from this bullshit. I will never get this time back. And sure, I'm grateful for the knowledge I have, but it has come at severe cost to my mental health. Thank you for reading this if you still are. This is like my only place where I can vent like this and it feels good to. If anyone has any advice on how to make it through the remainder of my final year it is welcome, as are any simple words of encouragement (sorry if this sounds needy, but I'm nearing the end of my tether).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 23:33:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Toxic peers in all honesty. The work load is manageable sometimes I get so apathetic that I just ignore it lol. Thanks for the support though, hope that everything is going ok in your world.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 23:41:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Final year before I graduate I meant, sorry if I startled you. I don't intend to kill myself over high school, it's not something that's worth dying for. I'm just worried that things will never get better. Thank you so much for your response, however. I fully intend to start cutting toxic people out of my life, it's just a little hard when I see them every day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 23:18:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/wholesomememes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 23:15:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is beautiful, thank you for posting it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 17:08:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>That thinline cabronita Tele (or whatever it's called) is pretty nice, if only it was a little less flashy. EDIT: And obviously, if the price was a little less too much-y.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I just want to hear somebody say "I love you" to me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 23:50:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Besides my parents. Just to hear "I love you" in a sincere voice, a real voice, a friendly voice... I know it's pathetic but I'm so fucking lonely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 00:35:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, this means a lot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 09:06:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stay strong friend. We believe in you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 09:08:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 09:12:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please don't die, friend. If nothing else, stay alive for your mother's sake. Then when you feel stronger, start reaching out to people. You can build a better life. I believe in you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Recommend me some math rock bands that have a jazz influence?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 17:48:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>It would also be nice (but not essential) if they had kind of a Midwest emo influence too. I've been getting into jazz a lot more lately, and I know that some math rock bands have a jazz influence, so I wondered if you can recommend anything along those lines. Besides American Football of course, I've heard both of their albums. Thank you in advance if you reply.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 23:27:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hopefully this will be me one day. Memes like this give me hope!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So, I let everyone down again today</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 16:03:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was supposed to be going on a short trip, but my anxiety about it was just too much and today I dropped out. So I let down the guy who was organising the trip. I've let down my parents, because now I'll have to lie to them that the trip was cancelled so they don't worry about me (and also so they aren't reminded of the fact that their son is a fucking failure). But most of all, I've let down myself. Because I've given into anxiety again. I always fucking do this. I CAN'T DO ANYTHING without falling into a spiral of worry and overthinking. I've knocked my confidence in myself for the future, and in the year I leave school to go to college this is pretty bad. If anyone has any words of advice, or can relate to the post then please comment. I don't want to sound needy but I'm sitting here hating every inch of my stupid fuckup self right now. EDIT: Ok, a few hours later I'm feeling a little better. Still mad at myself for what I did, and sad that I disappointed the guy running the trip but... I think I'm ok. I think. I guess that I now need to focus on ensuring that this sort of thing dosen't need to happen again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 17:48:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much. These words mean a lot. I guess I'm afraid to tell them the truth because this is like the exact same thing that I've done before, and I really thought that I'd grown a lot this year. But thank you again. I'm feeling a little more positive now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(17,m) Am I pansexual?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 09:28:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've thought of myself as bi for a few years now, and have experienced attraction to both men and women. Lately however I've been thinking that a person's gender identity wouldn't determine whether or not I was attracted to them, as long as I liked their personality. Does this make me pan?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Compressor pedal recommendations?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 20:17:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I realise that this question has likely been asked here a million times before, but I'm feeling too lazy this evening to find the post. I'm in the market for a good quality compressor pedal for tapping riffs and to even out clean fingerpicking passages. As I don't have much cash right now, it would preferably be obtained for less than  #163;100. Right now I'm considering the xvive lemon squeezer (I like the price but have no idea as to the quality). So, what would you recommend? If it's relevant, I play a squier cabronita telecaster (of course, I have a view to getting something better in the future). Thanks in advance if you reply.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 23:30:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>AND I SPENT THE WINTER WRITING SONGS ABOUT GETTING BETTER/AND IF I'M BEING HONEST I'M GETTING THERE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any post rock esque math rock bands?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 23:50:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of the reasons I love post rock so much is the dramatic, emotional soundscapes that can be heard in, for example, a lot of Explosions in the Sky songs. The kind of thing that makes you feel like you're floating over a canyon, feeling a warm breeze and watching the sun rising in the distance. Are there any math rock bands that do this? I realise that slight differentiation in sound is what leads to different genre names, but math and post rock are very similar in certain respects.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Clever Girl guitar tunings?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 21:13:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I plan to start attempting to work out some of Clever Girl's material by ear on guitar soon. Does anyone know what tunings they used on their No Drum and Bass in the Jazz Room record?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When your friend tells you that they are gay and you reassure them that their feelings are valid</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 23:54:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I don't think my parents understand what I'm going through</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 00:14:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know that my parents love me, and support me. But when it comes to my mental health, they don't seem to understand why I feel the way I do. Not only that, it's like they haven't even tried to understand. For example, they think that I'm just being a shut in when I'm scared to go out. They tell me to 'just go and talk to people' when I tell them I feel lonely. More than once, when I've been really worrying and stressing about something they've basically said to me 'just stop'. Now, my parents aren't bad people. They were very supportive when I told them about my sexuality. My dad drives me to my therapy appointments and waits for me no matter how long it takes. They've managed to help me through panic attacks. It's just really frustrating when stuff like this happens, because it makes me feel like I'm alone, and that no one truly understands me. And I don't get why, if they support me with stuff like this, they can't just at least try to understand why I feel the way I do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 01:04:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. Would the tab you wrote be available on the internet somewhere? I might want to use it as a reference point for my own attempts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 12:59:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>"She is the woooorst" *Ben Wyatt falls over*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Well, today it happened again...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 23:29:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yet another awkward situation. I play guitar in this guitar group thing. Last week the girl I sit near was absent, so the instructor gave me some sheet music to give to her this week when she was in. We play the same part for most songs, so it made sense. I should probably mention that I haven't really talked to this girl all that much, and until recently I kind of just convinced myself that she disliked me, or thought I was weird. Which probably wasn't true, at least until today... So, at the end of rehearsal today, I went over to give her the sheet music. Easiest thing in the world, right? All I needed to do was to go over, politely hand the music to her, maybe even say something nice and walk away having made a good impression. And yet, here's what I did: I went over with the music. Then I had a complete mental block. Instead of just saying "excuse me" or something I kind of just waved the music sheet around and mumbled "here's some music" to get her attention. Then she looked up at me, looking confused. I somehow managed to get the music sheet into her hand, and mumbled "sorry, that was weird" and started to walk away. But the interaction wasn't over, because she quite rightly had no idea what the fuck just happened. "Erm... is this for me?", she said. "Uh, yeah, that's yours" I said a little too quickly as I walked off. "Ok...thank you", she replied, looking at me as if I was a total weirdo. Which I was, I suppose. Anyway, that's just another memory that'll keep me awake at night for the next 20 years. This post was mainly to vent and I can't imagine anyone reading this far, but if you did then thank you. Maybe you can relate, or maybe you found it entertaining. If stuff like this happens to you then just know that you're not alone. Have a nice night/day I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scottish post rock bands that aren't Mogwai?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 01:18:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Title says it all, really. Of course we all know and love Mogwai but are there any other bands making post rock music in Scotland? Or does a Scottish post rock scene even exist?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Earth Is Not A Cold Dead Place</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 00:10:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can we just take a moment to appreciate how beautiful those words are? Not just as an album name, although it does perfectly sum up what Explosions In The Sky create with their music, but also as a general phrase. Uplifting, optimistic, euphoric, defiant yet peaceful. So much meaning in just eight words. The ability to connect with the listener on an emotional level can extend beyond the music.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 00:11:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>And while we're at it, just saying 'First Breath After Coma' or 'Your Hand In Mine' gives me chills.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 21:31:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looking for the obligatory "I love you Jesus Christ" comment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 22:32:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you. Now I can sleep tonight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So... erm... how do you... you know... flirt?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 00:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>This may not be 100% a bisexual issue. I am happy to remove this post if it isn't relevant to the sub. But all I know is that I'm attracted to guys and girls and have no idea how to flirt with either of them (17, M, never been in a relationship before and have a history of social anxiety with possible Aspergers). Therefore, I also don't really know how to tell if people are flirting with me (although I can't imagine why they would... lol). Does anyone have any advice or tips that can help me out? Is flirting with one sex different to flirting with the other? I'll be hopefully going off to university soon so it would be nice to learn a little more about this stuff so that I'm not completely hopeless at it if and when the time comes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 00:25:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you do decide to tell them, make sure that you are safe before you do so. Plan some kind of escape route (I apologise if I'm being overly dramatic) if necessary. It might be a good idea to have someone else there to support you while you tell them. Your wellbeing is paramount here. Ultimately if you feel that whatever decision you make is right, then it is the right decision to make. I know that this is confusing, but maybe it's worth taking a little bit of time to figure out what the best way forward would be? I would imagine that as you are their daughter and they love you, they will find a way to come to terms with your sexuality. Your feelings are valid and you have the right to feel happy about who you are. Good luck friend, and keep yourself safe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 14:33:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>You look so cool! I noticed that there's been a couple of mean comments in this thread, please don't let them get you down. You have the right to feel happy and proud of who you are, and I'm sure that your future is very exciting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 18:30:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Clever Girl are instrumental (and probably more math rock than emo) but their guitars give a similar sound to American Football and they have a saxophonist who's playing creates other-dimension level feels.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[QUESTION] Amp seems to be 'overloaded' by delay and reverb pedals?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 18:15:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I run my delay and reverb pedals (couple of Boss stompboxes) into the front of my amp (Ibanez TSA-30). I like to have a lot of delay and reverb, as I play a lot of ambient/post-rock music. The problem is, these effects seem to kind of overload my amp. Bass frequencies become boomier, and the overall sound becomes very muffled. I've tried dialling the bass back a bit and messing around with the pedal's controls, but to no avail. Just an FYI if it's relevant, I keep the volume at 12 and the gain at 9. I guess I could try running the pedals through the effects loop, but it's more convenient to just run them into the front end as I don't use amp overdrive and they are in a chain with dirt pedals. I've watched live videos of some of my favourite bands where they get a really crystal clear sound by running their setup in basically the same configuration as mine. I get that they have better gear than I do, and have a professional guitar tech but it can't be that hard to achieve, right? So can anyone tell me what I can do to get my delay and reverb tone to sound clearer? And also, does anyone know what causes this problem?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guitarists - what are your essential pedals?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 12:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Although some post rock boards are the size of garage doors nowadays, I still feel that less is more when it comes to effects. Musicianship and composition skill should be what makes your songs interesting, after all. So, what are your essential three pedals (or four at a stretch)? This post is partly inspired by an interview I saw with John Cummings where he says that in the early days of Mogwai (i.e. the Helicon 1/Young Team days), he only used two pedals. I mean, Mogwai's boards are absolutely monstrous nowadays, but anyway...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guitarists - what are your essential pedals?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 12:39:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Less is more when it comes to effects, right? What are your essential three (or four at a stretch) effects pedals? You see some pretty gigantic boards in the math rock scene, but I feel that sometimes this can be a distraction at the expense of the music. American Football recorded LP1 with no pedals after all, and I seem to remember an interview with Mario Camarena of Chon where he says that for a while the only pedals he used were a Boss TU-3, an Earthquaker Warden Compressor and an MXR Phase 100. A similar post to this went in r/postrock.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 15:12:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool. How do you find the clip on tuner in live situations? Still just as reliable?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 21:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>+1 for the Blues Driver. Awesome pedal, but not one that I see being used a lot in this genre. It's name really undersells it IMO, it can do anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When your friend asks you to tell them some of their good qualities</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 23:28:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Another American Football LP2 Appreciation Post</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 00:33:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I allowed to like something? I think this is a really strong album. Sure, some of the lyrics feel a little forced and the production is kind of shiny but underneath is all the vaguely jazzy Midwest twinkle that we know and love. The songs are great and the instrumental work is excellent (although not as much trumpet as I would have liked). It isn't as good as LP1. Does that really matter? I think that had a new band released this as their debut album (and maybe if some of the production layers were stripped away on that album) it would be viewed as a very assured and mature body of work, and a standout/benchmark album of the comtemporary scene. *Runs to take cover from the incoming downvotes*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Modern jazz artist recommendations?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 00:48:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been enjoying the album Together As One by Dinosaur (I suppose they could also be called the Laura Jurd Quartet) and this has given me an interest in hearing more contemporary jazz. What are your recommendations? I'm not a big fan of free jazz so preferably nothing along those lines. For reference (in terms of the kind of jazz I like), I'm a fan of Miles Davis (who isn't, though?), John Coltrane, Art Blakey, Cannonball Adderley etc. Thanks in advance if you reply.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 00:18:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Parks and Recreation is too pure for this world. I realised recently that I associate certain memories of good things that happened in my life with certain episodes. I've been struggling with anxiety and loneliness for a while now. I think I'm getting better now, but one of the things that would always help me cope and make me happy was Parks and Recreation. You can say that it's just a TV show or whatever, but it gives me hope that one day everything will be fine. And I am confident that whatever the future throws at me, with P amp;R as a companion I can face it. I love this show more than words can say. Sometimes I miss it. But mostly I'm grateful for the fact that it exists. I'm grateful for all that it has done for me, and all it continues to do for me. So...yeah. Thanks for everything, Pawnee. Thanks for everything, Parks and Recreation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[QUESTION] How do you defeat the dreaded GAS?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 23:46:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometimes I start thinking about gear and gear acquisition way too much... mainly about pedals... I think about re-modelling my whole pedal setup every few months. This distracts from actually playing and means that I waste a bunch of time thinking useless thoughts. So when you get Gear Acquisition Syndrome, how do you break through it and allow yourself to be happy with what you have?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 16:35:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>"This negative energy only makes me stronger... We will not retreat. This band is unstoppable."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 16:13:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not really that I want anything right now. Recently I managed to talk myself out of trading in some of my perfectly fine pedals for a boutique one. I'm pleased that I managed to avoid doing that, but I was just out for info on how I could guard against this in future.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 23:18:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey there dude. I'm currently going through tests to determine whether or not I have Aspergers. I don't know what they'll prove but it'll make sense if the diagnosis is positive because I really feel distant and alienated from my 'friends' and a lot of the people in my life. But seeing stuff like this gives me hope that maybe one day I'll be happy too. So thanks for posting this, and I'm glad you've found happiness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any fans of post rock/math rock music in here?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 00:16:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, I appreciate that this really is nothing to do with our sexuality. I am happy to remove the post if it is not wanted. I am a bi/pan guy who really loves the two genres of music listed above (bands like Explosions In The Sky, Clever Girl and American Football) and I wondered if anyone else in this sub feels the same way? I've never really met anyone else from the LGBTQ+ community who listened to this kind of music (not that I know of, anyway) so... knowing there were more than me would be nice. I mean, obviously there has to be more than me, I just don't know that for sure (gah, I'm awkward even on the internet). Again, I am happy to remove the post if it is not relevant, I just thought I'd go out on a limb.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 08:22:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Math rock is a pretty varied genre. It goes from emo sounding stuff right the way through to more jazz influenced/shreddy guitar music. Here are some songs I'd recommend - - American Football - Never Meant - Elephant Gym - Finger - Totorro - Home Alone - Chon - Waterslide - Clever Girl - Elm - This Town Needs Guns - If I sit still maybe I'll get out of here Those songs are pretty good as a starting point, I think. They cover a lot of bases throughout the genre, and some sound quite similar so you'll get an idea of the stereotypical 'math rock sound'. I'd defenitely recommend moving on to full albums if you like what you hear. Happy listening! P.S. yes, I do quite like Slint :) EDIT: Typo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 08:29:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>From a bisexual point of view (trying to tie this whole thing in a little) it's always meant a lot to me that their song 'Your Hand in Mine' doesn't use gender pronouns in the title, and as it's instrumental there's no lyrics of that kind either. It could be about someone holding hands with anyone, of any gender. I get that it wasn't intended as that kind of statement song, but I like the ambiguity. It's also a really beautiful song musically, as I'm sure you're aware :) For those reasons, it's my favourite love song.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 23:51:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really liked Florist and that band who played saxophones with traffic cones inside them (I can't remember the name). EDIT: oh shit, you had traffic cone saxophone band as your worst. A little awkward, I guess. I never clicked the link.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Those of you who play in 3 piece (or even 2 piece) bands - how do you keep things sounding full in a live situation?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 00:16:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any creative solutions that don't involve a truck load of guitar pedals?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>3-piece band recommendations?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 00:19:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know Elephant Gym and This Town Needs Guns, looking for a few more. It would also be cool (but not essential) if they differentiated from the standard guitar/bass/drums setup.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 18:57:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Woah, I remember my parents reading me Olivia! The illustrations in those books were so beautiful. And... now I'm happy sad. But in all seriousness, thank you so much for posting this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Recommend me some math rock bands that use wind/brass instruments?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 23:26:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've heard Clever Girl and American Football and love how the brass/woodwind sounds alongside the guitars, bass and drums. So, any more like this? Also, are there any math rock bands that use flute? I play guitar and flute (though neither very well in case that sounded like a brag) and it would be cool to have a band to inspire some original compositions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[QUESTION] Must learn jazz guitar songs (and also chord shapes/scales etc)?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 16:49:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Decided to learn more about jazz guitar and the theory behind it and I feel that playing some pieces would help me do that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 22:58:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>How did this trend for shimmer reverb come about? Seems like every pedal manufacturer is putting shimmer in there. EDIT: And also nice playing, getting some Spanish guitar vibes from the first part of the tune at least.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Question for math rock guitar players regarding compressor pedals</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 23:31:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is a compressor pedal totally necessary for this genre? I'm mainly thinking in terms of using it for tapping riffs, but also maybe to even out arpreggios and stuff. Right now my pedals go - Tuner - Overdrive - Delay - Reverb I get some pretty good tapping/general clean sounds when playing alone in my room with this setup, but I would like to form a math rock(ish) band soon and am wondering if a compressor would be good to help me stand out in the mix a little more. I'm going to get my guitar action lowered soon, which will make tapping easier but obviously it won't make me louder...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 19:44:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depending on how visible the patches are I reckon you'll make things fairly clear doing that, and it'll look pretty cool too! Post a picture when you're done?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"The Legos Were Right... Everything Really Is Awesome"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 23:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In praise of Agaetis Byrjun</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 00:56:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't quite comprehend the fact that this album is almost 20 years old... it sounds so fresh and unique, light years ahead of its time (and perhaps our time as well). It's almost as if the music rose out of the Icelandic landscape itself - it sounds as though it is a purely natural force, powerful and majestic and beautiful. Dense layers of harmonically perfect instrumentation, bowed guitar that sounds like whale songs and Jonsi's angelic voice over the top of it all; I have no idea what he's singing but knowing the lyrics isn't necessary - the raw emotion created is enough. I have neglected to compare it to other major post rock albums because I'm not entirely sure if there's anything it can truly be compared to - I haven't heard any other albums within this genre that sound quite like it, including a lot of subsequent Sigur Ros work. It is one of the few albums where when I'm listening to it (only when I'm listening to it) I can't imagine needing to hear anything else ever again. Anyway, that's my pretentious fan boy rant over with. Time to go and pretend I'm an angel alien foetus and make up my own language to moan ethereally in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So I read a lot of stories on here about bi folks experiencing erasure from gay/lesbian people</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 01:12:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>And I was wondering, to what extent is bi erasure within the gay community a problem? Obviously different people will have different experiences but it seems to happen a lot more than I previously thought (which I admit was not at all). I want to come out further after leaving high school, maybe join some lgbt+ groups in college. I just don't feel able to come out at school right now (just a weird atmosphere - I know a couple of gay girls but guys are expected to act a different way and I've only come out to two very trustworthy people). I guess I'm just worried that people will disagree with my sexuality even in lgbt places once I try to come out. That said, I'm out to one gay girl and she's cool with it, so... TL;DR - worried about experiencing bi erasure from gay/lesbian people in near future, wondering how bad this problem actually is</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why the fuck do I always have these moments of regret?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 01:16:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not a real question I guess, just kind of looking for a place to vent. I can't do anything, ANYTHING, without overthinking everything beforehand and regretting everything that happened afterwards. I wonder if I'll always be like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 01:20:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Death Star looks so ominous, like a ghost or something. Imagine seeing that filling the entire sky... even if you didn't know what it was you'd still realise something bad was about to happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 01:25:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit, that's awesome. I can't even change strings properly lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(gear) how to get guitir toan just lik Blamk-192</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 09:57:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tim Dillong is known to be the best guitar player ever and I want to get my setup to sund like bink 282 I trid sawing my gitar in half and taping the neck to the bottom part so I can only use the brij pick up and only playing with 3 strings but it didn't work and I keep getting splinters I also tried running a pedil called a "clon sentar" into my sick ass line 6 spyder but that peddle sucks balls it dusent even get close to the Blonk-128 sound Plz tell me how to get to the bike-41 toan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 14:17:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 14:45:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I heard somewhere (either in an interview with Chris Pratt or one of the P amp;R writers) that Andy was initially meant to be an antagonistic character, a douchey boyfriend who would be written out after the first or second season. Thankfully they changed that. I actually don't mind the first season. I think that they were still trying to figure out what to do with the show at that point, and trying to establish that it wasn't just an offshoot of The Office. I'll agree that the characters hadn't yet developed into the ones we know and love and the writing isn't as funny and dynamic as it would later become. I don't watch the first season as much as the others, and if I was introducing someone to the show i would tell them to start at season two. But it's nice to see that a show I love didn't come out the gate fully formed, because we can watch it mature (just as the central characters mature) as the series goes on. Also, the shot in the 'Rock Show' episode where the camera follows Andy through the gate towards the pit after Ann kicks him out is one of my favourite shots in the entire series. EDIT: Typo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"I'm sure you don't need me to tell you that these are the finest plastic dinosaurs money can buy"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 23:45:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've never kissed anyone before</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 23:34:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm only 17 so I'm not sure if this is a bad thing or not... I'm also really socially awkward. I want to kiss guys and girls but I kind of... don't see myself in a situation where that would happen? I'd like to have a connection with someone before I kissed them (or had sex with them - needless to say I'm a virgin) but I don't know how to ask someone out, or how to not act all awkward and weird if I actually went on a date. Any advice? Or can anyone relate?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Am I a failure? [Non-LGBT]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 00:00:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey. Bi/pan guy here. I appreciate that this isn't exactly an lgbt post and I am happy to remove it if it's not wanted. I posted it here because I didn't know where else to put it and, well, the lgbt community has been really supportive in the past. So, as the title says, I just kind of feel like I'm a loser. I don't think it has anything to do with my bi/pansexuality, and I do pretty good in school, but... I'm 17 and I barely know how to interact with people. I don't know how to initiate a conversation, I'm scared to spend any time away from home, I can't talk to someone without having a mini panic inside my head, I can't do anything without overthinking it and I sit in my room all day because I'm too scared to do anything else. I've never been in a relationship before, but even if I was in one I would be constantly paranoid that the other person would eventually figure out what a loser I am and dump me. This kind of paranoia even kind of centres around people who maybe like me in an un-romantic way. Every time something's going good for me, I find a way to fuck it up. So yeah, I'm nearly an adult and all this shit is still happening. I know that you're not supposed to think of yourself as a loser but when you spend Saturday night reading comic books and Reddit posts it's kind of hard to avoid it. Any advice? And again, I'm happy to move the post somewhere else if necessary.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 18:29:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>"This is worth the trip..."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Episode/s that make you emotional every time?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 18:33:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Part of the reason that I love Parks and Rec so much is the feels. The episode that gets me every time is End Of The World. Every character's story comes together beautifully, and the scene where Andy and April drive to the grand canyon with All Will Be Well in the background is IMO one of the finest moments in TV history. That's the most obvious one for me, anyway. I think I'll rewatch the entire series again to find more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Underrated quotes?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 18:46:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Book or movie. They don't have to be on the same level as "...but it is not this day..." and "so do all those who live to see such times..." but lotr has a lot of excellent quotes that don't get much attention. I'll start - "We will not abandon Merry and Pippin to torment and death".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 22:24:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in Scotland! Not the area Ron goes to, but... yeah!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What does the number after the note pitch mean?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 23:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like, I'll hear someone say "that's an A3" or whatever. Does this just refer to the note's scale degree/octave or something?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 23:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>You were right. I did enjoy that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 23:40:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool. So octaves have numbers?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So today I saw my guy crush looking as if he was flirting a little with my girl crush</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 23:45:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok, maybe it wasn't actually flirting but it looked a lot like that from where I sat on the other side of the room. It's kind of funny, I can't decide who to be jealous of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 23:54:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey there. This may seem like a weird question, but the name Blue Means Snow kind of fits well for a music project I'm working on right now. Do you mind if I use it? It's ok if you don't, I understand. The book looks really interesting, and I fully intend to get a copy at some point. It's interesting to see poetry done in this style, a modern exploration of themes that may appear to be normal at first but when considered carefully can be deeply profound. EDIT: And also of course congratulations are in order! Where are my manners? Great to see someone succeed in doing something they love!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 00:01:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not a lot of people know that "the fucking guitarist from simple plan" is the guy's actual name, congrats on your guitar knowledge</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 00:06:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can't go wrong with Clever Girl's No Drum and Bass in the Jazz Room.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 07:57:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, no problem! I hope the tour goes well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Discussion] I identify as a guy but feel very feminine - does this mean anything?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 00:05:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok, I'll elaborate a bit. I'm a 17 year old bi/pan guy. I identify as male, but have always felt quite feminine and I would like to explore this side of my personality a bit more. I like the idea of painting my fingernails, wearing eyeliner, wearing a skirt... these are all cosmetic things I guess. I have been wanting to do this for a few years now but just haven't so far I guess... I'm kind of nervous about it. Mentally speaking, I have always felt that I identify with girls more than guys. This is in terms of my emotional behaviours, my thoughts and feelings etc. (I apologise if it feels like I'm stereotyping 'typical female behaviours' here - that wasn't my intention). TL;DR - I identify as male; feel really feminine and would like to explore this side of my personality; am curious as to whether or not this means anything. I'll apologise again if you found anything I've said in this post to be problematic in any way. It wasn't my intention to typecast or offend; I'm just trying to understand myself a little more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 00:13:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, good for you. My senior year has kind of sucked, in all honesty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 09:02:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait, hold up. Is Ant-Man not in Infinity War?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guitarists - when writing multiple songs in the same tuning, how do you keep things interesting?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 14:17:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I write most of my songs in FACGCE. I only have one guitar, and if I was playing live I would keep it in that tuning for the entire set, rather than scrabbling to re-tune it between songs. However, the problem is a lot of the riffs I write can start to sound kinda similar... the benefit of standard is that it's easy to play in different keys, but it's harder to reach all that in my own chosen tuning. So, how do you all keep it interesting? I've asked this question in here rather than r/guitar as I'm more likely to get answers based on a math rock playing style.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[QUESTION] Are there any standard/open hybrid tunings?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 14:19:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>To get that nice open tuning sound with the convenience and versatility of standard tunings. This would be primarily to write songs in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 20:12:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>There'll be a heterosexual cowboy greeting you at the door</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 23:28:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would you do it for a behringer vintage delay? It has 'vintage' in the name so it's obviously pretty good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I recently bought a 17th-century lyre for 27$ at a yard sale how do I get it to do good djent toan ok</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 23:34:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I don't really feel ready for college but I don't want to defer either - advice?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 23:49:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>So... I still kind of feel like I'm just a kid. Plus I'm really scared about leaving home and my family. I would think about deferring, but I know that I would just waste time. It would amount to another year of waiting around, probably working a crappy job, and I would end up getting pretty lonely as well. I guess it's the change that I fear most. Which maybe means that I should face up to it. But my fear of leaving home is pretty strong also.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Comedians with a similar style to Bo?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 09:23:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>And while we're at it, what do you think it is that sets this style/Bo's style apart from other comedians?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 23:32:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your writing shows a real talent. You have a future, if that's what you want. In writing, I mean. Ok, I'll just show myself out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 08:14:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>So reversing American Football gives you an album full of Sigur Ros interludes? Nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Let's hear some super happy math rock song recommendations!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 19:58:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 20:01:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you familiar with the YouTube channel Let's Talk About Math Rock? The guy who makes those videos is based in South Korea. His band is called Mountains, I think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 23:23:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>God loves math rock.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Non-LGBT] I feel that no one will ever love me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 23:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just don't think anybody will ever see me as someone to be loved. I don't really know why but I've got this hangup that I'm a total loser in my head, and it's at the front of my mind all the time. I think that I am liked by people, but I am no one's 'favourite' person (as pathetic and self-pitying pitying as that sounds). Every time I'm attracted to someone I just kind of convince myself that they'll never like me back and even if they did end up in a relationship with me they would eventually dump me after figuring out what a loser I was. After being through therapy a bit this year, I've managed to fight off a lot of my depressive/anxious thoughts (which I think are unrelated to my bisexuality). But thinking of myself as someone who nobody will ever see as worthy of love is just kind of still there, I guess. Ultimately, the thing I want more than anything in the world is to hear a real voice, a sincere voice, saying "I love you" to me. I just don't know how this will happen. I don't want to beg for comments or anything, but it would really mean a lot if anyone had any advice, or even if anyone could relate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 16:44:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>IF YOU DIDN'T STAND BY ME... I'D BE ALONE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 23:51:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember hearing an interview with him where he said that when he was in high school he thought he was gay, and that was the reason as to why he didn't fit in with anyone. Maybe he was bi, I guess we have no real way of knowing. With regard to LGBT issues, I remember Cobain best for saying "I'm not gay but I wish I were, just to piss off the homophobes."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 23:53:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Run through a metal zone - Toan Heaven.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What are Edinburgh University students like?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 23:58:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have an offer to study music at the university of Edinburgh... the course looks very good, and I know that the university is well-respected but the thing I'm a little worried about is the people I'd meet. I get that not everyone is nice, same as how not everyone is an arsehole, but... I currently attend a state school, and I know that Edinburgh has a reputation for being a destination for private school (and sometimes very private private school) kids. I try not to judge people on their background but being surrounded by people from elite schools would leave me feeling kind of alienated. Also, the prestigiousness that Edinburgh has as a university is bound to attract people with a very self centered nature. Perhaps people like this wouldn't be on arts courses like the one that I have an offer for, but still. TL;DR - have an offer from Edinburgh, am worried about the kind of people I'll meet there and whether there will be a lack of people I can relate to and be comfortable around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 00:24:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>U need a tele ok</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 10:16:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>James "monkey" shafter from Quorn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[QUESTION] Must learn fingerstyle songs?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 10:22:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have recently been playing Angelina by Tommy Emmanuel, and would like to dive further into the world of fingerstyle guitar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[QUESTION] Tapping for rhythm guitarists?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 10:24:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I play in a math rock style a lot, and this style features tapping over broken chords. Could I use this to write rhythm parts, or does the tapping make it a little too lead guitar-y?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 14:23:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's funny, this morning my English Breakfast tasted like Darjeeling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 14:25:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>When a meme makes you brood upon your entire life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is it possible to develop perfect pitch?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 21:54:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>And if so, can you recommend any resources for doing so? Apologies if this has been asked already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 22:00:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I gave up trying to decide a long time ago. I love the relatability of Waving Through A Window... the comedy of Sincerely, Me... the emotional impact of You Will Be Found... Just a freakin' excellent collection of songs, to be honest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 22:03:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean as in the ability to identify a note by hearing it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 23:11:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok. So how would I go about doing that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 23:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think Connor just feels really alone, misunderstood and like people look down on him and bully him all the time. It's not really mentioned, but I think he probably has a bit of self hatred too, as a result of his drug use and not living up to his family's expectations. In the show (SPOILER ALERT) Connor gets mad when he sees the letter that Evan has written that mentions his sister, thinking that Evan wrote the letter and gave it to him to get a kick out of watching him freak out. I think this kind of shows Connor's situation, although his true reasons for killing himself are never made explicit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It hurts when you meet a person with a similar personality to you but you're too afraid to talk to them</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 23:48:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>This has happened to me way too many times. What's the main difference between me and them? They aren't a total loser. They actually seem like they know how to have a conversation without panicking. And then the fear takes hold, and I don't even try. I go home and I sit in my room, and complain about it on reddit to try to make myself feel better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is it that makes jazz music sound like jazz music?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 09:41:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Specifically, I'm referring to things like what scales are used, whether there are things like flattened fifths etc. I know that jazz musicians use sixths and sevenths a lot in their chords?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 13:59:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't intend it to be clickbait. Anyway, how would using clickbait in this context benefit me at all? I asked a question regarding music theory on a sub dedicated to music theory because I wanted to understand more about music. Clickbait doesn't make people answer my question, nor does it make people upvote my post. Are you really going to get mad over the way I phrased a question? Have you considered the possibility that maybe people don't just do things specifically to piss you off?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Looking to get into Batman. Where should I start?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 00:11:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't really looked into DC much yet, only Marvel and some indie stuff. I'd ideally like some modern Batman comics to read, although some all time classics would be welcome also, if they would add to my understanding of the character. Stories based on the Bruce Wayne iteration of the character are most welcome, and I'd like to learn a little about his world before getting into alternative dimension Batman stuff. One more thing, I'd like to read stories that only focus on Batman (and maybe Robin also) for now. So no crossover issues please (I might get into crossovers once I've read a few Batman solo stories). Thanks in advance if you reply! EDIT: Typo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What do 9th chords etc. mean?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 17:11:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I can understand adding the seventh note of a scale to a chord to make it a seventh, but what do chords such as a ninth and eleventh mean (for example Dadd9? There's only seven notes in a major/minor scale. Does it mean that you move into a different octave?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What are some good practice methods to improve technique on flute?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 17:14:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm getting quite good at playing with feeling, but I'd like to really improve my technique on flute and my knowledge of the instrument. What are some good things to learn and practice in order to do this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 09:29:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Happy (belated) trans day of visibility! You look like an incredibly cool person, I really like your shirt. You kind of remind me a little of Frank Iero from My Chemical Romance (sorry if that sounds weird).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 16:00:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, cool. You mentioned that you may need a little help feeling comfortable in your own skin... I just wanted to remind you that you have the right to feel comfortable with yourself. In time you'll be able to accept yourself as the wonderful person that I'm sure you are, but for now it's ok to be confused and even a little scared. You'll figure things out one day, and remember to be nice to yourself while you search for yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 23:44:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats! I wish that stuff like this happened to me :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 20:18:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>We really need a pro shot version of DEH. I'd gladly pay for that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 20:21:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Francis Poulenc's Sonata for Flute and Piano. I've been playing the second movement recently, it's absolutely glorious. For some jazzier stuff, I'd suggest some Paul Hart, in particular his City Life suite. This was mainly meant as music to be played by students, but you can find performances on YouTube.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 16:30:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was pretty disappointed to learn that Mogwai are bald middle-aged men in baggy jeans and adidas hoodies Who am I kidding, P O S T R O C K A E S T H E T I C EDIT: Freakin' app formatting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 09:04:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, what power supply are you using? And is it isolated?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 08:51:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unbelievable Gwenpool! Or Dr Aphra from Marvel's Star Wars comics.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Every time I start to form a close relationship with someone, I want to push them away</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 00:30:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know why I do it... am I afraid of being hurt, or hurting them? Am I afraid of the commitment and social effort that a relationship might take? Am I afraid that ultimately they'll find out that I'm kind of a loser, or that I'll find out they aren't a nice person? The strange thing is, I want to be close with people... I want strong friendships and relationships more than anything. Just every fucking time this seems possible and within my reach, I try to run away. Well, I guess I'm just good at fucking things up for myself. Maybe I'm just... broken.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 00:53:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so sorry that all this stuff has happened to you. I don't want to say that I'm in a similar position to you, because my anxiety is from less severe reasons, but I can relate a little bit... I'm about to graduate high school and I feel like I've failed having made it this far in life and barely knowing how to initiate a conversation, or how to even communicate without feeling unwanted and disliked. But there are strategies for making friends that I have discovered. The best possible method is to find people with similar interests to you. This could be something you like doing, it could be a band that you like listening to. If you can strike up a conversation based on that one thing (the conversation doesn't need to be scary, or about anything else) things can develop from there. Another strategy is (and I know that this is hard) forcing yourself into social situations. Try to strike up a conversation with someone who looks nice. It doesn't have to go anywhere, but the more you do this the more your confidence will build, and your judgement of situations will improve. And hey, if it does end up developing into something more, that's awesome! You have nothing to lose. Anxiety support groups are always a good idea, and will be useful in making friends (I'm not from your area so unfortunately I can't recommend any... in terms of online groups however, I've found that r/Anxiety and r/socialanxiety are both really helpful and supportive). But it doesn't just have to be support groups. It could be a group dedicated to a particular activity that you enjoy doing. Trying to start a friendship is always hard, but remember that it will get easier the more you do it. Just go with the flow and see what happens. Here's another strategy: never apologise for who you are. It seems that day to say I'm basically apologising for my existence, and this is kind of stupid really. It stops me from really enjoying things. I know that it's hard when you have anxiety, but you're entitled to say "fuck you, world. I'm awesome, and people need to know about it." Confidence will help you when striking up a conversation, or asking someone if they want to hang out sometime. I'm sure that other great strategies will be suggested here, and a quick Google search can bring you even more. And, lastly: there is always, ALWAYS, hope for you. You are never too far gone. You will be found one day and you owe it to yourself to never give up. It sounds like some pretty horrible stuff happened to you in the past, but your entire life is in front of you. You are never truly alone. Things will get better, I promise. I'm sorry if I didn't answer all of your questions. But take care of yourself, and good luck. Go and make yourself proud, and show the world how great you truly are!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 00:15:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll probably get slaughtered for this, but... learning Green Day songs like Holiday and When I Come Around when I was starting out on guitar really gave me a good grounding in rhythm playing. They'll introduce you to barre chords and locking in with the groove of a song. I realised recently that my ability to hold tempo whilst playing is partly down to all the palm-muted power chords I played in my early days on guitar. Plus simple songs like that are just plain fun to play.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 09:33:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every Freakin' Time. And even if I do manage to start a conversation, I just have a mind blank and say something weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 09:45:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>"You have a lot of overhead here..."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 23:12:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Do you wish I were taller?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 23:40:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>My two cents: I think that the breakup is probably necessary for Rosa's character development as a whole. New sides of her personality can now be shown. Also, Pimento's character isn't very sustainable in a comedic sense and trying to develop him beyond 'Rosa's crazy boyfriend' would likely take screen time away from more important characters. I could be completely wrong of course, but it's fun to theorise about these things. You never know, we may not have seen the last of Adrian Pimento. While it's probably for the best that Pimento is gone, it kind of bothers me that they put so much effort into introducing him to the show and establishing a relationship between him and Rosa only for that all to end quickly and without ceremony. I mean, the plot of several episodes focused on the squad trying to catch Jimmy Figgis so him and Rosa could be together. Pimento leaving like that just felt a little rushed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 17:11:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>See, that's the kind of thing that they only teach at Berklee.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 23:17:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meanwhile, the bi community is some non-descript character eating a Krabby Patty and avoiding eye contact.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 00:09:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Allow me to offer a fellow socially awkward bisexual a virtual high five.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(17/m) I think that I'm ready to come out (warning - rant)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 01:19:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>But there's still that seed of doubt in my mind holding me back... I'm still at high school. Only a few months until I officially graduate (and only a few weeks until I unofficially graduate) but it's still school, which is a pretty dark place for me. I'm not sure if people would understand or not... a couple of people are genuinely homophobic (there are of course really nice people who fully support the lgbt+ community and are even part of it themselves, but they are mainly girls. Guys are expected to act differently). I'm so fucking sick of hiding who I really am and pretending to be something I'm not... coming out would let me feel free-er. But I don't want to be made to feel distant, and I don't want to be bullied for it. Stuff like that would really knock my confidence in myself, and it could set back the progress I've made this year mental health wise. But staying hidden is making me sad as well... *SCREAMS IN FRUSTRATION BUT NOT REALLY BECAUSE IT'S MIDNIGHT AND MY ENTIRE FAMILY IS ASLEEP AND IT WOULD BE TOTALLY INCONSIDERATE TO WAKE THEM UP AND MAYBE I'M KIND OF TIRED MYSELF AND I SHOULD PROBABLY SLEEP YEAH I SHOULD DEFENITELY SLEEP AND THE ONLY REASON I'M NOT ASLEEP IS BECAUSE I'M THINKING ABOUT THIS PROBLEM AND I'M SORRY FOR RANTING BUT THIS IS SO STRESSFUL AND I JUST WANT TO BE ACCEPTED* Ok, sorry about that. If I haven't scared you off with that rant/generally being weird, any advice would be most welcome. This community has been really awesome and supportive in the past. If the rant made any of you concerned then don't worry, I'm ok and I'm happy with who I am. I've just been overthinking a lot of things lately. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 08:02:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, a few people at school know already. But that's it - just a few. I suppose it would probably be in my best interests to wait. Part of me wants to wait until I graduate unofficially - i.e. the point when I need to go into school to do exams but don't need to sit in there every day. I still have a little bit of time to decide whether to do it that way or not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 00:24:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be honest, R.E.M. have one of the most consistent discographies of any band ever. Everything up until Bill Berry leaving was either good, great or a classic and even some of the stuff released after then is still worth a listen. Me and my dad make each other laugh sometimes by doing Michael Stipe impressions. Singing "Hey, those kids are looking at me" or "Nightswimming deserves a quiet night" in a nasally voice is truly one of life's greatest pleasures.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 00:46:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Finding members for a math rock band can be pretty easy if you know where to look. Try your local cardigan and metronome store, or hang around outside some house in suburban Illinois in 1999. Or look for guitar players that seem to spend the majority of their set playing trumpet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 00:57:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess that I mean that I feel like I'm shutting off a big chunk of my personality. There's a lot I'd like to express that I just can't right now. A few people know already, and I think my plan right now is to just keep up with the stealth come-out and see where that takes me. Maybe I'll try and talk to the gay/bi people at school about it. Which will be a little bit difficult because those people are actually pretty cool and I'm incredibly shy. But that's a problem for another day, I guess. It's really nice to know that this sub is here when I need it, and that there are people I can talk to. Thanks for the support, friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 09:58:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, good on you. There's a lot of good material on Up. Airportman is one of their best album openers, and Stipe's lyrics on that album are some of the best that he wrote in his career.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 16:16:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>No doubt I'll regret commenting this later, but... oh my goodness that bulge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 23:38:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>A whole bunch of jazz... John Coltrane, Art Blakey etc. (Sorry for being that guy) And I'm relistening to Explosions In The Sky's discography at the moment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How have gay/lesbian people viewed your sexuality? And how can I stop thinking that I won't be accepted?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 01:04:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I'm looking for lgbt folks to be more open around. But I'm afraid (mainly because of stuff that I've read, I guess) that gay and lesbian people won't view my bisexuality as a genuine thing... I know that I shouldn't make any apologies for myself, but I've worried about it so much that now I'm having weird doubts in my mind. For example, I'll think "I'm not truly part of the gay community" or "my sexuality doesn't matter as much as someone who only likes the same sex." I know that these thoughts are absolutely ridiculous and I don't believe them at all, but I can't freaking stop having them! So, how have gay and lesbian people viewed your sexuality in the past? And any advice on how I can stop thinking weird thoughts like the ones I described?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 09:00:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's the guy who faked his death to become Chad Kroeger</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 23:47:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Billie Joe Armstrong. I don't listen to Green Day as much as I did when I was younger, but he was a really positive influence for me when I first realised I was bi... it was nice knowing that there was this guy in a band I liked who felt the same way that I did.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Going to college with social anxiety?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 23:14:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not good at making friends at the best of times, let alone when I'm in an unfamiliar place away from my family and scared of everything. All the friends I've made up until now have kind of been because I've been put with them. I'll see them in class etc. When I get to college, I guess it won't be like that. I'll have to approach people. And just the thought of that gets me kind of panicky. Any help?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 07:39:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not when I exit the app, no. I have to log out manually if I want to log out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Should I go to college even though I struggle with mental illness?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 12:04:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I have an offer from a good university. I just don't know whether I should accept or defer. I mean, I want to accept but the thing holding me back is concerns about my mental illnesses. I struggle with anxiety, social anxiety, am subject to occasional bouts of (non-severe) depression and am currently going through tests to determine if I have aspergers or not (the results of the tests won't come until after I have accepted or not). So the school has a lot of support for mentally ill students. But I'm really worried about how I'll react to being away from home in a different city. My reasons for thinking about deferring are kind of running away from the problem, but maybe that year will give me the chance to get better? Or maybe worse, since I'll probably just sit in my room all year. Any advice, or has anyone experienced the same?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[QUESTION] How to avoid arm tensing up when downstroking?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 17:25:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm learning Master of Puppets right now, with all downstrokes. I can't play it at full speed yet so I'm working my way up with the help of a metronome. The problem is my arm keeps tensing up, even when I play the riffs at slower tempos. I think that my picking technique is ok, picking from the wrist with my arm bent at just under a 90 degree angle. I've tried relaxing my arm while playing but it just tenses up again like two seconds later, although the pain does go away almost immediately if I stop playing altogether. Any ways in which I can fix this? Or will the pain eventually go away if I just power through? I'm not sure if it's relevant, but the picks I use most of the time are around 60 mm thick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 17:44:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm open to hearing some suggestions, I'm not going to laugh at anything that can help me become a better guitar player.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 17:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, Buddy Holly is awesome! Maybe saying Master of Puppets made me sound like some kind of metal elistist who hates all other kinds of music, but in reality I'll listen to pretty much anything that I like. If you had suggested Nickelback or something then I would have laughed, but Buddy Holly is one of the greats. Thanks for your suggestion, I'll get to work on Peggy Sue very soon. EDIT: actually, I'm not entirely sure what metal elistists think about Metallica...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 18:58:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. Is there a reason that thicker picks work better for that sort of playing than thinner picks?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 08:24:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kettle just beginning to sing...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 17:42:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>What did the shirt actually say? The post has been removed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 18:22:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Their new album Twin Fantasy"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What bands do you consider to be the actual emo (non-tumblr) emo trinity?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 23:35:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>No edgy pop punk here (or platinum selling albums, dyed black hair and vaguely creepy fan stories about band members having sex with each other). What bands in the real emo scene (past and present) do you consider to be main/quintessential three? This will probably just lead to further arguments about what actually constitutes emo, but oh freakin' well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[QUESTION] practice techniques to improve top speed?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 23:38:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm trying to play consistently at faster tempos. Basically, I'm trying to learn how to shred (or if you've ever heard a really fast John Coltrane sax solo, I'm trying to work out how to do that on guitar). Is it just a case of playing scales and arpreggios with a metronome? Or are there other methods I can practice?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 16:47:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hopefully I make it into the inevitable r/prequelmemes screenshot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 16:54:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Indiana is also the home of Leslie Knope, so it's not all bad. She married two male penguins, after all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 16:58:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'M THINKING ABOUT... LEAVING</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Rant] I'm lonely but too scared to do anything about it</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 00:09:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bisexual guy here, 17 years old. It's around 11pm, and so therefore my brain has decided that it's a good time to have a life crisis. Tonight's crisis topic is one that seems to come up a lot - the fact that I'm tired of being lonely/alone. I've never been in a relationship before. Never kissed anyone. I want to fall in love... I want someone I can cuddle with, laugh with, watch the rain with. But I'm afraid to actually go and make this happen. I've thought about it a lot lately, and I think that maybe it's because I'm afraid of being hurt (and there's also the fact that I think that no one will ever love me back, but that's a discussion for another time). I'm afraid of what will happen if I do get into a relationship and then have to leave for college next year. I'm also afraid of a relationship somehow holding me back from going to college. I'm afraid of being hurt by someone, but how can I be afraid of that happening if I haven't been in a relationship before? And then there's my various social anxiety issues which fuck everything up constantly... I'm going to start going to an LGBT+ group in my city soon, so maybe I'll meet someone there, but I don't know. I'm just so scared about this stuff all the time, and thinking about it makes me sad as it reminds me how lonely I am. It's like I'm too scared to try and let myself be happy, because of what could happen if that happiness ends. Or maybe I just don't know what I want at all. I don't want to beg for comments or anything, but it would really mean a lot if anyone had any advice, or words of encouragement. I just... want to be happy, you know? To be happy without consequences.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[QUESTION] Must learn techniques for jazz guitar playing?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 10:52:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>So say like if I was learning metal, I would learn stuff like sweep picking, legato etc. What are some key techniques to learn for jazz playing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 12:40:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been listening to a lot of Julian Lage lately, and he's kind of introduced me to modern jazz guitar. Aside from him, probably my favourite style of jazz is 'cool jazz' from the 1950's and 60's (Miles Davis, John Coltrane, Art Blakey etc.) EDIT: Forgot to mention Grant Green and Wes Montgomery, some other jazz guitarists I like a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 14:46:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>The theme from Drake and Josh is a better pop punk song than anything the majority of pop punk bands have written.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 23:34:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alec Guiness (a.k.a Obi-Wan Kenobi, one of the best fictional characters of all time) was bi, although I think he was in deep denial about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 09:29:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, now all we need is for Tiny Moving Parts to cover Rockstar by Nickelback. EDIT: Or hey, you know those Punk Goes Pop albums? They could have an 'Emo Goes Butt-Rock' series. So like Remo Drive covering Creed, Awakebutstillinbed covering Buckcherry etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 18:45:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's the difference between optical and vca compression?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to do emo scream/yell vocals?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 23:44:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mainly directing this question to vocalists in emo bands on this sub. I know how to sing from the chest, but I'm trying to figure out how to do Tiny Moving Parts/Awakebutstillinbed style raw vocals without hemorrhaging my throat. Any help is appreciated. Also, it would be real nice if there were no 'just shout lol' comments. I'm trying to understand the technique behind this so I can do it properly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Common jazz chord progressions?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 23:36:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>So like how pop/rock music styles commonly use some variant of I - IV - V - vi. What would a jazz equivalent be (as in Davis/Coltrane style cool jazz)? I've decided to devote the next stage of my music education to learning more about jazz, and I figure that a good place to start would be the chords it's based around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anxiety stops me from letting potential happiness into my life</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 00:35:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>"So yeah, I could go to this place where there are people I could become good friends with. But then again, they probably won't like me that much. And like, you know, awkward social situations" "Yeah, I could message this person. But they probably think I'm an idiot, and there was that one time I did something really stupid in front of them" "Hey, maybe I could ask that girl/guy (I'm bi) if they want to do something with me sometime. Actually, no. Just no" It's like I sabotage myself on purpose. Like I'm somehow afraid of things that have the potential to change my life for the better. And then I just don't do anything. I fucking sit in my room, and I think about how lonely I am, and the fact that I'm too fucking scared and set in my ways to change that in the slightest. Just... gah.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 00:38:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ben Wyatt. That is all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is The Rescue in circulation?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 23:57:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like, to physical copies exist (that aren't really expensive original print CD's on eBay?) Or is it available to download? This is the one EITS album that I haven't heard yet, so it would be good to make this right whilst also supporting one of my favourite bands.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Non-LGBT] Does anybody here read comic books? If so, what have you been reading lately?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 00:07:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll start - Lately my favourite series has been Marvel's Unbelievable Gwenpool. I'm a big fan of the quirkier side of Marvel, and Unbelievable Gwenpool is an excellent example of this. It's a shame that the series was cancelled recently, it's an absolute triumph in my opinion. I've also been enjoying Marvel's Star Wars stuff (specifically their Darth Vader and Dr Aphra runs), some of the New 52 Batman stuff (although this gets pretty dark sometimes and I'm kind of a wimp lol) and Seconds by Brian Lee O'Malley (the guy who wrote Scott Pilgrim). So, how about you? Oh and also, it would be really sweet of you to keep this thread spoiler free.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 00:13:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I go on guitar related subs sometimes, and I now get ads for lame, casually sexist t-shirts for guitarists to give to their wives. They basically say "I'm telling you through my wife that I play guitar!" So yeah, it would be real nice if targeted ads could go fall down a hole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 00:17:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>/unjerk I saw the "my friend peed in my guitar" post in r/guitar and came straight to this sub to find the inevitable post /jerk Put the shit through a metal zoan for sparkling toan ok</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 09:17:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really solid cover, cool that you managed to make it work with only one guitar player.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 09:17:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Preach...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 23:02:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[QUESTION] Ways to improve improvisation game?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 23:14:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Practice methods, tips and tricks etc. I've had a lot of fun in the past with improvising over backing tracks, but I don't think that this has improved my technique and I heard that this is actually an inefficient way to practice because you can't clearly hear what you're playing. But IDK.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 23:18:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 23:23:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, link didn't work, but thanks anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 23:31:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>East coast. How about you? EDIT: Typo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Feeling sad over a guy I know</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 23:43:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>So for the past six months or so I've been crushing on this guy I became friends with. The thing is, I'm pretty sure he's straight (he has a girlfriend, at least). This sucked for a while obviously, but while my feelings remained unrequieted, it was nice being his friend. Now here's the reason I'm sad. Because we've both unofficially graduated high school I don't really see him anymore, and he's going to college in a different city to me next year (I decided to defer my college entry to get experience, and will continue living at home). And so I really miss him. I think about how much I want to be with him and how I can't for so many reasons, and honestly it just makes me want to cry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 09:25:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Veep. It's basically a political satire, although it's been said that it's scarily accurate about some things. EDIT: I think that specific quote is from the fifth series, maybe sixth</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 23:17:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>*The act of looking at a photograph intensifies*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 11:51:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, sounds really good. What was your practice regime like for learning this stuff? Like, what sort of exercises did you play when you were learning to tap like this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 12:14:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>So yeah, I'm glad that this way it might possibly get renewed, but... what about those of us who don't have Hulu?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 12:57:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess. However, illegally watching a show centered around a police precinct would be too much irony for me to take. EDIT: Grammar</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(17, m) When I have a guy crush, I feel kind of excited. When I have a girl crush, I get low self-esteem.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 00:49:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I'm trying to figure this out in my mind. When I have a crush on a guy, I feel excited (not sexual excitement, just, like, excited), I feel happy, maybe even a little bit frisky. However, when I have a crush on a girl I just think something like "yeah well you know what, she'd never like you back. Like you could ever get someone like her, you fucking loser." And it works the same way with passing, non-meaningful attractions too. Hot waiter = yay! Hot waitress = avoid eye contact. Pictures of Benedict Cumberbatch = happy thoughts. Pictures of Aubrey Plaza = "Oh wow, she is a GODDESS" immediately followed by "and you're a pathetic creep who will die alone!" Does anyone else get similar thoughts? Do you know what might cause them, or how I can feel less guilty and more balanced about attraction? (Time for real talk) it's possible that the problem might stem from some depressive thoughts that I went to therapy for a bit this past year. But most of those went away as a result of the therapy, so I'm not really sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 23:38:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kind of Blue saw Davis and Coltrane experimenting with modes in their melodies/solos. I'm not sure if modes were used on So What though. Like you, I'm trying to understand the structures and notes used in jazz music more, so I'll take the advice of this thread and get to work transcribing/analysing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 23:53:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>[SPOILERS] It's always weird seeing what comics used to be like and considering what they are like now... this guy being carted off by the police in a "crime doesn't pay, kids" kind of way is now shown choking Norse gods to death and wiping out half the universe. It's also like remembering the silly puns that Cesar Romero made and his moustache being visible through his Joker makeup while considering that in more modern comics, Joker wears his own freakin' face as a skin mask.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 08:37:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>The NBC Twitter account saying "yogurt is shook" feels a little bit "hey there, fellow kids." But seriously, I'm so glad it's back!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to learn and memorize the circle of fifths/fourths?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 14:49:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand that this is a really important and powerful tool in music theory, I just can't seem to understand it or how to use it. Can anyone recommend any study techniques or things that helped them learn and use the circle?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 17:45:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>A couple of years ago, another guitar player who was a few years older than me told people behind my back that I was shit and "he thinks that he's good." I had basically only just started on guitar, so I really don't know what he expected. That really knocked my confidence, and to this day I still get really nervous about playing something in front of other people. Ultimately though, comments like that kind of just make those people bad musicians, no matter their skill level, because what kind of musician tries to discourage others from playing music? I try to channel shitty comments into getting as good as I can possibly be, and proving those people wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 23:20:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your Hand in Mine by Explosions in the Sky isn't really a song about bisexuality (it doesn't have lyrics) but I like the ambiguity of the title - the hands could belong to a person of any gender. Plus tbh, I recommend this song as much as I can. It's stirringly, inspiringly beautiful, changed my life when I first heard it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 09:25:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jeez. I mean, they didn't even use the meme right. And who the hell wants 50 boxes of fruit by the foot?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 13:26:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was about to type how one time a guy put his arm around me for a picture and afterwards I semi-involuntarily turned around and hugged him, but oh my...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 17:16:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Americ an Don My apologies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 14:35:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have. I found it to be a pretty good read, lots of interesting interviews with key musicians etc. The definition of post rock that the writer uses is a little loose, but I guess that it's loose in music terms anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 14:39:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>...and the occasional Nickelback/Foo Fighters/etc. song so that the station can show that it has a 'diverse' playlist</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 19:38:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has the buyer been identified yet? It would be a shame if it turned out to be some rich private collecter who'll just keep it locked in a glass case forever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 18:28:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, I know I'm a bit late but I just want to commend you on your comic taste! Gwenpool is an awesome series.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 20:55:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>*band members do a sick synchronised jump*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 23:39:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, the kind of love where you put your hands in your pockets while a girl kisses you like you're some kind of fucking pervert automaton... that's the kind of love we all want.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Recommend me a good jazz guitar book?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 20:40:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looking for a book of lead sheets for jazz standards, hoping that through studying the book I'll learn a little more about the theory and technique behind jazz guitar playing. Tab books would be ok, but at the back of my mind I'm thinking that I should learn how to read guitar sheet music sooner or later \(I know how to read music, just not on guitar\). So maybe a book that doesn't arrange things with tab. Books with solo guitar arrangements would also be preferable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 08:55:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Enjoy it, man. American Football is awesome live.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 15:59:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, but I do have "I can't trust myself with loving you" played through the Insane channel on a Line 6 Spider</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 12:25:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I SPENT THIS YEAR AS A GHOST AND I'M NOT SURE WHERE HOME IS ANYMORE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 19:45:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just wondering, what song is this text from? Ive seen it around a few times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(17, M) So I think that maybe I'm finally ready to come out (Vent)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 00:01:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's just this weird mental block holding me back... I guess because I really don't know what will happen once I actually do. But I just want to stop hiding who I am, you know? It's taken me a long time to get to this point, the point where I feel that just telling everybody that I'm bi is what I want to do. And at the same time, I just have really random worries. How much will the way people see me change? Will I just become "the gay friend"? Will things just become awkward between me and certain people, or will they just stop talking to me altogether? What if they don't accept me? Ok... I'm going to give myself until the end of the week. If the worries haven't gotten any worse and I still want to do it then... I may put out a Facebook post telling everyone. Kind of weird to think about. Basically, whenever I seriously consider coming out, I get excited and scared at the same time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 23:59:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mark Hoppus looks so fricking cool in that video... the way he sits on that couch...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 23:40:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great cover! Very smooth and defined.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 00:06:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>EPIC GAMER BRO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 00:34:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seriously, who the fuck actually finds this shit amusing? It doesn't even read like a fucking joke, more like a description of an abusive relationship. Imagine for a moment a young screenwriter trying to figure out how to bring their drama script together. The drama in question, that of a young woman who slowly finds out that her boyfriend is a serial killer, will go on to win several awards and be very popular for a while but for now it's script is patchy and needing development. The development required involves the need for a scene where the boyfriend does something to arouse suspicions that he is not what he says for the first time. However, the screenwriter cannot for the life of them think of what this should be. Taking a break, the screenwriter brouses through their favourite Facebook meme page. They come across a post showing a set of manipulative rules apparently set by a man for his girlfriend to follow whilst watching unimportant televised sporting events. Suddenly, the screenwriter knows how to develop their script. Everything falls into place.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Coming Out message</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 00:52:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, so I wrote this message that I will put on facebook to come out publicly soon, unless I chicken out again. I just wanted to know what this sub thought of it, and if there's any improvements you think I could make (stuff I could add/take away) - Ok so hey everyone, funny but actually also very true and sincere story for you all - I'm bisexual. Maybe some of you figured it out already, because I know that I've occasionally hinted at it in the past, either consiously or unconsciously. My coming out doesn't really change the person I am because I've felt this way for years, I've just never really told anyone (except certain people) until just now. I'm still not really sure if telling everyone is a good idea, but keeping it to myself has become rather tedious. If you decide that you hate me now then that's your choice I guess, but don't expect me to care about it. I understand that some of you may think about differently about me, and that's fine. All I ask is that you treat me with respect. This does not mean that I have a crush on every guy I know, if you really need me to tell you that; it is merely an aspect of my personality. Ok, signing off. Happy pride month.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(17, M) I'm worried that my brother will get bullied if I come out</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 12:33:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I know that my younger brother will be ok with me being bi. However, he's thirteen and therefore at an age when his peers could still be pretty ignorant about this stuff. I've just finished my senior year, but he's only a year into his time at high school (we live in the UK). It's not a particularly large school (around 1300 kids) and even though I'm not that popular word will spread around fast, even if I only tell people that I have on Facebook. My brother is a lot more popular than I was when I was his age, and I think that may mean that people who he's friends with will be even more ignorant about it. I'm just basically worried that if I come out as bi, he'll have to deal with people saying "see that kid, his brother is a fag" or whatever constantly, and getting bullied because of it. Any advice? I really want to come out but I dealt with bullying when I was his age and it kind of fucked me up for a while, so I really don't want him to go through the same thing I did.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 17:24:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, the point is that when I tell people in my year, it'll quickly get spread around school. People know that I'm his older brother and so therefore that's what worries me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are there any comic series similar to Spider-Man - Homecoming?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 00:17:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok so I may not need to do this, but I'll caution at the start just in case - this post contains minor spoilers for Spider-Man - Homecoming and The Unbelievable Gwenpool. I really enjoyed Spider-Man - Homecoming. I really like the modern day New York setting, but more than anything else I liked the fact that the plot was smaller scale (compared to, say, Avengers Assemble) and it just kind of had fun with itself. Watching Peter Parker balance superheroics with his mundane urban life was fantastic, and was a side of the Marvel universe that I hadn't experienced before. So I just wondered, are there any comic series (featuring Spider-Man or different characters) that give a similar kind of vibe. I finished Unbelievable Gwenpool recently (I know that I'm not supposed to like that series, but I do) and that came close to capturing some of the atmosphere, but the fourth wall breaking stuff and Gwen's glimpses into her past and future set it on to something else entirely. Thanks in advance if you reply!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 23:50:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha yeah, looks like that's the one I'll be checking out before too long. I'll keep my eyes peeled for other good looking series as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Started to get a little confused again (17,M)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 00:31:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been attracted to men a lot more lately... this has me wondering whether I might actually be gay. I know, I know, cycles and all, but... I think that I would prefer to have a relationship with another guy. It just feels nicer in my mind, I guess? I wouldn't rule out having a relationship with a girl, it just feels like I have quite a specific type when it comes to girls (kind of nerdy, artsy etc) and I wonder whether I'm more attracted to that personality rather than the person themselves. But the thing is I still appreciate beauty in a girl, in a "she's really cute" kind of way. The reason that this has me all confused is that I've pretty much been attracted to girls ever since I woke up to that sort of thing. It's just that this particular attraction kind of seems lesser compared to my attraction to guys nowadays. I haven't been in a relationship before, but that shouldn't matter too much, right? TL;DR - really confused because I'm a lot more attracted to guys than I was before, like the idea of a relationship with a girl but think that I would prefer to be with a guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 16:01:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>100% agree. I watched the prequels again recently and found myself thoroughly enjoying them, although lately I've been preferring Lord Of The Rings overall.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Non-LGBT] I'm like really, really, really freakin' lonely</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 01:16:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jeez, I hate being alone with my thoughts late at night... I just end up feeling this knawing hollowness until I eventually fall asleep. I just want somebody in my life, I guess. And yet I'm too scared to actually do anything about it. Some nights I'll convince myself that I'm just destined to die alone. And I'm only freaking 17! It's just I've been lonely for so long (never had a relationship, never kissed anyone) that its hard to imagine feeling anything other than this way. So I lie in bed at night, thinking of people who I know don't think of me. But I have to retain hope I guess. There has to be someone out there. I don't expect an everlasting relationship, just something, even for a few months or a year, something that brings light into my life... someone that makes me happy. Ok, tonight is a long dark night of the soul I guess... been having a lot of those recently. But I'll feel better in the morning, I think. It feels good to get all this out there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ambient jazz artists?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 00:42:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anything out there in this vein? I was listening to Brian Eno recently, and thought to myself that some syncopated modal improvisation over the beautiful droning textures would sound rather lovely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thank you, r/bisexual</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 01:53:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm probably just posting this because I'm tired and emotional, but thanks everybody. I've had a pretty tough year and faced a lot of crap. I was just so sad and scared all the time. In amongst all this I really came to terms with my bisexuality. And this sub helped me so very much. Thing is, whenever I felt low or lonely or panicky I went to this sub, and (to paraphrase Nickelback) every time I did, it made me laugh. It made me feel better about myself, better about being alive, seeing that all these beautiful, proud bisexual people exist out there in this world. And I felt that I was part of something wonderful. Now life is starting to get a little better (hopefully it stays this way). I still have struggles with my mental health, but for the first time in a while I feel that I have hope for the future. This sub has made me more confident about who I am, and now I can start living more openly. So, thank you, r/bisexual. Simply for being there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 12:39:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Catherine's behaviour comes as a result of a pretty crappy childhood and her parent's divorce. We can see that her mother is manipulative and controlling of her even in adult life. There's an episode when Catherine talks to her therapist about Selina and her therapist tells Catherine that she's been making the same complaints about her mother since she was a teenager. The thing about Veep is that every character is deeply flawed (except Richard... gotta love Richard). They are between them greedy, unsympathetic, spineless, overbearing and self-centered. Catherine's sense of entitlement is a character trait that fits into the entitled nature of her mother's political career. The fact that Veep can have such flawed characters and still have them be funny and engaging on-screen is testament to what a great show it is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 00:31:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got pretty ticked off when I first saw this... It's hard enough trying to be accepted by straight people without feeling like you aren't welcome in LGBT community. I'm glad it turned out to be fake, but it's a little concerning that people seem to be going along with it. P.S. I like the use of King Theoden here... I often have hear him saying this line in my head whenever I see some upcoming bullshit that I'll have to deal with. The Lord Of The Rings, be it book or film, is one of my favourite things of all time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 12:03:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>things</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 13:43:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like to see Miles being added to the MCU, although I don't think that Disney will kill off Tom Holland unless they want a riot on their hands.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 13:46:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>The "move, I'm gay" one gets me every time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Essential listening from the big composers?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 00:08:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I apologise if something to this effect has been asked here recently, I am happy to remove this post if it causes offence. Basically I'm wondering where to start with the work of the "big" composers - Beethoven, Mozart, Bach, Debussy etc. The fact that these composers did so much (most of which is considered excellent) is somewhat daunting to someone approaching classical music for not quite the first time, but the first time with a sense of purpose. Can you recommend any sonatas, concertos or symphonies, for example? I'm interested in all periods and styles of classical music, so I'm open to any suggestions you may have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do scars ever heal?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 23:41:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last time I self harmed was around 3 months ago... I have scars from then and scars from before then, so maybe like 6 - 9 months. Some of them were deeper than others, I drew blood most of the time when I did it but I don't think any went beyond the skin. The scars on my arms are very visible (to me at least) in certain types of light, and less visible in bright soft light (such as a shaded lamp). They're fairly dark in colour (my skin is naturally quite pale, and that's why I feel they stand out). I don't really know if any of that is relevant I just feel I should put it in the explanation. Will my scars ever fade away? I don't really mind one way or the other, I just want to know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>