<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject5549</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tips to pass and how I am doing. Not on HrT yet.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 17:17:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 21:33:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only a Psychiatrist will prescribe you drugs but a Psychotherapist won #8217;t. They are just there to listen to your problems.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 00:55:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your welcome good luck! Sorry you are having a hard time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 04:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the advice. I have naturally Afro hair but I #8217;ve been trying to grow it out. I look more cisgender in my opinion without it because when I go natural people misgender me more</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 21:12:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is the nicest thing I have heard lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 01:29:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be far it does take a high IQ to understand the Last Jedi. The force is extremely strong in this one and without a knowledge of the Star Wars Universe the themes will go over ones head. Their is also Luke Skywalker #8217;s nihilistic outlook which is deftly woven into his character. -his personal philosophy draws from Qui Gon Jin, for instance. The fans understand this stuff; they have midichlorian capacity to understand these themes, to realize this isn #8217;t bad writing, they say something deep about life. As a consequence the people who hate The Last Jedi are truly pathetic in their force abilities. Aka idiots. Of course they wouldn #8217;t appreciate for instance the intelligence in Luke Skywalker #8217;s lessons of Pantheistic philosophy. Which itself is a criticism of Jedi theology. I #8217;m smirking right now just imagining those scrubby nerf herders scratching their heads as Rian Johnson #8217;s genius unfolds on the big screen. Oh how they are suffering. And yes btw I have a resistance tattoo but it #8217;s for the ladies eyes only. And still they must prove they are merely .5 times less powerful in the force. (Preferably lower)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 22:47:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are goals!  #128525;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 00:52:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>So gorgeous!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Getting Litty as a Kiddy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 22:27:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Awe (n_n) such nice (^3^)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 10:36:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I Flush the Drains Down in Africa</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 12:03:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>