<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject1485</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>sneakytummytickler's first H1Z1 montage *caution extreme skill</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-27 06:15:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-27 06:48:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>i am not teaming in 90% of these clips.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-27 12:11:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>dont have to cry about it lol lighten up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-27 12:43:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>don't worry man, you'll get a win eventually i bet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-28 01:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is everyone so critical on this sub. Can people lighten up and relax a little bit? No one is trolling. I play to win, sometimes I just like to joke around a bit. Is that such a crime?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 18:00:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>pretty average. wouldnotwanttoteamwith/10</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 18:32:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol. describes how he wishes the free cam worked. simultaneously describes how it already works. gets salty when he gets called out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 18:54:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't seen a board full of positive posts in quite a while. I also understand i'm on reddit and 98% of people here are hyper sensitive politically correct daisy flowers but i'm not really one to sugar coat anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 19:00:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am not lying at all. I am not one to deal with lag or low frames in any game. I get too frustrated way too fast. But yeah the only problem i've ever had was in BR i would sometimes fall through the map when i landed but after some research i was able to fix it (don't fly in at too steep of an angle). I would however bet that my PC is better than 95% of other players machines.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 19:01:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dragon ball Z is badass at any age. thats just a straight up fact</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 19:09:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can only imagine what kind of lonely, boring, judgmental asshole you are in real life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 19:13:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awww did I put some poor little whiny babies in their place? what is up with everyone on reddit being so damn sensitive. stop being such a sheep. People need to harden up. Every time i post on here i feel like i'm being attacked by a bunch of moody 10th grade girls.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 19:18:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>how much fun did you have hiding for an hour? Yeah winning is cool but the real fun is murdering the other players knowing they have to start all over because of you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 19:19:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didnt even read this by the way lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-06 14:36:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>if you want to be competitive at all you'll learn to play 3rd person well. the only time i switch to 1st is when the angle is so steep my characters body blocks my line of sight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-10 23:46:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>damn heading over there rn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-12 07:08:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>its called missing, the guns are good but you're just bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-27 01:22:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. everyone starts at the same time, you just have to learn how to parachute better. 2. knowing where cars and medkits are is part of the game. it also makes it more dangerous to go for them because there will be more people heading for them. 3. this is a terrible idea. the point of crouching is to increase sneakiness but at a cost of movement speed. 4. hiding in bushes is already annoying enough. no need to make it worse. 5. this is a bad idea because all the driver and passenger would have to do is swap seats until they're both full health. 6. aiming is fine just learn how to aim better. 7. the circle on the map is exact. you just have to learn how to read the map. 8. the real rewards from BR are your event tickets. 9. Tip: if you want to be reloading don't pick anything up... 10. don't hold boost the whole time..... 11. you pick up sneakers in game. the only pay to win in this game is airdrop tickets for survival.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-27 07:18:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>sneakers are just rare drops in the game. the people who have sneakers have found them in the battle royale</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-05 01:33:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>ty zyzz bird</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-06 22:10:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>this seems to happen when i'm lagging</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-06 23:50:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>every dairy queen cone should look like that. I spent 4 hours of my training day perfecting my cone technique lol. They have to be perfect or we throw it out and redo it. Smalls have one bump up to larges with three bumps and the swirl at the top is a trademark of DQ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-09 19:43:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very wtf...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-16 19:18:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have over 700 hours mostly in BR and I see a cheater probably 1/400 games</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-17 10:14:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn you shot someone sitting perfectly still. Amazing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-18 04:31:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rejuv everything. Make sure to keep your mastery up and lifebloom/s up at all times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-18 04:47:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the first time I've seen a picture of someone fishing with thunderfury. Very original</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-18 18:51:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like you're playing on a potato pc</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-24 01:01:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>omg lol think for literally 4 seconds and you could figure this out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-25 01:22:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>smoke weed tahts what i do mid game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-26 23:02:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Luckily the last two guys were terrible</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-28 10:39:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the result of people trying to run a demanding game on their i3 laptops</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-28 20:17:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because people who complain about shit like this are usually of very low intelligence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-28 20:30:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I almost threw up listening to you stuff handfuls of chips in your mouth and talk with your mouth full. Fucking gross why would you upload this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-28 23:54:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>More semi auto or bolt action would be nice but hopefully not fully auto. This isn't cod</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-30 21:58:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>you probably didn't take more than 4 seconds to read the entire article. if you did you would have realized the robber was carrying a firearm and the man's wife was in the vehicle with him. I hope one day you get robbed and murdered because you're too much of a pussy to defend yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-02 21:11:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really don't think we need more fully auto guns. I do like the idea of older semi auto and bolt action rifles</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-04 05:01:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I learned a long long time ago to never stand on cars. I see you have learned as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-04 05:34:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great thread content. Devs are aware. We're all aware. Better make another thread about teaming</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-04 23:35:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>It can't be that much if you sold one mount lol. Why don't you just keep it instead of fishing for up votes on Reddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-13 07:01:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stop being lazy. /thread</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-14 00:26:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you knew anything about ballistics you'd know that a 7.62 round is twice the size of a .223 but travels slower. Better for short range but large stopping power. I'm assuming you're not very good at the game because normally people who have a good shot don't whine about how broken the guns are. Just get better. Explosive arrows are pretty OP though i'd agree</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-15 11:58:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you switch to first person you'd realize your gun is aiming right at the car. It sucks at first but you'll learn to not make that mistake again But to answer your question the bullet leaves the gun at the end of the barrel..............as one would expect...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 02:59:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have an opportunity to loot each boss once on each difficulty (LFR, norm, heroic). You can rerun each difficulty as many times as you want however you will only be able to use a coin roll if you have already looted that boss once on the same difficulty. You will not be able to even see the loot on the boss and you won't be eligible to receive it no matter what. You will also not count towards eligible looters in your raid meaning if master looter/need gt;greed is being used, depending on the cutoff, fewer pieces of loot may drop off the boss. To continue on your example, if you killed Kilrogg on normal, and you kill it again on normal, you will not be able to see the loot dropped. If you are loot master it will assign somebody else to distribute the loot and they cannot give you any of the loot. Nor can they loot it to themselves and trade it to you. Mythic still uses the lockout ID system. You can only kill each boss once and can't enter a different lockout ID than your own.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 03:12:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I really needed to make money fast... -Kill all 4 Tanaan rates for a chance at the Medallion of the legion (5-6k on my server) on each one of my alts. -Kill kazzak for felblight (150 each on my server) on all alts -The bonus bags for tanking and healing LFRs and heroics typically yield 500-600g each. -Clear all cats raids 25Heroic on all alts. -Depending on your level of fishing and cooking, 125 fish meals still sell for ridiculous amounts on my server. If you have 3-4 level 100 characters you could very easily reach your gold goal. You might even get hooked to how much gold you're making and start doing this regularly to save up. ;) If you are getting desperate, exchange garrison resources for most profitable mats from your trader. Keep your garrisons going all the time with salvage yard to get more gold and mats. If you get reallly desperate, ask a close guildy for a small loan if you feel comfortable. Just be sure to spend all your time making gold to pay him/her back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 03:29:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am an officer in my guild and we have picked up people in your situation and molded them into 95th+ percentile raiders. It is very possible. However you have to be willing to put in a lot of work. Start with one class and start studying. Understand your rotation and more importantly why that should be your rotation. Having a deep understanding of your class will separate you and make you feel comfortable surviving while still doing good damage in any tense raid situation. Then I encourage you to look up the fights. Understand every single mechanic for every fight even for tanks and healers if you're a dps. Players not knowing fights is the worst thing for a raid. You can even read tip guides on forums for your class for each fight on how to get as much damage or healing as possible. Now that you're comfortable with your class and the raid look for a guild. Wowprogress and the wow recruitment forums are great places to start. If you really want to raid make sure you can 100% make the raid times every single week. This is the number one thing my guild looks for. I don't give a shit if the best dps in the world joins my guild if they only show up to raid 70% of the time. Try to find a guild that has good progression that you might even be intimidated to app to. This guild will probably have much better players and being surrounded by good players will make you better much faster. Don't make the mistake of joining a casual/family guild that raids for fun and really doesn't care if they kill a boss or not. This will frustrate you beyond belief. The best tip I can give is join a good guild. Don't be afraid to ask other good players questions. Almost every geared raider is willing to help if they sense you are genuinely trying to get better. Other than that just join pugs to get gear while you're finding a guild. Make sure you have voice programs (ventrilo, raidcall, mumble.) Make sure you have the Addons required by the guild. (Bigwigs, exorsus raidtools, angry assignments, weak auras.) Feel free to message me if you have any more questions. I was in your exact same spot just a few years ago and now i help run one of the best guilds on my server.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 03:44:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>With only level 60 fishing this might not be your best use of time. But with max fishing and cooking you can just fish in your garrison and cook +125 secondary stat food. A single food sells for 50g on my realm which equates to about 10g/cast. (3specific fish+ 2 crescent fish) With only one 100 you might be in a bit of a pinch but do the 4 special tanaan rares everyday and do all the cata raids on 25H for sure. You might just have to resort to some old school farming/selling mats Other things that you might be able to do. The stat reroll items can be crafted for very cheap to make and sometimes sell for thousands of times what they're worth. This isn't going to make you rich in a day but every bit counts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 03:55:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>The two requirements as it is now. -Same armor/weapon type (leather-leather/2h-2h) -Character must be capable of equipping the item to transmog. (This includes level requirements and armor type proficiencies)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 05:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>No problem, I used to be super poverty stricken too so I know how bad it sucks. But once you start making big gold you get addicted and there's no turning back haha. You start actually checking the bmah and looking into trading card mounts. Good luck though! And if you give up and just do HFC you might get lucky and find a boe you can sell lol. Just sold some mythic shaman boots for 50k :P Gotta start saving up for the start of Legion!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 10:34:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Plus this is wrong. My hunter gets out bursted by our mages, rogues, ret palis and moonkin pretty badly. Sometimes even our aff locks. Now my ability to constantly switch targets and maintain high dps is the best by far</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 10:56:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I highly doubt they will ever remodel mounts. I can foresee a community outrage for purging nostalgic things in the game. If anything they will only ever add new mounts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 11:21:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>You definitely have a good start. The most important thing is to get your legendary ring quest done as fast as possible. For your other gear LFR drops gear that's like better than most your gear. In tanaan jungle there are armor items you can loot from various places and buy from a vendor that have a chance of being 650-695 when created. It's easy to acquire many of these quickly to get easy item level. The vendor sells armor and trinket tokens for 5k and weapons for 10k apexis crystals. A vendor also sells a boa item for 20k apexis crystals that upgrades any baleful piece to 695. Doing a dungeon or LFR that awards a bonus satchel will usually have several of these baleful items in it and maybe one of the upgrade tokens. They can be cloth, leather mail or plate so you can only use the Mail on your hunter but they are boa so you can send them to alts. Once you get to around 685-700ish (or before if you find a really patient/desperate group) you can do all the Warlords of draenor dungeons on a new mythic difficulty. You cannot queue for this like LFR but you use the group finder to join a group and you have to actually enter the entrance of the dungeon like the old days. This is by farrrrrrrr the best way of gearing up. Each boss has a chance of dropping loot that can be 685-720 item level. Early mythic gear is 720 btw. Pretty OP Once you start getting higher level gear you can then upgrade it with valor points that you get from doing heroic, LFRs, mythic dungeons and weekly quests. I would only upgrade pieces 700+ as you will soon replace anything lower. You can start doing Hellfire citadel on normal at like 695-700 I'd wait until getting 715+ to not be dead weight in heroic. Also as a hunter your marksman 2pc and especially your 4pc set bonuses from hellfire citadel are the most insane set bonuses blizzard has ever made. Get your 4 piece from normal or heroic hellfire as soon as possible to achieve god mode.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 11:33:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mm Hunters are extremely strong right now. Our mythic team has 4. I think they are pretty good in pvp with the other specs but I haven't had the time to pvp in a while. If you do all the hellfire LFRs and do all your mythic dungeons, depending on your luck, you could easily be 700 in a week. If you get some decent gear you might even be able to get into a Normal HFC to pick up some loot. My biggest piece of advice is look for maybe a wowhead or some other guide on the legendary ring and do everything you can to finish it as soon as possible. Also, for real the 4pc will make you cry it's so amazing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 11:45:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wowhead had formed a very good reputation for extensive guides. Basically you should be doing as many boat missions and garrison missions for the legendary quest items as you can. Also there is a weekly quest in Vol'mar where you turn in 20k apexis crystals for a huge chunk of legendary quest items. Depending on how close you are to finishing your tablets you're anywhere from 5-9 weeks from getting the ring. Then you get a upgrade item every week when you kill archimonde on normal or higher that adds 3 item levels to your ring and increases the bonus damage from the buff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 12:38:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-17 08:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would definitely say this is not true. It is good to join a guild as early as possible. Not only will they feed you gear if they don't need any of it, you will start forming friendships within the guild. You will be more comfortable raiding when you can relax with friends and you can get used to doing fights with the same strat every week. You also don't need to worry about dealing with terrible and toxic pug groups just to try to get gear.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-17 08:25:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sort of clever. Patience is impressive. This would be way cooler if you got something better than 10,000 perky pug costumes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-17 16:15:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm on mobile so I couldn't look very closely but here's a few general things. Some of your dps is shockingly low even when they didn't die. Your BM hunter is playing the wrong spec. Your other hunter needs to focus on the basics, (CS on cd, sniper training etc). You are 5 healing one of the least healing intensive fights in the raid. I guess for progression it's ok but if you struggle 4 healing now you are going to get nowhere on fights with high dps requirements. But looking at your healers almost every one looks like they should read forums on how to play their class a little better. People getting hit by barrage is literally unacceptable. Both tanks active mitigation is pretty bad. The time you guys spend between pulls is way too long. Unless you're discussing new strat, everyone should release right away or mass rez, eat up and be ready for another pull within a minute. This is a big mistake beginner guilds make. They only get 2 hours of actual raiding in a 4 hour raid because everyone is just sitting there staring at the boss.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-18 00:08:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol I love how upset you are because you can't tab target for shit. You actually had to make a Reddit thread you were so aggravated from falling to your death. Here's the thing, tab targeting has never changed. Please link the patch you think it changed in. Otherwise just shut the fuck up and learn to play.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-18 00:15:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>You still are so bad at wow you can't target mobs properly lol and cry about it on Reddit. And yeah I read some of your comments it's very obvious how upset you are</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-18 00:19:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so hilarious because I have sometimes taken a flight path right before someone else and then I'm like, "OmG quit following me xD!!!!!!!!!!!!" But I'm just joking because we actually just took the same flight path looooooooooooooooooooool better post it on Reddit!!!!!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-18 00:21:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Asking people if they are running out of things to say is usually the exact thing people who feel like they are losing the argument tend to say. It's all good man. At the end of the day, I don't make rage threads on Reddit about how I suck dick at tab targeting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-18 00:24:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so fucking hilarious everyone is seriously laughing so hard right now. Omg this may be the funniest thing anyone has ever said in wow. I would do anything to just go back in time and be in that LFR when this comedic gold first occurred. OMG this is so funny the entire world needs to see this..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-18 00:45:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are making this way too hard. I'm not sure why you'd want to do this I would just use the exorsus raid tools iskar assist. I didn't even know people used anything other than mouse over macros to heal. If having a tiny iskar assist window is really a huge deal for you just make a mouse over macro with that action button command you have in the post. And for the fel bomb. Several people get bomb debuffs. If you hold the eye you will see only one person you are capable of dispelling. It doesn't show up if you don't have the eye.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-18 00:55:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you have boa gear? Even if you don't you should have no problem face rolling dungeons. At your level I think you have basically everything but your mushroom. Druid healing is about anticipating how much damage your groups going to take. Keep lifebloom on tank and rejuvs on everyone is your tank is going fast. Wild growth is also too OP in dungeons. Be sure to use your cool downs as often as possible. like tree form, ironbark, natures swiftness, bash, tranq. You have them for a reason. If you have rejuvs on everyone, regrowths inbetween wild growth should keep everyone up very easily. Lots of new Druids don't trust in their hots and let them fall off because they are panicking and spamming HT or some shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-18 02:57:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>No I just don't think someone talking about a cucumber is the funniest shit I've ever seen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-20 04:23:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>My roommate has this. His big toenail falls off every few months. Been like that since he was a kid</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-20 04:36:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sad to see our society degenerate like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-20 11:36:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make some taunt macros so you can dos the add full time and just watch for when you need to taunt. If you're on mythic xhul you should know how to handle threat issues by now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-20 11:50:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Usually you can judge the raids competency pretty accurately on one pull. A lot of times good players don't join pugs to have a progression night. They join to kill all the bosses which is fairly easy to do if your group doesn't suck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-21 04:14:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look on wowprogress, wow guild recruitment forums, or there is a really cool new website called warcraftLFG.com that helps people find guilds</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-21 12:26:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol I started cracking up when you released and kept going</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-21 12:36:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need 58 to go to out lands not 56.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-21 18:50:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why would you even post this? This isn't funny or clever. You can down vote me as much as you want but I'm sick of pointless unfunny posts like this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-21 20:37:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe you can use some of that gold to buy some bags that are from this expansion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-21 21:51:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my god why do people obsess over clipping. Stop standing around fapping to your characters armor and just play the game ffs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-22 00:51:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>So lemme get this right. You and your friends are bad at pvp and get wrecked by premades which are made to totally destroy and piss off scrubs like you, then you come crying to Reddit? OP how many more years of middle school do you have?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-22 03:25:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm 22 and I wish I knew what it felt like to have $200</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-22 04:01:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>The shotgun spread was more concentrated in the last shotgun change. It is a random spread with each shot. He must have just gotten lucky and had a lot of them hit you in the legs dodging all your armor. Pretty lucky but not hacks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-22 06:41:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a job. Two in fact. I have to pay for my car, my phone, my tuition, my food, my apartment, my doctor visits etc.. all while taking 16 credits my senior year in microbiology. But thanks for the pro tip you fucking douche lord.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-23 12:38:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why are you playing frost</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-23 13:08:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>You really think they'd be doing mythic archimonde progression with their healer in a fucking airport?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 00:10:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah both our mages play arcane and say it's as easy as mm hunter. And they are highest dps on almost every fight. But I can understand if an average player doesn't want to maximize his dps and settles for a weaker spec that doesn't demand perfection.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 03:51:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol pve element? Yeah free gold and resources is for pve scrubs only. This only goes to show how bad at wow most exclusive pvpers are</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 11:11:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>While I don't agree with cheating at all, you can sort of understand where he's coming from. It probably sucks to be playing at high ranks without cheats just to keep getting beat by people with kickbots. It sounds like it is almost necessary to stay competitive at levels where everyone is kickbotting. However I hope he and everyone else who bots get a swift and harsh ban.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 11:54:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>While I respect your opinion, in my opinion RP is the saddest thing I've ever seen. Not only is it brutally awkward to encounter but how awful must your real life be to pretend to be somebody else in a video game. Just log on to murder bosses and stomp scrubs in pvp and leave the play pretend to kindergarteners. Basically when I see people RPing all I can picture is those cringe videos of 4chan meet ups where everyone is muttering quotes from memes and or meowing at each other, nobody has showered in weeks and have the social skills of about Helen Keller.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 12:20:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not a troll. It really just seems pathetic. I know my opinion isn't very popular but I just don't understand the lure of RP at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 12:49:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>You misquoted me. I said "I don't understand the lure...". I definitely understand what it is so please don't put words in my mouth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 14:27:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's called not giving a fuck about down votes because they don't mean a single thing. I'd much rather voice my opinion than worry about how many sheep hop aboard the downvote train because somebody has a different opinion than theirs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 14:39:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmao another one of these shit posts? I'll put it very simple. No one wants your under geared shit tank in their group. Get more gear=get invites. Tanaan gear, LFR/normal HFC, Crafted gear, valor upgrades. There is no reason for you to be mad when there are several easy ways to boost your ilvl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 14:39:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmao another one of these shit posts? I'll put it very simple. No one wants your under geared shit tank in their group. Get more gear=get invites. Tanaan gear, LFR/normal HFC, Crafted gear, valor upgrades. There is no reason for you to be mad when there are several easy ways to boost your ilvl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 14:56:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm on mobile but I'll tell you what I see so far. First your gear is not great. Without the ring you will be severely behind in dps but you still have a lot of room to improve. What other people have said is on the right track. Always make sure you have focus for chim shot and never should you let it sit for even a second and if possible always try to have it cleave. Pool focus before popping rapid fire and use your second pot with rapid fire+ring when you get it. Lust is just more haste and haste sucks but rapid fire gives you juicy aimed shot crit so pump as much damage into the ring proc as possible with agi pot and RF. I noticed for some fights your barrage damage is terrible (eg mannoroth). Barrage becomes a priority at 3 or more targets and is very powerful. (It will pad your numbers if you utilize it right ;)). For instance your barrage will be up for every set of imps on xhul and manno. Be sure you have the focus you need to barrage and probably chim shot soon after. Also for fights with adds try to kill shot snipe adds that are low hp. Kills shots free and does huge damage not to mention polishing off adds usually helps your raid. If I were you I would pug heroic council over and over until you coin the trinket. That is a huge source of agi and dps for mm. And ditch those poverty gems and get +75 crit. With your progression if you were in my raid I'd sit you until you maximized your gear especially if you were doing sub par dps. If you have more specific questions feel free to message me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 15:06:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I'm almost 740 because of welfare epics. That's great you like kicking a football around nobody is mad at you for that but don't expect to get drafted by an NFL team. For example in OPs post he talks about CC strategy for each pack of mobs. I would literally hate my life if I were in a group where chain pulling mobs into bosses and burning them all down wasn't possible. However there are other low geared players who wouldn't mind dredging through slowly. But 90% of people doing mythic dungeons aren't those players.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 15:17:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but at the end of the day rating is all that really matters to pvpers. I'm sure they don't go to bed after a night of getting wrecked by botters with a smile because deep down they know they are a better pvper</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 15:46:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol too many hunters??? If we all weren't fighting for gear I wouldn't care if every ranged in my raid was a hunter. They are too strong and can cheese a lot of shit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-25 04:50:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAH OMG GREAT POST SO HILARIOUS.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-25 12:25:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Proof</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-26 16:59:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Military nor civilians have tracer rounds for their rifles. I've seen a lot of fucking terrible suggestions in this sub but tracer rounds might actually be the worst one yet. If for some reason you're terrible at aiming you can see the round impact the dirt and adjust based off that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-27 12:42:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. During siege our GM was online dating a girl from the guild. When highmaul came out their item levels were very low compared to other people's because they were too lazy to do mythics or buy boes. Being in a pretty competitive guild everyone else was not pleased and literally the entire guild except the old GM and the girl left to make a new guild. Everyone liked the GM before but the girl was a total bitch and her damage sucked. 2. Same guild from the first one. Guy starts texting and "dating" girl from the guild. Eventually she gets tired of it and starts dating another guy from the guild. First guy shares her nude pics and tumblr profile to try to get people to be on his side saying she was just an attention whore. (She is but she is super nice everyone loves her). Fast forward a few tiers and the second guy who is kind of a spineless pussy albeit really nice guy, gets jealous because he thinks myself and other people are flirting with the girl. In reality we all had been playing together for years and we are pretty good friends actually playing other games together and being in voice chat almost all the time. Anyway he couldn't take it anymore and left the guild which sucked. He was one of the best wow players I've ever seen. He could easily get 99th percentile with any class he tried. 3. Last one is a little funnier. People started to get a little burnt out during mythic highmaul and we broke up and over months people trickled back in and we all joined this casual guild. Their leader was planning on leaving so us being experienced players took over the guild. The main tank was this girl who was really not very good but had a big mouth and she was getting rekt and the new GM told her she could call for externals if she needed. She fucking blew a gasket and rage quit in a glorious manner. Everyone was laughing so hard in vent she started crying and joined another. guild on the server. She tried telling us we didn't know anything about raiding and we all spammed her with all our realm firsts. The lesson is if you're an officer and want a guild to last, don't let people fucking online date. 99% of the time it destroys the guild</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-27 14:54:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure if you know how shot guns work but when you claim you hit the guy you were shooting you have no idea how many of the pellets in the spread actually hit the player and where it hit him. If you want the shotgun to be effective you have to be close enough to ensure a one shot otherwise I keep my AR/AK out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-27 15:04:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 03:11:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>How is this wtf? If I wanted to see someone missing a part of their toe I would just google it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 03:41:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sure it wouldn't be too hard for them. How can small private servers do it so well if it's apparently not even possible by the original coders? I call bullshit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 03:58:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are becoming more reliable if anything. Usually the guides presented on icy veins are not by icyveins staff but rather written and updated by top level players with the help of theory crafters and hours of meticulous simming and experimenting. They are not the bible but I would definitely not call them even the slightest bit unreliable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 13:23:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not saying it wouldn't require work but I doubt it would be as hard as they claim</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 13:42:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>That Mythic auto attack strat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 13:56:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow 2200g is literally nothing for how long that probably took. And I'm surprised he got that little ore. You can buy that much ore from a garrison trader for like 6000 garrison resources which if you have several alts is nothing. Not hating at all just surprised at how little rewards you got for that much effort. Well at least you have mining at 700 now lol. Btw the stones are for work orders at the mine. That much stone will last you months</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 14:08:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>For a while after the auctions end for the night the status of the auction will be "completed" and show the final sale price. However the auctions are wiped a couple hours after they end and there is a period between about 1am-3am give or take (my server at least) where nothing is on the bmah. So if you don't check before the bmah is cleared you will never know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 14:18:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>On Christmas Day my awesome guildmate mailed everyone on our mythic team 5,000g, some deviate fish and half a stack of 125 food corresponding to our main spec. Not only is she the nicest girl I've ever met on wow she also ranks on like every fight. Love raiding with her. Edit: best gift was finally winning the no wipes mount from trial of the crusader with a 99 roll just a couple weeks before they removed it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 14:29:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do this but before you do, queue for a random dungeon, pop potion while killing the last boss and then follow up with your bonus objectives. I leveled from 90-100 in 24 minutes (from the time I killed the last boss of the dungeon) on my monk. Took a little bit of prep work and planning but it was awesome and my guild mates reactions were priceless. Used every piece of xp granting heirlooms even the ring. Threw down a guild banner right before finishing the dungeon. Used the garrison xp pot obviously and only two of the 300% elixirs. I was full rested. Even if you don't go super extreme like I did it will still only take you an hour. Just almost finish all bonus objectives, pop elixir, finish them all, grab treasures if they are on the way. Source: I have 14 100s now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 14:46:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry rings not maxed nobody will take you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-29 01:28:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well First I figured out what ones I wanted to do, some are much much faster than others. Here's almost exactly what I did. I almost completed all three in frostfire ridge B.O. along with some quests that are in the same area as one of them. I did the dungeon, popped everything right before the first boss, then did the bonus objectives and turned in the quests. That gave me almost 2.5 levels. From there I went to gorgrond and did two very quick ones and picked up treasures nearby. This got me to talador which has several very easy ones as well, (touching the cats in the burning area, destroying the 6 portals and killing the orcs). This place is also loaded with treasures along the way. Got to 97 and queued for normal skyreach. Had my 740 guild mates run me through 3 times with the second pot and got 100. But I'm sure if you went to spires and stacked the bonus objectives with the bonus do garrison building you would be at least 99 if you entered at 96. This method would probably only require one more elixir which are 900g on my server so very worth it imo. Once you are able, go to the next zone asap, quests, bonus objectives and treasures give significantly more than the previous area.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-29 04:33:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol I'm so sick of these stupid ass posts. Tab target obviously can't read your mind but if you use it properly it always works.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-29 04:46:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>This has been noted on countless objects. And it also doesn't deserve any more Reddit threads.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-29 13:56:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>First of all strong English. Second, stop whining about the littlest shit and just appreciate the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-29 14:06:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not hard to trigger invasions. I dismounted over magnarok once and had to kill two mobs to mount up and the next day I had a Goron invasion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-29 20:38:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok well most people don't stare up at the sky so who gives a shit. Yeah I'm an asshole when people just complain about stupid shit all the time who cares about the sky. Next people are gonna be crying because the flower models are too low resolution. Who caressssss</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-30 06:56:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was also used as the icon for fervor</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-30 08:48:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>DELETE WINDOWS if clipping is so bad you have to make a post about it. Or don't be the worst race in the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-30 21:54:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol I apologize. I totally forgot about gnomes and goblins.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-31 06:50:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah don't be a dick. We must coddle the drooling retards so they never learn what wowhead is. That way we can have more stupid pointless threads like this one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-31 07:17:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea but I have to sift through the shit to find anything worth reading. Why not just google it I really don't understand</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-31 09:52:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a new player there are two problem solving routes. 1. Google it. Click first link. Done. 2. Be confused. Go to Reddit. Find wow sub. Post stupid question. Wait for someone to google it for you. Wait for them to write a response and post link that you would have found using option one. Click link. Done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-31 10:16:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who in this world has the capacity to play wow but has no idea how to google things. It just blows my mind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-31 13:44:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it was a question about a class or some aspect of the game I'd be more than happy to help. Check my posts I help new hunters and raiders all the time. I just don't get a post like this. Even if you are new to the game don't you think someone would think googling such a simple thing would be faster? Idk maybe he's new to the Internet and doesn't know what Google is. And I'm sure he would have discovered wowhead if he googled whatever he was looking for. It would for sure be the first link.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-31 20:34:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also not bad for pve. Offers a decent quick heal. Natures swiftness regrowth crits can save someone's ass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-01 13:01:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmao didn't quite think this one through did ya?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-01 14:43:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahahaha I was curious as well!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-02 11:30:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not trying to be mean but you should try tanking something that actually does something. You might fight it more stimulating than just a stationary boss with no special abilities.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-05 13:39:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. Have 11 max level chars. This game is over 10 years old I don't get how people still make alts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-06 04:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I play them all. Some more than others and some at certain times if they are good in pvp or have fun set bonuses in raiding. People who don't experience every class are really missing out on a lot of the game in my opinion. And understanding how each class works and a simple rotation will make you better overall on your main char.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-06 14:14:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a sad fucking life you got yourself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-07 20:48:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus christ you are one insane bitch. And i'm not laughing. You are just a total piece of shit damn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-08 10:08:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Have friend whisper you. 2. Screenshot and upload to Reddit with "look I'm a good person" caption. 3. Sit back as you get free up votes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-08 10:24:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree man. You gotta remember 90% of this sub is weird virgins on the spectrum who think shit like this is comedic gold. "OMG LEGIONKILLER LOLLLLL! the next expac is called legion! OMG LOL DURRRRR". You just gotta sift through the shitty posts to find the stuff worth reading,</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-13 19:32:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is only wtf because wtf why would you post this shitty of a video? Wasn't funny, wasn't interesting, wasn't WTF.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-13 22:17:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>That low of damage has nothing to do with RNG</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-14 17:00:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cute little mist babies don't even know old bosses</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-14 19:44:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Outbreak and Blood Boil for obvious reasons</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-14 20:12:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aaaaaaaaaaaaand who cares</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-15 21:14:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. Pet battle is such a waste of a week.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-15 21:24:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>FlightHUD is really nice. Allows you to fly perfectly level with the ground for most efficient travel time and you can place a waypoint so you can aim long flights perfectly. Selljunk is an obvious one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-17 00:18:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's so fucking neat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 23:48:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>OMGGGGGGG WTFFFFFFFFFFFFFFFF there is a window with brick right behind it. This is extremely wtf. Fuck yourself OP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 23:55:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me not posting anything is doing more for the community than posting stupid fucking worthless shit like this lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-22 01:35:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bet they were trying really hard in 1600 2s.. Because it's fucking 2s....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-22 01:45:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please post proof you've killed it "several hundred times"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-22 15:24:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Post proof.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-22 15:43:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post fucking sucked</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-22 15:51:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's cause women are so sexually repressed in their culture hey think it's normal to completely disrespect women. They aren't used to seeing beautiful women that aren't covered in big black tarps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-22 15:56:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please kill yourself before posting more shit like this again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-23 00:49:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>They will play exactly like they do now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-23 01:23:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder what the rankings would look like if you could ensure everyone had actually played the dungeon they were voting on when it was current.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-27 15:55:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>My guess would be someone doing their tarecgosa quest</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-27 16:20:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>MM hunter with mythic 4pc. If you've ever wondered what it's like to be God.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-29 18:05:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's easy if you know how but there's no way I'm doing this one more time lol Look for the small white swirl when the beams come out (have to have a sharp eye, it only shows up for like 1 second. Be ready to put a marker down). Have everyone stack there asap and discover the trivial add them finish the phase normally. Survive the maze and repeat 3 times. I'm pretty sure you'll get the achievement without the boss dying so if you don't get it you'll know</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-11 22:16:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>The largest eruption was estimated to have been ~50km. ISS orbits at about 400km so probably not. I'm not trying to do any actual research but if this was from the ISS it was probably with a very powerful zoom lens over a long time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-14 02:58:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chipmunk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-16 09:38:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use anzu and cleave trinket for mythic xhul and I'm only 726 ilvl. Feel free to go full dps on xhul as a DK, AMS turns xhul into a joke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-16 10:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here is a tip I was taught that seems very obvious but I see several hunters failing to execute properly. This will drastically increase your damage. Ring is going to be used soon (7-8 seconds) If you have thrill of the hunt procs that won't expire, save them. Start pooling focus but keep using chim shot. It's ok to cap focus if it's like less than 2 seconds before ring. Ring pops, rapid fire/potion instantly, pray to the Thrill of the Hunt Gods and blast off as many aimed shots and chim shots as possible (and killshots if you're in execute range). You will see massive number differences whether or not you are prepared for the ring or not. Many hunters make the mistake of thinking lust is where they should burst. If you didn't know this haste doesn't really do shit. If the ring isn't being used with lust, you should be saving your rapid fire and potion for the ring. If you're curious why message me and I can go into more detail. I also noticed you don't have the blademaster trinket. You should get it. Pug it over and over and coin every time until you get it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-16 12:21:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol I was sick of seeing shit that didn't belong in WTF so I made an example of this poster and I was banned for "racism or hate speech". Ok... I should have known better. This is Reddit. Even the WTF Reddit is run by soft, pussy ass thin skin bitches who get offended by literally anything and are making themselves feel good by pretending that PC culture is the way of the future. Grow some fucking balls http://i.imgur.com/9axkqWu.jpg http://i.imgur.com/eaSR0Nl.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-17 05:50:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>welcome to 2010</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-19 00:35:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah i dont care lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-22 18:14:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>worst post of the week. congrats</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-27 01:34:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thought you were referring to lagging in an online match. TIL video games have mechanics to make the computer accordingly competitive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-27 01:57:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Firstly, some odors only require a few molecules to detect the odor. Think of a plate with dried food on it. Simply running it under water may not remove all the food. Same thing with the molecules on your hand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-27 02:06:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Laughing is instinctual it would seem as babies laugh without cognitively attempting to copy someone they hear laughing. Think about when you laugh very hard. You don't stop and think, how am I going to laugh right now. It's very much just a reflex that differs between people because of the way they have "practiced" laughing since they were infants.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-27 03:04:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pineal gland is responsible for melatonin production. It's responsible for maintaining normal body rhythms which includes a pattern of deep sleep during the night time. You can purchase melatonin supplements. Apple cider vinegar he's referring to has claims to improve many bodily systems but has little base in actual science. Typically if people feel good when taking it its most likely a placebo effect. It does upregulate genes related to TAG and Fatty Acid catabolism but at a very low level.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-27 03:08:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where two plates meet no matter what type of fault, they can become snagged on each other to put it simply. They continue to be forced in opposing directions and when the force becomes greater than the friction holding them in place they slip and the amount of energy released is unfathomable. It sends waves of energy throughout the earths crust that can sometimes circumvent the earth several times. To answer your question is depends on how much energy is stored before the plates slip.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-29 08:06:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>In my experience it's not even really a problem to have a language barrier since there are a lot of groups that don't even communicate and still kill bosses. Honestly it's just that MOST Spanish speaking players are really really bad at the game. Yes there are bad players everywhere but 90% of Spanish speaking players I encounter seem like they are playing blindfolded.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-01 02:03:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL only Americans have rocks shaped like a handgun. thanks reddit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-05 08:16:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amazing content right here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-06 19:27:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Proper gaming laptop" lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-07 18:38:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can almost smell all your hardware melting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 00:06:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds inconvenient. Stop trying to brag about your laptop. Nobody will ever be impressed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 20:04:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>1849? That's what wives are for. It's a proven system thousands of years old. Look at single women raising kids now. The kids turn out to be unruly pieces of shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-09 02:18:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the worst brag post ive ever seen. You should just delete all your chars. Problem solved.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-09 04:15:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol I have 11 100s. Raid mythic on 2 of them so I'm feeling alright. I also don't bitch on Reddit about having run all their garrisons. If you don't wanna play wow, then don't do it. Easy now shut the fuck up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-09 07:01:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cause this sub doesn't need garbage like this post in it. You're basically just fishing for comments that will make you feel good. Like the comment you posted above about deleting your chars cause you never played them... Like are you that stupid? That's like throwing away all my xbox games because I don't play them much. Just a ridiculous comment clearly hoping for a sympathetic reaction that would make you feel good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-09 18:08:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just stop replying lol. I actually felt embarrassed for you reading this one. You might wanna re-read your comments and then consider deleting both your wow and Reddit accounts because obviously you have just the shittiest personality and neither community wants someone like you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-12 19:03:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Welcome to world of Warcraft</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-13 10:40:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great content</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-13 15:34:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg someone is using the same pvp set for transmog. Better post it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-24 17:07:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bQ__nRnO2mE this dudes channel is really cool he does a good job of summarizing and the flow is really good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-24 17:23:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really don't understand why people play this game if they don't want to be the best they can be. Blizz made it easy to change talents and specs for this very reason. there will always be a set up that maximizes damage for a certain fight and if you're not playing that you simply aren't going to do as well. Look at it this way. You are about to pull a boss and you open your talents. Instead of shockwave and stormbolt you see "more dps", "less dps". Why would you click the less dps option??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-24 18:33:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I completely agree you can definitely play this game and have fun and not be a top tier raider. I don't expect everyone to be analyzing logs and topping meters but what i'm saying is very easy small changes like changing talents and playing the right spec are just expected in a raid to be at least **maximize their potential** . I'm not saying you have to be perfect on mechanics or flawlessly execute their rotation. To continue with your analogy it would be like doing a slow jog to try to tackle someone. It's just sort of expected and at the very least, *courteous to the other 19 people in the raid who are trying*, that you'd at least try your hardest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-24 18:44:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you lol :D I like to think i make decent mogs. yes the below poster is correct, its the normal version of the brackenspore bow. Here are some of my other mogs i use commonly. The DK is just the heroic pali tier 11 with a different belt but i seem to get a lot of whispers about it, and my other hunter set. I seem to have deleted a few of my druids pieces for the purple set and the offhand but i tried to recreate it as best i could. I spent a little gold remogging so i could get screen shots pictures on the log in screen so i hope you like them :P If you want to know what any pieces are specifically just message me. http://imgur.com/a/fWkvh Another bow that goes well is http://www.wowhead.com/item=49844/crypt-fiend-slayer if you haven't completed your cmodes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-24 18:54:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.wowhead.com/item=60423/vicious-gladiators-chain-armor http://www.wowhead.com/item=60426/vicious-gladiators-chain-leggings IMO the gloves, pants, and chest from the Scourgestalker set are really bad. I like the chainmail look much more</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-24 19:07:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>i appreciate the sarcastic comment but honestly the only boost i used was the one i got for buying WoD which i used to make a horde shaman after deleting my 96 alliance shaman. I actually could have many more 100s but i deleted many high level chars to slowly change over to horde.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-24 23:12:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Swollen and Nooget are my mythic raiding mains but my first character was the druid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-30 22:26:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here is the thing. Having two characters at 740+, when i do mythics i wait for at least 725 ilvl. If we're just looking for one more i'll wait for someone w/ even higher ilvl. It's not that people don't like you, they just want to get them done fast and there are probably people queuing with a higher item level than you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-30 22:37:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>if i'm correct in assuming the pink chats are from a girl, congratulations to your guild on proliferating the perverted neck beard stereotype and creeping out every single girl who tries to play a video game. If not, then that's a weird conversation and your guild is full of 10 year olds if you or they think that's even slightly humorous.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-31 15:34:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>don't ever post anything ever again. you have no clue whats funny.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-01 05:34:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>The state of my life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-01 17:06:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>someone may be able to answer better but most likely when they write the code that asks the user to input their password they define a limit of characters among other conditions such as a capital letter requirement and or a number. It might also conform to older systems that cannot support larger numbers. But to ultimately answer your question it's so people cannot make insane passwords they will never remember.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-04 22:48:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Think of them like a construction crane. They grow and retract one unit at a time being either polymerized or depolymerized. When they retract, they literally pull on the kineticore where there is a protein protecting it. This is safety measure to ensure the there are only two fibers pulling (one on each side). When the fibers depolymerize enough, it pulls the kineticore out of reach of the protector protein and the kineticore degrades and the DNA seperates. If you are curious how they are told when to grow and shrink, look up M-Phase cyclins. Basically during each phase of the cell cycle certain cyclins are produced that bind to Cdks (which are always present). Depending on which Cdks have which cyclins bound, certain tasks are accomplished. One of which is the mitotic spindle formation and degradation by M-cyclin Cdk complex.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-05 20:17:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>i never double check before spending a million gold</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-16 09:16:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wehrlein on SS hit a small bump at the beginning of the main straight that happened to be one of the only wetpatches with DRS activated. Rear lost grip completely and he slid off, corrected well but slapped the left side of his car pretty good on the barrier. Red flag</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-16 09:18:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could have bought a ticket to China, bought a hair dryer and extension cable and dried the track off myself by now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-16 09:28:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol clenching my butthole every time someone drives over that wet spot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-16 09:36:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wouldn't be surprised if the marshals pull out and try to set a time to get into Q2.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-20 19:38:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Large clumps of proteins.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-20 23:56:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe the secretary of the treasury department decides on the person. I also know that they cannot choose anyone still living. I don't think there is like an open process with rounds of voting or anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-21 00:01:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Location and resources will determine how much communication they have with other cultures. Sharing ideas and goods helps grow population centers which helps grow civilizations. Also war. War has lead to the most rapid advances in technology in almost every war.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-21 00:16:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Black lights are coated with a layer that blocks most visible wavelengths. This is why they are kinda weird and purple when you look right at them. They do emit UV light that isn't blocked. White objects glow because usually whiteners* are added to make it more white but they also fluoresce under UV light. Teeth just happen to be white and happen to glow because there is something in the composition that actually fluoresces a greenish color. Which is why everyone's teeth always look kinda gross unless they have, *teeth whitening*. Which will be bright just like any other whitened product</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-22 02:52:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Due to the host immune response. Basically your immune cells recognize antigens in the saliva of the bite. They release chemicals(among many other things) that recruit other white blood cells from your blood stream into the tissue of the invasion. To do this the blood vessel cells spread apart just enough to let white blood cells crawl out of the blood stream and into the skin layers where the bite occurred. This allows fluid to also leak into this area. Essentially the hardness comes from increased fluid and cell density that accompanies inflammation induced by the white blood cells that initially respond to the bite. Edited for clarity</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-22 03:05:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>From what I remember in immunology it is the result of inappropriate T cell activation along with other white blood cells releasing degradative enzymes and other signaling molecules that cause cell death in the surrounding area. The cause is varied though ranging from nutritional deficiencies, stress and other unknown factors.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-22 03:19:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Crates are awarded at the end of matches to some players. Crates contain skins. You purchase keys to open crates in game. You can trade these skins or sell them on the steam market. For most sites, you enter skins you're willing to bet. Your skins are put into a pot with other people betting. Your chance of winning is proportional to the value of of the skins you put in the pot if you were to sell them on the marketplace roughly. These pots last about a minute or two before a winner is chosen. Them a fresh pot starts and the process repeats. The website acts as an intermediate for when you enter your skins you offer a steam trade to a bot account. If you win the bot sends you a trade offer with all the skins you won in that pot. Open steam back up and accept it and when you open CSGO you'll see your fresh skins which you could sell, use, or gamble with again. Skin gambling is just a way for people to have fun with garbage skins that would not sell for much or they don't use. You can go to YouTube and look for videos where people win several thousand dollar(market value) pots with like a 0.5% chance. They are pretty funny</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-22 03:24:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your brain realized something (that you consider) bad was happening and stimulated your sympathetic nervous system. Adrenaline release, heart rate increase etc... Just reread your post. If you didn't realize it and it scared you it's the same reaction except you don't know what's happening so your body readies you just in case it's an actual emergency situation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-22 07:56:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's just far too weak. And it's not always clear at night.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-22 08:15:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It depends. There are many interlinking cycles and pathways in your body. The most efficient energy production is glycolysis followed by aerobic respiration where sugars converted into water and co2. If glucose is not available you can turn fats into glucose and or break down glucose stored in glycogen. Your brain requires glucose for energy as it doesn't have the capacity to use fats. The levels of these molecules directly control the proteins involved in these pathways. If you have a lot of something, it will activate proteins to store it for later. If you are low on something proteins will be activated for breaking down storages to release them. The entire system is extremely overlapping and complex but your body doesn't run on a day to day basis. Cells always require energy. Sometimes more than others depending on if you're resting or exercising combined with when and what you ate your body will store or breakdown the necessary nutrients it needs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-22 08:28:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whenever your immune system encounters a new pathogen it creates antibodies specific for it so the next time around it recognizes it faster. I'm not sure what you mean by start getting weaker? As you get older your immune system weakens but introducing too many germs to your system will never hurt you unless the are virulent and cause a disease.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-23 20:57:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Intentionally bite your tongue as hard as you do unintentionally and I promise it will hurt just as much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-24 02:39:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are going blind temporarily. Your eyes are extremely sensitive and are used the image being different and basically you can burn them out if you stare at something too long. Even the slightest look a few inches away and back will "reset" your eyes and you can see clearly again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-30 03:38:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Diffraction</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-01 03:21:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>no problem. refraction is when the light is bend when it moves into a medium with a different refractive index. What is seen is here is the light scattering off extremely small ridge like structures on the scales that reflect the light in a way that causes destructive interference of nearly all the wavelengths of light except one. which is why you only see one color of the light at certain angles</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-01 10:13:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know if you just took a screenshot we could actually see what's going on and wouldn't have to see your bowl of cigarettes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-01 10:58:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why don't you just use what you like?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-02 22:38:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like he hit the wall and started boosting up it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-03 23:03:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>No the worst part is he completely missed a ball rolling 1mph in front of the goal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-04 01:11:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Watching a socially inept person intentionally act socially inept is unbearable. This is not funny. They tried a little too hard and made me cringe through the whole thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-04 02:01:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean I definitely get the "intentional bad commercial" angle but having someone act awkward who seems like he probably wouldn't do much better if he were trying to make a good commercial makes it really bad. Now if you look at the [Fight Milk](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=37VebUxrbKI), [Kitten Mitten](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5fP4emqw7O4) or [Invigoron](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RqePdfvOeiY) commercials, that is what they should be aiming for.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-04 03:05:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Save of the century"??? I watched the entire gif several times very carefully and didn't see a single save. Are you sure you uploaded the right clip?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-04 03:30:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your girlfriend is terrible</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-04 03:42:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahahhaha! So true bro!!! Only total noobs utilize their most powerful ability. What a loser!!!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-07 02:50:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is more like misplay of the game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-08 20:00:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>What</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-08 20:06:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>The ranking system is fine but I hate games that hide your mmr for no reason. The divisions are good but why not also show the mmr? Look at wow arenas. You know exactly how much you win or lose and you can see the mmr of your team and the others. I don't see the motive behind keeping it hidden to players... Edit: just read the part about you being ranked higher because you score more. Lol please read a single thing before coming here to cry. you have no idea how the ranking works.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-08 23:57:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>PSA: there is a practice mode</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-09 03:31:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you sure you should be writing a guide? You didnt even do the chain-shot-melee combo on the bastion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-14 05:49:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol it's clear people with about 2 hours in the game were allowed to vote. This is apparent by bastion having any votes for being OP and mccree not having 100%. They should run another poll for players who made it to at least level 50 if they want accurate knowledgeable answers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-14 05:55:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got to level 47 without touching d.va. She is the least threatening character to see on the map and her ult is really bad if you're playing against anyone with any sort of game sense. Never even had the urge to pick her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-20 10:47:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry I'm on mobile but horde 12/13M guild. We're looking for a few more dps. I'll message you tomorrow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-22 01:34:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>It says pinned until you hit a wall it says rekt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-22 08:21:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>You'll only drive 2 hours somewhere? What does that even mean?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 10:34:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just bad luck. Opened 45 in open beta and got 5 legendary skins. Level 30 right now and have 4. If that gives people some sort of indication on the frequency. Some are luckier than others though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Environmental Kills Compilation [mild profanity]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 11:16:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 11:42:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Genji is the most punishing counter to turrets and bastions. Also a Reinhardt with a sniper and pharah taking out the turrets sounds too easy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 12:01:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Coming from someone who has more hours than 90% of people, the only broken thing is mccree flash bang. The stun time needs to be cut in half or the cool down increased greatly. In response to the other bad suggestions I see: Zenyatta hp is fine(one of the strongest heroes btw) Bastion/torb can be easily countered. They good Winston is very strong right now doesn't need buffs. Lucio damage is very balanced</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 15:02:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I guess you're right. There weren't any betas so this is my first time playing it...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-29 14:36:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hell has frozen over</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-29 14:43:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>The paint has a more uniform surface which doesn't allow water to go anywhere such as tiny holes in the pavement so the wheel essentially spins on a very thin layer of water on the paint</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-31 23:21:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>hey would you mind adding me on btag? i wanna chat with you about a couple things</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Environmental Kill Compilation! AKA Lucio oneshots</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-02 02:36:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-02 06:26:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pro tip: turn skirmishing off</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-03 02:05:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>the funniest thing about this post is they match you up with players who have similar mmr to you. So if you're getting paired with terrible players chances are your mmr isn't very high</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-03 14:23:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've purchased the ra zenyatta, maori roadhog, raindancer pharah so far. I've gotten pretty lucky with crates getting the blackhardt, junebug dva, ribbit lucio, young hanzo, nordic mercy. so my next purchase will probably be a russian zarya skin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-04 14:04:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tank survivability logs?? You should be pushing as much damage as possible unless you're dying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-04 14:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh shit I thought this was gonna turn into a real good story</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 17:37:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idk but their servers give me so much trouble too. I'm hard wired with 100g down 13 up never ever have problems with other games. Except except RL servers sometimes jump to 200-500ms. Really annoying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 17:40:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol when did people get so soft? Gaming has always been about shit talking. Since halo 2 I've learned to take/give shit without getting my feelings hurt. Welcome to the Internet. Surprise! Some people are dicks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 18:29:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>But complaining doesn't really change anything. You're never going to get rid of these types of people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 18:50:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>on good days :P http://www.speedtest.net/my-result/5363942583 edit: oh i see your surprise now, i did say gigs. lol meant mb</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 19:13:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>caught a bunch of these in animal crossing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-07 07:56:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't get mad at him there are only a few titles to choose from. "Doesn't compare to the other goals on here but I'm still proud :)" "I did a thing!" "After X hours I finally got a goal worth posting." "I will never get a goal like this again."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-09 16:47:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even operating at normal temps, the higher the temperature the faster the component degradation. Spending like 50 bucks on a liquid cooler for your $400 processor is a good investment imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 00:29:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're investing in this I would go at least 250gb. The price difference when doubling memory is so small it makes it very hard to justify getting the smaller one. But for real you will be glad you went bigger. I promise</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 00:40:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>So you want a 1080 but you're ok with having a poverty power supply?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 00:48:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Worked great for me. Fan motor died on me though. Closed loop liquid cooling is not very expensive and much more efficient heat transfer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 00:53:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>What kind of mousepad is that????</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 00:56:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've never been a part of a release like this. Do you think they'll sell out instantly? If so how long until the 2nd batch typically?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-12 16:00:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>its really impossible to know right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-12 19:41:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Woah you shot the ball! Crazy clip</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-12 21:23:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>What kind of response did you expect posting an extremely below average goal that happens literally almost every game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ultrawide monitor compatability</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-14 18:11:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm currently using a Dell Latitude E6420. I have it connected to a crappy 17in monitor and i'm looking to get an ultrawide monitor. My question is if it's connected to an ultrawide via VGA are there any problems i'm going to run into? Will it even support an ultrawide resolution. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-14 18:25:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks for the response. The only thing that matters is there aren't black bars on the sides of the monitor. I really don't know how vga works or adapts the laptop resolution but what I need essentially is the widest screen that the laptop can display onto. edit: it will be used soley for office work. None of the typical specs really matter, its not for gaming or anything. display size is really the only point</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-14 18:38:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://i.imgur.com/mJTElir.jpg yes its fairly old and there is no hdmi port</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Help with VGA Ultrawide compatability</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-14 18:44:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm currently using a Dell Latitude E6420. I have it connected to a crappy 17in monitor and i'm looking to get an ultrawide monitor. My question is if it's connected to an ultrawide via VGA are there any problems i'm going to run into? Will it even support an ultrawide resolution? What would be the widest/biggest possible screen this would display on without any issues? Thanks! http://i.imgur.com/mJTElir.jpg edit: this is going to be used entirely for work, so literally the only thing that matters to me is being able to utilize the widest screen possible. The only display port on the laptop is 1 VGA port.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-16 00:44:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>This reminds me of Nookington's from animal crossing lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-16 00:49:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>obviously set it to 100%</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-16 00:58:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>hotfix in 10... 9... 8... 7...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-18 04:42:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>welcome to 2009</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-18 20:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sick fuckin vape</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-18 20:40:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's some serious rage quitting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-22 23:00:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>500g is prettyyyy cheap if you want to just buy a new one for your desktop btw .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-23 02:16:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes and the pure joy from putting your baby together will have you wanting to tell everyone about it for days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-25 03:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>And then you can't use any other keyboard in the world to enter data cause you're proficient with your backward numbers..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-25 22:46:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that's part of what makes melee awesome though. The primitiveness</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-25 22:54:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post lol... Infuriated that you can't instantly sell 5 cent cards because you don't know what emulators are so you angrily smash out this post and post it to Reddit... Try using google first</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-26 00:33:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-26 03:50:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you didn't find anything interesting then why not just save money?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is my power supply sufficient for new GPU?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-27 03:57:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Currently have a GTX660 that has served me well but it is within weeks of not working at all. My evga 1070 SC is in the mail but i'm wondering if i need to upgrade my power supply as well? PC part picker says my wattage draw is still safely under 750 but i wanted to get a real persons opinion. Current Build [PCPartPicker part list](http://pcpartpicker.com/list/f797hq) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://pcpartpicker.com/list/f797hq/by_merchant/) Type|Item|Price :----|:----|:---- **CPU** | [Intel Core i7-4790K 4.0GHz Quad-Core Processor](http://pcpartpicker.com/product/6vzv6h/intel-cpu-bx80646i74790k) | $326.99 @ SuperBiiz **CPU Cooler** | [Corsair H100i 77.0 CFM Liquid CPU Cooler](http://pcpartpicker.com/product/V2JwrH/corsair-cpu-cooler-h100i) | $119.89 @ OutletPC **Motherboard** | [Asus MAXIMUS VII HERO ATX LGA1150 Motherboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/product/pYyFf7/asus-motherboard-maximusviihero) |- **Memory** | [G.Skill Sniper Series 8GB (2 x 4GB) DDR3-1866 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/product/WtDwrH/gskill-memory-f314900cl9d8gbsr) | $37.98 @ Newegg **Storage** | [Samsung 250GB 2.5" Solid State Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/product/Ck98TW/samsung-internal-hard-drive-mz750250bw) | $74.99 @ B amp;H **Storage** | [Seagate Barracuda 1TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/product/dCxfrH/seagate-internal-hard-drive-st1000dm003) | $46.89 @ OutletPC **Video Card** | [EVGA GeForce GTX 1070 8GB SC Gaming ACX 3.0 Video Card](http://pcpartpicker.com/product/Tv38TW/evga-geforce-gtx-1070-8gb-sc-gaming-acx-30-video-card-08g-p4-6173-kr) | $619.99 @ NCIX US **Case** | [Corsair 750D Airflow Edition ATX Full Tower Case](http://pcpartpicker.com/product/Rwhj4D/corsair-case-cc9011078ww) | $129.99 @ Newegg **Power Supply** | [Corsair 750W 80+ Platinum Certified Fully-Modular ATX Power Supply](http://pcpartpicker.com/product/BJFPxr/corsair-power-supply-cp9020072) | $149.99 @ Newegg **Optical Drive** | [Asus DRW-24B1ST/BLK/B/AS DVD/CD Writer](http://pcpartpicker.com/product/2v9KHx/asus-optical-drive-drw24b1stblkbas) | $16.88 @ OutletPC **Operating System** | [Microsoft Windows 7 Home Premium SP1 OEM 64-bit](http://pcpartpicker.com/product/BVvRsY/microsoft-os-gfc02050) | $199.89 @ OutletPC **Wireless Network Adapter** | [Asus PCE-AC56 PCI-Express x1 802.11a/b/g/n/ac Wi-Fi Adapter](http://pcpartpicker.com/product/bQ8Zxr/asus-wireless-network-card-pceac56) | $61.88 @ OutletPC **Monitor** | [Asus MG278Q 27.0" 144Hz Monitor](http://pcpartpicker.com/product/fMcMnQ/asus-monitor-mg278q) | $487.64 @ Amazon **Keyboard** | [Razer Anansi Wired Gaming Keyboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/product/9nDwrH/razer-keyboard-rz0300550100r3u1) | $85.49 @ Amazon **Mouse** | [SteelSeries World of Warcraft Wireless MMO Gaming Mouse Wireless Optical Mouse](http://pcpartpicker.com/product/mDGkcf/steelseries-mouse-62220) | $83.09 @ Amazon **Headphones** | [Kingston HyperX Cloud II 7.1 Channel Headset](http://pcpartpicker.com/product/tZL7YJ/kingston-headphones-khxhscprd) | $84.99 @ NCIX US | *Prices include shipping, taxes, rebates, and discounts* | | Total (before mail-in rebates) | $2536.57 | Mail-in rebates | -$20.00 | **Total** | **$2516.57** | Generated by [PCPartPicker](http://pcpartpicker.com) 2016-06-26 22:04 EDT-0400 |</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-27 04:02:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>do you guys see any apparent bottlenecks or anything lacking with my build? I know what i'm doing but i know there are people here who have way more experience/knowledge than I do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 05:44:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>No shit lol. Don't know much about them but what really rubbed me the wrong way was in their plea on Facebook they linked the side profile of the guns and they looks reasonably different but the first person view down the sights they neglected to link were literally identical to call of duty.... Siding with Activision 100% on this. Edit:found the pics. http://i.imgur.com/W2XeVhI.jpg http://i.imgur.com/LjJxXIH.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 15:08:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>My evga GTX 1070 Superclocked is coming in the mail today. I have been checking sites twice a day since the release. At least it finally paid off</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>1070 erratic fan speed HELP</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 23:17:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Got my new EVGA GTX 1070 SC and the fans are insane on it. Heres what i've done so far. DDU to remove old drivers Replace with 1070 and install drivers from website in top PCI slot. DDU to uninstall drivers. Reinstall drivers again. Move 1070 card to lower PCI slot. Reinstall drivers. Still wacky. The fans seem like they're either teetering on the edge of a sharp temp threshold on the fan speed curve or it's just a bad card. I haven't had a lot of exp with graphics cards so i'm at a loss. Stress test graphs [Imgur](http://i.imgur.com/krF1FfQ.gif) [Imgur](http://i.imgur.com/f04kVp4.gif) I'm uploading a video right now so you can hear what i'm talking about. Will edit when finished uploading www.youtube.com/watch?v=1-8XodyT3Ag</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-08 08:57:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>your graphics power cables are probably long enough to reach around the back of the case and come in the bottom near the power supply. basically if its long enough to be hidden without stressing the cable, i do it. looks better and helps minimally with airflow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-08 10:48:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>ahh yeah the right side of my case isn't see through so thats where the rats nest is hidden away lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 05:20:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>what is zomies?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 17:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>your camera settings almost made the throw up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 19:22:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>you could have just googled "oldest picture on the internet"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 20:03:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm getting annoyed with NBC. Every time the race is cast on CNBC instead of NBCSN the digital broadcast is either unavailable or this week it was cut short without warning. For me the race started at 7:30am. I woke up at 10:00am and started watching the stream/replay at the beginning on NBC live extra. About 3/4 of the way through the race it just cuts out and starts playing the GP2 replay. The F1 race is nowhere to be found on the website. The other time the race was on CNBC this year the stream wasn't even available and the replay wasn't posted for days. Very annoying... and when i was trying to find the replay to finish watching they had posted a "highlight" with "Lewis Hamilton wins British Grand Prix". So now i didn't even get to finish watching the race AND they spoiled it...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 20:10:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually the race cut out while i was trying to watch it. Now the replay is nowhere on the site. Nice job NBCsports.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 21:22:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes it is working for me now. I checked when i posted my first comment and the most recent replay was still the GP2 race. Thank you for the direct ID link though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-11 06:16:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do the colors increase fps??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-11 09:45:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>...Oh shit *squirts*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-11 09:51:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got an Acer Predator 27" 2K 144Hz with IPS and GSync to go with my new GTX 1070 and it was realllyyyyy hard clicking the purchase button because it is so damn much but once I set it up i didn't regret my decision a single bit like I thought I would. In fact it was the opposite. I was seriously giddy and euphoric like Christmas morning it is so amazing. I truly didn't know monitors could be that awesome. You clearly don't have to get the same one but what I'm trying to say is invest in a good monitor and you won't regret it. Edit: spelling is hard</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-11 11:33:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would guess the frames aren't that intense and it doesn't change much but could you explain more? Is it CPU heavy? Just curious cause I've watched some civ videos on YouTube and it takes like 2 second for the new tiles to load when they drag across the land quickly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-11 15:38:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely wouldn't hurt! I had an HP W2207 which I thought was decent. But with the predator sitting next to it now it looks like a dinosaur. I really like the thin frame on the predator too. I can't recommend it enough if you don't have a budget lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 02:37:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>you don't play multiplayer do you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-18 09:29:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Other than something wrong with your settings, I've had problems with built in sound card (the little dongle with the volume/mic buttons) two times now. The first made the volume so quiet I could barely hear and the replacement stopped working entirely within 2 months. When on the phone with HyperX they said it is a common problem. They ship free replacements fairly quickly so just ask them and they ship it without any questions really.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-18 10:13:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>While the hitbox is pretty big a lot of this is due to the server tick rate. Just have to learn to play around it. Basically if you see a road hog play like you know you're going to be gripped. Stay at range or try baiting out his hook. If you know he's around the corner waiting, run out and immediately back and watch the hook fly right into the wall. Then you're free to get a million headshots on the big fat turd. While it is frustrating getting gripped when you probably shouldn't have been, you can easily learn to play road hogs like goddamn fiddle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-18 10:20:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not a bad idea but kind of comes with experience. I don't think we need our hand held with every single facet of the game though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-18 10:30:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can't expect much playing with random players.. Play with a full team and have some sort of strategy and it will be a million times more enjoyable even if you lose</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-24 03:10:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>but you missed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-24 03:27:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is like saying you want to play hockey but don't have skates so everyone should play it on grass. Just buy a headset its 2016. you could probably find one for free somewhere. Blizzard worked extra hard to put in an almost lag free voice com so that people could communicate. If you don't have a mic don't be upset that you can't call out to your teammates. pretty simple</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-24 03:31:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>you know you suck at hanzo when...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-24 03:33:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>i dont get it? this is fairly standard</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-24 03:37:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blizzard intended this. Its so you can't spam out turrets without a penalty. Imagine someone is chasing you and you are just running along throwing turrets onto the wall. thats a little broken.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-24 17:15:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The same thing is happening with NBC sports. Do you have a link to the race?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-24 19:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I was afraid things might escalate so I just dipped" lmao what a fkn beta. Let some guy playing Pokemon intimidate him so much he had to run away</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-24 19:45:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol Ireland. I heard of that little place once.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-25 15:00:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is like this on the Beta as well. I'm playing MM with a bear bet and he will just stand there sideways and wait like 3 or 4 seconds before finally attacking the mob i've almost killed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-26 00:28:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn I've never gamed this hard</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-30 12:04:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is not true</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-31 21:25:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit I was having a rough morning but I'm crying in laughter now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 01:24:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mirin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 05:57:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah we joined this game one goal down and the other guy had no idea why he was a junkrat lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 06:18:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just made a post about this too. The other team had a junkrat lol http://imgur.com/a/shA71#WMgBcbA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 08:38:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>He just tried to kill us :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-13 07:48:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blizzard customer service is always insanely good in my experience. Especially with in game wow tickets they make you feel like you're their only customer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-13 07:50:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you meant just discreetly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-13 07:55:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whaaaaaat!? How did I not know about this. My brand new Acer predator arrived with 2-3 pixels always red. I just accepted it because I didn't want to go through the trouble of returning my monitor for a couple red pixels.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-13 08:03:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>From reading all the comments it sounds like you just aren't actually rendering 60fps. The game might say you are but if it doesn't feel like it that might not be accurate. Are you in fullscreen mode? Using vsync? What game?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-13 08:10:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking about getting a closed loop gpu but I don't have that many fan slots to spare. I have two intake fans in the front and an exhaust in be back. My radiator takes both ceiling slots. What do?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-13 08:28:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell us what monitor, what game, what settings, what gpu</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-13 08:32:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Get rekt"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-13 16:12:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your gpu probably can't handle 60 frames during movement</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-14 08:06:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least it was fun back then</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-14 21:11:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>United States. Probably newegg or Amazon wherever I can find the best deal. There isn't really a budget. I just sort of need help finding the best quality low performance components. New peripherals would be nice but I can pick those out later</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-16 04:11:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/pcmasterrace</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-18 22:00:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You do damage</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-19 09:22:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Acer Predator 27" 144hz 1440p. i don't know why it took me so long.. you will never go back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-19 10:37:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Highest ranked player? Not sure exactly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-20 00:39:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>my favorite part was when he got shot. hope he dies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-20 06:57:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a new idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 02:03:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>the performance penalty is actually quite high. comparing your pc to a console is not a fair comparison.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-24 06:04:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>same boat as you. bought this when i got my 1070. Not sure what i was ever doing with a 22in 60hz monitor. https://www.amazon.com/Acer-Predator-XB271HU-27-inch-Widescreen/dp/B0173PEX20</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-24 22:28:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>other than the fact that there is a strong magnetic field directly beneath your laptop's hardware components</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-30 04:20:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>thought you were watching the kroll show lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-31 00:46:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Physics, not even once</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-31 01:28:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the sort of quality content this forum needs. Nice job op</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-05 13:00:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cause it's really impressive /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-13 01:18:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes this triggers me when I see setups where one screen isn't centered at the keyboard and mouse</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-24 21:48:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>your raid as a whole is doing about half the damage it probably should be...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-24 21:57:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure what you mean by relax but all you do is cast it and stand in it and keep casting?? not very stressful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-26 08:10:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>nice meme</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-30 20:34:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes but you want to use whatever will get the job done while not damaging whatever you're trying to clean. Acetone will act as a solvent for paints and finishes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 07:05:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>believe it or not there's this sick website called google.com and you can search for things like room darkening shades it will show you other websites where you can purchase them and they will deliver them right to your house.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-03 02:47:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Quality content. this needs to be seen by everyone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-07 13:46:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone else bummed the penalty isn't death...?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-09 09:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Doesn't matter how much other chairs are it's still $300 for a chair...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-11 16:16:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice Meme!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-11 16:28:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>ok</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-12 07:18:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Should have titled this. I am the guy who everyone has to wait for because he is not prepared for raid</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-12 16:06:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who said I'm salty? I'm just suggesting a title that would have been more appropriate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-18 06:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I must be missing something. the roadhog missed and then you ran away?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 07:27:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm no scientist but try enabling push to talk in your "User Options file thing"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 19:19:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't see the big deal. I love getting new high scores</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-24 17:56:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-24 18:08:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not this problem but I've had to send in the USB dongle 3 times to get a new one since I bought them in march... every time they said the sound card in them died</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 02:41:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>OK well wow I should have definitely checked here first when i felt like it was sorta buggy but I couldn't exactly figure out why. After reading this I realize it is buggy but get this. I moused over a pair of goggles i had x2 of and hit x. I then went back and opened the chest armor before it finished scrapping and it scrapped a rusted chest armor. At first I thought maybe i was crazy and I never had the armor but then i went back to the goggles and I still had x2 of them...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 12:47:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>The new MacBook Pro just came out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 18:55:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>This literally doesn't matter at all. The price is absolutely laughable even in the US. At this point, if you buy this laptop, you know nothing about computers, and you're an apple nuthugger. You are willingly letting them brutally gouge you for your money. Even if i was a billionaire I would never buy this laptop. I hope apple takes a hit for this bullshit they are trying to pull.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 21:21:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure why I'm being downvoted. Interesting article though I wonder exactly why that is. I in fact have a mac myself but if you look at the internals you get for the price you actually have to be backwards to think the new MacBook Pro is acceptable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 22:04:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok see ya</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 23:14:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can overdose and you might experience being way too high and vomiting. Overdose is basically the range between more than you wanted to do and enough to kill you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 23:16:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would never post this on Facebook but it did make me chuckle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you hack so hard you can't even get the last kill.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-01 02:53:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 07:24:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>feel free to quit playing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 16:49:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. this sub has become nothing but these type of posts. 95% of people are playing the game perfectly fine. Maybe figure out your own problems before coming here to cry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-03 07:18:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's actually pretty good. Try it sometime if you happen to see it at the store</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 17:00:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I took an international law course in college. The biggest take away is international law is basically not real.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 18:10:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>i watched this 3 times and laughed every time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 23:51:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>While i appreciate your assumption that I paid little attention I am very aware of how it works. While it is technically real, there are no real enforcement measures and just because an international agreement is made doesn't mean the individual countries actually have to follow it. The US is especially guilty of this. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_treaties_unsigned_or_unratified_by_the_United_States</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 23:58:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course you can find exceptions of international agreements and organizations. Many of these you could argue are obvious non-barbaric practices that benefit mankind that were formed into official "international laws"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 00:12:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>you can put structures around whatever you want but they are imaginary. Not a single country on earth has to follow them. its not real. Unless there is some way of enforcing them, many are merely recommendations not laws.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 01:13:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have just helped my argument. These treaties are real and only followed because it is already the right thing to do. The only thing stopping countries from breaking the rules is their image in the international community. Most countries who have a good reputation and or care about it, are already going to follow the agreement. Basically a country will follow international law because many times they are in alignment with what they were already doing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 01:18:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looking at your reddit history I am going to completely ignore you now. You seem to be an expert in every facet of life and attempt to argue everyone's posts even though you don't really know what you're talking about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 03:29:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>artifacts like that usually mean one thing...ripperoni.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 05:52:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm honestly not trying to be a dick but what would you change tomorrow that would help combat climate change.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 05:53:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I fucking love amazon for real</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 05:59:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>maybe they are using it for climate controlled or light sensitive business but don't want the "windowless prison" look</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 23:05:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>How did the ancient civilizations who made these know the areas would be vacation hotspots? /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 15:21:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>better than people whining about their framerate after patches</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 15:30:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>realistic damage doesn't mean better multiplayer balancing. I personally get frustrated by this but it does feel kind of nice not having everyone running around with bolt actions at medium range getting one shot kills. When you one shot someone with a sniper in the sweet spot range it is very satisfying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 15:53:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>these guys are my teammates every game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 16:05:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>This guy is pretty good but a lot of it is just picking off stationary targets who aren't even paying attention to him. What impressed me though were the kills on the guys in the blimp gondola and the boat. There was also a pretty sick noscope with the gewehr he had toward the end.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 17:45:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I'm not disagreeing that he's pretty good but I think many people could get the same multi kills he did if they managed to get into the same position.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 17:47:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>SMLE marksman mostly. Has the best short range sweet spot. Russian sniper has a longer range sweet spot. He also uses the gewehr and martini Henry in some clips</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 22:13:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had a some of my wow friends help me decide on a processor and mobo since it was my first build. I also was talked into getting a 660 which i'm very glad i did because it performed very well until recently when i wanted to get a 2k monitor i figured i'd better upgrade to a 1070</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 23:17:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>10/10 would look at again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 23:18:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>EMP /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 23:24:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>if i had a dollar for every time someone posted this bug i would have like 150 dollars</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The key is to not panic</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-08 19:23:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-08 19:29:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Frommer Stop or 1911 for me. I find if someone is close to me i can shoot once with my rifle and if i hit them or not i switch to my pistol. Both fire very quickly and are very viable when hip firing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-08 19:57:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I would not recommend that at least from experience. Hip firing pistols seems a little too strong in my opinion but i'm not complaining lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-08 22:58:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not disagreeing with you but why would increasing the scale shift the load to the gpu? Basically why would the cpu have to work less?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-08 22:59:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>well ancient aliens were real so...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 00:05:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have an i7 4790k and a gtx1070 and i get about 110 frames with 2k monitor on full ultra. my render scale is at 100. do you think changing it will help me? Usually I play shooters on ultra low settings to get the best fps but this game looks so good with maxed graphics.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 00:18:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>144Hz. In other games messing with the render scale murdered my frame right but I am curious now. Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not sure if I should be proud or embarrassed of this clip</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 00:24:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 00:27:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Medals seem to be very bugged right now. However when functioning properly, it is my understanding they cycle every week. So if you complete all stages of all five medals in one week you have to wait until they refresh the next week to get new medals. Currently it seems to spontaneously revert back to the prior weeks medals which is really frustrating and hopefully fixed soon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 01:02:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've had some times where i try to prone in a weird tight area and it squirts me out like 30 feet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 06:26:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>hahah thanks. are you sure you watched the entire middle of the video though :P</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 06:50:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hillary's favorite COD is Black Ops 3 just sayin....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 08:22:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>He would have never been involved if Hillary wouldn't have broken the law.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 08:56:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure https://www.whitehouse.gov/the-press-office/executive-order-classified-national-security-information https://www.law.cornell.edu/uscode/text/18/793 https://www.law.cornell.edu/uscode/text/28/1746  #8220;I did not send or receive any material marked classified, and I am very grateful for the hard work and professionalism of the FBI and the Department of Justice in resolving this matter. #8221;-Clinton http://abcnews.go.com/Politics/hillary-clinton-stands-claim-send-receive-classified-information/story?id=40446388 "110 e-mails in 52 e-mail chains have been determined by the owning agency to contain classified information at the time they were sent or received. Eight of those chains contained information that was Top Secret at the time they were sent; 36 chains contained Secret information at the time; and eight contained Confidential information, which is the lowest level of classification"-Comey "None of these e-mails should have been on any kind of unclassified system, but their presence is especially concerning because all of these e-mails were housed on unclassified personal servers not even supported by full-time security staff, like those found at Departments and Agencies of the U.S. Government #8212;or even with a commercial service like Gmail."-Comey FBI Director James Comey's entire statement as a source and I encourage you to read the entire thing. https://www.fbi.gov/news/pressrel/press-releases/statement-by-fbi-director-james-b-comey-on-the-investigation-of-secretary-hillary-clinton2019s-use-of-a-personal-e-mail-system Lynch said before Comey finished his investigation she would take whatever recommendation he gave her, basically forgoing her responsibility to make the final decision. In addition to that, Hillary was not charged because she was found to handle the material "with extreme carelessness" however the law uses the wording "gross negligence". Not a single person from the DOJ has been able to tell congress exactly what the difference between those are. Some sort of deal was clearly made between Loretta Lynch, James Comey, Cheryl Mills, and Hillary's team (Podesta etc..). Five people were given immunity in this case even though Comey agreed they were being cooperative before immunity was granted?? Cheryl Mills, Hillary's attorney for the case, was allowed to sit in during the FBI's questioning of Hillary AND Cheryl Mills herself was a material witness in the investigation! The level of corruption and bullshit with this whole investigation is overflowing. I truly encourage you to watch some videos of congress questioning the FBI and Lynch about their "decisions" during the investigation. https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCKzI8uTXAXjVgohgACHPz7Q</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 09:35:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Way to go plants. Thank you for trying to save us even though we don't fricken give a heck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-14 18:29:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>My suggestions. downgrade your cpu and get a better graphics card. You also should get a SSD. I wouldn't advise anyone to build a pc without one. Also i can confirm the case is huge. I have the same one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-14 19:18:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a 500gb samsung 750. you can get a samsung evo 750 250gb for less than $100. The 850 is out but i have had no problems with my 750 so far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Short edit of Max's charge to P3 from P16.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-15 00:55:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-15 00:56:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not my video: Credit to Rudolftevo on youtube. I was searching for a good HD summary of his race and this one is the best I found.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 04:02:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whoever was in the car probably died.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 04:05:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just trying to understand. So they make you take four photos and stitch them together? I could understand why this is better than one photo but how does it reduce glare and work better than a scanner? I find that hard to believe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-17 17:26:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>A surfers dream?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-17 17:35:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>If he were to get bitten. But ingesting the venom doesn't do anything unless it gets into his bloodstream through a cut or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-17 18:12:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>so basically you came here to post that the bombers travel in a straight line. nice tip.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 09:03:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was the "someone" you OP? Lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 22:07:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>i agree is suspicious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 22:12:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>in my opinion its more detrimental for your team because by the time you get back your team has been a man down for a good 10-15 seconds. but still hilarious nonetheless</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-22 17:10:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah my idea of a rank 1 tank and your appearance don't exactly match.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-23 03:35:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>My battletag is Spit. Of course she names bastion Spit.....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-23 23:45:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>zarya easily looks the best however it definitely wouldn't be my first choice to buy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-24 09:15:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>no idea. people are so mad now they should have played back when it was first released. they would have killed themselves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-24 22:57:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same with my rug http://i.imgur.com/lhUUurG.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 07:27:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh jeez how could i forget, quick play is for losing on purpose. good point</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 21:51:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chaffetz and Trey Gowdy are legends. I could watch them back corrupt slimy politicians into corners all day. You should check out this channel on youtube https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCKzI8uTXAXjVgohgACHPz7Q</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 22:27:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make sure your bios and chipset drivers are up todate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 13:21:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bummer. Makes the fact that some players have them a little more special</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 02:01:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think this happens to everyone when they play for too long. You just get undisciplined and over aggressive. Not only overwatch either</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 03:36:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like to think of it as a 5v6 except one team can't use a couple health packs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 03:40:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mercy regens health but 76 wanted to pad his ult</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 03:42:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Neat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 03:43:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sure these are #1 on blizzs priority list</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 03:57:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Welcome to the world of console peasantry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 05:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>i agree. i had literally become addicted by the summer of 2015. The game was so much more fun back then. Although it had bugs you just learned to use them to your advantage or play around them. I loved the rugged UI and unfinished feel to the game. So many good memories. It's definitely not the same game anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 06:31:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep she's definitely more useful than any sombra I've played with</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 06:35:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://i.imgur.com/vKQtzVq.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 06:41:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Luckily your aim wasn't very good or you woulda woken him up :P</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 00:53:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>holy shit i lost it at 1:30 when he purses his lips and goes "mmm Yeahhhh"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found an old linerider course I made in middle school!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 19:10:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 19:14:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>From Planet Earth 2: Episode 4 (Deserts) spoiler: the giraffe gets away</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 20:42:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>None :( I spent like 8 entire minutes making this too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 21:45:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>hahaha this vine actually made me think to do this! I originally just recorded it and posted it on my snapchat story and people thought it was funny so i posted it here too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 21:58:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for gold! Thank you for the nudes! And to the people who were hoping for dickbutt: /u/Omnipotent_Goose posted this http://i.imgur.com/WUGjYyA.gif</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 23:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every day my friend...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 23:27:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>it was at 12.8 and then started going down very fast lol. Albeit I don't submit content very often and don't really know how the system works.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 23:31:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you can disprove that I made this I will paypal you $1,000.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 23:34:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>if i'm being 100% honest, two dudes sent me pictures of their hairy chests and bellies. thats it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 23:36:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>damn 699 people claimed this was theirs before I even made it and posted it?? thats crazy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 23:43:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know its kind of sad. I spent 10 minutes and about 0 effort making a post that got almost 13k upvotes. I am disappointed in reddit right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 23:50:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got two dudes that sent me pictures of their hairy stomachs and that's literally it. Swear to God lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 00:28:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>so am i lol. lost faith in reddit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 00:42:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>how old is it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 01:16:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol the middle school part was just supposed to be a distraction. I'm scared at how many people think i actually made this in middle school...It was just part of the joke</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 02:18:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I posted it cause my friends thought it was funny I really don't care about internet points lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 02:20:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol no worries. I just posted it cause my friends thought it was funny. If I was making money off it i would be kind of annoyed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 02:38:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spend your money on a better gpu</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 03:20:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha no but i do live in michigan!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 05:32:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh thats strange because here it is http://imgur.com/a/s4ar6</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 17:32:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>i think its a conspiracy. It peaked at 12.8k votes and then dropped dramatically. theres no way you lose 50% of the votes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 22:04:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>No it is not my channel but I love it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 21:54:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you explain his right click? I have seen posts about it being extremely good but I don't think I've ever got a oneshot kill with it. Is it just about using it at the perfect range?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 07:46:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh damn is that what that was? I just left my game right when it started because I had like 400ms. I felt really bad because I hate when people leave but this probably explains it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 07:52:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right when you walk out of spawn, straight ahead you will see a broken bastion turret sitting on the balcony of the broken building. Jump onto it with bastion and then wait and leap over the house slightly to the left and you will be near the tunnel that leads around the left side of the objective. A lot of times the enemy doesn't notice until you start capping the point https://gfycat.com/FastAgitatedAzurevase</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 08:07:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most fears of "scary things" (spiders, snakes, insects, etc) are typically learned. Tbh, that thing is fricken crazy looking and if i were a kid I would for sure try touching it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-08 04:00:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like she's about to run out of water any day</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-09 08:05:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some of the best designed maps on Halo were user made forge maps. Same with counter strike. I really like blizzards maps but this would bring the game to an entirely new level imo. Opens up creativity for custom games and shenanigans. Really would let the beautiful game they created blossom</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-12 22:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I couldn't even finish to your nudes"- Chris Pratt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-14 04:03:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>How is it the most famous when I made it? Explain that to me please</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-15 22:12:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>e</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 07:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>i liked the part where it blew out my headset</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 22:34:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>your friend has never played csgo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is low level matchmaking just a gathering place for idiots?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 22:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have recently started playing and trying to get better. I admit I am not great but I have definitely gotten much better. I have gone from silver 3 to nova 2. But now, I haven't played a single game in the past two days where everyone on the team was trying... And i don't just mean they were bad. I mean they were either just spinning around in spawn, team killing, quitting first round, looking at the ground spamming, team flashing at the start of every round, playing every round with dualies, playing an entire round scoped in with a scout... etc. I really try to not let it bother me but after **two entire days** of not having a real match I'm very frustrated. Is it like this through all the ranks? How can I get out of this hell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 23:20:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>No if i'm not mistaken I need to be level 21? I'm only level 14 i believe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 23:30:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's hilarious when people comment shit like this because I know i made it. It really makes me wonder how you conjure this shit up in your head. I laugh so hard because I know for a fact you're wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 17:51:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you want a hug? What's the point of posting this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 02:15:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the comment nobody except me will ever read it lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 02:17:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's no such thing as an assault rifle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-14 03:23:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is illegal for anyone who thinks this is a good idea. But will you get caught? Probably not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Need a build for my parents</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-14 03:30:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I need help getting parts for a low performance build for my parents. It will be used for the internet and msoffice. I don't really know much about high quality low performance hardware so I'm asking you guys. A sleek discrete case and quiet is preferable. The cheaper the better but they aren't trying to skimp either. ~$500</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-14 03:38:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice this looks good. They definitely don't need a graphics card tho lol. And if they do I have an old gtx660 I could throw in there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-14 09:06:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why are they laughing so hard?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-14 22:09:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Neat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 07:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand what happened in the video but they were like dying with laughter. I thought I may have missed something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 21:10:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely a decent nebula</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-16 18:13:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Do you think you'll be able to work with Lewis?" "No it's going to be a total disaster and we hate each other which is why Mercedes have signed me". What do they expect him to say.....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-19 15:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>The game is shit. No point in installing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-19 18:01:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>welcome to h1z1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-22 09:18:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>define perfect square.....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-23 09:04:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scraping the bottom of the barrel to find them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 17:14:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who is we? You play for SK?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 04:07:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Worst Reddit post of the year award nominee</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-28 01:26:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Neat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-28 15:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The game has been dead for months</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-28 18:35:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you tried buying a new headset?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 05:59:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I typed this comment after I spit milk all over my computer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 05:03:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg do you climb up ledges now? That is so non-Halo I just barfed. edit: Keep the downvotes coming middleschoolers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 17:22:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don't see Christians detonating explosives strapped to themselves in crowded places very often do you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 20:10:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm allergic to peanuts and I eat there all the time lol. Never knew they used peanut oil</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 03:02:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>you tried</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-01 01:31:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>If i just said I eat there all the time with no problems why would i stop...?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 11:04:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is the point of posting this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-04 01:49:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol you salty little guy? I made this myself so please let me know how I reposted this. But all your comments are calling people faggots or telling them to kill themselves so I don't give a shit what an angry 9th grader like you has to say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-04 04:44:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn OP looks nice! Didn't cut any corners. /r/battlestations</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-06 01:02:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you don't know anything about hitboxes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 14:42:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then just delete your chars and play hello kitty island adventure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 16:07:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bet this kid thinks Big Bang theory is a good show</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 06:47:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could have typed that exact sentence into google and already be reading your answer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 17:45:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>All online. Just look up Linerider</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-25 17:57:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Our tank afkd to go let his dog in. After 10 min one of the healers jokingly said it got hit by a car. Tank came back two hours later because his dog got hit by a car.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-01 06:04:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>show me where its reposted from ill paypal you $1000</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 21:52:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>jesus christ this post is terrible</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-08 04:55:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Right click desktop 2. Nvidia control panel 3. Make sure resolution is 144hz not sure how people can't tell they aren't playing over 60hz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-09 03:57:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes thats clearly what i meant but i get downvoted anyway feels good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-09 08:09:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>i wasnt trying to be condescending really. i was just saying its very simple to check. what i meant was there is such a drastic difference between 60fps and 144 how do people not realize its not above 60.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-11 00:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>welcome to everyday on reddit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-16 08:53:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a no</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-16 22:50:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks im dead</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-18 18:04:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>BOIS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 21:05:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>wow amazing content, we need more posts like this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 04:37:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the only sticker he'll ever use kappa</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-01 21:57:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good communication on communication is important</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-02 00:49:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>just died at 66 too. Online banking timeout popped up in chrome and tabbed me out during rift boss feelsgoodman. At least i wont make that mistake again lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-08 08:32:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>i've paypal you $1000 if you can find it anywhere on the internet before i posted it. ill give you a hint: (you wont find it cause i made it) but good luck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-08 20:29:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>No you don't remember it from years ago because I made it only a few months ago. You are 100% wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-10 21:41:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reminds me of wotlk when i would wait for people leaving dalaran and typhoon them off their mounts and switch into bird form before i smacked the ground.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 22:47:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>any luck? didn't think so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 06:28:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes but you risk throwing your gun and having the round end leaving you with nothing. thats the whole point of using E to pick up near the end of rounds</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 01:53:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>About to click the link if they don't have a case hardened case in gonna lose it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 22:29:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>City of New Orleans is dismantling old confederate monuments because 7 entire people had a problem with them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 20:00:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>games dead btw</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 08:06:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>A ban for what?? Being a meanie in chat? Welcome to the internet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 08:10:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw the title and thought it was one of my awful high school classmates posting more click bait on facebook.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 08:13:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every one of my misses is an intentional fake</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 08:16:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Update: just rankedup to mg2</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 01:30:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>not a repost stay mad though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 23:35:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>ill make you the same deal i make everyone else. Find it posted earlier than I posted it and i'll paypal you $1000</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 02:55:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you slow lol? I uploaded that to post it to Reddit.....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 19:01:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then it's not a repost is it get banged</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 22:23:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I started out silver 3 never having played cs, bought some skins and now I'm mg2. How do you explain that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 23:51:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>this cannot be a serious post</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 22:50:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Huntsman case hardened. Won it in a $15 case and was very happy. I'm obsessed with case hardened anything and huntsman is the best looking knife imo. Wish I had better pattern but can't complain.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 00:22:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure what you did with the contrast and brightness levels but it's way too dark I can't see anything</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 20:38:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha I appreciate that but it definitely wasn't. I had seen a few on Vine before I did this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 20:20:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/upliftingnews</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-21 01:47:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>pH*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 02:30:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://i.imgur.com/u235JPY.gif</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 15:57:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not that bad compared to pictures I've seen of some other 3rd world countries</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 19:19:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Putting kimi on slower tires while seb was in clean air with fast tires was obviously going to lead to this... they screwed kimi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 02:39:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope this idea wasn't sparked by poor performance. I'm hoping he can find a way to get back into form and maybe enjoy playing playing more if he were being reinforced by solid showings on lan. I understand he may not want to do it forever but it would be a shame if he cut his career short because he got down on himself for hitting a lull.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 06:07:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's almost like that's how the country is supposed to operate...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-09 04:28:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>He barely moved one step after planting idk why you would look on the other side of the site.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 16:57:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do those warp time too?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-14 22:37:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>thats because it doesn't exist lol. OP actually thought the ball in his pen was a balled up wire lmao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-15 03:46:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean you don't have to be a pen scientist to look at the tiny ass tip of that pen and realize there's no way you could cram that long ass spring into it without it being the density of a black hole</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-17 17:56:03</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I'm no entomologist. clearly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 04:36:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>(  #865; #176;  #860; #662;  #865; #176;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-22 04:31:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trim your toenails</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 13:15:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get to watch one of these taking off all day at work as they practice landings at GSP. Nice pic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 06:07:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>all you had to do was look at the picture and figure out which one wasn't there....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-02 10:33:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Silence of the lambs is my second favorite movie. I seem to watch it like once a month.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-11 10:00:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Impressive data rate but I guess I don't see the potential applications if the terahertz signal is directional and the angle of the receiver needs to be perfect to reduce error rates.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 23:32:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>to show off the small cavities inside that you wouldn't be able to make unless with 3d printing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 03:58:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>looks like he just got his wisdom teeth out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 05:23:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>what rank are you now? just curious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 08:28:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I watch it literally all the time when I'm home. I have been doing so for 6 years. I've probably went through all the seasons on Netflix around 50-75 times not even exaggerating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 08:49:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>May be too similar to Mac Day but still couldn't funny</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 00:19:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Upvoted for Haas flag</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 10:11:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nothing would happen btw</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 07:12:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wasn't that bad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 22:54:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>this might be one of the best goals i've seen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 22:26:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I replace mine once every 3000 minutes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 01:23:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow this got WAY more golds than my linerider post..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 17:16:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>It says in the event info you can #8217;t trade items opened with decrytpors but not being able to upgrade is stupid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 17:20:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are letting you open crates for free just by playing how you normally would. It kinda sucks but just be thankful they are on the right track</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 01:19:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pm me the price for the sweetpeaches69 portrait</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 05:13:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>When twitter finally increases the character limit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 02:39:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>The laws of physics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 02:58:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Star Wars X-wing vs tie fighter</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 05:07:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>It seems like it #8217;s not recognizing the USB with windows on it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 22:27:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could really use an egg. I watch always sunny like it #8217;s the oxygen that keeps me alive. I #8217;ve went through all the season hundreds of times over the past several years. I #8217;m actually really hurt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 18:49:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just post on the misc I promise you #8217;ll get negged</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 19:00:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>All I see in that pic is a bunch of delicious candy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 19:04:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always thought Superfortress was pretty badass too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 17:08:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you #8217;re gonna repost at least get the animal right</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 12:50:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dad has a moon watch he wore for all his check rides (Gulfstream 5 captain) and he never failed. Hopefully I #8217;ll get to wear it for mine too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 00:07:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Big boi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 22:40:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was just thinking about this the other day!! If fruits disperse seeds by trying to get an animal to eat them why the hell is the avocado pit so damn big. Now I know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 12:47:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>This has to be fake</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 20:29:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d say most are unfortunately real</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 21:18:57</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Jerry_Sandusky123 #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yes daddy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 04:26:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 12:31:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>What if I told you the next picture in line is her with her kid and a forehead piercing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 23:36:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s the best scene in the entire series.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 16:44:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which one is the cell phone tower?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 22:21:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>... I just spent about 5 minutes trying to figure out what a AFAIK helicopter was...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 11:49:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work at a contact solution facility and we make our name brand and then just switch the bottles and labels and make the store brands. Literally the same tank of solution.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 20:21:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve had mine since 2015 and just now got a dead pixel last week. I #8217;m extremely happy with it. If you can afford it I would highly recommend it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 14:06:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did something exactly like this for my photography class in high school. I thought it was super creative and then I found 100 others online lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 21:45:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn #8217;t you just answer your own question?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 14:23:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Future of the game? Lol not sure if you noticed but the games been dead for a long time now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 20:34:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once you get your unit frames set up really well with addons it makes it way easier. Easily clickable and clean dot tracking is really important. For example back in wod if a target went into kill shot range its frame would get like twice the size so I mouseover and kill shot it without losing my target.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anybody recognize this colony?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 21:22:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 21:23:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>0.5cm diameter after 5 days incubation on TSA. Recovered from a personnel sampling. I see this recovered quite a bit but I can #8217;t seem to find anything similar online.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 22:59:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>No I work QC for a pharma company and I #8217;m unfortunately not qualified to ID anything yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 23:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know I love these guys. I see them pretty frequently when reading off our environmental monitoring plates for the aseptic processing area and they are always near perfect hexagons with awesome filaments</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 05:07:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I saved it. I #8217;m going to look at it with our ID tech this week. Probably won #8217;t be allowed to vitek it though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 12:53:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>1 cfu doesn #8217;t warrant a submission for some sample sites</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 20:47:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did the same thing. Waited for dark moon faire and got exalted real quick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 21:57:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>The game has been dead for a long time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 00:13:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trust me I have have a few thousand hours in this game my man. It #8217;s never going to be what it was</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 13:16:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>So basically you want a mythic Argus carry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 16:41:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure if you #8217;re serious but look up why vaccines work in a society.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 02:02:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did all of them in about two weeks too. Which includes leveling the 10 classes I didn #8217;t have at 110 when I resubbed about a month ago. Really not that hard</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 03:31:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>yikes. glad i got all 36 finished.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 17:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tried this on my rogue and hit an invisible wall. Had to fly all the way back and take the boat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 18:01:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it #8217;s instanced the same as going into ghostlands so it #8217;s not actually just off in the distance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Post your auto run and mount keybinds.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 13:21:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Autorun- ~ Mount- shift+spacebar</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 02:06:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whattttttre thoosssseeeeeeeeeeeeee</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found a pretty old montage I made while going through my recordings.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 04:29:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 04:31:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>its obviously not supposed to be taken seriously by the way. I just like watching it and missing the old h1z1 :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 18:17:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>So unbearable but I can respect the resident evil 5 T-shirt that guys rockin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 14:32:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Than*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 04:00:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should post this to r/funny10yearsago</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 04:02:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ever heard of a vpn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 04:13:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t think they had urban outfitters back then sweetie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 04:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t worry I have brez</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 18:36:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your marinara sauce comes in graduated containers?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 06:17:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry but fun was over 2 years ago</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 08:57:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Clearly a joke....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 07:16:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not possible</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 07:32:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Swift Alliance Steed by a long shot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 07:47:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got 36/36 challenges done I just wanted to let you know</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 21:22:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>What I #8217;m saying are the chances of doing all 10 dungeons and getting 2 pieces of loot is astronomically low</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 13:06:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah we get stuck with Brazil and Latin America servers and I #8217;d say 95% of the time they are just absolutely terrible players and you can #8217;t even talk to them because they don #8217;t speak English. I never invite azralon, ragnaros, quel thalas etc. to my groups anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 19:44:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>350 haste vers sword from freehold on my blood dk. BIS as fuuuuuuuuck boiiii</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 19:46:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s not unrealistic. Why would you invite someone at 320 when you are sure to get people wanting to join with 340ilvl. It makes no sense to invite someone with worse gear</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 20:38:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah exactly. So why would your requirements be anything but strict. Nobody i know wants to intentionally form a weak group. If I worked to get 340+ ilvl I #8217;m going to want other people to be as high as I am to have an easy run. It #8217;s not that we hate low ilvl players we just want it to be as easy as possible</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 21:20:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but it #8217;s even easier. I play the game to better my character as fast as possible. Some people don #8217;t want their groups to be charity events</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 21:32:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>No because I used to have a New Zealander in my raid team on a Chicago server and he was one of the best players I #8217;ve ever played with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 22:03:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah you know how many of those moose runs I did sweetie? But when someone makes up 20% of the effort in a mythic I want them to be as good as possible. How can you be entitled in WoW. Everyone starts at the same place. I wasn #8217;t handed this gear by my geared parents. I earned all of it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 10:18:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>The most fun era imo was before grouping was even introduced. Back when blue camo helmet was the big baller skin. Getting ear raped during the pregame lobby. Accumulating hundreds of the same winner shirts and bags. Stacking 8 medkits before the final circle battle. You never knew what kind of crazy glitch would end your game at any second. Seriously such good memories</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 14:49:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I only voted on the classes I have at 120 but it #8217;s crazy the results align with my perceptions of each spec so closely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>