<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject6946</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Jeice by my brother</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-30 20:32:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Done in pencils and charcoal http://imgur.com/VA5Treq</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not the original Grandpa poster</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-16 05:18:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;m American citizen, undecided voter, loving husband Ken Bone, Welcome to the Bone Zone! AMA</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-14 03:21:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello Reddit, I #8217;m just a normal guy, who spends his free time with his hot wife and cat in St. Louis. I didn #8217;t see any of this coming, it #8217;s been a crazy week. I want to make something good come out of this moment, so I #8217;m donating a portion of the proceeds from my Represent T-Shirt campaign to the St. Patrick Center raising money to fight homelessness in St. Louis. I #8217;m an open book doing this AMA at my desk at work and excited to answer America #8217;s question. Please support the campaign and the fight on homelessness! [Represent.com/bonezone](https://represent.com/bonezone/) Proof: http://i.imgur.com/GdMsMZ9.jpg Edit: signing off now, just like my whole experience so far this has been overwhelmingly positive! Special thanks to my Reddit brethren for sticking up for me when the few negative people attack. Let's just show that we're better than that by not answering hate with hate. Maybe do this again in a few weeks when the ride is over if you have questions about returning to normal. My client will be answering no further questions. NEW EDIT: This post is about to be locked, but questions are still coming in. I made a new AMA to keep this going. [You can find it here!](https://redd.it/63posi)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thanks for the support folks</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 18:13:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love seeing all the pictures of the folks I got to meet through all this craziness!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me as the official ObiWan Kenboni</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-01 04:24:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My interview with Washington University TV</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-08 20:08:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm Ken bone. Roast me. You know you want to.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 04:50:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Internet's greatest hits!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-04 22:21:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Great gift from my Santa!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-20 02:01:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>My secret Santa have me exactly what I asked for; a donation to the Saint Patrick Center! They are a wonderful organization that puts homeless people into stable and permanent homes. If you want to help them out this holiday season, or any time, go to stpatrickcenter.org Thanks to all toy Santas for making the season brighter! Ken Bone out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I am Ken Bone, a Dank Meme in human form. AMA</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 23:45:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am one of 2016's dankest memes come to life! The fat guy in the red sweater from the presidential debate. I'm here to answer all your questions with very few exceptions. The only questions I will purposely ignore are listed here in the FAQ: Did you get to hang out with Snoop Dogg? - No. I wish I had, but we couldn't work out the scheduling. Also I can't afford to get fired over a drug test. Did you get rich from being a meme? - No, but I did make a little over a year's worth of my regular salary. That was awesome. What's it like being a dead meme? - The meme may be dead, but Ken Bone lives on baby! And finally, PAY SPECIAL ATTENTION TO THIS ONE!! Who did you vote for? - I voted, but I'm not telling anyone who I voted for. IF YOU ASK ME WHO I VOTED FOR I WILL BAN YOU! I'm a mod, and I'm not afraid to abuse my power. It makes me feel special. This AMA will run as long as questions come in. I'll be here live for a few hours and will continue answering after that for as long as you want. [Proof](http://imgur.com/a/iAJaC)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's past time we choose the best of 2016</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 10:02:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>In a lot of ways 2016 was a tough year, but here at Uplifting News we're all about sifting through the hard times to find those stories that can inspire us, and remind us that hope can be found in the dark. With this in mind I am challenging all of us to dig through the year that was and put all the best and most uplifting stories of the year in one place. I've never run anything like this, so bear with me. It's going to work like this. Submit the most uplifting story you can find from 2016 in one of the following 10 categories: 1) Youth - Young people (under 25) doing something positive or uplifting. The main focus of the story must be a person under 25. 2) Energy - Near and dear to me. Find a story about energy that gives us hope for the future amid all the chaos that is the climate change debate. 3) Politics - This one is set to hard mode. Find a story about something in the realm of politics (does not have to be in the USA) that shows us that not all politicians are evil, at least not all the time. Story must focus on the actions of an elected official. 4) Charity - A true feel good subject. Help us find the top story about charity. This can focus on a little known charity, a fundraising effort, basically anything to do with a charitable organization. 5) Bittersweet - The stories that are tough to read can be the most important. Show us the best story of the good coming from something bed. The ending doesn't have to be happy, but the net result of the story should be positive. 6) Homelessness - This one is my personal passion. Share a story of a homeless person overcoming their situation, or a person helping the homeless community. 7) Community Outreach - There's a lot of overlap here. This could be a person or a group doing something to help improve their home community. This does not include things like Doctors Without Borders (though they are awesome), this category is for people doing good where they live. 8) Celebrity - A story of someone in the public eye who uses their position to help others. Please note: I do not count as a celebrity. Stories about me cannot win this or any other category (but they do make me feel warm and fuzzy) I hope that didn't sound vain, I just don't want you to think I'm baiting you into telling me I'm awesome. 9) Disaster relief - Tough times have hit all over the globe from natural disasters to man made crises. Show us people making a difference in areas hit by catastrophe. 10) Animals - This could be actions by an animal, or people helping animals. Who doesn't love animals? Sociopaths, that's who. There are plenty of stories that satisfy more than one category. A story may be submitted to several, but can only win one category. I will determine the winners for each category, then you will all choose one overall winner from those 10. The submitter of each of these 10 winners will get some shiny gold! To be clear, the winning submitters are the ones that submit to this post, not necessarily the original submitter from when the story was new. I will do my best to remove duplicate entries and only keep the first. Please remember that if I screw it up I'm not trying to single you out. Stuff just happens. Remember to follow Rule #1. Submit an entry by providing a link as a top level comment on this post. Include in the comment which category you are submitting the story for. You can also plead your case there if you want. Entries that do not mention a category will not be considered. These stories can be any story. It may have been seen on this sub before, it may not. Remember that no matter who gets picked the real winner is all of us. I'm hoping this contest will serve to catapult (or trebuchet) us into 2017 with some good vibes in the tank. The deadline for entries will be midnight central time (because that's where I live and I suck at converting the time) on Sunday, January 29th. I hope to announce the winners the next day, but if there are a lot of entries it may take a bit more time. I'll set up the post to pick the overall winner when the category winners are announced. Good luck to everyone!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ken Bone (me) doing a standup comedy set in Chicago. Be gentle. It's my first.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:47:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The winners of the best of 2016 have been chosen. Help us pick the overall winner!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-01 22:36:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>There were a lot of good entries into this year's best of contest. Thanks very much to everyone who participated. The category winners are listed below. To pick the overall winner I'm gonna keep it really simple. The categories were numbered, so I'm just gonna reply to my own post here with those numbers. Upvote your favorite one. The one at the top a week from now is the champ. Thanks again, and a special thanks to the rest of the mod team for letting me be a part of their community. I really like it here, even if I do have to swing the old ban hammer occasionally (a lot). Winners 1  #8211; Youth u/Meg-a-nerd Youth: Kids write letters to Trump asking him to be a nice president. I know it sounds a bit cynical but I thought it was a really sweet way of helping kids to learn to react with kindness and hope instead of dwelling on the scary things that might happen.https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/inspired-life/wp/2016/11/17/do-not-say-mean-things-kids-are-writing-to-donald-trump-asking-him-to-be-a-kind-president/?utm_term=.3fb01fe703a7 2  #8211; Energy u/Loccolibroccolli Energy: More jobs now in solar energy than Oil, Gas and Coal extraction/mining combined https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2016-05-25/clean-energy-jobs-surpass-oil-drilling-for-first-time-in-u-s 3  #8211; Politics u/GenesisEra Anyway, Aung San Suu Kyi becoming President of Burma/Myanmar in a free, fair election is promising for her country's continued democratisation and welcome back to the international community, as well as hopes for the average Burmese citizen. https://www.google.com/url?sa=t amp;rct=j amp;q= amp;esrc=s amp;source=web amp;cd=2 amp;cad=rja amp;uact=8 amp;ved=0ahUKEwiD_4TS5u_RAhUJ9mMKHWFcCEIQFggdMAE amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bbc.com%2Fnews%2Fworld-asia-33547036 amp;usg=AFQjCNGOiiYjknyKXIh8pBZPIHdTTpHLdQ 5  #8211; Bittersweet u/Miniblitz Bittersweet- the entire world of football (soccer) coming together after the Chapecoense tragedy where the plane carrying the ACF players to the biggest match in their history crashed on its way to Columbia for the first leg of the Copa Sudamericana final, killing 71 people. Many players paid their tributes, and many matches held a minute of silence, including arguably the largest rivalry in the game, El Classico between FC Barcelona and Real Madrid of Spain https://www.google.com/url?sa=t amp;rct=j amp;q= amp;esrc=s amp;source=web amp;cd=8 amp;cad=rja amp;uact=8 amp;ved=0ahUKEwig3Lqf5-_RAhVMzmMKHUcFBj0QFgg_MAc amp;url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.foxsports.com%2Fsoccer%2Fstory%2Fwatch-chapecoense-score-first-goal-win-video-highlights-brazil-soccer-013017 amp;usg=AFQjCNEzrK_PpfuveIasxCwUT-5w1fXcfg amp;bvm=bv.146073913,d.amc 6  #8211; Homelessness u/turqua I nominate the stray dogs of Istanbul receiving blankets by amazing volunteers for category 10. subject6946 note: Reclassified as category 6 due to lack of entries. The dogs are homeless. It #8217;s a stretch, I know. 7  #8211; Community Outreach u/Dextero_Explosion I guess I'm going to submit this one as category 7, community outreach; I think it probably fits better there than homelessness or youth. I nominate the story of the Philly frat feeding feeding the homeless at Thanksgiving. It's easy for some to forget that the homeless are people. It's inspiring and uplifting to see young people making a difference in people's lives. http://www.nbcphiladelphia.com/news/local/100-Homeless-People-in-Center-City-Get-Thanksgiving-Dinner_Philadelphia-402807786.html 10  #8211; Animals u/Meg-a-nerd Animals: Pandas and Manatees are no longer endangered. http://www.worldwildlife.org/stories/giant-panda-no-longer-endangeredhttps://www.fws.gov/news/ShowNews.cfm?_ID=35428 Since everyone wanted to make their own comments I guess I'll count them by hand. It'll be the number of upvotes on my original comments, plus the number of separate votes. I'll remove the comments as I count them to ensure they only count once each. CONTEST ENDS SUNDAY NIGHT AT MIDNIGHT CENTRAL (US) TIME! EDIT: Locked. Tabulating results. I'll remove vote comments as they are counted to ensure that I don't count them twice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>IamA Still Ken Bone, the guy in the red sweater. AMA!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 02:44:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>The original AMA is about to get locked and the questions are still coming in. Since you still have questions, I still have answers. AMA about life, politics, sweaters, the perils and joys of memehood, or whatever you want. I'll go ahead and answer the first question for you. I'm not telling you who I voted for. [Proof here](https://imgur.com/gallery/pnOef) [The original AMA here](https://redd.it/57dw9a)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Loved Post's version so much I had to do my own.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 01:46:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 19:49:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nothing racist, that's for sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 19:49:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>AMA #2 is still going for another week or two. Interest has trailed off so I don't think we'll need a #3.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 21:49:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Environmentalism and animal rights were not contributing factors to the Nazi government's ability to round up Jews. Gun confiscation was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 22:19:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe not politicians, but it would deter the hell out of the soldiers. That's one of the great things about our all volunteer armed forces. It's hard enough to get Bobby from down the street to act against his own countrymen, but when those countrymen are packing serious hardware Bobby is probably going to tell his superiors where they can stick it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 22:20:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rights are not given by the government. We are born with them. Endowed with them by our creator as it were. They are supposed to be protected by the government.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 22:21:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>But they did have the vast majority of industrial strength, telegraph lines, and railroads.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 22:28:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm very much on your side, but I think an educated populace should take the #1 spot with having them armed a close second. Educated voters can defend against "tyranny creep" where our rights get taken a bit at a time. Our weapons stop them seizing our rights all at once.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 22:32:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I also have guns the government doesn't know about, because there is no centralized gun registry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 22:38:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the same reason you can't have a browning machine gun. Because it's banned. There are some that would make the argument that we should be allowed to purchase ANY weapon that the government has access to. I don't agree, mostly because I can't afford an F-22 fighter jet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 22:46:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the beauty of the all volunteer citizen military. It's pretty tough to get your cousin Dave to turn his weapons on Jimmy from down the street.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 22:47:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nobody gave me my rights. I was born with them. The government is supposed to help me protect them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 22:50:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Iraqis had Nerf Guns? My AR might not be a predator drone, but you still wouldn't want to stand in front of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 22:53:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I eat a banana I do it because they are tasty. They also have the benefit of being full of potassium. Potassium is not my primary motivation for eating the banana, but it is there regardless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 22:54:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Neat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 23:08:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bananas are not silly, sir. They are both delicious and packed with essential nutrients.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 23:09:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's where the guns come in. When the government refuses to acknowledge the democratically legitimate will of the people they must be made to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 23:17:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wanna bet?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 01:30:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Remember to delete this if you ever get accidentally famous.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 05:01:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>A black banana with a pistol grip would be considered an assault banana and therefore illegal in New York and California.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 06:45:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for coming to the sub looking to learn. The more you know about guns the safer you can be with or around them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 06:52:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't realize Ariel Winter came to this sub. Welcome, I'm a big fan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 18:47:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha! Mega celebrity. That's a new one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 18:47:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love shooting. I should do a collection post one day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 18:27:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure they are. There's only a few thousand of them in the whole country.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 23:52:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. You are in the minority of people who understand what undecided means to pollsters. I simply cannot convince people that I wasn't some moron who was completely in the center of two vastly different choices.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 23:53:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really? Because if anything I was hinting the other way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 05:53:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not universally. Go check out what r/politics has to say about me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 16:31:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Runs into Amy next to the copier* Oh my God! Can I get my picture with you?! You're like, my favorite! You were great in that Baywatch movie. *Amy runs away screaming to HR* Guys, I think I did it wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 16:33:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>The sketch is a better actress.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 19:17:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sadly there were wars before 1940.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 19:38:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>My character has a red shirt and a mustache. He's a loose interpretation of a former minor celebrity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 20:42:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey! I will not have you speaking ill of my fallen meme comrade like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 20:44:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>True. I just wish we had used a better Italian.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 21:26:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then I must be a better moderator than I thought I was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 21:31:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see where you're going, but he didn't think it was unknown. He thought he had a shortcut to the Indies. He only thought this because he grossly miscalculated the circumference of the Earth. He didn't think there was anything there but water.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 22:28:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>S N O O P B O Y E is best B O Y E. 10/10 would watch Scooby Doo with Snoop and Little Snoop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 12:42:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. Hi.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 12:42:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 17:29:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, I appreciate that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 17:36:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>When most people pine for the "good old days" they are only thinking of the good parts. Huge economic growth, rapid increase of the standard of living, and a single income family being perfectly sufficient to fund a comfortable middle class lifestyle. They leave out the bad parts, and also seem to forget that those days were only really good to a specific class of people. I like to give folks the benefit of the doubt and assume that they are wishing for the good parts only, and that they want the good parts spread more equally among all people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 17:47:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>The polling agency asks how likely you are to change your mind on who to vote for on a scale of 0 to 10. Undecided actually meant that you were equal to or greater than 3. It may have been 2, I don't 100% recall. With, 0 meaning no chance, and 10 meaning it's a coin flip. At this point in the survey they have not mentioned the debate at all, and you do not know that you are being screened as a potential participant. Everyone on the stage that I talked to had made up their mind for the most part, but were willing to change their minds if new information came out about one of the candidates.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 21:14:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>The point is that the 41.6 million per year quoted in the sign is spent by the same agency, on the same population. The viagra is for service members since it is covered by their health plan. The birth control is the same.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 21:15:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>A guy I worked with had a respiratory infection. The VA hospital gave him Advil. After waiting 6 weeks to see the doctor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 21:37:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know. I'm not a doctor, but telling him to suck it up and give him over the counter pain meds was probably the wrong option given that he now has diminished lung capacity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 21:47:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>TBF that may have been what they gave him. This was years ago I might have the brand wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 20:30:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll grant you that, but Fleming didn't go on to murder or enslave thousands of people after his discovery.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 23:53:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>He was talking to your mom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 06:31:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>It got my attention.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 06:45:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>May the road rise to meet you both!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 06:50:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>A good meme never really dies as long as it's remembered.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 07:07:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Drunken spin hook kick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 22:01:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 22:01:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 22:06:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eating lunch with my wife. Then we're going to the new Jackie Chan movie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 02:37:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Such a movie would be amazing. Especially if it starred Tim Allen as the egotistical lead with acclaimed character actor Alan Rickman in a supporting role.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 14:36:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is one of the most random and contentious threads I've ever been summoned to. Fuckwad. That does have a nice ring to it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 14:37:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who should play me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 14:43:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get it. Just messing with you. BTW I'm a gun owner who is in favor of slightly tighter gun control. The two things are not mutually exclusive. Keep it up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 17:12:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>If the price is right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 17:13:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell that to the New York Post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 18:43:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>For a second I thought the loop of the gif was a rez forcing you to start over on her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 18:45:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, then it would need to read "greater than 50%." At least means greater than OR equal to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 18:51:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats on getting Gus to give the biggest smile of his life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 19:00:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>MWGA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 05:25:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>You linked my user name but said that you thought I'd abandoned it. Strange. For the record this is my only account and I've made a dozen comments in the last 24 hours.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 05:27:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not as much as you'd think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 19:23:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Statistically there is a better chance that I will be the next President than this crazy thing happening.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 22:11:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright that's 2. Just need about 49,999,998 more. We'll get there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 03:18:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>No he doesn't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 03:18:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who planted me? Do I get paid?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 03:19:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't like Obamacare, I simply acknowledge that it's better than nothing. It needs major improvement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 03:20:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess I might as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 03:22:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's the only one they'll run pictures of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 03:24:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Enlighten me. How was I seeking attention?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 03:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I generally don't like commenting on stories about me. It draws trolls. But since you asked...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 04:05:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I gave them 10% off everything I made, Izod gave them ten grand, and the publicity got them a lot more. I don't know all the numbers from people who donated in my name, but all told with everything I think it was close to thirty thousand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 04:29:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yahoo really loves buying and then ruining media sites. Especially if they are missing a vowel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 05:26:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nothing makes sense if you don't think about it. That's some Jaden Smith level shit right there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 05:48:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know. I'm trolling the troll. You gotta let it play out man. Most don't take the bait though. They're too cowardly to respond even when it's anonymous once you confront them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 05:51:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Toppo goes all out on hand day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 12:49:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. Hi.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 15:56:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gohan. Piccolo sacrifices himself for Gohan somehow (again) angering Gohan. Gohan uses his superior intellect to figure out Ultra Instinct and uses his anger to fuel it. He looks like his ultimte mystic form but is surrounded by SS2 arcs of electricity. He has learned from his past overconfident mistakes and gets straight to business. He punches Jiren in the gray alien junk screaming that it is all for his family, and the family in the locket of the erased universe. No matter what actually happens, this is what I will see when I dream about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 16:06:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the same piece of human filth that prompted Aly Raisman to publicly speak out against the way USA gymnastics has failed to protect its athletes. (The doctor is the filth, McKayla is the victim just to be clear)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 21:07:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would you like to advertise on my podcast?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 21:10:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really love that "colon" is in quotation marks here and garden hose is not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 23:35:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Getting duped by an internet troll is not illegal. It's not good, but it's not a crime either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 23:45:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>It accomplishes exactly what "Political Dig" wanted it to accomplish. Traffic to their site. They don't care that the actual content is garbage. They are warming their hands over the dumpster fire that is American political discourse and we're all letting them do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 19:29:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm blown away by how great this is! Right down to the hair style. Special thanks to your mom for spending an additional nine months making the most important part, you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 21:40:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 22:00:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 14:29:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>My man!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 15:38:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have nothing to say, but I wanna shit post anyway. So here it is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 15:41:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's because you don't know me and my wife.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 15:42:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seeing good people like these two be happy makes me all warm and fuzzy like.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 17:52:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 17:53:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's almost like I'm a regular person. The only difference is that I dictated this comment to one of my assistants.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 20:39:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because he's overweight and has a mustache? Not all fat white guys look alike, racist! /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 20:40:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>My pants are also tight, but it's just because I'm too fat for them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 04:25:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did start it. The episodes out so far. Soundcloud.com/thekenboneshow It'll have to really grow before I can get guests that you've actually heard of. It's not like I have a booking agent or a list of people's contact info.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 04:27:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was actually the last game of 2016 on dec 20. I spent the entire third period on the concourse doing photos, but the team gave me the tickets so I didn't mind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 04:28:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Based on the number of trolls and assholes that still ask me this I'm going to say no.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 04:55:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry not 20th, 30th. The last game of the year. I'm very sure of that. I still have the ticket stubs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 17:40:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once or twice. It's usually a misconception about my personality or sexual preferences.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 17:52:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have the look of a guy who can improve any person's day. Also, sweet scarf. You have a really cool look going with the super well kept beard and your style.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 17:53:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>You might not speak the language, but everyone in the world can understand that radiant smile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 17:53:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can honestly say that seeing your bright eyes and infectious smile have improved my morning. I bet you do that for a lot of people without even realizing it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 18:47:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Keep in mind when watching this that when he says "Mr President" he is speaking to the President Pro Tempore of the Senate, not directly to the President of the United States. He is talking about Trump to be sure, but not directly addressing him. This changes very little of the content, but I thought it was important to make that distinction since many people are assuming he is speaking directly to Donald Trump.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 20:03:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>As the proud owner of a 'stache, I salute Lanny's glorious example.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 01:31:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brave</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 01:31:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brave</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 01:33:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Work at the coal fired power plant. Nothing changes. Cities do not run on independent power grids. It's all connected. The power we make gets bought by users in over ten states.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 01:36:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really appreciate that. I'm recording the next episode in a half hour. I'm not kidding when I say that knowing you (and hopefully more people) like the show makes me excited to do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 01:38:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>The same as it's been for months. He's not as bad as the media wants you to think, but he's not good. I don't like what I see. I take it all one issue at a time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 01:38:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. That was a really fun one. They put me in a really sweet hotel in Beverly Hills.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 01:43:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>My only interaction with him was on air. He had to leave immediately for another show. Everyone said he is a good guy, and not just the ones that work for him. I liked him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 03:46:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just happy to be on a list.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 04:44:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Upvoted because Blues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 06:08:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does it, or just gets accused of doing it. All the same to the mob.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 06:10:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now you tell me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 06:35:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sent shivers down my spine, body aching all the time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 09:25:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sitting on the glass for the first time at that game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 18:55:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are only forgiven for the homosexual acts that used to be crimes. There is no removal of actual crimes like burglary.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 18:56:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just the gay stuff that's no longer a crime. Actual crimes would remain.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 18:59:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not, but it was until about thirty five years ago. It was still on the record of a lot of gay men. Now it's not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 21:35:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Heroes get remembered, but legends never die.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Happy Halloween you bunch of drunks!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 02:10:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 14:50:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have never played. I don't even have a PC. Some jerk stole my user name and killed you with it. This is an outrage!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 15:23:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>This makes me so sad. If I was out of work and got offered training to do a new job I'd walk over broken glass to get to that training even if it was CERTAIN that my old job would come back in the future. It would give me a job in the mean time, and I might find out I liked it more than my old job. Especially if my old job involved working underground.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 18:58:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's more arousing than it should be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 19:00:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like I said before, I think it's sad. If you have no work and get offered an avenue to get work you are crazy to turn it down. I don't really see the down side unless you have to give up income to attend the unpaid training. I can at least see the difficulty in that situation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 22:20:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please stop feeding the trolls. Just report them so I can ban them. You are giving this idiot what he wants.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 22:31:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm banned from off my chest for commenting on the_donald. I got summoned to the_donald by username (happens to me a lot) by a troll. I made some snide comment telling him to kiss off, and was instantly banned from about a dozen subs. You can't even participate on t_d to disagree without being labelled a troll.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 23:51:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like I said, I only commented there in response to being called out. Offmychest has not responded to my attempts to get unbanned. And alt accounts are for cowards and trolls.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 00:03:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I should circumvent site wide rules by using an alt to get around a ban? I have no alts. I stand by my words and expect to be judged by what I say, not where I say it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 00:55:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a strange thing to be accused of not being yourself. Rest assured that I am in fact, me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 14:13:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think I can help you there. I was never subscribed to it, and I don't know how a ban affects your ability to alter your subscription. Best bet would be to go to *edit subscriptions* on your list of subs. On the desktop version of the site, click the three lines icon next to the home button, just above the snoovtar to get a list of your subs. Edit option should be on the bottom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 20:45:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, don't worry. he's suspended for five meaningless games at the beginning of next season. Weak.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 04:24:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's cool I guess, but I hope to God nobody has retirement money interested in hopes and dreams. I'm worried that some small investors bought into the hype thinking Tesla would make money at some point in the near term.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 04:30:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see a lot of people citing the success of Amazon in this way. Just keep in mind that this strategy can be very risky. A lot of businesses have gone under by over investing in growth before establishing stability in other areas. It doesn't always work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 14:39:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tesla has so much love in the investment community I think they can survive the growth period. My real concern is that other, smaller businesses might see this as the way to reliably build themselves. I'd hate to see the little guy get hurt trying to copy a giant company with nigh unlimited capitol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 21:18:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am thrilled to have you here! If you were hoping that the rest of government operation would be a bit more streamlined than the immigration process, I might have some bad news for you. Otherwise it's pretty cool here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 23:52:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Movie marketing is the same way. I got paid 10 grand to film a 30 second promo. It took less than an hour to film and it never aired. They set cash on fire and hope a few people will stop to watch it burn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 23:56:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>This troll will not answer you any more. I banned it. Please do not feed trolls.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 23:59:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You picked a good one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 23:59:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Indeed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 03:35:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't feel very good today, but the fact that you pulled through makes me feel better. Thank you for sharing and thanks for sticking around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 03:42:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>This story showed up on one of the subs I mod. If it makes you feel any better I banned everyone who made a sexist comment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 06:02:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know why I have fans but I'm glad you're one of them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 18:46:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's some profound shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 05:30:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah, it'll be super easy to get. To three stars. The other couple hundred shards are available for a buck each in the shop. Nowhere else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 06:54:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fortunately his "bathroom bill" died in committee and never passed. Not for lack of trying by him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 06:58:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Normally I'm ok with these stories getting removed from the sub. I don't like to see the sub clogged up with "first female African American immigrant mayor of some small town" because those stories reinforce the idea that race and gender are important to the overall quality of the person. This story I found noteworthy because her opponent ran his campaign almost completely on hate for her. He refused to debate, wouldn't talk issues, only wanted to attack her personally and she beat him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 21:26:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was lucky. Growing up my school had maps, such as the Iraq.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 01:44:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought she was all black with a light complexion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 16:27:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or do. Whatever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 00:50:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm my own publicist, and I have a mustache! I've never committed sexual misconduct though. Two out of three ain't bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 21:02:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I forgot the last one ended. I didn't get any questions for a few days and didn't restart a new one. I think a year long active AMA is still pretty good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 21:09:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought she came out with this a few months back. I could be wrong, but I was thinking that she came forward and was one of the trailblazers that led to other women being encouraged to do the same.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 01:51:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I still get at least one moron a week asking "wtf, how are you verified?" The answer is simple. People pretended to be me. I provided proof that I am the real me. That's it. I can't make them understand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 06:45:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I made it the main topic of my podcast this week. If all 8 of my listeners call their senators maybe we'll be ok.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 06:53:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>[The Ken Bone Show](http://www.soundcloud.com/thekenboneshow)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 16:42:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I apparently suck at Reddit link formatting. Here it is in plain text Soundcloud.com/thekenboneshow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 16:43:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's already a bone zone podcast that's pretty popular. We decided to keep it simple.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 16:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Keep in mind that the debate was after some crazy news stories about the candidates, but the selection process for the participants was before a lot of that came out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 16:46:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was just the post. I got like forty more for my replies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 16:47:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>My family calls me Kenny. I've always preferred Ken so that's how I introduce myself so friends end up knowing me as Ken.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 16:49:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>We've been getting a few hundred per week. We only crossed a thousand yesterday. I might lean too heavily on the self depricating humour but it's how I keep myself grounded.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 16:49:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really appreciate that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 16:50:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mostly the same as always with occasional random pictures taken with strangers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 16:50:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It'll drop on Sunday evening. Monday at the latest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 17:17:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm afraid when I hear stuff like this. Obama=bad, Trump=good our the other way around is a horrifying way of thinking. I funny think Blunt actually believes that. I think he's just being a political shill. I guess just try to ask very simple, leading questions like "why do you believe that corporations should have the right to charge different prices based on ideologies?" Also emphasize that in today's economy internet access is no longer a privilege. It's a need and should be regulated as a utility just like phone service.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 20:04:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're falling into the classic trap of two party politics. Just because Trump has a big downside does not make his opponent good. There were over 1800 other eligible people running.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 23:03:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>VP is the best. It's super prestigious but you don't really have to do much unless your boss dies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 02:16:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>The years long election season that we subject ourselves to in this country is disgusting. I will not feed into by even guessing with three years to go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 05:22:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember me too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 06:24:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please God no.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 12:43:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only a matter of time before the "all or nothing" argument was made. I guess I can't be pro gun but also accept some regulations. I guess you missed the part where I said I'm not in favour of that law because it won't work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 01:38:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The thing is, the Ken Bone Show is likely to have a lot of opinions based on the experiences and opinions of Ken Bone. I try to see things from many perspectives but ultimately I have my own view. That's what gets on the show.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 04:25:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's just until you get back on your fit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 04:34:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I keep telling you guys I don't want to be president!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 23:23:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just once. Super fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 23:23:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least I'm higher than Joe the Plumber in this stupid thread.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 00:59:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought his set was killer start to finish. A true prodigy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 03:47:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's fun. I like it here. I do not have and will never have an alt account. I'm not afraid to be myself anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 19:08:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I miss you too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 19:08:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 20:09:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not Ryan Reynolds, but I gave you my upvote.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 21:39:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm good. You?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 21:40:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I seem to be famous just for existing. I'm like a lesser Kardashian.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 03:27:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 19:55:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Send me a PM</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 22:33:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You caught me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 22:36:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love the intro as much as I love "poached eggs."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 23:14:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friends call me Ken. So you can call me Ken.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 23:16:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. [http://www.Soundcloud.com/thekenboneshow] We just recorded episode 7 last night.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 01:20:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is on iTunes. Thanks for listening!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 04:50:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You already were.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 05:17:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are indeed worthy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 05:23:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't make memes my friend. I am the meme.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 05:29:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go to r/iama. Sort by top all time. The highest one that isn't Barack Obama is me. The proof is there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 05:30:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're already there. Feel free to send me money anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 05:53:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You already are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 15:03:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>It sure does</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 15:04:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just here to engage with my fellow redditors and have a good time. I'm happy that people enjoy it so much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 16:27:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry that you are dealing with health issues. Things like that will pass. The fact that you are a responsible, clear headed gun owner is forever. Hats off to you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 17:55:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not mad at you. I don't want you to be mad at yourself either. This is a tough situation, I won't lie to you, but I know you can handle it. It's clear that you understand that you've made a mistake and that you are ready to start dealing with it. That makes me proud. It also tells me that no matter what happens you're going to be able to make the best of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 18:06:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always liked you too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 08:11:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand your point but I think this is different. If her support for the writer was given in an off the cuff way or overheard by a reporter I'd be with you. But this was a prepared statement that she's retracted due to backlash.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 08:56:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>1) No they are not. 2) Even if they were Roy Moore would still be a pedophile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 23:57:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's never been a show that leaned so heavily on gunplay yet displayed such a low level of understanding about it. The A Team was a more realistic combat simulation. I've seen Scwarzenegger reload more often than Carol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 05:34:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>He attac but he also protec</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 13:38:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Occasionally. I only got recognized a couple times last night. I have a beard right now and that really throws people off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 16:55:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I guess.](https://imgur.com/gallery/xw8bf)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 21:03:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excellent muzzle discipline. A lot of people would accidentally point the weapon at a person by waving it around when this happens. She kept it in a safe direction at all times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 22:13:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gerrymandering is a serious issue but does not really come into play in state wide elections. Your district does not matter in a Senate race. The problem here is our broken two party system. The majority in Alabama has the choice between: A) a morally repulsive person who will vote their way on issues or B) a democrat (who seems like an ok guy, I don't know any different) who will vote against their wishes. There's no third party option and the party primary system can't replace Moore at this point. It's a no win for a lot of them. Personally I'd go with the democrat and just hound his office all the time to make him represent his constituents rather than elect a gross pedophile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 22:30:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you ever do decide to give shooting a try make sure to learn about the safe operation and handling of the weapon first. If you choose not to try it out that's cool too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 06:43:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good idea. Aaaaaaand done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 18:56:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Several possibilities here. Unfortunately the most common is this. I don't have my own web site and I never did. A lot of them popped up and ripped people off. The only place where I sold anything was through represent.com If you ordered from there and didn't get it we can try to get you a refund.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 04:41:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have no clue. They handled everything. You can try contacting them. I'll back you up, but I'm not affiliated with the company in any way. Still with a shot I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 17:20:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>A lot of florists do it this way. You tell them what it should say and they either print a card or hand write it themselves all nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 23:08:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for deciding to stay with us. I'm very happy that you were able to get the help you deserve. The world is a better place with you in it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 01:28:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not locking this thing. It's like a bug zapper for anti Semitic trolls. They can't help themselves and then ZAP! Banned.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 02:22:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ban everyone who is an anti-Semitic troll. I don't see how I could have been more clear on that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 02:28:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well in a thread about the holocaust guess which ones we'll get. Now quit being a dick head.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 04:30:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your friend is ripping off Dave Chappelle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 05:32:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, so you want to accuse our soldiers of murder? I'd call that a gross rule one violation. Bye.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 02:26:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last year my Santa gave to my favorite charity on my behalf. I loved it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 02:32:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah, I heard that's what I'm getting this year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 03:52:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>The new Air Bud sequel looks pretty sweet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 05:04:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>You cannot hope to contain the stache.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 22:59:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's for suckers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 02:50:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have their number.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 15:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 16:35:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It does sound kind of like me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 17:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>If that's what investigations into important matters cost then fine, but what makes these things cost so much damn money?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 23:39:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't spend nearly as much time doing interviews. I do pics with random strangers a lot and record my podcast. Otherwise normal. Apparently I still have fans though. Thanks for being one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 23:43:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still seems like a lot I guess. That's ten thousand man hours at the steep rate of five hundred bucks an hour. If they find something or definitively prove there was nothing it'll be worth it. It's only a waste if it's in between.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 00:10:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the one that was a waste. It basically concluded that "we couldn't find anything illegal but the whole situation was odd." That kind of thing fuels conspiracy nuts for years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 03:13:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>While this is totally true it is a separate issue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 02:14:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tears of the Sun is a good one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 03:52:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post has been removed because it shows no evidence of regret. For all we know that lady likes getting Spartan kicked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 16:02:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Serious question, not trying to mock you. When you say submarine telescope, do you mean a periscope or like a special telescope that can be underwater on the deck? I don't know submarines but I think they are neat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 19:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Neat! Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 22:29:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post has been removed due to showing no evidence of regret. You don't know, this kid might like getting bashed in the head.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 23:06:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post has been removed because there is no direct evidence of regret. It was clear that his intention was to run from the beginning. Was he supposed to just stand there?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 23:08:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post has been removed due to containing no direct evidence of regret. You don't know, that might have been what he was trying to do. Maybe he just needed a concrete powered nap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 14:55:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post has been removed. It is a repost of a story from our front page using a different source. See link below for original. https://www.reddit.com/r/UpliftingNews/comments/7hgqep/rapper_meets_80yr_old_words_with_friends_player/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 14:57:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post has been removed. Less people dying is good. No people dying would be uplifting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 14:58:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post has been removed. It is a repost.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 14:59:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post has been removed. It is a repost.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 17:41:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. Since the incident I've decided that we should all stick by our words and learn from them if necessary. Throw away accounts are for trolls and cowards.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 22:30:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://soundcloud.com/thekenboneshow If there's an issue you are really passionate or knowledgeable about we could have you on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 20:17:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>The issue is that you can fuck up a chihuahua in the head real bad and it will never be able to kill your neighbor. A pitbull on the other hand is dangerous if handled improperly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 05:01:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I volunteer as tribute!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 22:08:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please elaborate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 22:08:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. I don't know OP, but we must be friends.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 02:30:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I approve of this cup.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 05:22:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>And I'm not going to tell you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 18:22:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post has been removed. It is a repost. Looks like someone beat you to it by about an hour. Thanks for sharing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 18:23:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post has been removed. It is a repost. Thanks for sharing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 18:25:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post has been removed. It is a repost. Thanks for sharing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 18:28:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most of the bitter part seems to be coming from you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 20:42:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are a small team. When we choose to expand we'll probably announce something. It's not in the plan right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 00:56:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only for big name guests though. Peons like me don't get to practice first.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 00:58:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not always rehearsed for the host. The guest seems rehearsed because they've told the same story or answered the same question dozens of times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 01:39:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been on a few of these and can tell you basically how it goes. One of the producers comes to you while you're getting ready (makeup or whatever) and talks to you about what the host is likely to ask. The host is typically busy during this time and you don't see them directly. Of course if you're there for a specific thing like plugging a movie you are pretty much guaranteed that that's what you'll be asked about. Sometimes the host will decide to ask totally different stuff than what you were prepared for. That probably happens less to big name people who have the clout to refuse to return in the future. It happened to me all the time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 02:23:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like old memes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 02:45:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 13:20:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>About $150k. I was lucky and made a few good deals. There potential to make more if you're willing to compromise your principles, which I was not. You can also make basically nothing if you screw up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 13:21:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check out my podcast if you want to keep up with what I'm up to. Soundcloud.com/thekenboneshow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 05:03:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think six. Maybe seven.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 02:29:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Israel got attacked by a bunch of enemies at once, then beat their ass in only six days, only to be told they couldn't actually keep the territory they won in the course of their legitimate self defense. Seems like a crap deal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 02:34:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>US per capita contribution is nearly 9 times that of China and they are our largest economic competitor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 02:41:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bad behavior does not excuse other bad behavior. They can both be wrong at the same time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 05:30:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>90 out of 100 is 90%. The other 10 didn't vote. It was 90 to 0.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 01:39:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm from the internet and I think your hair looks great!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 01:48:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 06:20:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>You deserve each other. I'm happy for you both. May the road rise to meet you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 06:28:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Former pizza delivery guy. I always start the car and get moving before putting my seat belt on. It saves about three seconds. Over the course of a night it might add up to a minute and land me another run. One extra run could be the difference between making the rent or not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 07:43:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Future Dear Husband or Damn husband if he's in the doghouse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 23:12:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool name.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 16:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so glad that my relevance already ended so I didn't have to see myself on here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-26 18:03:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That head is not worthy to sprout from my sweater.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 06:51:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any picture with that face in it is automatically a good picture.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 21:19:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Justice gets a little disproportionate with the kick to the face after he's down. Yikes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 07:19:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm the other Ken. Ken Bone. Totally different.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 07:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is some sexy ass trigger discipline.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 20:28:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 00:37:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go Northwestern!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 08:01:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>From the start of the video until the guy is shot dead is seven seconds. It's not reasonable to expect a scared random guy to comply with screamed orders from across the street within seven seconds. It *is* reasonable to expect the police to NOT MURDER PEOPLE!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 03:08:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell me about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 05:43:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's very good! I love the art style. It reminds me of late Dragonball or early DBZ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 05:49:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nothing to apologize for. You look quite lovely. I'm a big fan of the cable knit sweater!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 06:07:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post removed. No evidence of regret showing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 06:10:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>6 feet for construction, 4 feet for general industry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 06:12:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree. Not hooking off at 14 feet is stupid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 23:23:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please don't hide that smile. It looks like it could brighten up anyone's day!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 03:38:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know that guy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 03:38:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Send pics of your mom and we'll see.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 07:04:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's because I'm not a coward. Read it all you like. I'll never delete it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 07:04:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. I wish.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 07:05:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>More during the season. I'm mostly over in r/stlouisblues for now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 07:13:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>They have my written permission already. I just don't get any money. They did give me a bunch of free copies of the game though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 07:38:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post removed. No evidence of regret is visible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 08:01:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same to you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 09:07:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>You said the magic word!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 11:36:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your hands look a bit similar. I thought you had two left hands for a second! Congratulations. May the road rise to meet you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 11:42:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Somebody stole the wheels. Rough neighborhood.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 07:57:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sure you are selling yourself short, but regardless of your hotness level people should not be bugging you for nudes. That's not cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 08:02:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for showing us your sweet jacket.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 08:08:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the reason Van Halen had their famous "no brown m amp;ms" rule in their rider. It shows attention to detail. They had a lot of complex and potentially dangerous stage elements and pyrotechnics. If they saw brown m amp;ms left in the bowl they would know that their directions hadn't been followed. Then they would know that everything needed to be checked over again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 21:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is though. The rider includes everything the artist requires from the venue including how the stage must be set up. Most are detailed enough to include electrical requirements, specs on how much weight the stage must be able to bear, and what materials should be used. It's usually a big document and it covers way more than what stuff should be in the dressing room. The event coordinator for the venue is in charge of oversight for the whole thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 08:02:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's obviously wearing a transparent cortosis glove.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 20:00:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>If only there were some other way for police officers to communicate over vast distances. You don't need telepathy when *you got radios mother fucker!*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 09:34:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll say Diana or Lucy. Those names both say "classy but cute" to me and I think that fits you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 09:38:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>My goodness, those eyes! So lovely. Please don't let a bad day set you back. You're doing great and I know you'll continue to do so!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 21:46:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the most inappropriate way my picture has ever been used.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 01:28:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish I could put on such a bright smile while feeling under the weather. Get well soon!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 05:11:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>He committed a felony and in the course of this felony a person died. That's enough to charge him with murder in most jurisdictions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:48:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:48:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:57:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your dorm is lame.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:57:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 18:27:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's if you smoke while sleeping. If you sleep 8 hours it jumps to a cigarette every 8 minutes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 18:59:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am genuinely sad that you got downvoted for this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:06:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hanging with Macklemore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:16:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>The ones I've done the most with are St Patrick's Center for the Homeless, Greater St Louis Honor Flight, and the Megan Meier Foundation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:59:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Use the report button, make my life easier in getting rid of this garbage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 00:12:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not really that fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 12:14:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. Born in Granite City, live in Belleville.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 05:50:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Outranked by a country full of murder-spiders. America has truly reached a new low.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 06:18:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>No one is as bad as the New York Times thinks Trump is. No one is as good as Trump thinks Trump is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 07:01:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL my dad is a top 3 country.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 09:14:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're greater.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 21:12:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Consider yourself noticed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 21:13:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have *a* red sweater, but not the original. I sold it for charity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 07:14:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I showed up the last ten times this question was reposted. I'm sitting this one out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's time to select the best of Uplifting News 2017, and we need your help!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 15:29:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>2017 has come and gone. It wasn #8217;t easy. It wasn #8217;t perfect, but we got through it together. With all the chaos and noise that dominates the news cycles today it is easy to think that the world is doomed. We all seem destined to shout ourselves hoarse about the everyday outrages that have become all too common. But that doesn #8217;t have to be the case. Members of the Uplifting News community know that it #8217;s not all bad. Where others say  #8220;no news is good news, #8221; we say otherwise. Good news is good news and we are here to share it, celebrate it, and use it to remind ourselves that being alive is pretty freaking sweet. With that in mind it #8217;s time to look back on the year that was and pick out the very best of the best. The stories that remind us of the goodness that can be found in bad times, and the bright spots that punctuate dark days. Help us comb through 2017 and find the most uplifting news stories that were. In each of the following 10 categories there were stories that made 2017 a good year for those involved, or at least showed that good can be salvaged even from tough situations. Please search through the news of 2017 and post the stories that best exemplify Uplifting News in these categories. The best stories will earn gold for their submitters, rules and directions can be found at the bottom. 1) Youth - Young people (under 25) doing something positive or uplifting. The main focus of the story must be a person or group of people under 25. 2) Energy - Near and dear to me. Find a story about energy that gives us hope for the future amid all the chaos that is the climate change debate. 3) Politics - This one is set to hard mode. Find a story about something in the realm of politics (does not have to be in the USA) that shows us that not all politicians are evil, at least not all the time. Story must focus on the actions of an elected official. 4) Charity - A true feel good subject. Help us find the top story about charity. This can focus on a little known charity, a fundraising effort, basically anything to do with a charitable organization. 5) Bittersweet - The stories that are tough to read can be the most important. Show us the best story of the good coming from something bad. The ending doesn't have to be happy, but the net result of the story should be positive. 6) Homelessness - This one is my personal passion. Share a story of a homeless person overcoming their situation, or a person helping the homeless community. 7) Community Outreach - There's a lot of overlap here. This could be a person or a group doing something to help improve their home community. This does not include things like Doctors Without Borders (though they are awesome), this category is for people doing good where they live. 8) Celebrity - A story of someone in the public eye who uses their position to help others. This can be through charitable efforts, positive role modeling, or just being an all-around admirable person. 9) Disaster relief - Tough times have hit all over the globe from natural disasters to man-made crises. Show us people making a difference in areas hit by catastrophe. 10) Animals - This could be actions by an animal, or people helping animals. Who doesn't love animals? Sociopaths, that's who. There are plenty of stories that satisfy more than one category. A story may be submitted to several, but can only win one category. The mod team will get together after one week to determine a winner for each category. Your opinions in the comments will weigh heavily on our decision, so please let us know what you think of the submissions. Remember to follow Rule #1. Submit an entry by providing a link as a top level comment on this post. Include in the comment which category you are submitting the story for. You can also plead your case there if you want. Entries that do not mention a category will not be considered. These stories can be any story. It may have been seen on this sub before, it may not. Remember that no matter who gets picked the real winner is all of us. I'm hoping this contest will serve to catapult us into 2018 with some good vibes in the tank. The deadline for entries will be 8:00PM U.S. central time (because that's where I live and I suck at converting the time) on Sunday, January 21st. I #8217;ll lock the post at that time so no more submissions can be made. We #8217;ll announce the winners soon after. There can be up to two winning selections from each category. The submitter of each winner will win shiny gold! Good luck to everyone!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 15:33:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Flaired post as misleading. Thanks for letting us know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 16:11:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then the year wouldn't have been over.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 16:29:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>The most common cause of dandruff is oily scalp, not dry. This leads to buildup against the skin which irritates it. It can also lead to minor yeast or bacterial infections of the skin which causes flaking. The first step is to make extra sure you are rinsing your hair thoroughly after washing. Like really thorough. I'm not saying you aren't rinsing well, I'm saying that you need to rinse like a maniac. Using a soft brush to brush from the roots while in the shower can help. As for remedies stick with the selsun for at least a week. One day is not enough time to judge. Every dandruff shampoo has differences, one may work for you. There are some natural remedies that work great as well. Lemon juice and tea tree oil are both good hair treatments that serve as natural anti fungal and anti bacterial agents. Lemon juice especially can help balance the pH of your scalp and prevent the oil buildup that leads to the flakes. Try two tablespoons of juice directly on the scalp for about 2 minutes while in the shower, then rinse with a dilute mixture of two more tablespoons mixed in a cup of water. Finish the rest of your shower then wash and rinse with dandruff shampoo. One last thing, I know it itches but don't scratch! Scratching irritates the skin further and opens it to further infection making the problem worse. Good luck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 17:58:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good point on the water temp. Needs to be not too cold because it will close your pores, but not too hot because it can damage the skin or denature the helpful proteins in the remedies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 21:46:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 03:15:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't change titles. I'm not spez.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 04:55:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>The democrats are doing the exact opposite of what I think they should be doing. They could be setting up a "big tent" of moderate to center-left politics to catch waves of voters that are going to want to jump off the Trump train. Instead they are moving hard left at the party leadership level. Tons of republicans are now stuck with either Trump, who they don't like very much, or do a 180 on most of their political beliefs. Give them candidates who represent them in a common sense moderate way and they will jump aboard with the dems in huge numbers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 23:03:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are around 1500 electric linemen from the mainland in Puerto Rico helping. Many of them have been there for months. When 80% of the whole transmission grid is destroyed it's going to take a lot of time to fix it safely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 00:07:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sadly these dog nets often trap dolphins by mistake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 22:12:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll happily be the understudy. Maybe I can play a Hutt in the background. Oh ho ho ho.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 02:42:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get the joke, I blame you anyway. The alternative is to blame myself and I'm not ready for that yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 02:42:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>So you can't drink beer when you watch hockey? What's the point of being alive then? Poor bastard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 08:40:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 20:17:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I already have one of the top comments here from 22 hours ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 21:11:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's wrong with the town hall debate?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 01:29:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. Very cool of you to say so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 17:34:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Such is Mango!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 20:18:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's just a phenomenon in statistics that the longer you do something with consistent odds, the closer you will get to the average. You might win a coin flip 20 times in a row, but over time if you keep flipping the coin you'll experience a regression to the mean. Your win rate over a large sample size will get back to around 50/50.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 20:28:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>As of January 17th there have been 39 poison control responses to teenagers eating Tide pods in 2018 according to the New York Times. As I said on my podcast, if you are dumb enough to eat a Tide pod please be sure to swallow the whole thing and die.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 21:06:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Being alone can be really hard. I'm sorry it's so tough on you right now. Please try to remember that you are a worthwhile person no matter who else might be around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 15:53:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a bit harsh I'll admit, but I'm only referring to people who should know better. Little kids and the mentally unwell such as dementia sufferers should be protected from Tide related death.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 01:01:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who disturbs my slumber?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 05:21:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's scarier if they don't enjoy it. Thinking of them as mindless biological machines that kill only because it's what they are designed for is chilling to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 06:05:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a good point. I think my biological machine thing is specific to sharks or bugs. Really alien stuff with black dots for eyes. Lions and bears seem able to have a personality. That makes them scarier to me in a different way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 06:09:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm the meme in the red sweater from the presidential debate. Ken Bone. As for Reddit fame I had the number two AMA of all time. Couldn't quite get number one. Thanks Obama.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 07:26:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was going to reply to your comment, but I died.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 21:20:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>44 #176;F in Rochester today. Good on her for braving the cold for those kids.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 02:36:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Heat wave.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 07:24:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are certainly not ugly. You have a very striking look that is very beautiful. Immature children on those subs just want to see cookie cutter blonde girls striking identical poses. They don't know what beauty is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 07:15:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's allowed cuz it's cool</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 23:15:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>St Louis Blues legend Jaromir Jagr.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 02:15:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whoa there. I'm an American internet personality and I never tossed a woman of a roof.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 07:45:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn right. Blues legends.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 22:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>The m14 has a firing rate of around 700 rounds per minute. That means a 20 round magazine would last 1.7 seconds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 00:03:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 00:05:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. Alt accounts are for cowards and trolls. Also, write a new joke already for Christ's sake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 14:04:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's my name alright.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 14:07:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Guests are given an honorarium of $800. They have the option of having it donated directly to any organization, or receiving the money directly. Travel and lodging are paid for by the show. The hotel they use in Beverly Hills is extremely nice, and flights are first class where available. Source: was on the show.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 17:09:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes it is Ken Bone. Bill was very nice and the crew is top notch. Unfortunately he had to leave before the post show so we didn't get to interact much off air, but I did like him very much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 21:26:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I prefer cycling. Running is very hard on my knees.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 21:40:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd rather be a libertarian, but whatever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 21:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Having no idea what you are talking about or what my responsibilities would be I'll say...sure, why not?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 21:59:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am unwilling to publicly support any bill that I have not thoroughly researched and I don't care about college football. So don;t hold your breath.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:00:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am more than willing to accept the idea that not all libertarians are transphobic a-holes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:17:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I went because they asked me to. They gave me scripted talking points. Peering behind the curtain isn't always fun. Sorry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 23:34:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>The future of energy in our state lies in renewables, but solar and wind cannot be stable and reliable without significant investment into transmission infrastructure. Fossil plants are on a ticking clock, and while they can be part of our portfolio for years to come they cannot support our needs alone. We must invest in thorium based nuclear and renewable energy along with much needed updating of our transmission grid if we are to meet the energy demands of the 21st century in a responsible way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 00:48:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would be honored to carry on the work of the distinguished Murpple.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 00:49:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>The ability to Bone should be enshrined in the constitution.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 00:52:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Inability to debate in the realm of ideas leads to ad hominem attacks such as yours. I prefer to keep this debate respectful and above board. Also your mom is a slut.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 01:11:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, YOU listen. To your mother's moans of ecstasy while I plow her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 02:26:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I said I'd bang her, not that I had grabbed her by the pussy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 02:26:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>God I hope not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 02:29:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>We currently rely heavily on the court system to check the power of executive orders. This is largely because legislatures are typically very slow to respond, owing to the political quagmire they usually find themselves in. I would seek to work in a more non partisan manner to speed up the process of legislation. Compromise is not a dirty word. It is the foundation of fair governance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 02:30:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Already answered.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 02:30:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mutual.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 02:33:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Regions are great because of their people. I will continue the work of generations past in empowering the people to find their own greatness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 02:35:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anywhere I can get chili Mac and a peanut butter shake at 3am after a whiskey bender is A OK in my book. It was my great grandfather's favorite place and it makes me think about him every time I'm there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 02:35:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 02:37:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. For three reasons. 1) I don't have it any more. 2) I'm not a cartoon character. 3) I don't want to overheat while I'm sticking it to this dude's mom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 02:48:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not registered with any party. I do tend to have more libertarian viewpoints. Personal liberty. Smaller government. Accountability.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 02:58:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not 100% sure. Let's ask u/wil</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 02:59:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nani!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 04:36:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't fully understand the question. The obvious response is "what is a football?" Or are you looking for "what is leather?" Or "what is a prolate spheroid?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 04:43:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Except while being tackled.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 19:32:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've had much more contact with Ethan. He has gone out of his way many times to be kind to me and help me out. It's no contest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 21:09:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely nothing wrong with that. If she finds working on the cars hands on to be fulfilling then no one should try to tell her it isn't good enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:24:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Target made me show ID to buy Tide pods yesterday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 17:23:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't realize politics caused earthquakes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 19:27:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't argue with that logic. Riddle me this though, what does US politics have to do with Haitian infrastructure?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 19:28:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>This makes me so happy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 18:21:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have. It's not as exciting as you'd think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 04:55:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/gallery/4VuURiL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 01:09:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems like you haven't forgotten me, and I know your mother hasn't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 01:11:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>They were not born in the US. If they had been they would be citizens. They were brought here by their parents as minors.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 15:04:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good God, man. Out of nowhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 15:06:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>The increase in performance is not worth the money. Besides, your gun is a model 1911 which is too old to be compatible with the 1080Ti.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 03:03:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post has been removed. Reaction to pain is not evidence of regret per the rules.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 06:51:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>80% of the entire grid was destroyed. I'm shocked they were able to fix it this fast.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 06:53:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. That's why they have to refer to them as customers. They don't know if a house holds a family of ten or a single person, and businesses have no people living in them at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 07:47:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not on that scale we can't. Not yet. We're working on it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 08:00:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Adding an additional power disconnect switch to lock out in a convenient spot is a hell of a lot cheaper than a workers comp claim.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 16:26:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is no failure here. Congratulations on completing one of the most difficult feats in sport. With determination and data tracking like this it is only a matter of time before you achieve a new PB.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 17:34:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>The one? I've banned a dozen people for this same joke in the last five minutes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 21:03:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blues Traveler was a popular act featuring harmonica solos in many songs in the 90s. Really upbeat and catchy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 13:18:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aren't you sweet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 20:36:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Should be golfing today. This is nuts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 20:37:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds good to me. Been meaning to get to a game with the wife.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 20:47:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tickets bought. 329 row L seats 20 and 21. Come say hi! Watch me get drunk!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 20:47:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 20:48:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tickets bought</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 06:03:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate him leading his songs with those instructions. In English it means "press the skip button."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 06:40:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>A Steve Jobs type guy invents a totally immersive VR world called "the oasis." Human culture is redefined by the oasis. Kids go to school in it, people work in it, economies become based on it. It's more real than the real world to many. When he dies his will outlines an Easter egg hunt" top search for some very well hidden items he had placed in the VR world. The clues to find the items are based on his obsessions with gaming and 80s pop culture. The first person to find all the items becomes his sole heir, inheriting billions of dollars and a controlling interest in the oasis. The story follows Wade, a high school student trying to find the items and outlines his friendships and struggles with his competitors as well as the efforts of a dangerous corporation to get the items first and take control of the oasis for itself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 04:04:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Captain Americow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 00:43:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you take all the tax deductions you can? I do. So does everybody. If she didn't break the law then no problem. Governments are awful at handling money. I'd much rather see everyone pay the least they legally can and give some of what they save to charity. Pay extra taxes if you want. You'll be in a pretty small club.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 01:01:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try to get your reps to change the law then. She paid the taxes she was legally required to pay. You want to pay more that's cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 01:40:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do want them to pay their taxes. She did pay her taxes. Pass more taxes if you want her to pay more. She did what everyone should do, pay her taxes. She then went further than that and gave a bunch of money to charity. The government is a crappy charity. No one gives them extra if they can help it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 03:51:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not missing it. I don't agree that it is immoral to pay the smallest amount in taxes that you are allowed under the law. I think it's smart.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 04:19:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't have different standards of morality for myself than I do for anyone else. Has she ever stated that she believes it is immoral to pay less in taxes? If not then there is no difference.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 04:51:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perhaps Ms. Watson feels as I do that the government is not the highest moral authority, neither is it the highest force for good. Therefore she is using her discretionary funds to aid what she believes to be a higher force for societal good than government. It is neither immoral nor hypocritical. Your argument implies to me that you believe all charitable contributions should go to the government do that they can administer everything. I could not disagree with that more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 05:44:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am not trying to put words in your mouth. I am genuinely confused as to what you're getting at. You seem to be saying that she should voluntarily give the government extra money. I contend that almost no-one would do that. Most people who want to find social causes beyond those funded through taxes do so through charitable giving. If you agree that charitable giving does not need to involve government, and that she is not breaking any laws, why should she pay more to the government at the expense of charity?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 06:10:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have persuaded me to say nice things about you. You are indeed a great debater. Good job and the very best of luck to you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 06:46:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've never seen one. I guess they only play on Fox News and the like. They do a terrible job reaching out to spread a pro gun message. They only seem to preach to their own choir.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 03:10:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not giving them a whole day. Half an hour. My final offer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 21:24:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will never not upvote Jay Sherman. Vive Jay Sherman, Vive Quebec!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 03:01:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Take it as a positive. There are so many women running that statistically some of them are terrible candidates.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 03:37:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can't gerrymander the Senate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 05:04:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which is precisely what the Senate was intended to do. I have no problem there, but factor in the electoral college as well and it does go a bit too far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 02:55:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whatever. Blues legend Wayne Gretzky alongside other such Blues legends as Martin Brodeur.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 04:02:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Batman gave him that black eye earlier in the episode. Dude learned his lesson.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 04:16:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was here before anyone cared and I'll be here long after.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 04:48:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Been there, my friend. The fact that you think enough of yourself to reach out for a little support makes me feel proud of you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 04:54:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>A couple of fly away hairs just means you were strong enough to survive a tough day. Each one a badge of honor! Keep it up!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 05:05:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>No candidate won a majority. A solid majority voted against every candidate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 05:08:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fat pride? I'm pretty fat. My fatness is not a source of pride. It's just something that I accept. In fact I work toward changing it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 05:16:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Touch #233;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 05:30:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not taking anything away from the victims of these tragedies, I want that to be clear. I know this is a highly emotional issue and as a father I understand feeling this way. That said, your children are statistically in much more danger of being killed in a car accident on the way to school than they are of being murdered at school.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 05:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Number 1 at women's ice hockey.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 14:49:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 16:09:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have seen this phenomenon first hand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 17:01:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really appreciate you listening. Tell all your friends! New episodes in a couple of weeks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 22:28:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Removed. Recent repost. Thank you for sharing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 22:32:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I spent 2 hours yesterday removing hateful comments from the thread. It may have ended up getting removed entirely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 23:22:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know, I didn't do it. Good idea on the lock though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 23:22:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 23:27:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>The dude loves his daughter and thinks she is the greatest. What dad wouldn't?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 23:27:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. It's barely a witty burn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 00:11:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uh, yeah. I think my kid is the greatest. He didn't win the "best kid in the world" contest though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 02:09:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. I never amounted to anything. You got me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 02:16:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>The first post got removed by the auto moderator due to a high number of reports. Trolls do that. The time between removing your post and reinstating the other one was about 15 minutes. That wasn't good enough for you. Therefore you respond with  gt;Why? Just lock the thread. That's why the functionality is there.  gt;EDIT: This goofy ass dude just locked this thread and didn't undelete the original and lock that one. Amazing mods we've got here at /r/UpliftingNews. Mods volunteer their time. We wade through hundreds of troll posts trying to keep subs like uplifting news as free of hatred and bigotry as we can. It takes time. In addition we have to deal with entitled, butt hurt dickheads who can't stand having the rules enforced and demand that everything happen the way they want it right now. Throw your little fit and stamp your little feet all you like, it changes nothing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 16:34:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that a rule in this sub?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 16:50:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>To add a bit to this. Imagine it's Christmas time. You walk by one of those bell ringing Santas. You have $3.27 in your pocket. You drop the change and a dollar bill in the kettle. What's the likely response from the bell ringer? Is it: A) Thanks, merry Christmas Or B) Fuck you! I know you could afford to give more you piece of shit! Where's my other $2!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 17:05:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not attacking you and I fully agree that it is not your responsibility to fix others at your expense. I am however a bit confused because I can only see two alternatives to doing the fixing. 1) Probably the preferred method, don't attack yourself to people who need fixing or 2) Be stuck with a profoundly flawed person who will not change. Again, not trying to be confrontational. My perspective here may be far too narrow. It just seems if you're with a flawed person it would be better to either leave or try to improve them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 19:48:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like I said, I don't want a confrontation. I want to learn about the problem. I can't experience it from your perspective. I can only ask you to help me understand. If you don't want to that's fine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 19:49:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like the charity still got five bucks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 20:26:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nani?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 23:19:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depends. Is your mom knocked up? I guess either way I could make it work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 23:42:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>It just gets a little old having to deal with the same cynical comments every time there's an article about a charitable donation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 23:43:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do all my moderating outside.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 00:07:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats on the "win"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 02:55:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't you worry. The ban hammer is polished and ready for action.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 17:40:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Been a fan since RvB season 2.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 19:29:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Needs some aggressive Bone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 19:40:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>That last 15 seconds perfectly captured the spirit of this team</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 19:41:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hear Seattle wants a team. Give them this roster and let us do an expansion draft</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 16:25:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>My AMA ran for 6 months. Answered a question the very last day before it was locked. Take that, Matisyahu.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 03:07:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was in the best shape of my life when I posed for this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 13:31:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. Hi.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 05:48:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Removed because it didn't fit the uplifting news vibe. Upvoted because it wasn't mean and it made me giggle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 03:55:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>We lack the ability to transmit that power from the sunny places to where we use it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 15:05:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's so difficult because their whole power distribution system was destroyed. They are basically having to build a new one. I'm glad they were able to make this much progress already. Electricity is being restored as fast as it can safely be done. Medicine, food, and water on the other hand should be distributed much more efficiently. Those relief efforts were royally screwed up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 15:51:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>The supplies and distribution aspect has been shameful and there's plenty of blame to go around. I wish we focused more on that than the electricity. Power is the one thing that's getting fixed at a reasonable rate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 02:48:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish I had a bad ass range in my yard like him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 05:33:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 15:55:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Removed. Someone beat you to it by two hours.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 20:03:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>That will be Google's defense and is unlikely to be publicly available until it is presented in court. They don't have to show their hand yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 23:56:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's no such thing as leagues, and if there were you would be in the majors.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 01:18:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's the most realistic magic eye picture I've ever seen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 18:49:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>We don't normally do animation live. It's a terrible strain on the animators wrists.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 06:09:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Saiyan giant monkey form. It's as good an explanation as any.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 02:01:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have a friend here buddy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 21:30:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 01:36:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 23:46:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brockton, Ogdenville, and North Haverbrook. Monorail, monorail, monorail...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 02:09:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn! I had Brockway typed out and changed it because it didn't look right. Live and learn I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 02:09:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry mom, the mob has spoken.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 02:13:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wanch to be smooshed?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 03:41:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>RID Magnus is an awesome display piece. Perfect scale with so many other figures, looks great with them loaded in carrier mode. I always have him on my shelf.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 18:33:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>But I am.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 18:33:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 18:34:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>No I didn't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 18:36:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>The best joke I ever stole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 18:37:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don't say...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 18:38:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. Recording the next episode tonight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 18:38:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only because I work up a sweat railing your mom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 18:39:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 21:02:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Soundcloud.com/thekenboneshow. Also on YouTube, itunes, google play. Search "The Ken Bone Show" Thanks for asking!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 21:03:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>We were picking up momentum. Didn't want to wait too long.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 21:04:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds fun. I'm available if needed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 23:53:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 00:09:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>This plant is in the town where I was born. The town was dying without those jobs, glad to see them coming back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 15:44:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Removed. No evidence of regret. No reaction at all in fact.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 15:50:38</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;A fail is not a regret. Some ripper eating a swellbow while trying to bone a rail on the backside, (that's skater lingo for a bad crash. I looked it up (made it up)), isn't regret. There should be a look of surprise, and an expression that clearly says, "Oh no. Oh, God no. I really should not have done that. Why did I do that?" From the sidebar</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 15:51:14</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;A fail is not a regret. Some ripper eating a swellbow while trying to bone a rail on the backside, (that's skater lingo for a bad crash. I looked it up (made it up)), isn't regret. There should be a look of surprise, and an expression that clearly says, "Oh no. Oh, God no. I really should not have done that. Why did I do that?" According to the rules of the sub you do. Otherwise this is just one of the million fail video subs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 15:57:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's on the sidebar. It's the rules and guidelines for posting. Yes I'm serious. This is a niche sub for very specific types of content. That video does not fit the requirements.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 05:30:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a different skill set. I'm a reasonably capable public speaker and I never get nervous in front of crowds, but I'm a lousy actor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 05:14:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Miranda Cosgrove? We don't get too many TV stars here. Glad you're here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 05:16:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Buddy, I don't know you. I've never met you. In fact I only know one thing about you. That is that your life has value. It's worth living. I'm rooting for you man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 05:54:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Happens all the time. Doesn't matter to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 05:57:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>We've had presidents that had native Americans exterminated or forcibly sterilized. Trump can be bad without being the worst. Hyperbole helps no one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 06:17:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 22:56:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>When elected we will also make the "fall back" on Sunday nights to get an extra hour sleep for Monday morning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 23:13:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>All are welcome in the zone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 23:15:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, but I have a podcast. Search itunes, youtube, or soundcloud for The Ken Bone Show. Soundcloud.com/thekenboneshow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 23:40:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll look into it, thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 23:58:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stable too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 00:00:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Renaissance artist martial art practitioner rocks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 05:40:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 16:23:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Woohoo! We're not the worst!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 03:46:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mawp...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 23:08:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Removed. No evidence of regret.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 23:06:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm 35 and have been married for 14 years to my favorite person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 02:51:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks btw. Most people think I am much older. Probably because I am fat and bald.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 02:55:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this post old enough for the F listers to come in? If not I can come back later.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 03:42:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty sure it's not me, but thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 14:21:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Google it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 01:21:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/upliftingnews We try to keep it good there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 21:22:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>This kind of tragedy crosses fan bases and loyalties. We all mourn the loss of little Axel. [raps stick on boards]</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 12:40:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Removed. No evident regret. From the sidebar:  gt;A fail is not a regret. Some ripper eating a swellbow while trying to bone a rail on the backside, (that's skater lingo for a bad crash. I looked it up (made it up)), isn't regret. There should be a look of surprise, and an expression that clearly says, "Oh no. Oh, God no. I really should not have done that. Why did I do that?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 12:44:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Removed. No evident regret.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 22:01:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would get him disbarred. Defense attorneys have to defend their clients to the best of their ability, even if they know the client to be guilty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 01:55:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why would you think that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 01:57:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>NOT racist. You got that from the source.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 01:57:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me neither</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 01:58:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Submarines</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 01:58:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could have been worse</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 02:02:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 03:14:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everybody makes mistakes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 03:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure I'd go that far, but thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 18:50:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I honestly see no difference between Oliver's behavior here and any run of the mill internet troll. Messing with people "for the lulz" is one of the lowest forms of comedy. He is capable of better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 19:13:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mike Pence did not write this book. Oliver is "just fucking with him" via his daughter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 20:01:16</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Dad Jokes and Lame Puns contaminate shitty science. We reserve the right to remove all Dad Jokes and throw them in the pile of hazardous waste behind our laboratory. Top rule of the scientific community.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 06:38:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly all the legalese confuses me until I can't tell which way it is supposed to read, but your interpretation seems to be right. Sucks. I was really hoping I was reading it wrong and it wasn't so bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 23:32:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>No real problems recently. I still keep busy traveling, talking to fans, doing my podcast, but nothing like it was. Thanks for remembering me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 00:03:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just starting out actually. You can see the first episode of season 2 on my YouTube channel. YouTube.com/thekenbonezone My pc just died, so we are in a short break while I fix it. We'll be back next week. We talk news and politics a lot but try to keep it light. It'll be available on most podcast apps and sites soon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 01:50:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel I would also be qualified for such a professorship.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 03:27:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry you're not happy with your appearance. If it helps I am exceptionally happy with your appearance. It's lovely!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 14:02:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then you are indeed fortunate. We try to keep it pretty strict in this sub. Use the report button liberally to help us out. We really appreciate it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 14:10:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Working on cleaning up the comments. This post came in the middle of the night for the mod team, sorry it got out of hand before we got to it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 14:13:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. Bar / bat mitzvah is automatic when you come of age regardless of whether the ceremony is done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 17:28:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Saw this reply in my inbox with no context. Was very confused for a minute.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 17:57:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got mentioned on The_Donald by username, saw it in my inbox and replied. Having a comment on T_D, even a simple reply to being summoned by name was enough to get me banned from offmychest and about a dozen other subs. Banning users for commenting on other subs is a violation of site wide rules, but the admins never seem to enforce it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 17:58:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am really glad that you exist. Please continue to do so. You look like you'd be fun to be around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 23:12:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post removed. It is a repost and blog spot is not a news source.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 04:53:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't you fucking apologize!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 04:55:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why would I spend all that effort removing a bunch of anti-Semitic garbage just to repeat it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 05:09:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Loved listening to Panger try to politely comment on Schenn taking a shot to the cock.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 17:26:59</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Farewell, Master Holbytla!' he said. 'My body is broken. I go to my fathers. And even in their mighty company I shall not now be ashamed. I felled the black serpent. A grim morn, and a glad day, and a golden sunset.' From Return of the King. King Theoden defeated the 'black serpent,' the greatest warrior of the Haradrim before being fatally wounded by the Witch King. This line is spoken to the hobbit Merry as the King is dying. Theoden had struggled with the idea that he was 'the lesser son of greater sires.' That he was unworthy of his mantle of king and his deeds in life did not measure up to the glory of his ancestors. Here he finds peace after helping to save the city of Minas Tirith through his great victory and sacrifice. His last words were to Merry, who he had great fondness for. He expressed his finding of peace and accomplishment. His final thoughts were of his family and his people, wanting the best for all of them and proving that he was a great king in his heart. They were also tinged with a bitter sadness at parting from a life and friends that he had only recently reconnected with. This quote and the next few lines below never fail to affect me. It's the most powerful passage in a trilogy full of amazing language and feeling.  gt;Merry could not speak, but wept anew. 'Forgive me, lord,' he said at last, 'if I broke your command, and yet have done no more in your service than to weep at our parting.'  gt;The old king smiled. 'Grieve not! It is forgiven. Great heart will not be denied. Live now in blessedness; and when you sit in peace with your pipe, think of me! For never now shall I sit with you in Meduseld, as I promised, or listen to your herb-lore.'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 00:39:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's Gnarls Barkley.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 04:40:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a big break. I'd be pissed if that were a Blues goal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 19:08:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually I specifically said I did not vote for Jill Stein.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 19:09:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this where we post the pics of me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 19:52:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're worthy, you're worthy, get up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 21:22:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Between the shirts and some other stuff we raised about $40k for them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 21:22:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 21:23:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. I have refused to say who I voted for. All I ever acknowledged was that I voted for a real candidate, one of the top 3.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 21:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was there. I didn't say that. I said I don't like him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 23:06:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are noticed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 23:07:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trump, Clinton, Johnson</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 23:08:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I said who I voted for it would just be seen as a shameless attempt to get another 15 minutes of fame. I don't want to do that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 01:19:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool. I was getting worried there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 01:26:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/gallery/tjMYX</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 02:07:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 03:15:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 19:42:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have cut off people that were actively making your life worse. It'll take an adjustment period, but soon you'll see that you did the right thing and your life will start getting better every day. Also, you are a gorgeous shade of orange and your dog and human are both adorable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 04:45:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vova busting his stick and leaving it on the ice is exactly how I feel. How many times have we watched an amazing talent waste his best years here before getting fed up and cup chasing elsewhere?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 22:40:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>ok</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>u/subject6946's circle</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 22:41:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 23:52:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>key: iminkenscircle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 03:55:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wanted to see how far it would get. Turns out 12. I don't remove my comments.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 19:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post removed due to being a repost. Someone beat you to it by 3 hours.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 19:51:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I looked at some of your recent comments and it seems like you're a really wonderful young lady. You go out of your way to make others feel better or give them heart felt advice. That's very kind and shows you are a quality person. As for your looks I'm almost speechless. Amazing make up work and such a great smile in your pics.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 04:10:12</DATE>
    <TEXT> #3900;  #12388;  #9685;_ #9685;  #3901; #12388; BLUES TAKE MY ENERGY  #3900;  #12388;  #9685;_ #9685;  #3901; #12388;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 04:30:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>No fair! You changed the outcome by measuring it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 06:53:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>If everyone looked up everything for themselves Reddit would die.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 18:10:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Despair? Absolutely. Shock? Hardly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 06:21:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 07:30:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks man. I didn't even know I was lost.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 17:01:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 19:37:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Submarines. Get it right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 16:35:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've considered it. Until now I wasn't sure if there was any interest at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 23:42:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Totally "we." I absolutely would have banned you if I saw it first. Inciting violence is not allowed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 08:37:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Removed. Regret is not shown.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 03:24:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Girl #1 has a concussion. Girl #2 gets an exploded uterus.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 14:25:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess I should write a book.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 17:15:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had to turn down the dimmer switch in my office to counter act the brightness of that smile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 03:25:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've banned 3 people from r/upliftingnews already for celebrating her death.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 15:41:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let's get the obvious out of the way first. You're gorgeous. You have a striking look. Soulful eyes, amazing bone structure, skin and hair straight from the movies. The real issue here though is your worth. You are beautiful, but that's not what gives you value. Your worth is intrinsic. You have it not because of what you look like, but because of who you are. And who you are is an amazing and captivating woman. You have worth and value that runs far deeper than your skin. The kind words you give to others reflect who you are inside, a kind and loving person who makes the world a better place by being part of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 19:26:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>If your Senator is so distracted by the existence of a nearby baby that they can't carry out their work then you need a new Senator.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 19:45:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's selfish about her trying to continue representing her constituents?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 17:51:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 20:05:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's an amazing and perfectly crafted look for you. I love that instead of the cookie cutter prom dress you found an elegant way to express your individuality while maintaining the formal event aesthetic. 10/10</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 02:26:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>We seem to have no tolerance for anyone doing a good thing unless they are perfect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 15:11:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post removed. No visible evidence of regret shown.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 21:10:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then report them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 02:57:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>No bottle caps at the school unfortunately.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 03:01:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really appreciate everyone's concern. We're working to get Logan back into school as soon as possible. His principal has referred the matter to the local police and will not allow him back to school until an investigation is completed. We are not currently interested in suing our punishing the school, I just want my son allowed back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 03:02:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>The tweet where I originally shared this photo was a direct response to this student. I was trying to encourage him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 03:02:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like you too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 03:03:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>My son is going to shoot up a school because our name is unusual? Fuck you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 03:04:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Foam ear plugs. They have a better NRR than over the ear muffs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 03:20:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>The SCAR is unbearably loud. No way would I shoot it with no ears in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 03:43:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfortunately this decision was made after school let out today. Being that late in the day we haven't been able to do much. The police captain I talked to said he would talk to the principal in the morning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 03:45:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't even get to read OPs comments before they pussed and deleted them. Coward. Oh well. Thanks for the kind words.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 03:46:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 03:46:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's me alright.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 03:48:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really appreciate all the concern and kind words. We're working to get Logan back to school. He's just psyched he's getting at least a 3 day weekend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 03:49:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>The principal is treating the caption of the photo as a threat, even though it clearly is not, and Logan didn't write it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 03:52:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>The principal is choosing to treat the caption of the photo as a threat. It's not. And my son didn't write it, I did.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 04:01:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>But I love bait!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 04:04:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was originally on my Twitter. Kyle Kashuv tweeted that he had been questioned by school security after he posted pictures of himself at a gun range. I replied with this photo to say that he'd done nothing wrong. I captioned it "Here's a pic of my son learning to shoot safely under my supervision. Maybe those security guys should talk to him too."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 04:11:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are wearing foam ear plugs, you can't see them from behind. We are going to give the school a chance to be reasonable over the next couple days before we bring layers into it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 04:39:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The police captain also seemed confused as to what he was supposed to investigate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 04:40:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I should really pay more attention to which sub I'm in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 04:43:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>In response to Kyle Kashuv tweeting about being questioned by school security I shared the photo with the caption "Here's a pic of my son learning to shoot safely under my supervision. Maybe those security guys should talk to him too." Not a threat, and not even written by my son. He is being punished for my actions which are themselves not worthy of punishment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 04:44:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are wearing foam ear plugs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 05:12:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>In that case how could I leave?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 05:14:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who wouldn't care about me? I love me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 05:14:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 05:14:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>The nice guy thing is SO 2016.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 05:15:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're wearing foam ear plugs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 05:16:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 05:18:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sup?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 05:19:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hot take on a 13 year old kid's appearance. You must be have really high self esteem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 05:20:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 05:26:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rental. Being a meme doesn't give you SCAR money.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 05:27:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blood pressure up a bit having to deal with this. Otherwise good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 05:45:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are wearing foam ear plugs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 05:45:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are wearing foam ear plugs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 16:12:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope you get to talk to a famous person some day</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 16:16:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>The police captain I talked to didn't seem to know what he was supposed to be investigating. Unfortunately we learned of all this after school hours. The police are going to reach out to the school today to see what they want.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 16:18:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The really bad part is that this was not my son expressing himself. He doesn't even have a Twitter account. This was me posting a picture in reply to a Parkland survivor who had been harassed by security for going to a gun range. The school is punishing a child for his father's words.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 16:20:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>In context I don't think it does, but even if it did they are my words. My son didn't do anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 17:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meeting with a detective in a few minutes. We'll know more by the end of the day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 23:33:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just talked to the principal. Logan is cleared to return to school on Monday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 19:24:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I totally am.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 04:50:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen it done better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 05:02:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your grandfather's name is as cool as mine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 17:28:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>That high stress workplace is a better place because you are in it. You seem like a person who vastly improves a place by being part of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 22:00:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which part is wrong?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 06:01:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Enjoy being a meme. Normally I'd advise you not use your real account for meme purposes but I guess it's too late for that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 14:06:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 17:45:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>White dude checking in. I only think about my whiteness if race is being discussed or if I get a terrible sunburn. Like the rest of us, I just think of me as me. Race, sexuality, all that other stuff we argue about doesn't come into play at all in my self image.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 04:08:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Umm...thanks. I think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 04:10:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same here. If our cost was a third of what this article said we'd have gone bankrupt long ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 05:28:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>They used to roam in herds numbering in the millions. Then the white man came.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 06:14:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brother, I know memes. I AM a meme. This is a God damned glorious meme.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 17:43:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Canada doesn't get too riled up over the thought of 747 door gunners. As long as you keep flying and don't land in Canada they don't care.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 07:20:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude, don't post your number on Reddit. It's against the rules and it's a terrible idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 07:21:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You might feel meh, but you don't look it. Fabulous eye make up. It's a stunning look overall.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 07:26:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>It sucks that you are sad, I know that feel. On the bright side, everyone that saw your smile is now happy! It's so sweet and infectious. You must spread joy everywhere you share it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 07:30:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for getting that so quick. I hate to see a thirsty dude dox himself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 08:51:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for sharing but I'm afraid someone beat you to this one by a few hours. https://www.smh.com.au/healthcare/final-donation-for-man-whose-blood-helped-save-2-4-million-babies-20180511-p4zerp.html This post removed due to being a recent repost.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 19:11:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>IT'S A REPOST SO I REMOVED IT!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 17:31:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the sweetest, most genuine smile I've ever seen! I hope life gives you more reasons to show it very soon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 21:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the so close to the comment I made that got me labelled a racist by the New York Post. Never get internet famous under this user name.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 03:59:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Likely because they had been actively misled by corporate interests.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 05:36:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Umm...yeah. That's exactly the point. Once people are educated in the issue they are overwhelmingly in favor of net neutrality.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 13:14:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. You're not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 15:20:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>No lawsuit. Thanks in part to media pressure he was back to school after only missing one day. I announced it, but peaceful resolution isn't as fun as outrage so weird didn't really get out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 16:33:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone filed a police report over the tweet and reported it to the school as a threat. At that point the school has little choice but to act. I blame the person that filed the report. I know who it was, and if you see this ML, fuck you. Stop trying to punish my son just because you don't like me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 22:31:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post removed. No evidence of regret visible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 04:40:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>The real tragedy of what you're suffering from is that you can't see what we see. We see a stunning young woman with a lot to offer. I hope some day you'll be able to see it as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 18:09:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are some reports that this kid was being bullied BY the staff. Apparently the football coach is awful to the players.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 06:35:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't get what is being protested. The dude is a dick. Do we protest outside a person's house now because they're a dick?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 16:35:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair enough. I thought maybe there was more to it that I was missing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 05:05:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>15 years ago I was a broke, single college student living at home and working for minimum wage at a bowling alley.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 05:43:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Birthday buddies! Other notable people sharing our birthday are Bill Murray, Stephen King, and Colonel Harlan Sanders.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 16:38:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now I'm not single</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 02:09:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>But you insulted him first.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 05:01:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some cities refuse to abide by federal law. Let's pass a law to make them follow the other law! It's foolproof.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 12:16:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm 35 and it's not my birthday but thanks I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 05:32:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd sacrifice all my sweet, sweet karma to bring unidan back. Always loved seeing him pop up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 22:53:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Post removed due to recent repost. Someone beat you to it by a few hours. Thanks for sharing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 23:13:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't let bad behavior excuse bad behavior. Don't let people you find morally inferior to define what is acceptable. Someone has to be the first to be better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 04:20:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. Welcome back to the Bone Zone!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 05:33:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Works best with fake celebrities.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 17:39:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>According to other articles I read on this he is expelled for threatening other kids / teachers with knives.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 01:47:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who the hell is that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 02:32:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nothing against Harry or against pride month but this is the wrong sub. This sub is about the Big Cat rescue of the same name. Sorry for the confusion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 03:13:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry, I don't know. Good luck though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 03:23:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because all the cool kids hate Trump. The chill thing used to be avocados. Before that it was bacon then cupcakes. Now it's blind partisan hatred. Much less appetizing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 04:19:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>The other trumpets? I've been very publicly critical of Trumps rhetoric and policy. I'm simply pointing out that there is a wave of virulent hatred for all things trump from a bunch of people who couldn't name a cabinet member for a million bucks. It's cool to hate Trump. All the celebrities tell you to do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 04:26:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>What makes you say that I ignore bad stuff that he does? I have criticized his words and actions on Reddit, Twitter, tv, radio, and on my own podcast over and over again. When I say blind this is what I'm talking about. I say something that's not pro trump, it's just not anti trump. This gets me PMs calling me an asshole within 10 minutes from people who have no idea what my actual stance is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 04:47:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tons of them are justified. I never said that hating trump was wrong. I said that some people do it because it's the "in" thing. Pop culture says hate Trump. A lot of people who have no clue about any trump policy hate him because they are told to. Because it's cool. If you know anything at all about the issues and you hate him anyway I'm totally cool with that. He brings it on himself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 05:00:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>At no point have I said that it's not ok to be anti trump. It's perfectly ok. He invites criticism with every word. All I'm saying is that a whole bunch of people who know nothing about WHY they hate Trump hate him anyway. I think it's crazy to deny that pop culture is wildly anti trump and that people who otherwise would not care at all hate him because it is the thing to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 05:13:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can not possibly deny that there are people out there who only hate Trump because it's the cool thing right now. I'm not saying it's wrong to be anti trump. I'm only saying that some trump haters do not care or know about the issues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 05:14:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that the level of political discourse you want? Why let the moral standard be set by purple you find morally deficient? Bad behavior does not justify bad behavior.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 05:14:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bad behavior does not justify bad behavior.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 05:19:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's definitely a market for pro Trump or other right wing programming that advertisers are happy to sign with. If this article is accurate it says a lot less about the type of programming than it does about the hosts. Hannity and Ingram are controversy magnets. That's bad did business. Also their shows suck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 05:24:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think that and I didn't say that. Hate him all you want. That's your right. There's plenty of reasons not to like the guy. My entire point start to finish is that some of the peopke who hate Trump only hate him because of pop culture influence. They know nothing about WHY. Even then they are perfectly free to feel however they like.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 05:25:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never used the word majority. I don't think it is a majority, but I'm damn sure it's not zero. There are people who hate Trump and don't know why. They just know they hate him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 05:27:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>About what? About things I don't like about Trump? Travel ban. Tariffs. Twitter nonsense. Wasteful border wall. Stupid inflammatory rhetoric. Narcissism. Typical stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 05:28:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't mean to imply that and I'm surprised that people are saying that conclusion. There are plenty of reasons to not like trump.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 05:31:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>They could, but they don't all do it. It was the same with the Obama haters who paid no attention. Only difference now is that pop culture is on the side of the haters. A percentage of the population is always going to be haters who don't care about issues. Those people just happen to be on the same side as popular culture this cycle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 05:32:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>More hate is going to beget more trump.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 05:34:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let me just call my pals at Gallup and get them to run a poll of political engagement vs trump sentiment. Look. It. Up. Yourself. Or don't believe me. It's a comment on the internet for Christ's sake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 05:48:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>If we're going to stay calling for statistics for an anecdotal point I'm going to kick it back to you. Prove that every single person with a negative opinion of trump is informed on the issues. I'm willing to bet everything I own that there are people who couldn't name the VP, a cabinet member, or correctly identify any trump policy who hate him anyway. I cannot believe I've succumbed to a political argument for over an hour about a stupid joke I made about how nobody likes trump. Enough internet for me. You win.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 05:51:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every news station but Fox is openly anti trump. LeBron and Steph hate Trump. The Eagles don't want to go to the white house because Trump. Acceptance speeches at awards shows are about how Trump sucks. Every late night talk show host hates trump and makes it a point to tell everyone that they hate him. You can't tell me that has no effect on the folks that otherwise don't care about politics or issues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 05:57:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://digiday.com/media/politics-pop-culture-news-trump-era-political-news-everyones-beat/ http://theweek.com/articles/647139/how-pop-culture-coopted-politics https://www.npr.org/sections/politics-pop-culture A whole section on NPR titled "politics and pop culture." The influence is real.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 06:05:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>And you're that guy who makes up words in an attempt to put down strangers, similarly for no reason. Now that we've got the introductions out of the way, go fuck yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 12:51:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Talk about it all you want. Just be honest with yourself and see that it has an effect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 13:24:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course you can. The entirety of my point is that people who otherwise would not know or care are influenced by pop culture. Decide for yourself if that's good or bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 19:29:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go find an adult with Down's. Look them straight in the face and tell them they would be better off dead. That their life is not worth living. See if they agree. I get the feeling that people with genetic disorders would prefer to be alive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 19:56:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't have them any more, but don't kill them. Cryogenically freeze them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 22:37:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>So we're back to killing them then.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 00:22:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't say is acceptable. I banned the guy for this joke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 04:17:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm glad you cleared up. That before picture looked like some of those hurt. Thanks for your husband's service! Those of you that remain in the home front serve in their own way too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 04:28:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rules vary by state.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 18:35:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not even my own favorite, but thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 06:19:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Both photos are really attractive for different reasons.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 02:02:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not really. Sorry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 23:43:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my close relatives is a small business owner and a very conservative man. This post does not describe him in the least. From his perspective, and that of many other small town conservatives the "liberal hate" comes from multiple sources. The first is ideology. Not hatred, not economics. Simply an opposing view on how the affairs of state should be run. They want everyone to succeed and live the best life they can. Including immigrants and minorities. They just have very different ideas on how best to achieve that. Most of these ideas center on the belief that the government is too big and inefficient to look out for everyone and would serve the people better by getting out of the way. This leads right to the second reason. The original post ascribes hate to these people when in many cases there is none. Does racism exist? Yep. And most of these small town conservatives think it is just as disgusting as the "city folk" do. When you say things that generalize whole groups they get mad at you. If you state that the whole south is just a bunch of bigoted hicks, guess what? The whole south is pissed at you now and therefore much less receptive to your ideas on policy. That's human nature. Third and finally, These folks have been taught since birth that their homes and their work is central to who they are. "We've been [coal miners, farmers, shop owners, ranchers, steelworkers] for generations and we're proud of it." They have been told by their parents, their leaders, and all of culture since they were little kids that if they work hard they will prosper and that family is paramount. Turns out that wasn't the case. You can work pretty damn hard at the farm and never get ahead, and if you want to succeed you may have to move away from your family and your home. Then along comes the party of compassion that wants to help everybody to tell them that not only were mommy and daddy wrong, you were an idiot to believe them. "Abandon your lifestyle and assume ours, it's the only way." They are now being told that their homes and their work (which are central to their identity) are irrelevant and should be abandoned. Not only that, but their ideas are not only wrong but somehow secretly evil and they must be evil for even considering them. How could there not be a backlash from that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 23:57:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>1) I don't hate you and at no point did I ever say that I do. 2) If your compassion and willingness to help only extends to people who will love you for it you won't be helping many people. This is the same justification that conservatives use to suggest pulling foreign aid. 3) Redistribution of wealth is totally against conservative ideology. Those are proud people. Don't expect them to do a complete 180 on their beliefs just because they are the ingress in need.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 00:56:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Again, you keep saying "you guys." "You guys" does not include me. I'm a moderate who is ok with government regulations and programs. Anyway: Conservatives believe that if you want to help people you just do it. Charities, religious organizations, or plain old doing it yourself. They believe that government is a poor steward of your money and that using the government as the primary means of helping people not only won't work but can actually make things worse. As evidence they'll point to the generationally impoverished who can no longer exist outside of a welfare state environment. They don't want that to happen to them and their kids. In addition they'll argue that charity has no value if you're forced to give. They'll say that you're not giving away your money, you're giving away other people's money by taxing them whether they agree with the cause or not. They find that immoral.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 03:40:45</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I accomplish nothing by donating on my own There you reach a fundamental disagreement between American conservatives and liberals. There's not a lot of talking that will bridge that gap. From there you have to work on agreeing to disagree if you want to stop the hate cycle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 06:13:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's getting increasingly hard for me to articulate the classical conservative argument because it's not my own viewpoint but I'll give it a shot. Of course we have to establish basic services like roads, defense, education, fire, and police but as much as possible that should be kept at the state or local level to avoid bureaucratic bloat. As far as social welfare programs conservatives believe that they should be left in the hands of communities and non profits. They don't trust the government to oversee those programs efficiently or fairly. In keeping with the fire analogy they might argue that they don't trust government to decide whose house is protected and whose is not. And they definitely don't believe government is capable of taking care of them all. I'm happy to continue the conversation in the morning, but keep in mind I'm playing devils advocate for a lot of this and I might not be the best source of information. I'm fine with social programs, I just wish there were more oversight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 20:28:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey now, that's not fair. They don't just murder the sick and weak. They string those poor bastards along real slow while bleeding them totally dry of money first.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 02:44:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>They told me I broke the internet once. It's still here though. I guess we got a new one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 02:53:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've already done this one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 06:46:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish this were so. Plenty of people make their identities the focus of their political careers. Not just marginalized people either. There's plenty of republicans who run on their cowboy image. Roy Moore rode a horse to the polls.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 06:51:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>He didn't claim that. He said that some people voted for him because he is black, which is undeniably true. It's just as true that others voted against him because he is black.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 06:54:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>It saddens me that it is election season. It's fucking five months until the election. It's like seeing Christmas trees in the store on Halloween only worse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 07:12:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nobody used the word disproportionate. And off the top of my head here's a well publicized account of a well known Preston claiming that voting against Obama is racist. https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/morgan-freeman-sparks-outcry-tea-party-racist-239872</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 00:05:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>2GWH is a lot, but it would only last the state about a half hour at full draw.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 01:20:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work at a power plant that puts out 1,600MW. That's 1.6GW. We can power around 3 million homes at peak. Massachusetts has about 6.5 million people so around 2 to 3 million homes. With that plus business and industrial usage I'm pretty confident in my half hour estimate. Maybe an hour. Definitely not much more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 03:51:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Coward deleted his account too. Probably the same troll I banned an hour ago for posting the same story under a different account.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 17:04:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>In law. Married to David's brother.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 17:09:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>The origin of the phrase is not racist. It is sometimes twisted to have racial connotations because of the word "spade" becoming a racial pejorative. The original and intended meaning in common use comes from the gardening tool. As in "don't call a spade a shovel." This has similar meaning to "Don't make a mountain out of a molehill" but is usually used in the context of don't call something what it is clearly not just to suit your argument.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 19:34:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>She was married to Andy Spade who is the brother of David Spade. Her maiden name was Brosnahan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 23:40:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>No you can't. You can use your religion as an excuse not to use your artistic expression on their behalf since artistic expression is protected speech and is therefore protected from being compelled against your wishes. The bakers custom decorations are considered free speech. In the same ruling SCOTUS ruled that the baker would be required to sell them a cake that did not bear his custom decorations.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 23:50:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Oxford English dictionary.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 02:16:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Should you be able to demand that a Muslim chef make pork chops for you? Why is your right to eat what you want or may who you want more important than the chef's right to free exercise of religion? The government cannot compel people to use their freedom of expression in a way that is contrary to their religious beliefs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 02:21:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Turkey is on the council. And China. And Cuba. And Qatar. And Pakistan. That's not an opinion. That's a verifiable fact. The guy you responded to may or may not be a jerk. That has no bearing on the fact that the Human Rights Council is stacked with dictatorships that have no regard for human rights.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 05:24:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>What law? Supreme Court decisions are not law. There is no law, only a ruling starting that in this very specific case a business could not be forced to act against the religious conviction of its owner. You accuse me of ignoring reality. Maybe you just don't understand it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 05:51:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry professor, it was the Cambridge dictionary, online edition. The etymology courtesy of an NPR write up where the author concludes that while the phrase is not racist that we shouldn't use it because short sighted people such as yourself might interpret it as racist. I disagree and believe we should not throw out pieces of language just because racists try to steal words.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 15:37:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Google it yourself. Both of the things I just cited are in the top 5 results. Mistaking Cambridge dictionary for Oxford is an easy mistake to make. Besides which you are the one who made the initial claim. The burden of proof rests with you. I have shown that the phrase is not racist. Prove that it is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 16:01:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>This administration seems to live putting people on camera that are breath takingly awful at communicating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 16:53:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Attack me personally again and you will be banned. You asked for sources. I provided them. You continue to call me a liar. Only one of us is acting in bad faith.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 18:52:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>It seems to me they actually have way less wiggle room. Sessions' zero tolerance policy means they couldn't let folks go for minor border infractions even if they wanted to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 18:58:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do agree with what I think you were saying though. There's a real danger that the bad apples among the ICE agents (every organization has some) will get away with wrongdoing or abuse because the administration wants to appear tough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 20:03:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>The new version of this is omitting vowels on purpose like Tumblr or Flickr.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 21:11:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>The policy in question has nothing to do with separating children. The policy is one of "zero tolerance" for unlawful border crossings. Anyone caught crossing illegally is arrested, including asylum seekers who do not follow the proper protocol. This has led to a large upswing in the number of arrests and therefore the number of detainees. By law you can't keep children detained with parents (for their parents alleged offenses) for more than 20 days. They have to be given over to family members, foster care, or otherwise cared for. Most of the kids have no family members available to care for them since their family just got arrested and there aren't family members already in the US in most cases. The foster care system is slow and was overwhelmed. This quickly led to a situation where the kids had to be detained and cared for separately. ICE and DHS were in no way prepared to handle this properly which showed a stunning lack of foresight. There are now only a few options available: 1) The administration backs off the "zero tolerance" of enforcement. This does nothing for those already detained unless they are also released. This is very unlikely. 2) Trump issues an executive order allowing the kids and families to be detained together. Not ideal but at least they are together. This is also unlikely, and not technically legal according to a 2016 ruling by the 9th Circuit Court of Appeals. It would lead to a lengthy court battle, but again at least the families aren't torn apart. 3) Congress changes the laws. Several bills are scheduled to be brought to the floor today. I don't expect any to pass. I expect more partisan bickering since it is more politically expedient than actually working together. We need serious immigration reform. We will never be rid of illegal (undocumented if you prefer, it's all semantics) immigration until we fix legal immigration. No amount of walls, drones, or ICE agents will ever change that. Edit: 24 minutes later and Trump goes with option #2. I am genuinely surprised. I'm glad the families can reunite and we can end the stupid and cruel practice of separating families, but don't let off the pressure. We still need a long term legislative fix. Contact your representatives and remember their actions on this matter come election time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 21:40:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you very much! I try to be as fair as I can and it really means a lot to me when someone is kind enough to say something nice about it. I was actually expecting a bunch of hate since politics is the way it is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 21:53:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would be thrilled with a massive turnover in Congress this November. Regardless of party. Just vote "someone else" as long as they are qualified. The current reps have had their shot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 22:11:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think America is a great place to live. I see no reason not to let people in to become Americans within reason and with proper vetting. According to Standard and Poores the population growth rate is currently at 0.7%. I'd cap the immigration rate at some fraction of that. I don't know how much, I'm not a Sociologist, but I feel like between a third and one half would be appropriate. What I mean is, for every 2 or three Americans born we could afford to let one naturalize. Maybe I'm way off but that part can be tuned. To become a citizen I need to know 3 things about you: 1) You are not a felon 2) You don't have any serious communicable diseases, and 3) You don't have a bunch of guns or drugs hidden in your butt. If you make legal immigration reasonable and attainable you take away the incentive to do it illegally. Then it becomes more safe to assume that the people doing it illegally have something to hide and punishing them makes a lot of sense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 23:51:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could go either way. I'm not required to have any skills. I guess what I'd settle on is no social safety net for naturalized citizens until they display marketable skills. In other words you are not eligible for programs until either you have contributed to them or were born to parents that have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 00:26:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Woohoo! More bourbon and motorcycles for me!!! Surely this won't make them more expensive for us Americans as their manufacturers struggle to maintain profits in the face of diminished foreign markets. Right...guys?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 01:56:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am a mod. You're free to disagree all you like but you have now personally attacked me no less than three times. I would ban anyone for doing that to any user. You were warned.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 22:52:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're Americans now. We've been out for months. Saves on heartbreak during the actual event</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 01:48:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm afraid you found the wrong kind of pride. This sub is about Big Cat Rescue. It's pride like a pride of lions. Happy pride month though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 16:31:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 16:32:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I graciously accept. When will the car arrive for me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 16:35:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Emperor sounds like so much work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 16:36:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're ever in southern Illinois leery me know. We'll hug it out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 16:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy crap somebody is listening to my podcast. I gotta tell my mom...who does not listen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 16:38:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was a fun trip. A lot of the older people thought I was just some jerk hogging the photo back drop and getting in everyone's picture for no reason.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 16:40:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 17:45:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>His point was that they reached out to him and asked him to work unpaid on an article describing how harmful it is for people to work unpaid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 17:52:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Near St Louis, Missouri. A little town called Shiloh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 18:35:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work near there in Marissa</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 05:24:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the nanny was the mom's nanny who worked for the family even after the mom was grown. Then she was the gestational surrogate/nanny for the kid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 06:06:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the problem though. The family separation thing was terrible and zero tolerance for misdemeanor offences is sketchy at best, but now we've gone and handed Trump another "fake news" distraction to use. He doesn't even have to work for it. He's a master of marketing. It's the one thing where he is undeniably excellent, and we keep giving him material that's purpose built for him to use to market his talking points while undermining his opponents. It plays right into his hands.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 06:09:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't see your kidneys in this shot so I guess I can't speak to that part, but the rest of you is aces!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 22:25:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think the way you acted was improper at all. The only thing that would make this story more proper would be if he had run his bike into a tree while he was busy being a dickhead. To hell with that guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 03:30:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's for sharing, but I'm afraid you found the wrong pride sub. This sub isn't scout human experiences at all. It's devoted to big cat rescue. Pride like a pride of lions. Happy pride month though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 04:05:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Get in, loser! We're going dumpster divin'.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 05:05:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>It happens all the time, nobody here minds. If you like big cats check out the sub. The rescue does a lot of great work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 01:35:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Needs more cat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 03:11:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Autobots, rock out!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I was the subject of a clue today!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 02:14:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 02:54:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's nothing like it was but I still get recognized occasionally. Plus I travel a fair amount doing speeches for schools and non profits.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 03:26:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Give me money? You're way off. Usually a charity or a school club (high school or college, young republicans or young democrats typically) will contact me on Twitter or other social media. Some have my number or email they've gotten from other organizations. They ask me to come do an event. If I can do it they have a fundraiser to pay for my travel and I go speak at the event. I don't accept pay from high schools or non profits.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 13:12:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because we ran the two most statistically unlikable candidates in history against each other. "Undecided" in the political polling sense means you are not locked in for any candidate. Both major candidates sucked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 14:34:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something about glass houses and stones.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:16:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's for people who are afraid of their inner selves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:21:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've moved on to your mom. 10/10.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:23:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>In most instances I consider it a donation of my time. I'm really not a big enough draw to justify much expense. They would risk not making a profit on me. I only get money from private events and those are rare these days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:26:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Romney '12, Obama '08. I'd love for Albert to come home for his last year or two. I met him at his Pujols Family Foundation gala in '16. He still loves the town. Great guy too. His son AJ was pretty excited I was there. Super cool kid. He knows every sports superstar there is so they were normal, but the internet meme guy was a rare treat I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 22:43:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't feel the need to be original when jackasses make the same joke for the five hundredth time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 23:23:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't tell me how to live my life!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 04:30:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry you're having a tough day. On the plus side everyone who saw this picture had their day improve.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 20:11:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your nose seems to have come through wonderfully. It's cute as a button just like the rest of you. If you wind up with any residual marks or scarring just remember: Tiny imperfections make us individuals. They make us beautiful. If Cindy Crawford can have a mole and call it a beauty mark you can have a little mark on your adorable nose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 02:09:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your friend did a good job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 04:44:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Waiting for a group to organize a "shit in" since this policy was announced</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 17:27:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>He didn't do anything. He was the victim of sexual assault and came forward about it. He's been getting some backlash from jerks who think that since he's a big guy he should have committed battery against the guy who did it to him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 00:26:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>M E T A E T A</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 01:51:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>My usual lecture has four points. 1) Politics doesn't have to be hateful 2) Don't trust everything celebrities tell you 3) Fame for its own sake is not a worthwhile goal 4) The problem of empathy for people you only know via a screen I can do an hour on any one, but typically I do about 60 to 90 minutes on the four combined followed by Q and A.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 21:24:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 00:45:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>More freedom and equality by eliminating words! Thanks Big Brother.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 06:27:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is a big switch. As to why, my guess is that he actually listened to a lawyer for once. Never talk to investigators until you have to and never without a lawyer. Frankly I'm surprised he listened.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 18:58:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>The show premiered in the seventh year of the Reagan administration and ran for eight more years after he left office.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 23:03:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>He lives on the west coast and hangs out with fugitives. I don't see how he could have gotten to NYC or Wakanda in time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 00:00:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Did you see on the news there was another alien attack today?" "Yeah, now get back to work Scott." Now you have your acknowledgment and have successfully drained all the surprise from the end of the scene.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 00:33:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your being down voted because a picture of Trump text has nothing to do with this sub. Removed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 17:19:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>We've all seen dozens of the "attractive tumblr girls." We've only seen one you. And that's good. You have a unique look. People sometimes struggle to stand out while you do so naturally. I wouldn't change one thing about that face. It's lovely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 17:34:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gee, the two major parties have different views. That's weird. /s I ran down the list and on about 80% of those votes Republican voters response was probably "Good. Keep doing that." I can't speak for anyone else, but when I say both parties are the same I don't mean that they stand for the same things or that their level of corruption is equal. I just mean that they both suck and we need at least one more. Also that we should replace a huge chunk of Congress regardless of party affiliation. Vote "someone else" in November.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 22:42:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Program started in 2000 so 18 years. It's a 4 year program so 14 years of graduates. There were 20 graduating seniors this year and I can't find data on previous years so we'll have to assume that's about average. That gives us 280 graduates total. She therefore represents 0.35% of the total number of nanoscience grads from VA Tech. Black women are around 6% of the total US population meaning statistically black women represent only one eighteenth of the graduates that they would if it were evenly distributed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 00:14:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 00:17:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also it's a coyote not a wolf.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 20:48:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't come up with this joke, so I'm not mad that it has been stolen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 04:14:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You never know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 03:57:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't though. We haven't talked about it. I'll go if they ever want to have me on but they're drawing pretty big name guests.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 17:53:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>This has been a long time coming. Matheny inherited a championship team and we've seen progressively worse results every single year under his leadership. Is it all his fault? No, but managers set the course for the team. His course was wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 03:16:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was a fun couple of days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 16:48:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably because you aren't a coward.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 21:59:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a crime.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 00:16:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>The New York Post might write an article about you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 01:17:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I also don't make dozens of jokes about fucking little kids. And I'm not the public or creative face of my employer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 05:27:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why does that surprise people?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 05:48:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll be honest, laying on my couch in my undies browsing Reddit on a Friday night doesn't feel very legendary. Thanks though, this kind of thing makes a guy feel all special.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 06:55:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could clear my schedule.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 17:52:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.Youtube.com/thekenbonezone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 08:48:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>The nation wide inflation average for 2017 was 2.1% with a forecast of 1.9% for this year. Do you live in one of the harder hit areas? Housing costs have really hurt some places.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 09:00:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>After reading the title I was worried I'd have to resort to the old "only skin deep" platitude. Fortunately for me I don't have to because you're really pretty. I hope you can see what we see some day soon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 02:14:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>How is the dad supposed to know? All are equal when a dad sees them kick their child.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 04:38:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your mom hasn't forgotten me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 18:31:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll be in DC while he's in my home town. Weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 18:07:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>This sub is where I first heard this joke. It's the circle of Reddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 18:11:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't change that outfit. Ever. You look fabulous. Not "pretty good for having three kids," just plain fabulous for anybody.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 19:40:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>A very merry unbirthday to you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 19:40:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 04:00:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Forgot this is a young crowd. In "Alice in Wonderland" the Mad Hatter and the March Hare celebrate unbirthdays on every day that is not their birthday. "A very merry unbirthday to you" is part of the song they sing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 06:30:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool. I thought it was just because I was referencing a 60 year old movie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 15:34:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I signed off on this. The folks that make this puzzle and the game do their best to get the permission of anyone who is depicted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 17:09:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>On a setup like this you want to hand tighten all the nuts first. Then you torque them in sequence. The numbers written in marker next to the nuts are the order you do them in. You usually tighten a bit at a time following the sequence until they are all at the predetermined tightness. If you do them in the wrong order or if you tighten them too much at once you can cause the entire structure to shift or cause damage to it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 20:06:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could. Probably won't though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 16:22:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>The sadness I see in your eyes breaks my heart, but I can see past it. I hope that soon you'll be able to see past it as well. You are a person of deep feeling. Your hard times are some of the hardest and I'm willing to bet that the good times will be some of the best. You'll get there. We're all on your team and we want you to get through this valley quickly and unharmed. Don't change yourself. You're amazing the way you are. Instead simply do your best to see yourself the way we see you, as a strong and beautiful person, even if it's only for a few minutes at a time. It's hard but you can do it. We're here when you can't do it alone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 05:13:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I won't be happy until they give me the role.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 19:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not a whole lot. Working mostly. I still travel and give speeches occasionally also.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 22:15:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whatever makes you happy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 20:11:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll speak to pretty much any crowd that invites me. I met Charlie while at the recent event and spoke to him for all of 10 seconds. I went because Kyle Kashuv asked me to. If David Hogg asks me to go talk to an anti-gun crowd I'll do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 22:09:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate you helping to spread this message. Sometimes our brains aren't perfect, just like the rest of our bodies. There's no shame in ADD meds, anti depressants, or any other psych based med just like there's no shame in taking insulin for diabetes. Just what the doctor ordered.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 00:06:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sweet Care Bear uniforms. Only an awesome person like you can bring rugby toughness to something so cute.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 05:30:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>You seem surprised. I'm not. I've always been me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 03:24:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not only is the costume fantastic, but that smile says you had a great time. That's what it's all about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 03:27:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I like his boots better but all the rest of the elements go to you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 16:16:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post removed due to violation of rule #3  gt;3) No Animal Abuse. We love animals. They are capable of regret, but we don't want to see videos where their regret is the fault of humans, involves cruelty, injury or is in any way unpleasant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 16:23:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Flair this man!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 16:31:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's all I needed to know. He sucks. I was going to try to see his perspective like, "maybe he's also working a lot and they divided up the housework in a fair and rational way and laundry was her responsibility" or something, but no. He's just looking for a maid that sleeps with him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 19:28:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 14:42:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 22:05:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>St. Louis Blues legend!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 17:56:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>You better stop this hate speech against memes. We're a protected class, buddy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 04:30:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>If your intention was not to sound mean you failed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 15:13:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>In general if you wonder to yourself, "is this racist?" about doing anything, then don't do it. Even if it's not. In this specific case, it's not as long as it's used properly. Examples: "I'm finna get out of here" when leaving work for the day. No problem. "You finna be in trouble" to a black person. Big problem. Context is everything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 15:55:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's both. Unless it is the way you talk all of the time, you should not try to "talk black" to black people. That's patronizing and racist. If you use finna all the time and everyone knows it you're good, otherwise you come off sounding like you are trying to "fit in" to a culture that individual might not fit in to themselves. It would be like saying to them, "Yo, brotha! How you livin'?" or something when you don't normally speak that way. It comes off as you assuming that they do speak that way based solely on their skin color.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 23:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>If anyone cares, I banned this T_D dwelling tool for the following comments (among several others) in Uplifting News, a sub where the only rule is "Don't be a dick."  gt;Jesus you are scum of the earth. Get a grip. Wrong on everything, clearly uneducated, no reason to even respond to you  gt;Lol and now the violence begins. Just order some tendies, mommy will be home soon.  gt;Nice comment. Just as vapid and uninteresting as your mind  gt;I didn't assume anything, you laid your stupidity on the floor for all to see.  gt;Omg you only get dumber as you get angry! This is hilarious. He seems to split time between The Donald and trolling transgender kids on r/trans with the occasional visit elsewhere to dig for downvotes. Decide for yourself which of us should be ashamed. To address you directly, please go outside and practice falling down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 05:03:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe I'm wrong, but I thought we already knew this part.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 13:55:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's freaking bizarre. Personal space people, respect it. When I have to squeeze past someone I put my hand up palm out about shoulder level as I'm saying "excuse me." That way if it's loud you get the hand gesture of "just trying to get by, hands where you can see them" and if there is accidental contact it's just a hand on the back or shoulder. Of course if there is contact it is followed up with an additional "excuse me" as well as a "sorry I bumped into you."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 14:21:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>If Cohen has more to give why didn't he use it to bargain *before* pleading guilty? Is he hoping to get a light sentence or is he blowing smoke?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 12:33:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everybody in those regions just held hands and sang around campfires until 1776 I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 14:00:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't try it if I were you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 23:58:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. Hi.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 04:50:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>He lives to poop on parties.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 22:43:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do the 4X10 work week and it's fantastic. Three day weekend every week, and if there's work that arises late in the week the worst case is usually working Friday to get it done leaving a standard weekend intact.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 16:22:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>10 hours</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 16:33:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>10 hours EXTRA TEXT SO THE AUTO MOD WON'T REMOVE MY COMMENT FOR BEING TOO SHORT AGAIN. GOD FORBID YOU GET ASKED A QUESTION WITH A SUCCINCT ANSWER ON THIS SUB.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 21:41:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's not weird. What's weird is that I have one with your face.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 22:20:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not quite as public as I used to be, but yes. I usually call myself a public figure because referring to myself as a celebrity sounds egotistical.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 22:31:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>In that case, great job!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 04:15:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, every fat white guy looks like me. Racist. /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 00:01:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here to present the first place trophy, last year's champions, Bill S Preston, Esquire and Ted "Theodore" Logan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 20:05:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nobody calls out my boy! Any prank invasion will have to go through the Bone Zone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 05:57:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry that happened to you. Are you recovering alright?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 06:07:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure, if they can relocate to China where the deposits are. And also be completely retrained anyway since rare earth metal mining is vastly different from coal mining.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 06:09:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most coal plant workers are not manual laborers. We don't shovel the coal into a furnace by hand you know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 06:58:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not gonna just sit back while my boy is getting called out. Any attack on the fupa has to get through the Bone Zone first.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 17:41:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure, why not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 17:42:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can say with confidence that there are no coal fired power plants anywhere in the country that have people shoveling coal into the boiler by hand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 17:44:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Coal mining is physically taxing, but it's not just labor. It requires a lot of training and certification, and the actual work is a lot like construction or heavy equipment operation depending on the job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 00:00:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I refuse to fight Hugh Mungus. I couldn't bring myself to punch him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 16:15:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>C-C-C-C-Combo breaker!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 02:09:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why did you feel the need to attack the person you're responding to personally? We don't allow that here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 04:52:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Completing the dailies and getting to 600 energy spent for raid tix gets you about 3250 a day give or take. More if you're farming in excess of the 600 obviously.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 14:16:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hadn't thought of that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>