<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject2182</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-30 13:47:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>If Katie wanted to help Clark, why didn't she just tell him?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-30 14:02:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Zander wouldn't be so careless to just leave his phone lying about and that too with accounts logged in(unless he didn't perceive a threat anymore, which is not obviously wrong). Unless he had to leave sooo urgently that he he was tensed and he forgot, or because someone visited him right there and kidnapped him-maybe Katie/David's other accomplice? /u/Zandsand90 does the phone look like it recently took a tumble?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-20 05:01:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>CDs and iPods</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What to eat/do when you have eaten something that's too sweet and as a result have gotten a headache and feel nauseous?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-30 13:10:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do you refill a highlighter that says "refillable" but can't even be opened?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-30 13:39:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-15 05:54:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apple did mention that it is possible to have only the function key row displayed all the time. I would hope to find it in the settings. I think Excel should add a setting to enable it only in-app, rather than having to enable it system wide.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-15 06:27:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can we pin our favourite folder to the Touch Bar? i.e like a more accessible Dock?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-15 06:53:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>iFixit's teardown of the 13" non-Touch Bar model reveals that the SSD isn't soldered and can be removed. Refer to step 10: https://www.ifixit.com/Teardown/MacBook+Pro+13-Inch+Function+Keys+Late+2016+Teardown/72415</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 15:14:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, read about that yesterday after I commented. The non-touch bar model has a removable SSD while the touch bar models don't. Really weird. You'd expect it to be the other way around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's the difference between "blank" and "none" screensavers in Windows?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-06 17:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Took apart a printer on its way to the dump. Any parts worth keeping/studying in detail? (Electronics noob here)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-11 09:02:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 05:01:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Slightly off topic... Apple should make a charger like a measuring tape. None of this folding would be required and at any point, the length of wire that is out of the charger would be just the length that you need. So if you're closer to the charger, then you're desk doesn't have multiple folds of wire on it. That said, it should also have the lock mechanism like a measuring tape if you do want a longer cable than the distance b/w the socket and the laptop for easy maneuverability or whatever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 08:36:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm an iPad Mini 1 user who migrated to an iPad Air 2. Get the 9.7" one. You won't regret it. The 9.7" takes up lesser space than you might think. But the extra screen real estate makes for an amazing reading and surfing experience. In fact, whenever I have to read a PDF document/textbook I strongly prefer to read it on my iPad vs my MBP and every single time, I feel thankful for having taken the 9.7". And I've watched many a TV Show on the 9.7" whereas doing so on the Mini just felt plain uncomfortable/not so fulfilling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 08:40:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use an Air 2 and my room mate has a Pro 9.7". While the speakers are better on the Pro, I can assure you that you won't be let down by the ones on the Air 2. Both of them are excellent. My Air 2's speakers put out surprisingly loud sound. For on-bed watching, they are more than enough. Audio has never been an issue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 16:31:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder why it was discontinued.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The iPhone 7 is not the only device which can't be connected to a charger and a headphone at the same time.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 14:55:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 15:35:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>iPod Shuffle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The iPhone 7 isn't the only device that can't be connected to a charger and a headphone at the same time. (x-post r/pics)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 15:39:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 16:13:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could always have loaded any MP3 song you want into these. Even on iPhones.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Maths lovers of Reddit, which is the most elegant proof you have come across?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 09:58:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 11:44:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Messages can be used to text only if you have an iPhone right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 11:48:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Windows doesn't create a new full screen window for the split apps. It just resizes both to either side of the screen. I personally prefer to have a separate full screen window.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-22 19:03:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Hitchhiker's Guide to The Galaxy series by Douglas Adams. Downright hilarious!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-22 19:07:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Totally agree. I know some app's been busy hogging in the background if my battery drops more than 2-5% overnight. That's when I go find it and turn off background app refresh for that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-22 19:10:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The "when they're brand new" clause sounds like either you've had the feel go down as the case faces life or else you don't know what's going to happen to your case and are just being precise now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 12:05:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fed:"Well, break point? No probs. Here comes another ace."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 12:13:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still alive in the set..phew. That was a bit close.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 12:15:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>5th it is!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 03:34:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>When this one zooms, you're going to see a Doppler shifted paint job. Sorry, couldn't resist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-01 03:34:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Facing a stagnation of sorts doesn't mean it's declining. Its products are still top notch, just not as great/better than the previous one as we all expect them to be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 08:18:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is it that a space held together by largely gravitational interaction (spherically symmetric) is cubical?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 08:21:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>But why would you apply cubical boundary conditions to a space which is more likely to be spherical? Is it that what goes on inside won't be affected by the boundaries? But then we are interested in the boundaries too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-19 04:52:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly! We have *evolved* to become oxygen consuming life forms right? So, there may be other types of life forms too. My question is what is it that is needed to create that first spark of life?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-19 07:47:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Major breakthroughs happen only because of the many small revelations before them. I don't think Einstein's papers would have come out if the Michelson Morley experiment hadn't been performed. And the reason for that experiment to be performed is staunch belief in existing theories and the need to **confirm** them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-19 08:16:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sure. But given our understanding of the Primordial Soup and evolution, I thought there might exist a decent definition of the difference between a grain of sand and a cell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-19 09:23:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was using sand as a proxy for the non living.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 12:53:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can see something similar even in iOS. Especially prominent with the iBooks icon. The orange background is stationary and when I move my head sideways, the book moves along with me. I wear glasses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 14:29:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The paper that they wrote was submitted on 21st November. http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v542/n7642/full/nature21360.html</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 06:04:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Keeps glancing at crush. Crush turns and catches your eye. You smile. This happens 5 times every minute. Earns title of thecreepyassholeattheback.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 09:23:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Geek would be a better word than nerd. I believe the factorial mess has already been pointed out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 08:27:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm an iPad user: 1) Proper keyboard support. I find it half baked right now - forcing me to lift my fingers up and swipe. 2) Better split view in portrait. Screen should be split up and down, not sideways. 3) Option to set defaults - browser, pdf editor, music...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 14:21:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair point. Maybe the split keyboard can be opened by default? But many people might not like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>