<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject1264</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Finally told my parents</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 18:28:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>They say the first step is the hardest, and damn, they weren't wrong. I spilled everything, all the thoughts, my actions, my time by the tracks. I almost brought my poor mum to tears, i feel so guilty, like a burden to my family, they've promised to support me and get me to the doctors asap, so thats something. Hopefully ill get some medication or something to help me cope with my feelings, or some therapy, idk. But, was i wrong to mention the tracks?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 19:32:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for all of the support</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 22:00:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Youre right</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 23:41:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im not as far through life as you are, but your feelings resonate with me, i do well at school, yet im falling apart, im sure that with enough time and effort, i could improve, but i just dont see the point</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not excited about my birthday.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 19:48:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im not looking forward to all the fake smiles ill be giving out to my family like free candy. I dont care about presents, i dont care about them, they dont care about me, not really. My parents have been pestering me for what i want, i cant think of anything, not even for this depression to leave, i dont care anymore. Apathy is a bitch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 21:31:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I swear ive seen this post or something similar before</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My birthday's tomorrow</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 20:59:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>And i couldn't give less of a shit about it. School's gonna drag like a bitch, then ill be home and be pestered by my family giving presents and shit, i wonder if my mask will hold all day? Or if ill crumble infront of everyone. The only thing good about it is that ill finally have enough money to replace my broken DS4 controller, so then i can more effectively isolate myself. FML</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 21:13:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>No Mans sky, fortnite now and again, and crossout mostly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 21:27:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its relaxing, i can just walk around an alien environment, free from worries and just enjoy the landscape</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Someone explain some stuff to me?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 23:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi, young and from UK here. So every few weeks i visit a doctor/GP whatever at my local medical centre, we talk about how my life has been, feelings, whether things are getting worse or better etc. What is this? Therapy? Counselling? Something else? And two days away im getting what i think is like a mental health 'interview' at a local community building. What this? Therapy, counseling etc? Im feeling a bit nervous and scared at the second, like they're gonna tell me im fucked or something? Anyone been through something similar? Advice?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 23:45:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! Thats put my mind at a little more ease</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 23:48:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like an asshole, id try to move on</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 23:50:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell someone you trust, from my experience, it was awkward for months, but they will 'get over it' in the best of ways</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 23:52:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/thanksimcured</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 08:48:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Afaik, all or most pencils dont have lead, they have graphite, which is carbon , non-toxic hopefully you will be alright</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>