<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject2547</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>fruit is artwork,</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-09 07:43:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Solar Eclipse at 80% (Australia 2012 taken 5 hours ago)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-14 01:51:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-21 14:10:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>some of these responses are funny, but this is some of the stupid stuff i did as a kid: 1. pissed on the power point outside with my little brother because it annoyed my mum. 2. giving guinea pigs a bath and got distracted and walked off, they died 3. found an injured bird when it died mum buried it and said it was going to heaven, she found us in the back yard an hour later screaming why hasn't he left yet? 4. nearly killed our horse in winter trying to keep it warm, lit a small for that got out of control, almost lost the house aswell. 5. tried to chop my dick off with gardening shears 6. used to run around after EVERY shower EVERY night with a towel as my cape because i was nakey man 7. mum bought me an electric piano for a few hundred dollars, i got annoyed with her so broke it with my piss 8. got annoyed with my mum so walked up stairs to my room, covered the stairs in tacks... then forgot 10 minutes later and went jumping down the stairs, painful. 9. beleived in santa til i was 11 10. used to throw rocks at my little brother and tell him it was raining... there is alot, lot more... EDIT: we dug the bird up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-25 16:18:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm in rehab on leave, and haven't been on Reddit for 3 months.. What is the top 5 most important things I have missed?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-22 07:06:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't been on Reddit for 3 months because I'm in a rehab for alcoholism, I'm currently on a 5 hour leave.. Can you guys please tell me top 5 most important things I have missed on Reddit in the last 3 months? In your opinion of course.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-22 07:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>5 nothings?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-22 07:25:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks brother</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-15 04:59:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd kill it for a grand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My 6 year old sister died from heart disease, I now raise funds for heart disease research, how can I be better at my job?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-26 13:11:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>My sister was 6 and died from heart disease, she was on the trampoline and had a heart attack, so I got a job for the heart foundation raising funds for them over the telephone. What can I do to be better at my new job? Everyone hangs up on me I feel I'm letting everyone down.. please help</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-06 15:58:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please fuck off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-06 16:05:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Convinced a 17 year old girl that when giving birth, dogs shit their babies out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I have a chick best friend, get over it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-28 02:36:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-01 02:16:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am a woman.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dropped a gearbox on my hand. Woops.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-01 02:24:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-01 02:30:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seeing my surgeon today. The fingers I have left are crossed for a good outcome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Blood Moon, from 'Mt Isa' Australia.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-09 01:37:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Blood Moon, from 'Mt Isa' Australia.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-09 01:51:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-10 05:36:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude, fuck off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-10 07:07:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Prepare how, mate? Fuck your apocalypse shit off lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-26 13:29:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>"It"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-27 00:00:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not really joking... Go check your local news website they should have it by now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mums' of Reddit, is having a baby like taking a big shit?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-04 21:43:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is how my female friend explained it to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-04 21:48:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>She had twins. She said it feels the same as taking a really big, relieving poo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Serious] Does having a baby feel the same as taking a big shit?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-04 22:23:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is how my friend explained it to me after she had twins.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-04 22:29:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would make sense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>want to see (m)ore?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-23 08:28:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First Bdsm with new girl, how?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-13 16:40:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>New girlfriend had sex, lickes her out 20 min then 10 min sex, that was it. I then did same in mormimg. Apparent she is big on BDSM, im taking cuffs, tape to her houae for my first try at bdsm... What else should I take? And how do I star? ALL TIPS apprexiTesw.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I have 6 days to raise $200 the cause is to help babies survive their first 30 days of life, please help reddit.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-24 08:28:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-24 08:29:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>6 days, $200 left to raise, please help Reddit, Minumum donation is $1AUD, help create the miracle families need. Every cent counts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First logo, can I please get some feed-back?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-11 10:50:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm doing a diploma and to make a logo was in 1 of my projects. http://imgur.com/b0m6gxw It's for my fictional design business, tell me what you guys think please and give me some feed-back on what I could do differently or better. Thanks! edit: Okay so I now know I haven't created a logo in the above link, here is a logo http://imgur.com/bDYCCGB if I could get feedback on both that'd be great!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-11 11:11:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, thanks! What would I do differently for a logo? Like, how could I use what I've used there, to make a logo?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-11 12:04:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://imgur.com/bDYCCGB So then which of these 2 do I use for business cards? And if I use number 2, what good then is number 1? Should number 1 have been done differently?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-11 12:09:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://imgur.com/bDYCCGB So then which of these 2 do I use for business cards? And if I use number 2, what good then is number 1? Should number 1 have been done differently?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can I get feed-back on this, I'm learning photoshop!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-12 04:21:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a student, I'm just learning to use photoshop and would like some feed-back or tips on how I can do better! Please and thanks. http://imgur.com/fX3Mcpe,F5jemJZ</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-12 05:31:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just if it's done smoothly etc any mistakes or things you can see I could of done differently or better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-12 05:45:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>What tools would you recommend to use for doing that? Do you know of any tutorials to help with shadows? Thanks for your feed-back!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Silver III need coach, sick of being bad</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-15 19:30:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please... Help, just 1-2 hours of your day, I am sick of being bad and want to progress to the next level. My Skype alias is "subject2547" and same goes for my LoL alias. Add me please, and help. I have a ton of recordings and also software for you to watch me do live games.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-26 22:17:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>How long is it supposed to take before we can play? :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-28 17:10:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I is his cousin, so I guess that's a "no" then?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-28 18:33:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>wanker</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-28 18:33:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>wanker</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-07 15:56:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I could "insert something here" I would be soooo happy...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-07 15:57:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck? This should be tagged NSFW.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-07 16:09:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mangoes [edit] I always used to eat mangoes off our mango tree out the back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-07 16:21:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Proof.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-07 16:23:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>OP is a troll.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-07 16:32:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought "do you like cock"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-09 01:57:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should be careful posting this shit.. You'll answer questions about their gang? C'mon.. You're gunna get yourself and family killed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-09 13:39:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I the only one who thinks they look pure evil?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-10 05:24:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was little, 7 or 8... My mum had long finger nails all of a sudden, I asked her what happened? She told me a story about how she was at a pub and there was a gypsy who offered her a wish for her good customer service, Mum thought it was a joke so wished for long fingers nails... I immediately called her a bitch for not wishing to be rich and proceeded to cry... I realised a few years ago, I'm 26.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-12 11:46:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's wrong with South California... ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-12 14:35:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Think thats the sort of thing that will land me in jail for credit card fraud lol, no thanks..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is "Naruto: The Last" available on DVD yet?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-14 12:21:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is Naruto: The Last available on DVD yet?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I bought her this so she had some room..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-17 10:57:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-21 16:40:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Farm barrels for BP and farm ore nodes...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is so cool.. Yay science!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-24 02:09:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Reddit, can you impress me with one sentence?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-04 09:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-04 11:19:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>no philosophical figure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-04 11:19:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>no philosophical figure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-04 11:19:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unimpressed. Wtf Internet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-04 11:19:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Quiet, drunk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-04 11:20:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because I'm more impressive than you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Reddit, off the top your head... What is the coolest thing you said or done?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-06 08:05:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-06 08:25:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sometimes when I'm falling asleep, I get paralyzed, why?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-12 11:07:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's happened twice in the last week, whilst trying to go to sleep, I experience a buzzing sensation, like vibration... Like I'm falling asleep MEGA fast, it startles me a bit and it's then followed by me being awake but unable to move or talk, the longest this state has lasted is 3-4 minutes. What is this? Should I be going to see a doctor? Is it dangerous? edit: What is causing it? I've never had it before, except for within the last week.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does honey disinfect a wound?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-07 13:17:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-09 05:55:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>A big kick in the dick and balls.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-09 06:12:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sobriety.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-09 06:39:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Farting. Women farting is fucking disgusting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-09 06:43:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have anger issues :3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-09 06:51:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like you just explained it... Downvote.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-09 06:55:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks more like the dogs tongue, not the babies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-09 07:00:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is she telling you not to pass away?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-09 07:01:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>No.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-13 16:10:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was 11/14 a second ago... You're a liar. http://imgur.com/Qna4HtG</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL you get more nutrition from nuts/seeds if you "activate" them before consumption</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-15 15:38:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My new girlfriend is a Brat, how do I do BDSM with her?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-18 07:31:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I just found out she's a Brat, I never knew what it was so I looked it up, and I'm turned on. I want to do some BDSM with her but how do I do it? I was thinking of next time just shoving my dick in her ass and punching her and tying her up and stuff, what do you guys think?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-18 07:38:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do they actually like that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-18 07:59:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you mean for being abusive? I thought sluts loved that sort of thing...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-20 10:14:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah except guys were not made to take it in the ass, sluts were... I'm meant to dominate not her ask her about her feelings... DOMINATION!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-26 14:18:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>your cells age because of a thing called free radicals, they are produced as a bi-product of a chemical reaction in the body.. which can be anything from breathing to eating bla bla bla... free radicals fuck your cells up, then when your cells multiply they are a little bit shitter than they were before... the way to slow down aging is by eating anti-oxidants, they will stop the free radicals from attaching to your cells, suiciding in the process... meaning when your cells multiply, they are better than they would of been had that free radical attached to it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-26 14:22:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ed Sheeran</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shouldn't it be 360P? Not 480P?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-26 20:03:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>360+360 is 720P plus 360 is 1080P... what is this 480 and why?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"America will fall", is this bullsh*t? Can anyone link reliable sources to back it up?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-27 15:00:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 17:06:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why risk injury? Keep good form.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 17:10:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>No man. There is a 90 minute window, give or take, for you to get energy into your muscles. Don't listen to these other guys, if you wait more than that you will put your gains and recovery time at risk. You want to consume quick carbs straight after your work out, to release insulin to your blood which is a growth hormone. I got 12 kilos in 12 weeks by drinking 1 letre of water, 6 table spoons of glucose and a teaspoon of creatine straight after a work out. This isn't sustainable for a long time, so only do it for 8-12 weeks, or you risk getting diabetes. After that, consume a meal with regular carbs and protein and fats, then any meals after that should be Low GI foods, such as quinoa or fruits/nuts etc and tough to digest meats.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 17:15:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you don't use it, you lose it. Keep a healthy, balanced diet and you will lose less, ofcourse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 17:26:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey mate. I'd recommend going something like; Upper Body, Lower Body, Core, Cardio. This way you aren't over training anything, especially your rotator cuffs. Lift heavy, to increase muscle mass, which will in-turn raise your metabolic rate. Try to eat only low GI food until after you have trained, you can then eat some high GI foods straight after (in your 90 minute window) as those carbs will be used to help fuel muscle recovery and restore energy supplies. After your post-work out meal go back to low GI foods. Don't eat too close to bed time, because when you sleep your muscle recovery is fueled by burning fat. Feel free to ask any questions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 17:28:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Work shoulders 3 times in 4 days? Sounds like a recipe for a rotator injury.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 17:34:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bro... Go to the gym, of course you can go to the gym. Be safe and aware of what you can and can't do, and everything will be fine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 17:37:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chest works shoulders, Back works shoulders, Shoulders works shoulders. I don't think there is a reason to throw in the shoulders day, when he will be doing his shoulders on chest and back day. He will injure himself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 17:41:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was a really good answer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 17:46:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure, the delts will only be stabalisers in some of the exercises, but your 4 rotator cuffs can be easily over worked. I'm not saying it will happen but my experience as a personal trainer tells me not to train clients like this. EDIT: New clients*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 17:51:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is because of your fight or flight responses and adrenaline. Your body thinks you're running for a reason, so it gets rid of everything in your body that doesn't need to be there, to help you in combat. People have been known to throw up as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 18:11:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Source? I'm a personal trainer, and working your shoulders 3 days out of 4 is how you can injure yourself, probably a rotator cuff... It's common sense, I don't need to source it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 18:43:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe experienced lifters can train like that if they set out their program properly, but it's not a good idea to throw this at a new comer... No need to be a dick head, mate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 18:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Indeed. For a new comer though, I would recommend just avoiding this all together, until he's a bit more experienced. Keep it simple.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-30 03:55:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I studied on campus with a reputable company here in Australia, I've got my cert 3 and 4 in Fitness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-30 13:28:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can see him?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 06:39:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's because my chest muscles are more developed than my back muscles, I think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 17:25:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>nah you're fine, just make sure your program is adjusted accordingly... i'm a personal trainer, i can help you if you'd like.. what are your goals? fat loss, muscle building, both, fitness?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 17:26:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pshh...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 17:31:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>man... dump that prick, he doesn't know his stuff! i'm a personal trainer, a good one. listen to me. anything up to 15 degrees on your feet rotated laterally (outward) is fine, anymore and you start activating muscles you don't wanna activate... so totally parallel is wrong... keep your shoulders back and down, and don't lean too far forward... easy... you need to watch for pelvic tilt, which is at the bottom of your squat, if you get too low for yourself (everyone is different) you will see your pelvis tilt... do it infront of a mirror, your glutes are huge man (your butt) your quads will fatigue before your glutes which is why they probably feel sorer, try packing on some weight... get a new personal trainer EDIT: also, try to make sure your knee's aren't bending in, like toward each other, and i'll say it again, get a new trainer! charging you for quality service, SERIOUSLY!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 17:38:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>it completely depends on your goals mate, and your current fitness level, what are your goals? and out of 10, rate your fitness level</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 17:39:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>roughly, moderate to high intensity training session is gunna be about 2000kj or 500calories for an hour</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 17:48:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey buddy, good on you for getting help instead of giving up! you will progress I promise you that.. If your goals are to gain muscle and lose body fat, stick to compound movements when you exercise, so recruiting more than 1 group of muscles, for example... Dumbell curl, isolated... Push-up, compound... (a good way to tell is if you're using more than 1 joint IE a squat uses knee and hip, they both flex and extend so it's compound, where as dumbell curl only uses elbow) this will burn most amount of energy. Also, if you're doing shoulders, make ure you aren't over working them, people get out there and go "oooohh I need a big back so i'll do a huge back day, oh i need a massive chest im doing chest day next... oh yeah now i need massive shoudlers, shoulder day is next"... Hello, you've worked your shoulders 3 days in a row... Even though you're doing a chest press you're still using your anterior delt, even though you're doing a seated row you're still using your posterior delts... Take a few days off, 4-7 days until they feel fine, then ease back into it, be sure to BREAK YOUR ROUTINES UP. I suggest for you if you're new in the gym, maybe do like... Upper body (chest,back,arms) lower body(legs) core and cardio, 4 days... That way everything is broken up nicely... You don't necessarily HAVE to smash your shoulders, chest and back will work them, but if you insist of OHP and training your shoulders, make sure your form is right. Ask me about proper form if you'd like... By doing compound exercises you disrupt more muscle which means you burn more energy at the time, and more muscle needs to repair over the next 2-3 days, raising your metabolic rate aswell, even throw in 20-30 minutes cardio after your session to burn extra weight. Don't go too intense though, stay at around 55%-75% intensity to maximise your weight loss</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 17:58:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>You'll be fine... Make sure you're eating the right foods, at the right times, and make sure your form is good, you will be okay. Feel free to ask me any questions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 18:07:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you want to gain muscle mass, you should be upping the weight. You want to only be able to JUST get out 10-12 reps on your first set... then say 10-11, 9-10 and so on, this will create the best hypertrophy. Also be sure to eat properly and at the right time. Feel free to ask for tips.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 18:14:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm... Your abs are your abs, there is no top and bottom only left and right sides of your rectus abdominus muscles. You need to burn fat. Could I suggest changing your routine a little? Upper body, Lower body, Core, day off, repeat. Add 20-30 minutes of moderate intensity cardio just to burn a little extra weight after your strength training (Say, 60-70% intensity). Lay off any high GI foods until after you've trained (refer to this http://www.fitandfabforlife.us/uploads/1/2/5/6/12569263/4894854.png?696 High numbers = High GI. Predominantly you you want to eat low GI foods, except after training, because you need to carbs in fast to refuel your muscles and also to release insulin which is a growth hormone. Feel free to ask any questions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 18:17:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>3000 calories a day? that's 12000 kilojoules? Wow. Too many mate. Eat about 1500-2000, that should be plenty enough. Also, only eat high GI foods after training, predominantly you should be eating low GI foods through the day... This should give you some idea of what to eat. http://www.fitandfabforlife.us/uploads/1/2/5/6/12569263/4894854.png?696</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 19:51:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>No... It's not... Your BMR is probably 7000-ish kj that's what you need to live doing nothing... If you're consuming almost double that, you're going to put on weight, fast. Simple.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 19:55:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. I don't see much reason for you to use your ATP/CP energy system, this is "gear 3" or your fast twitch fibers. You want to work anywhere from 1% to 80% intensity with your cardio, meaning a walk to a 3/4 pace jog (this varies depending on your fitness level, for some people a brisk walk could be 60% intensity, for some people a brisk walk is only 30% intensity, be honest with yourself as to how hard you are working out. I strongly recommend you to do some kind of weight's training, as it will increase your metabolic rate as well as burn fat while you train. The reason it will increase your metabolic rate is because of recovery. If it take 2-3 days for your muscles to stop hurting, that's 2-3 days of recovery. Your body requires energy to recover so it will burn fat. Your diet is also a big factor for you. You want to refrain from any high GI foods except for after you train, to replish energy supply to your muscles. Predominantly you want to eat low GI foods throughout the day. http://www.fitandfabforlife.us/uploads/1/2/5/6/12569263/4894854.png?696 Here is a glycemic index table, the higher the number next to a food type, the higher GI it is. You want to eat mostly low numbers. EDIT: Source - I'm a personal trainer. A good one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-02 15:48:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, he's right... I'm a personal trainer myself, and I'd have to agree with him, you just get a better work out. Stabalisers are engaged, your core is more engaged, and you can't cheat by having a dominating hand take more of the load.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 09:20:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not a beginner, I'm a personal trainer, but I don't have a strong understanding of this stuff. It's not a myth either, lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 09:24:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't mean 100% depletion on my ATP, but it's enough for those type 2 fibres to not want to work as effectively.. So, I'm not getting out as many reps because I'm only allowing 1 minute between sets? Am I better off lifting only 70% and resting for 1 minute? Or remaining doing what I'm doing with 3 minutes rest?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A question about muscle fibres and energy systems.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 09:26:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, the title would of been huge. When I train chest, I smash out my first 3-6 sets, anything after that I can't lift very heavy because of fatigue. All my ATP supplies are depleted, so this means I'm now using my lactate energy system and type 2 fibers, instead of my type 2 b fibres, right? and lifting sorts 70-85% then if I fatigue more, I'm using my aerobic energy system and my type 1 energy systems... Once I fatigue to this point, I'm still going to get a pump, but am I still going to grow much from training in this zone? My understanding is that type 1 muscle fibres have minimal growth and type 2 have moderate muscle growth? Please... Don't comment if you're guessing, Exercise scientists and educated responses only. Should I lift only at say 80-90% so I can stay in my lactate system and not deplete my ATP supplies completely?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 11:33:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty sure what I said is accurate. What is wrong about it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 11:41:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does your 5th point mean it's hard to gain muscle mass lifting less heavy sets, and easier doing more slightly lighter sets? My goals are to gain muscle mass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A question about energy systems and muscle fibers.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 12:12:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry about title, but I didn't know where to start, or how to not make it a paragraph long. First thing is first, my goals are to gain muscle mass. So, I lift heavy, probably 75% I guess? I dunno, I get 12 JUST, then 10, then 8 (dumbell chest press for this example). So I guess this is using my glycolytic system and type 2a fibres... But after I do my chest press, I go to do a machine press and I can't press very heavy, do I need to wait longer between sets and changing exercises? Or perhaps I'm lifting heavier than I think, and am using my type 2b fibers? Am I not waiting long enough for my ATP/CP supplies to rejuvenate?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 12:20:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought that if my type 2b fibres begin to turn off, then type 1 and type 2a will be left to do the job. Doesn't that mean I'd begin to start using a different energy system, or not necessarily? Does the energy system just depend on intensity despite the muscle fibers being used? EDIT: I get 12 JUST, then 10, then 8 (Dumbell chest press for this example)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 12:41:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, what muscle fibers would I use for hypertrophy, type 2a right? What is a way to indicate to myself what muscle fibers I'm using, do I just measure my intensity? Say... Getting 12,12,12 for my db press? And type 2b would be say 1-6 reps? and type 1 would be 15-25 reps?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 12:45:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Varying rep ranges through training blocks or undulating periodisation is probably a good idea. Can you elaborate on this? I just want to know what is happening and what is being used and all that when I'm exercising. I'm training to be a personal trainer see, so I think it's important I understand all this stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-05 15:58:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's lying to prove a point. Fore shame.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-07 07:04:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the spoilers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-07 13:33:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't say you broke rules, I just said thanks for spoiling part of the anime for me...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My person trainer gave me this program. I'm new to the gym and my goals are to gain muscle mass, what do you think guys?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-07 13:37:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I fill in the x kg every week to measure my progress. Here is the Program -- gt; http://imgur.com/2Kg5Oo5 EDIT: Also, if I should change anything, what and why?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do I get a border for my Team Rank?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-07 15:39:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do I get a border for my ranked 5's rank? Or just solo q?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-07 15:42:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>What? In a normal game I keep a diamond bordeR?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-16 22:14:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there a source anywhere to confirm it's today?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I thought this was a nice gesture..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-20 07:04:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the best way to condition shins for Muay Thai fighters?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-03 13:22:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been searching around online for quite a while, and found various things like whacking it with lumps of wood to rolling it out with a rolling pin, and even just good old fashioned kick a bag, lots, for many years. Though I can't find anything with solid sources, and I was hoping someone who is credible from Reddit could point me in the right direction. Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 23:45:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, mate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-23 13:18:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>wow... mark your shit as a spoiler, donk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-24 16:06:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright. Is there a reason why runners need to top their glucose up more often, like a marathon runner? 2 and a half hours is a LONG time to be training for, with nothing to top up. I mean, the liver only stores about 100gm of glycogen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 06:49:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do my heal aura's heal my eggs against betsy? I can't seem to get the DPS to kill her...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Some leaked footage of the Warcraft movie.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-01 09:37:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-02 12:27:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>A God C:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can someone please give me the ins and outs of meditation?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-03 12:40:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is it? How do I do it? What does it feel like? I have a lot of anger. I have a lot of character defects in general. I have been told meditation will help me to cure these things, but I don't understand how. I have Googled to learn how to do it, but it says just concentrate on my breathing... How the fuck does that make me less angry? Do I have to think about something, or what? I don't get it... Please, I want to work on myself, help me. Thanks in advance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-05 17:33:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why :(? Did she die instantly? Where do you all find this information. The only thing I find is they are trying to charge him, are we sure he did it? Or does everyone just reckon it was him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>And I grew up to think bikers were scary..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-07 12:34:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ideally, how long should I train before my first amateur Muay Thai fight?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-09 13:01:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>26 year old male, pretty fit, been doing Muay Thai for 2 months. There is a tournament coming up in November, so by the time of the tournament I'll be at 4 months. Is that a substantial amount of to be ready for a fight? Or do people usually wait longer? I know you can't really make the call because it depends on the individual a bit, but, lets say on average. EDIT: This is just an interclub tournament, shinguards and 10-14oz gloves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How long should I train before my first amateur Muay Thai fight?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-09 13:16:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>26 year old male, pretty fit, been doing Muay Thai for 2 months. There is a tournament coming up in November, so by the time of the tournament I'll be at 4 months. Is that a substantial amount of to be ready for a fight? Or do people usually wait longer? I know you can't really make the call because it depends on the individual a bit, but, lets say on average. EDIT: This is just an interclub tournament, shinguards and 10-12oz gloves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-09 13:17:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>My man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-09 13:21:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd probably be fighting people around the same skill level as me, also, please check the edit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-09 13:42:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah it's just an interclub with gloves and shin guards</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-09 13:44:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. Please check edit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-09 13:44:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check the edit and let me know if you feel the same way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-09 13:45:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check the edit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-11 11:36:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>fuck you i'm going to win fights and become a talented fighter</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-11 11:39:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>What? I just thought his answer showed some heart... Also, the thing he said about experience was cool. I wasn't after any answer in particular, you fuckin cock sucker.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I have massive self confidence issues, and just want an honest, anonymous rating. (Sorry for the poor quality.)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-14 12:39:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I have massive self confidence issues, and just want an honest, anonymous rating. (Sorry for the poor quality.) [M26]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-14 12:53:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I just finished my first ever meditation, is it supposed to be difficult?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 09:11:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I realise it's supposed to be a very simple, peaceful thing.. I was finding it very difficult to think of nothing, I spent more time reminding myself I'm supposed to be thinking of nothing, than I did thinking of nothing. I focused on my breathing a bit, to distract myself. Will it get easier to focus on nothing? When I found myself focusing on nothing for 3-4 seconds I would then realise I was focusing on nothing "omg I'm doing it" lol. I must admit it felt relieving to think of nothing, though very unnatural to me. Peaceful, but sure enough my brain would come storming back in thinking of all kinds of things.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 09:25:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, so even the pro's don't think of nothing for hours on end? Thanks a lot for your feed-back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 10:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>"A crazy hyper-active monkey, that's drunk, and being attacked by a swarm of wasps. The idea is to take away the alcohol, the wasps, and calm the monkey down." Thanks for your in-put, I appreciate it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 14:37:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>i feel that if i'm focusing on my breath i am still focusing on something, and true peace would come from focusing on nothing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 16:39:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Intuition.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can someone explain why nm3 is 490 ipwr but nm4 is 900?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-20 18:45:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can someone explain why nm3 is 490 ipwr but nm4 is 900? Is nm4 still possible? How?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-23 01:13:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or maybe you're in Dungeon Defenders.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ectogenesis or 'artificial wombs' to be expected in the next 20 years.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-28 03:40:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can someone please tutor me?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-30 15:23:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi there, I've been playing league of legends for about 3 years, but I am stuck in silver. I don't know how to get better, and I just want to stop being bad. I'm a student at the moment, and paying loans etc so my income is very limited, but I can arrange some kind of payment, is anyone willing to be my tutor? I'm friendly and a fast learner, PLEASE help me :( EDIT: I'm in OCE server</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why does human growth slow down so substantially once we leave the womb?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-02 13:45:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-04 08:35:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>This aint any 19 year old. It's Sage Northcutt, he has 77 martial arts world titles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>f I go from Gym straight into MuayThai, should I try eat between them both or just eat after MuayThai?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-07 05:30:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would it be better to eat between gym and MuayThai? Or after the 2 of them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-07 05:56:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll only be in the gym for 30-40 minutes. I have no need to train in excess of 45 minutes atm. I might just drink some kind of quick carbs between them then, maybe some glucose water with a little bit of sodium.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-07 09:34:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because you need to fuel your body properly, to maximise recovery times and performance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-07 10:53:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to compete, but I'm still in the beginner class. The gym is next to MuayThai and MuayThai is an hour away from my house, so it's best to train them both at once if I can.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-07 11:19:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I won't isolate anything, like, if I went and did tri-extensions I'd be struggling to punch, lol. I'll just stick to some pretty basic, functional, compound stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Meth, not even once.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-09 06:38:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A pregnant woman goes into a coma...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-13 10:03:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>A pregnant woman goes into a coma 3 months into her pregnancy, 7 months later she wakes up and is told by the doctor she had successfully shit out twins. Due to her being in a coma, her brother was given permission to name them. "Oh no, not my brother, he's an idiot! What are their names?" "The girls is called Denise" "Oh that's not so bad... What about the boy?" "Denephew"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ELI5 What is Obama doing to help terrorist groups and why?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-13 10:14:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I lost my watch at a party once...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-14 01:38:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I lost my watch at a party once. I saw this guy stepping on it while sexually assaulting a girl. I walked up to him and punched him right in the nose. No one does that to a girl. Not on my watch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-15 04:04:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I fucking love Russian woman.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If everything in the Universe, from the big bang, didn't happen exactly the way it did, would I still be here?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-15 07:33:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>If everything in the Universe, from the big bang to life on earth, didn't happen exactly the way it did, would I still be here? I'm talking about from the big bang, molecules bouncing around, diffusion, all the tiny Billions of variables that could of been different, if any of them were different, even by 1 molecule or something, is it possible I might never have come into existence? I didn't know where else to put this I'm open to suggestions for a re-post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-15 08:18:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what I'm asking, that's exactly what I'm asking, on a much larger, more complex scale.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-15 08:20:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've basically came to the conclusion that everything in the entire Universe happened in that 100% truly perfect way to give me life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-15 14:08:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not so much referring to a meteor on the other side of the planet affecting my conception. Though, what I'm saying I guess would mean that if everything didn't happen the exact way it did, my parents would not be banging, and that asteroid wouldn't be there to hit a planet either, so I'll include it anyway. If all molecules did not diffuse and the universe did not cool down at the exact rate it did and all the other stuff that goes with it, that meteor and planet might not even exist, much like earth. What I'm trying to say, I assure you, is a very concept grasp for me to handle, and I'm struggling to get it into words with just a few sentences.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-15 14:08:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you elaborate on your answer please.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-16 06:02:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I'm saying if everything didn't happen as it did, would I be here. Exactly, as it happened.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-16 06:03:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like you're the only person who comprehended my question. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-16 06:07:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well philosophy deleted it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-20 08:28:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would give me different results than what I'm after. Thanks for your input though, friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-20 15:46:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like, do reverse fly's using a band?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>That 70's Show premiered in 1998 and was based in the year 1978, 20 years prior. If there were a modern day equivalent, it'd be called "that 90's show"and be based in 1995. Have fun feeling old as fuck.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-20 15:56:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-20 16:44:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is it stupid? It's a perfectly legitimate question, I'm asking what I would have to do as far as training the posterior side of my body, to make sure I don't get muscular imbalances. You are stupid, not the question.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-20 16:46:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Inb4powertrippingadminbansmefromadvancedfitnessbecauseihurthislittlefeelings</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-20 18:50:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I want to do endurance training, train my muscles to become efficient in removing lactic acid, and to become a lot more durable. They are 2 different energy systems. Training the way you said would result in hypertrophy, which is muscle growth, not really what I'm after.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-21 04:13:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's mind blowing cause you're a dog cunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Back to the future in ACTUAL 2015!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-21 07:13:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>900 Dollarydoos?!? Let's change the name of Australian Currency!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-22 00:01:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to survive heart attacks, doctors guarantee this can save atleast 1 in 10, so let's share it with the whole of Reddit.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 06:45:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-29 14:57:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Colese is what she takes. I think it might be IBS after doing a little research, but I don't know how that would affect her energy levels?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Model from Goldcoast Australia begs judge not to have conviction after a meth fuelled car accident so she can fulfill her dream of living at the playboy mansion</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-05 23:12:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Locals rally to continue trying to save a dog stuck under ground, after authorities gave up and abandoned the dog.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-06 12:19:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-06 13:56:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry for your loss. Beagle's are great dogs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-06 21:51:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's safe :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-06 21:52:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's safe :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-06 22:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should attach proof when you say things like that, also, here -- "They argue that a medium-size dog consumes 90 grams of meat and 156 grams of cereals daily, resulting in a footprint of 0.84 hectares, while a Toyota Land Cruiser uses 55.1 gigajoules yearly, equating to a footprint of about 0.41 hectares. However, they make some questionable assumptions #8212;first off ignoring that dog food is mostly byproducts that might not otherwise be used in the human food chain; then by assuming that the vehicle will only be driven 10,000 km (about 6,200 miles) annually. According to the Department of Energy, the true U.S. average is more than twice that, at 13,700 miles. Sightline also points to a number of ways in which the energy the SUV uses #8212;supposedly including the cost of manufacture #8212;was severely underestimated, with the true figure about three times what they give, before including indirect impact like roads, bridges, and fuel infrastructure."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 07:15:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're allowed to care about more than 1 thing at once.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 08:56:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>No it's not. People care about the wars civilians are dying because of. People care about the homeless. People care about disease. People care. It's the corporations like the Governments who won't do anything about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the point in doing 200+ crunches?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 09:31:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>At my MuayThai gym, I find myself doing 200+ crunches per session, which is neat. I mean, it's big numbers we hit some times 400+ but.. Why? Wouldn't we be better off doing them weighted, and growing the muscles? Doing that high reps won't produce much muscle growth, rather condition them to remove lactic acid more efficiently.. Thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The sky over Brisbane, Australia.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 10:04:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 10:40:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would there be any point in training high reps at class, and in my own time, say at the gym, doing hypertrophy training on them with some weight?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 10:41:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol, no. They want to make money, not waste it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-08 05:44:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice, and here I am always trying to nibble the chocolate off to see what's under it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-13 05:34:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>My Dad's friends all call his Spec, cause 'back in the day' he was really good at this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ELI5: What is atmospheric pressure?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-13 05:38:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-13 13:06:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh okay, another person told me lots of masturbation would help. I think what you said makes more sense, and my willy is starting to hurt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why is my teacher telling me that carbs cannot be turned to fat?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-14 09:40:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I know, what the fuck? I'm confused too... Is this just his personal opinion? He said that, carbs are bad because the body will burn them before fat, meaning the body will store fat instead of burning it, cause it wants to burn the carbs first. He said, you can't turn water in to wine, you can't turn carbs in to fat. I've always learned that excess energy in the form of carbs, will be stored as energy to be used later in the form of fat, so what the actual fuck?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Facebook.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-15 01:32:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-15 01:36:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>He said there is no scientific studies backing that carbs turn to fat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-15 01:38:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Heaps of people have explained it here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-15 01:39:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Proof and further explanation please.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-15 03:16:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>But I read a lot of stuff that says it's not complicated or rare :L If you eat more than your BMR in a day, the excess energy will be stored as fat. It is not rare to eat more than your BMR in a day, can you please explain this better, if I'm not understanding it properly?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-15 03:21:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Umm.. Okay.. So.. Carbs are broken into glucose by enzymes, glucose goes to the blood stream, then the pancreas will release insulin to push the glucose into cells to be made into ATP, stored as glycogen in the muscles or if the body is in excess (those storages are full) will be turned to triglycerides (fat droplets). I just don't get it, because people are saying that for the carbs to be turned to fat is a 'rare' thing. I don't think people being in excess of their glucose amounts is very rare. In fact, looking at our obesity epidemic, I'd say it's common play. By saying this, you're saying it's no longer energy in Vs energy out...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-15 03:33:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>But, I have been taught that glucose can be turned into triglycerides... By the liver.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-15 03:40:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't get it because people are telling me it's very rare for carbs to be turned to fat. When everything I read tell me it is not rare at all. Glucose will be in the blood stream, the pancreas releases insulin to push it into cells and any excess is sent to the liver, to be converted to triglyceries, which will then be stored in fat cells. THIS makes sense to me. This explains why eating too many calories can put on weight. People saying that carbs cannot be turned to fat, or it's very rare, does not explain to me how eating too many carbs can make someone gain weight. Other than it being consumed with large amounts of fat, but for me this is not a common thing. I'm talking about with a regular, healthy diet, but larger than average portions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-16 05:37:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, but I disagree that carbs being converted to fat is a rare process.. other wise where do they go? They can't be stored if the stores are full, excess carbs are broken down to glucose and sent to the liver to be turned into triglycerides which are stored in fat cells.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-16 11:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh, yeah you may have a problem activating your glutes, just check your knee's aren't bending in, keep your posture good. Youtube posture if you aren't sure, and go from there. What you need to remember though, is that your glutes are HUGE. It's fine for your lower back or even I guess your quads to fatigue or get more DOMS than your glutes, this doesn't mean they aren't activating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The people have spoken.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-17 12:01:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-17 12:04:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>It gets the enzymes and stuff all crankin, releases nutrients etc that would help it turn into stuff...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-18 06:12:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fucks me dick head, I'm just telling you why people wanna 'activate' their almonds. This is what they think. Go argue your point with someone that gives a shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 05:53:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep, sweet. I got this covered. PT Student here. You sit infront of a computer all day, so you probably sit with rounded shoulders, giving you a tight chest and lengthened back muscles. A posteriorly tilted pelvis, which rounds your lower back, giving you tight hamstrings and lengthened glutes. You also probably have tight hip flexors, and IT band, anyway, here's what to do. You need to get a Physio Foam Roller. Youtube how to roll out your Quads and IT band, and your chest, this will release those tightened/shortened muscles. Also search up some good stretches for these muscles VIA youtube. You need to strengthen your erector spinae which is muscle in your back, just back extentions will do for this. You need to strengthen your Glutes with some hypertrophy training, like squats. You also need to strengthen you retractor muscles in your back, so doing Rows and Pull downs etc will fix this. Feel free to PM me if you have further questions or just ask me here, this will take you from tight hips, tight hamstrings, curled shoulders hunched over etc to a nice straight posture, for the most part. Obviously I can't give you the perfect routine for rehabilitating you without being face to face, but this will make some MASSIVE improvements. EDIT: Core stability exercises will always help you too, get a fit ball and do some core stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 07:03:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey mate, if I was able to be with you face to face I'm sure I would be able to be of some benefit to you, but I really don't want to go prescribing something to you, for a situation that I can't see for myself. Posterior and Anterior tilts from being at computers and stuff are easy because they are common. I would really recommend you go to see a physio therapist, they can help with this. It could be mechanical issue that has caused a muscle imbalance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 07:10:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 07:18:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep, sweet. I got this covered. PT student here. Lifting the weights, building your muscle mass is good, this will increase your BMR which is basically the amount of energy your body requires in a day to stay a alive, assuming you did nothing but laid in bed. This is why you lift weights to lose weight. Lifting weights the way you are uses an energy system called ATP-CP and will not burn much fat or carbs, but will increase your BMR, because your muscles grow and require more to live and also they need to be repaired, which also costs energy. SO THAT IS LIFTING, now CARDIO uses an energy system called your aerobic system. In your aerobic system you will use a different energy source, your source now becomes Muscle Glycogen (carbs) and fats. So your body will literally use fat as a energy source, as well as carbs. What you are doing is fine. You need to lift heavy, to increase your muscle mass and your BMR and also to expel more energy by repairing those muscles, and you need to do cardio because your heart will be happy and you will use fat as an energy source. you're 19 so your max heart rate is about 200ish, you want to exercise at 30-55% intensity when you do cardio, so 30-55% of that max heart rate is where you wanna be to maximise your fat burn during cardio (You must take your resting heart rate into consideration, so if it's 60, 30% extra of 200 max will be 100-170BPM. Sorry for the long winded answer, but I felt it necessary so you can understand. Enjoy your life, friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 07:26:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>What kind of running do you do, sprints or long distance? What are you trying to achieve? I can't give you a good anything unless I know what you want, everything is good but maybe not good for you... Are you looking to increase endurance cause you want to run further? Do you want to run 100-200 meters?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 07:30:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any beginner should just dedicate to 2-3 times a week, build a foundation of stability for their exercises by doing high reps of medium intensity say 60% of 1RM. After you have a solid foundation of this, and are able to work out 5-6 times a week without damaging anything or getting severe DOMS, you will progress into strength gaining, where your weight will increase and the reps will drop to about 8. You will stay at this weight until you can reach 12 reps of that weight, then increase it by 5-10%. You continue doing this until you are big as phuk. From strength training you can begin to go into power lifting, but it's another ball game entirely and you probably have no interest. PM or ask for more information on power lifting, have a good life, friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 07:34:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep, sweet. I got this covered. PT student here, and I'd be more than happy to assist you. There is 1 problem with the post though, what are your goals?? Looking at your sets and reps I'm going to assume you're after muscle mass, you wanna get bigger, get ripped, stay low body fat and look good. If that's the case, how many days can you dedicate to a week at your gym? How long do you have to dedicate per session? When do you want to reach your goals? On a scale of 1-10 how important is it that you reach your goals?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 07:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>[like this] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EfwRzjk-6Hs) Use a small ball, that's not too hard I.E tennis ball.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 07:51:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's good to keep a program for 6-8 weeks. This helps you keep track of your gains and can help to motivate you seeing them. Much longer than this though and you will start to plateau, but you can for example, just do variations I.E From bench press into incline bench press or push-ups into wide pushups, lat pull downs into wide grip lat pulldowns etc. This will cause you to use new neural pathways and stimulate your muscles in different ways resulting in growth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 07:57:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>These aren't signs of cancer lol. You're unfit, that's all. Headache is from lack of oxygen because your body isn't super efficient yet and delivering it around your body while you're under stress, which will change in time. Your ankles are just unconditioned, you're probably running on concrete, try running on grass, or a softer surface. The prickly itchy feeling is also fine, just continue to do what you're doing. I'm just going to add though, if you're looking to lose weight you should be lifting weights and cardio, not just cardio.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 08:16:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I would always recommend strength training to any person in the world, strength training will ALWAYS have benefits. Stronger glutes, quads, calves, back and core are ofcourse going to make it easier for you, you'll also look a lot better, healthier/fitter. Is it necessary to complete the hike? Probably not :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 09:15:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can see improvements in a few weeks. Depending on severity of muscle imbalances etc, but I'd say in most cases the problems can be corrected in 2-3 months. Unless the problems are mechanical meaning the structure of the skeleton due to birth defects etc, but yeah, muscular corrections not very long.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 09:23:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can't. Nothing significant anyway, there is no point targeting your wrist, lol. If you want to grow the muscle near your elbow though, the stronger your grip, the larger these will be. Also, do variations on your bi-curls.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 09:28:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uh, this is stupid. PT student here, and bench press is one of the most popular, most utilized chest exercises in the world for a reason. IT IS GOOD. It's compound, it's functional and it's simple. You will get a light weight when you start where you can do 12-15 reps for 3 sets, you will continue with this weight until you hit 20 reps for 3 sets. Then increase the weight to a point where you can only do 8-10 reps for 3 sets. You will continue with this weight until you can do 3 sets of 12, from there you will increase the weight by 5-10% every time you can do 3 sets of 12 of your new weight. This is safe, this is progressive, this is not dangerous at all. Your form will come into it but hey, the form for a bb benchpress is not very complicated, youtube it. Tell your parents to let you do a bench press because it is awkward telling all your friends how stupid they are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 09:32:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's DOMS - Delayed Onset Muscle Soreness. It peaks at 24-48 hours after your workout, it's fine. If you feel it is not in your muscles though, probably lay off heavy chest exercises until the pain stops, and lift lighter next time until you're stronger.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 11:06:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>So you're saying, because of the glycogen lost during an anaerobic session of higher intensity, fat will be taken from fat cells post-workout to refill the glycogen stores of muscles? Is this assuming you worked out on an empty stomach and didn't eat afterwards? Cause I believe your glycogen stores would be replenished from those carbs rather than fat. Could you please link a source for this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 11:09:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always learned that anaerobic exercise will burn more fat in volume, but less in percentage compared to aerobic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 13:31:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Genetics. Some peoples genetics will have them store a higher fat % over the abs, making it so that even with great diet and exercise it can still prove borderline impossible to get abs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 15:30:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>But the energy being expended during aerobic work out is derived from fatty acids, which is fat... From your fat cells. Where as anaerobic work outs the energy that is expended is carbohydrates... Working in Anaerobic state also will result in minimal strain on your muscles since the intensity is only going to be about 50-60%, where as hypertrophy would stimulate the muscles resulting in an increased energy expenditure for the next 48-36 hours, I really just don't understand what you're saying and I want to, I'm not saying you're wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 16:09:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I know that beta oxidisation will occur due to caloric defecit, but it also happens during an aerobic work out, because that's just how the body will get energy to fuel that specific work out. Are you saying that the body does not oxidise fat and use it to fuel aerobic exercise at all? Or are you just saying, despite that, it's still better to do higher intensity aerobic or anaerobic stuff because you will have a bigger energy demand to get the work out done, resulting in higher expenditure for the day? EDIT: I just don't see why getting your caloric deficit for the day using aerobic exercise isn't better, because not only do you get the defecit, you also literally melt the fat off while you're doing your aerobic cardio. The fat will literally be oxidized and turned to free fatty acids to be burned as fuel while you run, or jog or what ever. Where as anaerobic, you will be helping to reach your deficit the same as aerobic, but not oxidizing fat during the workout, instead burning carbs. EDIT: Are you saying that the amount of carbs that will be used will out weigh the fat burned if the workout is of a higher intensity?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 16:19:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like I smashed that nail right on the head with a big sturdy hammer. What you quoted is just me being confident in my ability to do so.. Problem?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-20 05:53:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, so you're saying that the fat % burned at 50% intensity is higher, but not the volume, compared to 70%? That makes sense. So because of the glycogen depletion during a 70% work out, fat will oxidise post work out to replenish the glycogen stores? That's so interesting. Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-20 11:42:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh really? Interesting. That makes me want to mix up my diet for 12 weeks and see what changes I can record, AMAZING! Thanks a lot, I enjoyed this. Have a good life, friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I probably won't be going for best brother of the year award any time soon... Or best father.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-20 13:57:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I probably won't win brother of the year... Or father.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-20 14:17:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-20 14:23:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>She hasn't shown him. It kinda says in the meme that she said no, then did it anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-20 14:43:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or I could not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-20 14:51:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>This.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-20 16:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, he's living happily with his wife and nephew.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Poor kitty, help my brother and his girlfriend who's cat was hit by a car and needs an operation</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-03 12:50:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Brother and his girlfriend' cat was hit by a car, help us to fix it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-03 12:51:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's the best way to keep my body highly alkalized?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-04 06:52:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eat vegetables? Buy a special powder? What should I do to my diet to make sure my body stays highly alkalized?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-05 09:29:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>How can I learn more about alkalinity, do you have any suggested reads?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-05 09:29:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>How can I learn more about alkalinity, do you have any suggested reads?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My girlfriend has changed her diet now and suffers from a lack of energy, but the changes were all positive, help?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-15 09:52:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>so my girlfriend is about 5"2' and she was weighing in at 39kg or 85 pound, so she was pretty skinny. She also has some sort of digestive problem, caused from stress, which is why she lost all the weight in the first place, anyway...I'm a personal trainer, and I have a decent understanding of balancing macro's and how to eat clean, so I've been helping her. So we changed her diet up to nothing processed, we eat tons of veggies fruit and meats, try not to buy anything packaged and make our meals ourselves. She is also exercising now, and drinking an all greens powder once daily, and due to all of these things she has indeed gained 5 kilos in just over a month. Despite all these positive changes to her diet and weight though, she says she feels flat, low on energy, bloated, is this just because of the diet changes? Will the body adapt to the new diet and go back to normal? Should we book in to a dietitian or a nutritionist? She has no allergies. EDIT: I also had her drinking a 70:30 carb:protein powdered shake twice daily for the initial 4 weeks, which has been pulled now and she now sources all her calories for the day from food stuffs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 00:55:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Enough carbs, yeah. The other 2 I'm not sure, would we check at a GP?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 00:57:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>She did have water retention in her legs for a couple of days but it seems to have worked itself out. Should we just go to the doctor and get her bloods done?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 00:58:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>She isn't under the stress anymore. She was working massive hours weekly and had an alcoholic boyfriend and she was just suffocating because of everything, that was 5 years ago. So she's been struggling with weight for a very long time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 01:01:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, thanks for your input. It's not celiacs she's been tested for sensitivity to foods, because her brother is Celiac. I wasn't with her when she was seeing the nutritionist so I can't really figure out what it is, but it sounds more like something closer to IBS, and her body wasn't creating it's own energy properly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 01:03:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, she's getting enough carbs. We're going to see a specialist, we're just working out the best approach.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 01:03:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, we also put her on a 70:30 carb:protein shake twice a day, to help with her daily intake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 01:16:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, how do we test for adrenal fatigue, will her doctor do it? More importantly, do you have a suggested read on how to fix it? I've just done a quick flick through some things and it certainly appears to be contributing to her situation, though I feel like something else is at play. Another redditor mentioned electrolyte imbalance, I feel that's at play also.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 01:17:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you please elaborate on malabsorption?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 01:41:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, well I'm a bit scared I'm going to have killed her now.. What should we do, book her in to a doctor asap and get referred to a dietitian? As for a more short term solution while we wait, should we get her an electrolyte supplement and maybe some vitamin supplements?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 01:49:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure you're following the thread properly... You're making it sound like she was overweight. She was underweight from stress, and is still 2 kilos underweight because she has muscle atrophy. Her body fat levels are healthy now we need to build her a few kilos of muscle that's all. We're trying to repair the damage the stress did to her body.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 01:55:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also, will it be fine for her to continue exercising with me? I have her doing interval stuff, she does about a 15 minute mid-high intensity circuit with me. While she is at risk of adrenal fatigue, refeeding syndrome etc will it be fine for her body to go under the stress of exercise? Or should I just tone the intensity down a little bit?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 02:47:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>We aren't really calorie counting, but at a rough average probably about 50-30-20 and she sleeps fine, just struggles to wake up sometimes. EDIT: I just mean it takes her a while to feel lively, sometimes up to an hour.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 02:48:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will a doctor really be able to help? Or are we best to get referred to a nutritionist/dietitian and seek help from them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-18 01:16:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>So as a dietitian, what do you think is going on?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What do I need to consider when designing a circuit?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-19 02:43:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I know when making a gym routine I need to consider a lot of things I.E hypertrophy is 8-12 reps and endurance is 15+ and power lifting is 1-6 I also need to consider the right tempo and do bigger muscle groups first etc, but what do I consider for making a circuit and what will influence these things?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-19 04:37:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that was of no help, hey, thanks for being a dick though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-19 04:55:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because I'm not asking for a program designed by pro's, I'm asking for what I should consider if I make my own, your reply contributed toward my answer zero. EDIT: You're a dick for insinuating I'm useless and have zero knowledge of fitness, and I should rely on the programs of a pro rather than seeking knowledge on how to understand the thought processes that should go in to the design my own effective circuit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-20 03:53:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm already a personal trainer and have an educated understanding of how to design programs of all kinds, I'm here looking for what other people consider important so I can broaden the way I do things. Not once did I say I'm inexperienced. You are the one who cam on here saying I'm inexperienced so I should just do what the pros do. Even if I weren't experienced the question is still asking what others take into consideration when designing a program, meaning I am wanting to better the way in which I design them and better understand the thought process people use when designing a program. All you did was say don't bother learning you obviously suck just copy the pros</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-21 05:21:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mate.. I'm not mentioning those things because I'm not making a specific program. I'm asking what things to consider while making ine. What don't you understand here? I feel like this really isn't very hard to understand... Then you insult my skills as a trainer simply because you are either ignorant or stupid, stop embarassing yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-25 03:58:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your blood pressure, friend. You need to see a doctor, to me this sounds like high blood pressure, but it could be more serious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-25 04:30:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personal trainer here. Your carbs are too low, that's the problem. You need carbs, it's broken down into Glucose which is your body's primary energy source. Your organs, muscles and brain need glucose. There can be instances where messing with your macro intake is a good idea, but 95% of the time 55% carbs 25% protein and 20% fat is fine, you just need the right AMOUNT of that, and also the right kinds of carbs. Stick to your same caloric intake, just alter the %'s of each macro you're having. EDIT: Maybe even try like 60:20:20 since you're not trying to muscle build, and you're doing a lot of cardio, you need to up your carbs :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-25 04:35:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eating poorly while you're drunk is a terrible idea. Let's take McDonalds for example. I've had 12 beers, the alcohol is coursing through my veins and the body is desperately trying to burn it as energy. So then I eat a burger, with carbs and fats in the same food item. My body will prioritise the alcohol to be used as energy over these 2 things, so guess what? They are converted to fat, so that the body can use the alcohol as energy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-25 04:35:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eating poorly while you're drunk is a terrible idea. Let's take McDonalds for example. I've had 12 beers, the alcohol is coursing through my veins and the body is desperately trying to burn it as energy. So then you eat a burger, with carbs and fats in the same food item. Your body will prioritise the alcohol to be used as energy over these 2 things, so guess what? They are converted to fat, so that the body can use the alcohol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 05:02:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, I do, as much as I can :) Thanks for your concern though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 05:07:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah mate, cardio will help you lose weight just fine. 30 minutes on a bike every day and you cut your calorie intake, that will lose weight just fine. Personally though, I recommend you doing some training with weights or even just body weight at home. If you build muscle, the cost of energy for your body to live every day goes up, so your daily intake for calories to live for a day goes up, which is good, because that means your metabolism is higher. The higher your metabolism the better, for losing weight. Not only that, you will expel more energy during workouts if you have bigger muscles, and also you will burn energy by training your muscles because it costs energy to repair the muscles. EDIT: You should also still be incorporating the cardio into your weekly schedule still.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 05:08:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's your routine at the moment, can you break down your week for me? Also give me a rough idea of what you generally eat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 05:13:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>How long have you actually been training for in the gym prior to starting the ICF5x5? Do you have any injuries or illnesses?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 05:16:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great to hear you're pumped to start weights training, how exciting of a time it is for you, my friend. Remember, you are the only thing stopping you from having the body of your dreams. PM me if you ever need help with programs or anything, and I'm ALWAYS happy to help :) Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 05:20:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, sweet :) Sounds like you really put a lot of effort in to fitness, and trying to live a healthy lifestyle, that's so good :) Perhaps break your week up a little bit differently though. Push/Pull day, Core, Legs and then perhaps do a cardio circuit or something on the 4th day, then you rest. 4 days work, 1 day rest, repeat. How come you do the plyometrics, do you have a specific goal? Are you just trying to lose weight, or build muscle? Or both?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 05:28:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I'm from Australia, and it's really kind of... I mean, I have seen all these work outs and I just don't really believe in them. Every single person has different goals, there is so many variations to what every person needs that I've never believed in a 1 program suits all sorta thing, I don't know that's just me personally. It's a good program though, don't get me wrong. If I were you though, I'd go back to Chest day/Back/Core/Legs/Rest/Repeat. I'd be doing your lifts at heavy enough to do 10-12 reps. So let's use bench press for example, get a weight you can only lift 10-12 times. Keep that weight, until you can reach 15 reps, you then increase the weight by 5-10% and repeat the process until you are big as fuck. Doing this will ensure that you are building muscle safely, you're progressing and growing in a safe, steady and measurable way. You will have good strength in all your stabilizer muscles and won't be at risk of injury.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 05:31:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also, when I see people in a gym, weather they are over-weight, ripped, skinny, male, female... I only think one single thing... Good on you for giving a fuck about yourself enough to get in here and look after your body. People in the gym don't judge you, they are proud of you for wanting to step up and say "No more, this is when I change, TODAY!" and anyone who judges you, is fucking scum, and I promise you that their opinions don't matter! I'll say it again, I'm roud of you for making the decision to make change :) Have a good life, friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 05:38:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey mate! Yeah it can get confusing, haha. Never mind, I will help you as much as I can :) If you were my client, I would go: Chest Day. Back Day. Core. Legs. Cardio. Repeat. As for sodium and sugar, don't bother counting, just don't have any where possible :) Try to not buy packaged or processed foods, and you'll be okay. For your program, you want more upperbody sets, than lower body sets, but you want your chest day relatively equal in sets to your back day. You will get your weights heavy enough to do 10-12 reps, you'll keep that weight on that exercise until you can do 15 reps, then you'll increase the weight by 5-10%. This will guarantee you steady, safe progression and will decrease the likelyhood of injury. Youtube and Google all your exercises before you use them. Google terms such as "Top 10 chest exercises" or "Best leg exercises" to make your program with. Here's a hint though, if a exercise sounds really fancy and difficult, it's probably trash. Stick to the good, compound exercises (compound means more than 1 muscle group is being used) like a good old fashioned squat, or bench press.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 05:42:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, awesome. I'd do a 4 day split, Chest, Back, Legs, Core. I'd train in the morning at the gym, and do a 20-30 minute body weight HIIT circuit at home. That would help ensure you continue to grow muscle, which will increase your metabolism etc to help you lose weight, as well as the HIIT to burn extra energy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 06:00:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, if you were my client I'd have you doing a strength program. They not only burn energy, but you will continue to burn energy afterwards because you need to repair from it. Also you get bigger muscles, so you will burn more energy everyday just from that, too. Men or women, both should train with weights. I know a lot of women are scared of them because they don't want to get huge, but you won't... Not easily. You don't have the testosterone levels to get that big. Also, stop drinking the protein shakes and just source your protein from meats/nuts/vege's etc. You should definitely eat fruit, please eat fruit. Eating fruit won't make you fat. Just stay away from packaged/processed foods, eat clean, train mean, you will lose your love handles :) edit: you should do a little cardio as well, but strength training is important.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 06:02:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should reach muscle failure at 12 reps, that's the weight you need. You should do that 3-4 times. A beginner would do it 1-2 times (sets). And I don't see much point in exercising longer than 45-60 minutes for the every day person. There is reasons people would need to train more, but they are usually athletes or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 06:17:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's all based on science, lol. Yes, all the information I learned was up to date. I'm employed at SnapFitness, at a club in Australia. Every 2 years we have to have accumulated 100 CEC points, the points are acquired by completing courses etc in fitness, be it even something simple like a kettle bell short course.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 06:30:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, excellent. Such great news to hear you are going to start training, how exciting for you :D I would start off with 2 full body hypertrophy sessions and 2 circuit days, and walk for 30 minutes around your block or something 5-6 days a week :) Leg Press Push-Up Lat PullDown Bridge Lunge Machine Chest Press Cable Row Leg Raises That could be your exercises for your full body work out twice a week. You'd do 2 sets of them, and have the weight so you can do about 12-15 reps, so, you want your leg press to be heavy enough so you can only push it up 12-15 times before you can't do it again. You will have to find this weight with trial and error, same with all the other ones. If you can't do a push-up on your toes, then do it on your knee's, if you can't do it on your knee's, then lean against a wall, or a bench and pushup off that. When you can do the exercise with say 15-18 reps, you need to increase the weight by about 5-10% so you can only do 12-15. Doing 12-15 reps will build stabilisation, in 6 weeks you want to change the weight so you can do 10-12 reps instead of so high of reps/ Sorry, this was a lot to take in, do you have a question?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 06:33:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>EDIT: Lifting weights like this will build muscle, which will increase your metabolism to aid in weight loss, it will also help to tighten and tone. Girls don't really end up massive, you don't have enough testosterone, so it's very hard to get massive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 06:36:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some people just genetically have higher fat stores over their stomach than others. What you could do though, is some weighted core exercises. So, crunches or sit ups with a plate/medicine ball, renegade rows etc to build your rectus abdominus which is your 6 pack. Doing a ton of sit ups won't give you a 6 pack because the reps are too high, it's endurance training for your abs not muscle building.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 07:07:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah so, I was thinking some kind of interval circuit. Buy yourself some Dumbells, they don't have to be too heavy. Squat, push-up, crunch, mountain climbers, lunge, reverse DB fly's, bridge and burpee's. 30 seconds on 20 seconds rest, at the end of the 8, you rest for 1 minute and do it 3 times. Should be about a 20 minute work out at a reasonable intensity, you can add more seconds to the work so 40 on 20 off or u can take some off 20 on 20 off to make it less or more intense. That may or may not be a good circuit for you, I haven't had much of a chance to talk to you, but you seem healthy and didn't mention any serious health conditions so I'd say use it if you please, if you can't get dumbells, instead of reverse flys or rows just google a replacement bodyweight exercise for your back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 07:21:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great, best of luck :) PM me if anything comes up or just ask here again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 07:33:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just didn't really see a point in replying, lol. I bench 100.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-29 00:04:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha. See the tag? I'm a Muaythai fighter. I haven't got a reason to have a high bench because it has absolutely no benefits and is detrimental to my physique as a fighter. If i wanted a large bench, I can guarantee you, I'd have one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-29 00:20:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would say, higher reps and lower rest, but when your repa get too high you need to add weight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-30 04:02:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey mate, I'm a Muaythai fighter, not the same sport but same principle will apply in that the most fit will win this fight. That's just how it is for amateur fights like this. Skipping is probably going to be the best for you, it's an incredible cardio workout. As for eating, just don't get anything packaged or anything processed, eat lean meats, clean carbs and good fats. Probably buy yourself a bag too, a boxing bag. Since you're only training 2 days a week with a trainer, you want to practice as much as you can in your own time. Don't make your son watch you get bashed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-30 04:17:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just drink it with water if you want less calories, drink with milk if you want more calories.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-30 04:19:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Push-ups and Squats.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-30 04:47:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>What, why? How could I make it more fun?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-31 08:26:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I am.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[WP] You find out that you are a clone of the real you, and one of you must die.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-01 00:35:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-01 01:11:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>As long as your body is getting enough carbs to keep up with muscle repair and to keep you functioning normal you're fine. Getting enough protein in your diet is incredibly easy, focus on carbs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-01 01:26:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Carbs is just as important as protein. Protein is literally just bricks, they are useless building blocks without carbs to put them together.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-02 12:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks a lot me and my girlfriend just read it and we enjoyed it :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-02 12:43:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks a lot that was cool! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 05:35:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>October? That's 10 months away. You can be doing 50+ of both of them by that time. Keep doing the chin-ups, it will grow your bi's. As for the pull-ups, trying getting up, by jumping or something, then lowering down over a 4-5 second period, these are called 'negatives' and although this is training in an eccentric phase (going down), it will give you gains for your concentric phase (going up). Train again as soon as you no longer have DOMS, if you reach a plateau and stop getting DOMS, just train twice a day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 05:42:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Training with DOMS isn't a very good idea. It may or may not be safe to train with them, but also, your muscles are not fully repaired and will not train at 100% and if they can't train at 100% there is no progression. You will train one day, the next your muscles are fatigued at 50% their capacity in strength, the next day they are sore at 85% then they are 100% but you wait 1 more day after they are recovered, because they are super compensated at this stage. So they did x reps, then they get stronger so they don't go under that much stress again, your body adapts. So you want to train within this period, you don't want to train with DOMS, and you don't want to train too long after they are gone either. You want to train when they are super compensated and can perform at 100% or you're not getting the most out of your training.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 05:50:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need to hit your right carbs too man, carbs is what fuels your muscle repair. Protein is nothing but building blocks and then you need carbs to do all the labour to put them together.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 06:18:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey mate, sounds like you need to stretch, and you can use a foam roller to help as well, just use youtube to find how to use it properly. Also, remember that your bones and tendons need to get gains as well. The rest of your muscles might condition really fast compared to them, that could be the reason why you're in pain. Make sure you're progressing at a safe pace.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 06:22:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just do body weight stuff man, until you can find yourself in a better situation to lift heavy weights. Variations of push-ups, chin-ups, pull-ups, a ton of core exercises, work out at the local parks, squats, lunges, jump lunges, jumping squats, side squats... There is a ton of things you can do with your body weight to get ripped and look good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 06:23:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why don't you just eat properly, so you don't need to take supplements. EAT CLEAN, TRAIN MEAN!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 06:53:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>What, you can't actually believe that, can you? A crunch only uses the rectus abdominus, where a plank uses the entire core...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 06:55:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you do a crunch it's an isolated exercise, meaning it targets 1 specific muscle. This muscle is the rectus abdominus, or your 'abs'. When you do a bridge, you activate your entire core. That is why a bridge is better, because it activates more muscles, and gives you a better work out, where crunches don't do much at all except strain your back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 06:59:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, it's you that has misinformation. [Here](http://imgur.com/FhGfA10) is a graph I drew for you on how super compensation works. DOMS is a very clear indication that your muscles are still fatigued, and training with fatigued muscles means you can't lift to 100% of your capacity. You should wait until your muscles are repaired and super compensated before training those muscles again, to ensure you get the most out of your workouts. EDIT: Also, after the person is able to do 12 or more pull-ups the risk of injury etc dramatically decreases so you may be able to get away with it. Below this though, and they are essentially doing hypertrophy training, and NEED rest. Once they're over 12 reps they are basically doing endurance training, so they will have a way lower risk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 07:13:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Um, legs (especially glutes in this instance) can easily be fatigued for a week lol. They are probably the only muscles that can be fatigued for that long though. That isn't what I said at all, DOMS is an indication of fatigue, fatigue isn't indicated by DOMS. You don't need DOMS to be fatigued, lol. If you are fatigued, you do not and can not perform at 100%, if you cannot perform at your peak you will not reach your potential, because you will not your muscles as much as it could have. Fact.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 07:18:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're doing less than 12 reps it is not endurance, it's hypertrophy... If you're doing hypertrophy, you need rest. I said before, if you're able to do high reps, you can probably train more often. EDIT: Also, I reached a plateau a few years ago, doing push-ups. I was doing 500ish in a session, and couldn't find a way to bust out a single rep more, some days I couldn't even get up to it, my range was like 470-500. It came down to rest time. I found with a rest, day, instead of doing pushups every single day, I was able to break my plateau.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 07:43:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most of the core.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 07:46:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sitting down all day will lengthen your glutes and weaken them and tighten your hamstrings, it will put your posture way out of whack. Look man, all I'm saying is that considering you're only training your rectus abdominus for endurance by doing crunches, I think they're stupid. The only way they would be good is doing them weighted, because they will actually give you aesthetics like a 6 pack. Doing a bridge will train most of your core instead of isolating the 1 muscle, but again, a bridge is also better weighted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 07:48:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm aware of that, but there is way more training in the CP energy system at 1-8 reps. You are training to gain muscle mass. at 12+ you are mainly training your muscles to remove lactic acid and to get higher reps, you don't need bigger muscles from then on so they just won't grow(much). If they are hitting the same muscle groups groups 4/5 times a week you can guarantee there is not very much weight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 08:18:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah man, myfitnesspal is the best one I know for that stuff, and yeah definitely need to lift. It will increase your metabolism heaps, because of the muscle recovery and also will give you a bigger daily intake of calories because of the increase in muscle size, which will make it easier to burn fat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 08:20:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can easily do 20 pull-ups by the end of the year. You can either do a ton of negatives, so getting yourself up by jumping or a friend, then lowering yourself over 4-5 seconds. This is training in the eccentric phase (down) but it still gives you gains for concentric (up). You can also find an assisted pull-ups machine, which will also help. EDIT: Realistically, the best chance for you to be able to reach your goal, is to lose weight. Watch your caloric intake by using myfitnesspal or something, and also do some hypertrophy training and also cardio training.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 08:25:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Core exercises won't burn fat, lol. Lifting weights and cardio is how you lose fat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 08:29:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need to lift weights. I strongly recommend you do some kind of a hypertrophy program to help you build muscle and get stronger, don't worry though you won't end up muscly like a man, females generally don't have enough testosterone. Obviously you still need to do cardio too though, so maybe do cardio 5 days a week and lift weights 3 days a week (perhaps 3 full body work outs, or upperbody then lowerbody then core, the days can also overlap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 08:34:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're right, sorry. You can't spot reduce fat, if you want to lose fat, it comes from everywhere equally, you can't choose where. The best way to lose weight is to recruit muscle mass, so lifting heavy weights with compound exercises, also doing cardio will burn fat aswell. I like hypertrophy because it builds muscle, which means it costs more energy for your body to live every day cause it's bigger, so you have a higher metabolism. That means it's easier to lose weight, but cardio is equally important.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 08:38:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're feeling tired, fatigued, slugging during your days, struggling to get out of bed and under performing when you train, you're probably over doing it. If your energy levels are still high, you can focus and feel alright, then you can continue. Try not to train muscle groups if they still have DOMS, you need to let everything repair. You could also get some vitamin D and calcium supplements if you wanted, just to assist your leg bones etc while you're easing into the jogging/running. EDIT: I notice you're doing Ab ripper, I can only imagine that's because you want a 6 pack, which is fine. While you're trying to lose weight though, you should probably just focus on doing large compound exercises, so you can maximise your fat burning and increase your metabolism as much as possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 08:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hypertrophy is the name of the type of training you do to build muscle mass and strength. It's heavy, you can only usually lift the weight 6-12 times. EDIT: As a beginner, you want to have it around 12 reps, so heavy enough that you can only, say, do a bench press 12 times. This is because it's safest for you, then you'd continue with that weight til you could do 15 reps with 2 sets, and you'd increase 5-10% weight, to drop you back to 12. As you get stronger, you could drop the reps and increase the weight, so you can do say 8-10 bench press reps, but you do it the way I said first, so that you can build stabiliser muscles etc, so you don't have 120KG swaying uncontrollably above your face.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 08:46:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure, no problem. Let me know if you ever need help, I'm always happy to help out :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 08:47:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, nothing wrong with it, but you can also just eat more. I'd rather just eat more, but each to their own.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 09:59:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey man, do you have access to a gym?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 15:11:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you test blood glucose before and after?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-29 14:07:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is photo shopped.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[WP] You alone find information that suggests just 30 years ago, the world had an average IQ that is 50 points higher than it is now, but a terrible accident has resulted in the humans we see today, and was covered up by survivors of the disaster.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-29 10:48:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New kitten playing in leaves I have prepared for starting the fireplace.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 05:19:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 10:52:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>In Australia, Winter has just begun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-05 09:26:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>"F**king nut case" Kelso yells after the Taxi, as it screams off sideways collecting a street bin in it's path. After a few steps, in god knows which direction, he also notices he's covered to his thighs in mud and water, which the taxi driver basically threw him in to, after seeing the birth-mark on his neck. He usually covers it with a scarf or his jumper, but it was an unusually thick, hot, muggy night. He thought to himself on his way out "Who'd notice it at this time of night anyway?" He stopped leaving the house without covering it unless he *had* to, at about the age of 13, this was when he hit high school. One of the teachers went crazy on his 3rd day.. He earned the nickname 'The Chosen One' which is a direct English translation from 'Alesul' - The teacher was screaming it at him, after seeing the birthmark. Apparently also trying to burn it into his skin during wood works with Pyrography tool. This was his favorite new subject up until this day. Rest assured the teacher was put on sick leave and admitted to a psychiatric ward, but the kids never forgot. After beseeching the directions home from a clerk at a nearby 24 hour shop, he started trudging home in the once again, pouring rain. After battling the elements and traffic for about 15 blocks, he finally knew where he was again. "It might be a sh*t day, but thank f*ck I can follow directions" he was thinking to himself, as he passed another dank back alley. It was then that he heard the name 'Alesul" come eerily from the alley way. Kelso stood frozen, the hairs prickling on the back of his neck, beads of sweat trickling down his spine and nose like ice. He took a few steps back to get a decent look down this alley way, and saw nothing notable.. He stared for a few seconds before turning to leave "Everyone has given you sh*t about this birthmark since you were a kid... It looks like a dragon, sure, but it's just a great coincidence. I can guarantee you, stranger things have happened, than a dude being born with a birthmark that resembles a dragon" Now turning, and taking the first of his last hundred or so steps home, he see's in the corner of his eyesight, the bright red glare of a pair of eyes. Not regular eyes though, they were sharp, jagged. Fuck the shape, they are the size of footballs! After what must be only a few seconds later, he hears the gushing of wind. The sound belting his ears, like long slow drums, slowely fading... He gets to his feet, and runs! "My legs are so sore... No they're numb.. How much longer can my body keep sprinting? I thought home was closer than this?" He ran as far as he can, "I'm at my limit.. But my front door is just there!.. I can make it!" he says to himself as he pants, grudgingly dragging numb, dead legs toward it while gasping for air, taking in long draws of the icey cold air which is hurting his lungs and throat. He collapses on the ground, suprisingly not due to exhaustion, rather he was forced down by another gush of wind. This time it was not the sound but the force of the gush itself. He hits the ground hard, seeing stars. He slowly raises his head, and through the pouring down rain, sound of traffic in the distance and through the ringing in his own head from clashing it against the concrete, he see's this big dark figure with crimson red eyes, and shining teeth the size of your arm.. It stares at him before hissing "I've found you Alesul"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[WP] You are a scientist and specialise in the field of quantum mechanics and decide to get high, and have an epiphany, and suddenly realise how the entire Universe really works, then after a few seconds of bliss you forget what you were thinking about.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-14 04:50:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[WP] You possess rare DNA and have the ability to have your body cure any kind of cancer, scientists are savings millions of lives with new science using your cells, when you are assassinated. 12 months later you are born again because scientists got approval to clone you.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-05 07:38:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 11:14:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>NSFW huh? Is that cause you have an 'outtie'?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-21 13:23:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Yeah, well when she slept with Jerry, I really thought she was a bitch, so I made sure to kill her in as gruesome way as possible" Death chuckled to me over the phone "People picture me as this really horrible emotionless dude who just goes around killing people, but I have a job man. You humans won't stop fucking so if I don't do my job, shit get's real" Well that's true, there is already 7 billion of us. "Anyway, meet me at the usual place it's about time we catch up, 7pm don't be late or you're dead" What the fuck? "AHHH I'm just kidding Paulie, you know I wouldn't kill you buddy, cya then" Death says cordially before hanging up the phone to me. Wouldn't kill me? Bullshit. You've given up on trying because I'm too smart for you, you hooded bag of bones. There was a lot of close calls though, I'm glad you finally gave up old friend. As I push open the old wooden saloon doors, and take my first few steps from the aching heat of the sun, I feel instant relief. Walking along the dark dusty floorboards, soaking up the coolness of the shady room, I pass a few shady characters sitting at tables whispering among themselves, but I walk passed with no problem. I get to the bar and take a seat on the stool, grab a glass of whisky on the rocks and start sipping away, waiting for my friend. After some time of listening to drunks have conversations and a fight nearly breaking out, I hear the familiar sound of the saloon doors swinging open. I look back to see the hooded figure sweeping across the room and then sit up the back in the darkest area of the pub. He beckons me over with the wave of his boney hand and I signal him 2 fingers for 2 minutes. I had to piss. I come back from the bathroom and Death is reseating himself at a different location with 2 more drinks for us both. I take my drink up from the bar and position myself in the seat next to him. Time passes as we talk about things catching up, death telling me stories of the funny ways he has had to bring people to their fateful end, and me laughing giving him idea's on what to do next. Death nudges a drink toward me and says "Here take a sip" "Nah I've had enough, I should really get going soon pal. We can't drink like the old days I have a family now". At this Death get's a little excitable, and really urges me to have a drink "Just one more drink come on please, one more drink just have a sip, just have one sip buddy for old time sakes" I look at him with curiosity and oblige. I take a sip. "YES! I've DONE IT! After 20 fucking years I got this little punk bitch! Ever since he was a fucking teenager this asshole has been eluding me and out smarting me!! I knew the only way to get him was to trick him in to thinking I liked him." The mortal looks me in the eyes with pure desperation as he is clearly struggling to breath. Ahhh I love that sound, you know that sound when someone is gasping for air? They are kind of wheezing as the air whistles in and out of their swelling wind pipe? "I... Thought we were friends" the idiot says to me as he makes his last ever hand grip on my sweet hood. He falls to the ground and now all I have to do is escort this suckers soul to the other side. I earned a drink. I sit back in my chair, twirling a shot glass in my boney finger tips smirking at how smart I am, better knock back this shot and get back to work. "Idiot" Paulie thinks to himself, as he looks over the hooded figure while sipping down the last of his poisonous shot glass. "I told you not to fuck with me, now death is the one that is dead" "Probably should of kept a closer eye on me if you're going to poison me, instead of getting caught up bragging about killing people and looking around for victims, you make me sick." Out of no-where the lights go dim, and everything around him stops moving. Mid conversation, people are frozen. A jug of beer a drunk man had clearly knocked over, frozen in the air. An ominous sound resenonates from deep within my head, and my skin begins to shrink and dry up, everything turns from colour to grey. In a frantic panic, I stumble to my feet and sprint toward the toilet knocking bins and chairs over in my path. Busting the door open, I run to the sink and peer into the empty, hollow eyes on my face. Draped in a jet black material not of this world was my skeletal figure, *I am now death.*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-21 13:56:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, I've only done 1 other about a year ago. It was fun writing it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Today, Steve Irwin would have turned 55. Happy Birthday mate.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 01:59:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 02:03:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I also cried like a baby, I was 17. Huge fan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 02:27:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Prime Minister, he would have had my vote.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 03:02:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or I'm Australian and grew up with him on the TV and have spent 27 years being a fan and want to keep him remembered.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 04:01:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't really follow main stream celebrity going-ons, but when Steve died I was absolutely *devestated*. Such a passionate animal lover.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 04:04:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know, 44, right? Now that I'm 27, that feels so young. So much accomplished in those few years, the whole world respects him for his passionate nature.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm pretty sure nearly all cats would fit size 0-3 month old baby clothes. I wish this would become a thing.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 06:04:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 06:44:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahahaha. Please update me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Analemma from 1998 to 1999. (The sun at the same time and spot over a year)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 13:33:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 17:39:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty sure this belongs in /r/WTF</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 17:43:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was an *awesome* movie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>KFC debunks terrible chicken rumors, like a boss.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 10:52:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 10:52:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't even know how 232 people believe this guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 11:01:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>i...i like steak and tomato sauce</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hummingbird eggs are about the size of a jellybean</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-06 14:39:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cop handles vicious dogs like an absolute boss.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 07:33:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 11:55:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>NSFW: A friend of mine always walked her dog not on a leash, her dogs were really smart. We were walking around the block then crossing a road and going to the ovals to throw the ball, we get to the road and she tells her dogs to sit and they sit. We are standing there talking for about 15 seconds and after this truck coming, we see an opportunity to cross after it, so we wait. As the truck is about to pass us, her Border Collie stands and walks *very* casually in front of this truck. **Boom**. I tried to grab it but considering how slow the dog walked, it happened very fast, she is screaming at the top of her lungs. I walk up to her and hug her very tight, and continue to push her towards home. She's screaming and screaming and crying and I keep pushing her toward her house. She begins to tell me to go and check on her dog and I agreed, as long as she goes home. I walk on to the road, cars are beeping, there is like 3 or 4 different tones of horns and I just raise my hand in a *stop* fashion, flip a couple of guys off and continue to walk (It was about 25M). There is the dog, dead. I pick up the bulk of the corpse, as it's back legs were smashed off from impact, and I feel all it's broken bones inside this dogs skin. It's 100% dead, the tongue is hanging out to the side and everything. All the horns stop beeping, and I get the dog off the road, I was carrying it with my arms out like a forklift. Thick, suffocating copper smell of fresh blood results in me vomitting a few times as it's blood is running like a tap all over my legs and arms. I stuck around and dug 2 holes for the dog, the second was because she didn't like the first location, and I moved him to where the flowers are. Morale of the story - Your dog is a dog, put it on a fucking leash, please.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 12:05:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is foam, dude. He's foaming.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 12:39:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah, I had a good look. It's definitely foam. EDIT: I'm not sure actually, but as best as my eyes can tell, it's foam.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 13:31:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>The dog also died on Valentines day, I can't even make this shit up - I swear to God it's true. She cried for months, but she has healed now as best you do from these tragedies. She had a second dog on the walk with us, his name is Wally. She still has Wally, he is her life now, she is always uploading silly and crazy pics of him, he's very loved. This is [Zeus](https://imgur.com/a/Er8P8), the one in the accident. This one is [Wally](https://imgur.com/a/4SIb4).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-09 14:12:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is the sexiest fucking cosplay I've ever seen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 10:43:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-16 12:44:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Forcefully? No. That's a terrible way to put it. "12 Stepping" is just alcoholics coming in and talking with your friend about themselves, their alcoholic issues and how they drank, who they were and where they were going. They also talk about where they are now that they are blessed with sobriety and how they achieved it, if your friend wants the same life as them then he will be willing to make "the steps" to get there. You either do The 12 Steps like millions of other alcoholics have done to achieve sobriety, or you don't and sadly probably die (Or other unfortunate circumstances i.e homeless, prison, broken family) like so, so many millions more. No one can force you to get sober, anyone with decent sobriety can clarify this for me. You can lead a camel to water, but you can't force it to drink.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-16 12:49:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unless he is willing to take steps to change there is basically nothing you can do. The alcoholic has to want sobriety, it doesn't matter what anyone else thinks, he probably isn't even aware the alcohol is the problem (I know myself, and many others were not aware for a long time). Maybe when she leaves him or he hits some other kind of rock bottom like hospital or a prison he will admit he needs help, I'm so sorry. Also, it's not your fault. The approach you took is the best you knew how, you did all you knew how to do and that shows you cared. Unfortunately caring is not always enough. This is one of those sad things that happens to millions, you're not alone in this scenario and how it played out. Perhaps try going to some Alanon meetings. They are like AA meetings, but for people who have suffered living with the alcoholic, it can be very stressful and can really take it's toll on you. It would be good for you to understand what happened and what to do from here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-21 05:45:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, look at the little man trying to be serious, he's just so cute! Darn him, I want one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I was banned from a Subreddit, I had to draw this to have the ban lifted. (I'm reformed)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-21 20:09:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-21 20:10:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a Lemur sitting on a Saint Bernard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 05:05:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It has nothing to do with a lack of dignity, I obliged because I thought it was hilarious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's the nicest thing someone ever did for you at no benefit to themselves/for free?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 11:00:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Impressive, badass Pigeon racing traffic on a highway!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 16:15:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 01:11:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whaaaaat? As an Australian, I am not impressed. That thing is *tiny*.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 01:15:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>For reference, Goon is a cheap af wine, they come in 4Letre caskets for about $10-$12AUD for $9-10USD.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's something you didn't understand as a kid, but now you do?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 08:39:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 00:38:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems a bit of a drama queen to me, nothing was gunna happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scary winds of Cyclone Debbie, thrashing an Island just off QLD, Australia.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 07:18:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 07:23:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Caught up in the moment, thank you for your forgiveness, Senpai.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 15:27:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>zombiesunflower you're an idiot. I'm all for unnecessary comments but you really take the cake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 21:51:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>You probably took the ice-cream as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-30 18:58:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm willing to donate and risk my $20 on him being a liar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 16:12:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the "Green" is referring to a business name or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-01 15:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man, that girl is damaged. What happened to make her behave like that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The best things in life, aren't actually things...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-01 23:39:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-01 23:43:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lego is great until it's under your feet, then it quickly becomes the worst thing in life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What advice would you give your 21 year old self?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 00:37:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 18:36:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you okay?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 21:37:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't even know what this is but it made me hungry. Is this a real order and what is it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-04 02:28:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Discrimination, I hope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If we had proof Valhalla were real, how would the world be different?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 03:02:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 00:16:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>You gotta do that, and not be fat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A man bans 14-18 year old black people, and dogs, from entering his shop in Melbourne, Australia.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 10:33:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I accidentally ended up with a lawn mowing business, what do I do?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 06:27:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, I put an ad on Gumtree and Facebook saying I would mow lawns for $40 just to help make ends meet while I study. I have 5 or so houses to do now, so I had an idea. I grabbed my phonebook and called like 300 people in my city, i had about 15 people say yes. I'm purchasing 5,000 leads in my city so I can do this legally now that I know how many people I can get. What do I do though, to stay safe legally and out of tax debt? I live in Australia.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 02:34:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was a bit unnecessary but ok.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Water running down Mt. Uluru, Australia.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 06:01:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 10:19:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's called Mt. Uluru Source: Me Mrs is an abo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Officer: I'm sorry to say, it looks like your girlfriend has been hit by a truck...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 03:20:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me: Yeah but she has a good personality</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just adopted this guy, I think he likes playing outside.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 04:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 04:32:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It rains a lot in Australia, lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 04:33:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ngaanyatjarra.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 13:07:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>She said it's commonly called Mt. Uluru among her people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 13:15:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bump - Waiting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>22 year old personal trainer and volunteer fire fighter to be charged with 5.8Kg of cocaine leaving Columbia airport, claims to be innocent.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 07:05:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 07:07:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Poor girl, her family has a donation thing going on, to help with lawyer fee's etc and to get over to Columbia to support her. It's [here](https://fundrazr.com/51EP39?fb_action_ids=10155358629815087 amp;fb_action_types=fundrazr%3Astory_update) if anyone wanted to support her and her family.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-06 08:36:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, what? I saw this, like, 12 months ago? some dude made this like, drew it some how... OP is a liar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-13 02:16:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>You saw it on Facebook because it came from Reddit, a hundred times now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is something you saw happen that you didn't think was possible?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-13 03:23:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What can I do to prepare for starting a business?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-19 06:54:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm getting a small lump sum of about 20 grand. I want to start a lawn mowing business. I can buy a trailer, a push mower, a ride-on mower and some other bits and pieces all for about 10 grand.. But like, what else is there to it? What should I be learning here? Any tips?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You woman gotta' realise, making us sleep on the couch ain't that bad...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 05:48:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's kinda manly, makes us feel like we are camping. With an angry bear nearby.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What sort of tutorials do people wanna see?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-27 03:55:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi, I have over 100k battle score, over 25 million chips and I've been playing the game since it's release. I've come first in the world for the weekly rank multiple times, and top 10 twice for prestige leader board. I decided to start sharing a few tutorials, as the ones I see are made by people who don't even have 50k battle score. What do you guys think I should start with?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-27 05:33:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Interested? Comment here to ask questions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-27 09:55:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mortar, Tree, Ninja.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-27 09:56:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>really?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 02:09:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, this is me correcting you. You're wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 02:09:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 11:31:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice dude! Keep it up, they are both terrible!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 03:02:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Which is now deleted" grow up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 09:23:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Grow up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-13 03:33:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Proof please.... Stop lying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-18 03:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice... You typed it up for me... Well done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 13:27:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Riiiight, of course it is... Prove it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-24 13:23:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol, nice photo shop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>AMA Request: I need a Flat Earther to answer some questions for me, any volunteers?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 02:51:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, before we start asking questions or delve into anything, I just want to say this first: You have the potential to convert me to your religion here, if you are true to your God and love him and are in good faith, it should sadden you, and bring you to tears the thought of me going to Hell, unless you aren't true to your religion. So please, answer a few questions for me to the best of your ability. 1) What was the catalyst that brought you to believe in creationism? 2) Do you honestly believe the grand canyon was formed in only 10,000 years? 3) Have you ever Google experiments you can perform on your own at home, to test whether or not the Earth is flat through physics? 4) I'm gunna go ahead and leave this one open, for anything you feel you might want the world to see. Throw something of your own in here ;) Really excited to see some replies, hope this works out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 03:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what I thought.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 04:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe that's why I have no replies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 08:32:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're commonly lumped together, I'm not sure what you mean.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 08:33:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is a collection of people who group the 2 together into 1 super retarded idea. I know most people believe in 1 or the other, but this AMA refers to all 3. Who believe in 1, the other, or have them lumped as 1.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 08:34:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're good at PS, but they're are right there, look.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm Australian, and wouldn't know what a Crocodile looked like if it wasn't for that beautiful SOB, Steve Irwin... RIP</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 09:42:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 10:47:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where the fuck did you grow up that you see Crocodiles? In the part of QLD I'm in I can only see them at the Zoo that Steve made. Eat a dick you munted cunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-06 01:58:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Um, yeah you're good.. You really psycho analyzed me well, you must be like one of the worlds leading psychologists or something, cause man, you know me better than I know myself. When am I getting married? Is my first kid going to be a boy? Can't tell me that? Oh.. I thought you'd at least make more shit up for me. You're wrong, this is a legitimate question and if I'm accidentally grouping 2 lots of people together, it's probably because they belong together. These questions came to existence because of my having conversations with people LIKE THIS, or reading about people like THIS, or at least one or the other.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-06 01:59:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't get me wrong, 98% of Christians aren't retarded enough to believe the world is flat. Im a Christian'.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 13:11:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I dunno about all guys... But if we're dating and I'm okay with meeting your parents, it's to see if your Mum is hot and how you're gunna age.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 09:20:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do yourself a favour and see if the Mum is hot, it's genetics bro. Don't gamble with something you have to spend the rest of your life with, it's science bitch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My first day back on Runescape in 5 years, can I get some help please?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 12:22:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have no idea how to fight... My stats are 99-92-99-95-95 with 92 prayer... But like, what's this revolution shit? There is abilities lol so cool but how tf do I use them? I want to go and fight at God wars or something, but I looked up some fights and I have NO IDEA what is going on.. I've Googled it and do not understand wtf I'm reading either, LOL. Can someone please like, explain it to me? and aura's and like, yeah I dunno... I just want to be able to do end-game content but I don't understand anything. Also, I can sell a Santa or something, money isn't an issue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 12:25:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about like Aura's etc? I don't understand the entire game :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 12:29:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, this is what I need. So, I'll check out dps rotations etc, thanks, and I'll start at GW1 you said? Is there a particular boss I should start with then like something I should work toward? What about potions and Aura's etc is all that really important?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 12:29:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>35-40 isn't old and fucked..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 12:30:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. I said I meet them to see if my partner is genetically fucked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 12:44:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow thank you so much dude this was awesome. I have Amulet of Souls, Malevolent Head, Chest and Legs, dual Drygore Long, Torva Boots and Razorback Gauntlets. How does that sound to you for bosses? I'll read the stuff you gave me and start with GW1 and QBD I think. Thanks a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 12:54:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you have any idea how hard it has been to find this information as a new guy? Way too hard, sincerely thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 14:18:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, and I didn't say old and fucked, so I don't even know why you randomly commented something so unrelated to the original post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 14:19:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks man! How does prayer work these days?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 14:59:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's just something to be weary of, I never said that either... Man you just say stuff hey, words, words, words! edit: i,e if her mum is a big fat thing you can take precautionary measures to ensure your wife doesn't end up a huge whale by having a good diet and encouraging her to exercise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 15:56:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Makes perfect sense though. Mums a fat bitch, daughters a fat bitch. No one wants a fat bitch, what don't you understand here?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If cockroaches can survive nuclear fallout, what's in bug spray?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 08:01:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 08:03:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow really, damn. I always liked Santa Clause and I'm not an idiot, so I'll take not a cent under 60k. Thanks man I'll look it up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 10:21:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you pay the 2 grand a week while you're in Uni etc?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 10:57:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, for reference the law was enforced yesterday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 11:01:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because of the thing...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 11:01:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Watched heaps of movies, can confirm he's probably heard it's not too difficult.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 13:12:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>[For](https://www.reddit.com/r/todayilearned/comments/6q0642/til_that_the_7th_time_that_park_ranger_roy/?utm_content=comments amp;utm_medium=hot amp;utm_source=reddit amp;utm_name=frontpage) | [reference](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Roy_Sullivan)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 02:03:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit! This story was so huge... How tf did she get proved innocent?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 12:23:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw this same thing on a girls advice page on Facebook, hmm...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 04:51:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Japanese Jiu-Jitsu is striking? A quick Google search confirmed striking is a very small component of Japanese Jiu Jitsu...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL "a dog will lick his butt but won't eat a pickle Road" is actually a place.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 05:05:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>15 teens hospitalized after raping a donkey and contracting rabies.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-17 04:18:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scam alert! My friend just uploaded this and I thought it was genius.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 04:20:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mayweather to fight Mcgregor with a hand injury</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 14:13:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you're Aussie and try to nickname the fan and fail</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 16:09:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What questions would be asked at an interview for a produce team member at a super market?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 12:32:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 12:33:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't afford to fuck this up, in all seriousness, please help me Reddit. I have already got these: greatest strengths weaknesses/plan why woolworths? why should we hire you? MAKE SURE YOU HAVE QUESTIONS FOR THEM Are you a team player? What challenges do you think you'll face? Why do you want to work with us? Can you work under pressure?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 13:12:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks a lot, man. This was good advice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 13:14:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks a lot, it will help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-08 02:54:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>More like junky parents teaching their kids how to be thieves super young, that was rehearsed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-08 02:55:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's bloke, mate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 04:17:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude that's an awesome idea! Talking to someone in there working I mean... Thanks for your reply man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL how dangerous the gympie-gympie tree is, when I was younger my brother and I attacked my cousin by whacking him with the leaf multiple times across the back at a swimming hole (did not know it was this bad LOL).</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 02:03:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can I cut 6kg in 2 weeks?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-11 15:20:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I weigh 79kg and 180cm tall, medium build, low body fat... I have a Jiu Jitsu tournament in 13 days and I'm trying to decide whether to register for the 79kg division or 73kg, will I be able to cut the weight in that time? What method do you guys use and can you link me to a solid guide? Thanks in advance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 00:02:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, you're right I'm a white belt. I decided to not cut last night and just enjoy a good technical roll while I learn, but your idea affirmed I made the right decision man, so thanks for giving me your time!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 00:03:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You rub the magic lamp and get one of those douche genies that make something bad come from whatever you wish for, what do you wish for and how do you word it so the genie can't fuck you?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 13:27:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Angry guy sick of waiting in-line at the bank leaves and comes back with gas and lights the bank and himself on fire.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 09:24:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You're allowed to breach the time travel laws but only to troll people in insignificant ways, what do you do?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 11:03:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 13:12:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus Christ. I thought the joke was that we are changing it to CAN!!! ONE LETTER! From can't to can... Then you showed me the truth... Do I thank you for this? I'm not even sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The first 4 months of life! Meet Woofy.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 12:20:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 23:51:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why tf would anyone ask a vet that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's the coolest thing to write in a Birthday Card?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 09:07:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 23:21:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reminds me of crawling out of that casino (rainbow coloured lights) at about this time... Triggered.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 00:07:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>because CSGO is dead and so is this shit subreddit, get a new game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Checking out the new place.... No thanks.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 00:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 23:17:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>"2 Radio show hosts" I thought to myself - "I bet it's Hamish and Andy".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 00:20:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Started drinking by age 16, a couple of months before my 18th birthday I was in Max Security Jail. Small crime spree's while drunk and on benders consumed my life for the better part of the next 10 years. My brother and myself were arguing over who gets to drive his car to this party we're going to. Anyway, long story short, he falls out the window and I run him over, broke his ankle. To me, this was just me hurting my brother and fucking his legs up. I definitely felt bad, but at the same time it wasn't my fault and he knew that, too. This seemingly small event (On a scale against everything else I've done) speared me towards a rehab centre, because jail is boring and I didn't want to go back. From there my life changed from trying to get out of going to jail to being on a road of recovery. I had a couple of small slips, but I'm now almost 3 years clean and sober.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What do you think would be the 3 personality traits that would be most dominant in someone that's 1,000 years old?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 07:31:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 23:26:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sure I'm not the only one, but I want to find out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 23:28:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>But no one else can, and everyone even calls me a liar? I do it all the time at doctors, they end up with all kinds of messy readings while trying to get my blood pressure and heart rate... But why can't anyone else I know do it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 00:12:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You stupid bitch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is flipping dead?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 03:46:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>My main was hacked so I'm playing a high melee pker (99-94-99). I have no money (about 15mil) and want to start flipping the ge. Is flipping a dead thing? How are the wait times these days? Any general tips? Thanks in advance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 15:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you psycho-analysing me? Lol fuck off nerd you don't know me, I was genuinly curious 30k exp is really low, and I didn't bother to check for other posts cause I was on a phone. Shouldn't even have to explain myself to you, scum.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's something cute you do for your partner that they don't know about?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 13:23:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I finished 3 books today..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 06:34:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Might not sound like it, but that's a lot of colouring</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>HDD is enclosed in a big box where as a CD is not... How come?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 12:45:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 03:08:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can tell the bar is a solid colour by looking at the far left, then moving your eyes along the bar to the far right. You can see the brighter bit lengthening and shortening.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I don't wake up when I fall/hit the ground in dreams, AMA!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 03:08:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 03:13:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always continue to dream. For a brief time (sometimes, not always) the dream becomes lucid and I control the dream before it blends into a normal dream where I spectate. EDIT: The impact is pain free, if that's what you're wondering. I just hit the ground like a pancake and stand-up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 03:27:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>The lucidity begins during the excitement. Say I'm on a ride at a themepark, and the bolts start coming loose. I start getting those feelings of free falling in my belly (Which I fucking love, mind you). It's when the bolts come loose, or I'm staring off the edge of a cliff. When the butterfly's begin the dream is mine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 03:29:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. I used to wake up as a small kid, then it changed to 50% of the time and it just slowely stopped happening. I finally stopped waking up at about 13-14.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 03:40:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. I like the falling dreams, I love the feeling of free falling. Also I don't have to bother getting out of bed to pee and try to get back to sleep.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Well, that escalated quickly.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 10:19:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 11:08:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, Nutrigrain Bars are nothing like the cereal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 12:43:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most morning I can wake up and tell someone what my dreams were about (Probably 90% of the time). I always remember lucid dreaming in very clear detail though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 12:44:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a negative. I always seem to know I'm dreaming and that nothing happens when I hit the ground so I enjoy the butterflies you get from falling. I love those butterflies you get when you drop, or are on a ride at an amusement park, or bungee jumping.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>High School Band bring their bus driver to tears when they play for him to celebrate his last chemo treatment.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 05:30:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 00:23:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Riiiiigggghhtt... Because the government telling lies can break the laws of physics... There is tests to prove 100% it's round in your back yard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guy stabs his friend with fishing spear</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 08:07:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL It was this day in 1996 (16th february in australia), Happy Gilmore came from four shots down during the final round of the Tour Championship to defeat Shooter McGavin and win the Gold Jacket.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 04:00:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 08:01:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>add that to the wank bank, won't ya</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 10:51:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>2 in 3 Australian's don't understand religion, even the religious :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 17:52:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>You sound a bit jealous of my Karma.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 22:06:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Zero shame. Lots of Karma, eat my ass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 22:07:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Btw it's my Reddit Birthday, so up-vote me. It's my birth right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 03:51:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>The top half</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 11:48:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>nice man, are you just starting out? very good for a beginner</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 17:05:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you're better off getting 50 silver chests before you start on gold. If you're new to the game it's important to get an item in every slot, they don't need to be the epics/purples, just something. The power boost from nekid to white/green in every slot with a couple of blues here and there will be **huge**. From there you would start to hunt purples/shiny's, that's how I'd do it anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anyone know how to farm gems using a script?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 04:10:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I found [this](https://www.reddit.com/r/idlechampions/comments/7tj1kq/gem_farming_script/). I got a copy for 2 resolutions there, tried them both and nothing happened :( I put them into notepad++ and then saved it as .ahk, then when I double click the file nothing actually happens lol. BIG QUESTION, does this one still work? Can someone help me get it working? Is there another script out there? Thanks so much in advance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Help with my computer randomly restarting?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 03:10:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Temp is fine on all components, doesn't over heat even under stress, diagnostics on ram done everything there is fine and checked there is no loose hardware anywhere... only thing left i can think of is power supply... here is a screen shot of my [speccy](https://imgur.com/a/5saL5lw).... my PSU is 600w, any idea's guys? obviously I'm not a pro at this so apologies if i've missed anything or if i sound like a noob</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mumma possum saves baby possum, can confirm it lived.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 15:07:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How does returning to a martial arts and belts work?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 09:28:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, I got to purple belt or 4th kyu when I was a teenager. The art was Ryobu Kai it has a Shotokan back ground. I was 14/15 at the time, quit to do various other things on and off including Muay Thai, boxing and BJJ. I have never got too serious past non/light contact competition. I'm 27 now, so 13 or 14 years onward I want to finish what I started and become a black belt in the art I studied as a kid. The problem is though, it took me 2 years to get to 4th kyu, do I have to do it all over again? Or can I rehash/fast track? How does it actually work? Thanks in advance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How does returning to martial arts and belts work?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 09:44:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, I got to blue belt or 5th kyu when I was a teenager. The art was Ryobu Kai it has a Shotokan back ground. I was 14/15 at the time, quit to do various other things on and off including Muay Thai, boxing and BJJ. I have never got too serious past non/light contact competition. I'm 27 now, so 13 or 14 years onward I want to finish what I started and become a black belt in the art I studied as a kid. The problem is though, it took me 2 years to get to 5th kyu, do I have to do it all over again? Or can I rehash/fast track? How does it actually work? Thanks in advance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 11:30:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but... It costs a lot of money to do that 2 years of training over again :L In gradings I mean.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 11:31:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry 5th kyu, and it was probably more like 2 and a half years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is 2 things that are delicious on their own but horrible together?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 14:41:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 16:20:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck I hate those stupid dogs. Get a real dog.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Americans is like "Everything in Australia can kill you"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 14:47:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 14:52:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Edit: Americans are like\*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 15:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 15:36:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, but the increase in new privately owned guns since it happened has \*dramatically\* decreased. A large % of those guns from 97' or what ever it was, would be old and fucked now, from lack of care. There hasn't been anywhere near as many guns purchased since 97' as there were guns seized, which means now, 21 years on, we're at a very large deficit.. Very low chances of being gunned down by an AR\-15 in Australia than compared to the "great" US</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 02:39:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Guns don't kill people, people kill people, AM I RITE?!?!?! Yeah so take the fucking guns off the people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 03:22:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like how you didn't quote the part where I said they weren't maintained properly, lol, you're a joke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 14:00:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>\`So like, if people are bad, take the fucking guns off them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is 2 days a week enough to progress?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 14:35:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>1 day technique, 1 day open mat... I read a lot of online stuff on concepts etc as well as techniques from lots of sources, to try and find things to learn and practice on the mats during my rolls, so I'm taking in BJJ content daily just I will only be able to train 2 days a week now that I'm taking this job. Will I still progress? I mean I'm not in a race, but I would like to get to a coloured belt some day if I can... Thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 15:42:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>.....i don't know any solo drills :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 15:43:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>work my brother, monday to thursday is 1pm\-9pm at night, friday is 11am to 5pm and the weekend is free... so i figured ill work all week, hit the friday cause its early and smash an open mat on the saturday</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 15:43:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>help prevent injury lmao, thanks man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 15:44:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't actually done many open mats, and I'm intimidated... So I sit there waiting for people to ask to roll, and when everyone is done I go home :( What should my approach be? How should I be acting to make these guys fill my head with knowledge? I want them to teach me but I want it to be natural lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 17:08:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>nice, wish i had the same amount of time as you :P good luck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A picture taken of a brother and sister, 4 hours before her life was stolen by cancer. Fuck cancer.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 15:04:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 15:05:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>This picture is from a news article. Decided to share it with Reddit because fuck cancer. No 4 year old boy should be saying the permanent goodbye to his little sister, breaks my fucking heart.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 15:13:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>:'(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fuck cancer. Picture of a small boy saying goodbye to his baby sister, she passed 4 hours later.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 15:52:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 15:52:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Found this on a news article, full details here: [https://www.9news.com.au/world/2018/06/13/12/23/heartbreaking\-photo\-matt\-sooter\-adalynn\-addy\-jackson\-cancer\-diffuse\-intrinsic\-pontine\-glioma?ocid=Social\-9News](https://www.9news.com.au/world/2018/06/13/12/23/heartbreaking-photo-matt-sooter-adalynn-addy-jackson-cancer-diffuse-intrinsic-pontine-glioma?ocid=Social-9News)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 15:52:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cancer sucks :( Fuck you cancer!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fuck cancer! A young boy saying his final goodbye to his baby sister, she passed 4 hours later.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 17:35:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 17:35:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Absolutely fucking heart wrenching :(](https://www.9news.com.au/world/2018/06/13/12/23/heartbreaking-photo-matt-sooter-adalynn-addy-jackson-cancer-diffuse-intrinsic-pontine-glioma?ocid=Social-9News)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 21:03:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>All good bro relax, it's not a competition. I shared it 3 days ago and it was removed for wrong sub reddit. Just a story I'm sharing, I'm sure it's happened before when more than 1 person share a tragic event. Get a grip on yourself, bro.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 15:56:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cause it's full of bacteria and sweat and diseases and shit, and it's rubbing up all over your partners face and breaking the skin exposing them to the risk of infections? This aint karate brah, wash your belt, it's respectful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 15:59:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>You indirectly accused me of Karma whoring, my previous post was removed for being in the wrong subreddit so I re-posted, have a cry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 17:33:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're joking it doesn't apply to you then, you can just leave it there like you never even read it my friend. I'm sure some one will read it and go "fuck he's right that's yuck" EDIT: Chill</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 15:59:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're not doing the same retarded thing with your thumb in the recent photo, but up-vote for being close.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My girlfriend suffers from a crippling nerve disorder, and I want to cheer her up with a flower garden but don't know where to start</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 13:14:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have no idea where to start :( I don't even know what type of seeds or flowers to get, I don't even know what grows in my area or how to pH the soil or what they eat or anything, I mean... How tf I do this? I'm making her a 1.2mx1.2m raised garden bed out of some untreated pine, I'll fill it with some decent soil but like, then what? Do I just order what ever seeds look cool and chuck em in? Or do they have to be special seeds for certain times of year? Do different flowers need different pH soil or can they all just get along happily together? Living in South-East QLD, Australia. It's a subtropical region, any information is muchly appreciated, I really want to help cheer her up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 13:25:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>signet marigold, cosmos, impatiens, geraniums, phlox, daylily, pansies, fragipanis, these are the seeds I have in mind, but is it okay to just plant them whenever or does it hav to be at a specific time of the year?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My girlfriend has a crippling and progressive nerve disease, Reddit can you please help me make her a flower garden?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 13:37:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>First of all, I know very little about growing flowers! I think the closest I came to growing flowers, was growing weed when I was younger. So, I love in South East Queensland in Australia. It's a subtropical area, and I want to make her a 1.2mx1.2m raised garden bed to have 4-5 different types of flowers in. She suffers CRPS and is very limited in what she can do some days, but she LOVES flowers and nature and I want her to have a flower bed to go out and read a book by, while I'm at work and her condition is incapacitating her. Basically the thing that's confusing me the most is, what flowers grow at what time of year? And can thy all live in the same soil or are flowers really picky and like their own pH levels etc? After looking up flowers for a while, I liked signet marigold, cosmos, impatiens, geraniums, phlox, daylily, pansies, fragipanis but have no idea if they grow in my part of the world, or if they grow harmoniously together in a 1.2 squared raised garden bed. What do you guys think I should grow? I'm looking to germinate/plant the seeds in 2 weeks, and have the garden bed constructed in 3 weeks, ready to plant the germianted seeds/seedlings in to. Do you guys have any suggestions on flowers I can use and how to grow them please I have no idea what I'm doing and really need help to brighten my loves life a bit, she's in a dark place living with a level 7-8 pain ever day and somtimes can't even walk... Pls Reddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 15:10:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>i was gunna staple sheets of that black stuff for drainage rather than putting an actual bottom on it, does that sound ok? i mean this is coming from a place of no experience, maybe im better just letting it sit ontop of the natural dirt? i wanna keep their roots inside my nice soil though thats why i thought of putting the fabric across the bottom for drainage and stop stop the roots digging into shit soil.. just made sense to my uneducated self</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 15:11:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>perhaps i'll plant lots of native stuff around the outsides of the little courtyard type thing we have, she's allergic to bee's haha so i'd hate to make her a garden and kill her with my love</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 10:29:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>doesn't that number only work in 1 country?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hey, Australia! Facebook finally added the aboriginal flag to it's emoji list, we WON!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 10:44:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 04:20:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just so you know, that's ego.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So, let me get this straight.... (mindfulness meditation)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 15:26:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just sit down in a quiet place, shut my eyes, and focus on my breathing and basically my existence, if my mind begins to wander, I just observe the thought with no judgement and gently guide myself back to focusing on only the breath... Or do I allow myself to continue off on a wild journey, but all while focusing on my existence and what my thoughts are doing? Like, do I just observe my brain and where it wanders, or do I deliberately take myself back to focusing on just breathing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 15:32:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I'm training my brain to only think about shit that I want it to, not random shit? I'm confused on the goal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 16:03:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Isn't that what I said but with more words? Lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 16:53:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not trolling you, dude. Training my brain not to churn up random shit, and training my brain to channel in on only the shit that's useful - that's the same thing, at least I can't tell the difference.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 16:58:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You explained that really well, thank you! I'll also follow your link.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Her Majesty the Queen is OP and fuck and needs to be nerfed.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 17:49:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hi Bike go'ers, how much do you think this is worth? 05 LS pro senior 50 full auto, KTM $AUD</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 03:01:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to pass a drug test in 2 hours (documented evidence)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 04:30:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>So [Here](https://imgur.com/a/ndnI9A6) is the documentation on the method used and also the test results both before and after using the method. NOTES: Vitamin B2 would be better than centrum for a bit of colour, try to drink hydrolyte water for the last 600mL of water, and a small supplementation of creatine will also help toward better test results. This was only an at home test, and I am going to be re-doing it tomorrow morning running off 300mL top ups rather than 200mL, as the test is only barely worth calling a pass, but nonetheless that's a damn pass. Will update tomorrow on whether or not the 300mL intervals results a stronger negative and also will report on b2 for colouring.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 05:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have them backwards sorry, the top picture isthe second test (a pass), you can see on the THC panel that I have 2 lines, you need 2 lines for a pass. Then under that is the method, then the third picture is the original drug testing panel, where only 1 line shows on THC panel, indicating a failed drug test.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 05:42:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have 2 more drug tests, I'm tweaking the method tomorrow by swapping centrum for 200mg of B2 and also the intervals are being changed to 300mL at a time, and the last 900mL will be electrolytes. I'll post back with photo's and results. That's 100% a pass but I feel like I can get a stronger line. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:15:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>None of that comes from Jesus though, it comes from Man. Just because it's in the Bible doesn't make it real, only what Jesus and God said matters, and I showed you Gods word above. Jesus warns of falling into the trap of being a fake christian, maybe this is a test for humanity to over come, it doesn't take much critical thinking to realise where I'm coming from. The 3 pieces of information I've provided null any argument against homosexuality I've come across so far. Especially yours.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:19:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Show me where Jesus says that homosexuality is a Sin. Also, why would God have them be born so that they are chemically wired differently so that they are attracted to men, if it was a Sin? It's God's direct and intentional work to have them the way they are. It's the exact same as someone being born with only 1 arm, it's just the way they came out by chance, so how is that a Sin?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:22:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get that Paul said all that, but Paul isn't Jesus and Paul saying all that doesn't change the fact that Jesus said all these other things contradicting the judgemental behaviour towards each other. God is Love and if a man Loves another man, who are you to deny that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:24:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Side A seems legit. Also, good on you for calling it side A.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:26:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Taking into consideration the 3 points I have provided though, it would make our judgement an unfair one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:28:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're using a lack of evidence as evidence.. Jesus not once mentions his view on homosexuality, which is where you need to start your own critical thinking. Taking those 3 points I've given you leaves no room for judgement against homosexuality or any reason to believe that it's a Sin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:29:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Bible says it's not right, not Jesus, so no that's not love. Love would be accepting them 100% for who they are and encouraging them to love one another as more love = closer to what God wants as god is love. If you take the 3 points I've given you into consideration you can see that the judgement is not a right judgement anyway, lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:31:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but, those 3 points I've mentioned conflicts with what Paul says VERY hard. And Paul isn't Jesus, IDC if he's his representative, he's Human and Human's make errors, A LOT.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:32:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>If god's word is not up for debate then I implore you to re-read the 3 majour poitns I've made, because they nullify any single argument anyone can come up with against me. I speak from a place of love and love is a place of God, therefore I am speaking God's truth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:33:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see you're part of the Anglican Church, is this the view of all Anglicans? I want to start going to Church again, but this really conflicts with everything I believe and it makes being a Christian hard for me..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:35:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>An unconditional love toward our brothers and sisters would result in us encouraging a man to love another man. A man loving another man only does 1 thing, bring more love into the world, and God/Jesus is love. Why would God/Jesus not want more love in the world? The entire homosexuality debate does nothing but divide people, cant you see?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:37:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your judgement and lack of compassion toward your homosexual brothers, and the fact that you are discouraging more love to enter the world, makes Jesus cry. He wants love to spread, encouraging a man to love another man does nothing but spread more love/more of God, and by deeming homosexuality as a Sin you're only dividing man, not bringing the brothers and sisters we're supposed to have unconditional love for, closer... Rather you're pushing them away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:42:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>The New Testament brought fourth a new way of living, OT was different rules of living. The most up to date information that we have at our disposal about God and Jesus (NT), says to love one another unconditionally, love thy neighbour like you love yourself... How is discouraging a man and another man to love each other, bringing more love into the world? Our job as Christians is to have people know us by our love, yet when a man tries to love another man, we call them a sinner and we try to "save them" lmfao. It seems we are doing the opposite of what the NT and Jesus teach, which is to unconditionally love one another and to encourage love and bring more love to the world.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:44:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right, but our most up to date scripture gives us direct orders to love one another unconditionally, and to spread love through the world and to preach the word of God. How is telling someone not to love another person, spreading love? How is that bringing human kind closer together? It's dividing us as a race, and even pushing homosexuals away from God, because fake Christians can't seem to understand the simple concepts of just loving one another unconditionally, and not judging one another.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:45:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's an act that has been judged by Humans, incorrectly judged. The 3 points I've made point to the fact that Jesus would encourage homosexuality. Jesus wanted MORE love in the world, a man loving a man is doing exactly that. How is bringing more love into a world, when we've been told to love each other, spread the word of god and not judge each toher... How is that Godly? It's not, it's Sin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:48:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>How would you know if it's Love or Lust? Plenty of Gay couples have lasted a life time, just like man and woman. It may be mentioned in OT scriptures that homosexuality is a sin, but keep in mind that was written by man. The 3 points I've made completely nullify any arguments you have because it's the most up to date scripture we have. If the most up to date scripture we have, says to love thy neighbour unconditionally, to judge not lest ye be judged and to spread the word of god and love.. Then how can you sit there and say that a man LOVING another man is not right? God is Love and God is good, I speak from a place of non-judgmental love therefore it is the word of God.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:50:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brother, it's my job to call you out for sinning. You are ignoring Jesus direct orders, to love one another unconditionally and to spread love across the world, by saying the love between 2 men is less than a love between a man and woman is dividing the human race, not bringing us closer together, please open your eyes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:53:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't doubt he was being loving, because he thought he was doing the right thing. The 3 arguments I've presented to you though, the directions given to us directly from Jesus himself, contradicts what Paul said though. For us to say the love between a man and a man is less important than the love between a man and a woman is a direct attack on God, because god is love. Please open your eyes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:59:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>The newest scriptures we have available to us, is the NT. In the new testament Jesus says love thy neighbour like you love yourself, he gives us orders to spread love and the word of God across the world. How is saying the love between a man and another man is LESS than the love between a man and a woman, doing Jesus/Gods work? Its the exact same thing and it's derived from the exact same place, God. How do you have authority to say it's wrong, when Jesus said it's right? As long as it's love, and you are not doing wrong by the partner, there should be no reason for us to see it as a Sin, for it is love. Love does nothing but bring the world closer. The 3 arguments I presented to you contradict everything you've said, and the scriptures I use as evidence of my claims are from the NT, not the OT... How can you say that because the OT says this, then the NT is wrong? The NT is the new way of living that Jesus has set out for us to try to follow, which is love each other unconditionally, and not judge one another. The fact that you see homosexuality as a Sin is judgement in itself, especially the fact that you're insinuating that the love between 2 men is less than the love between a man and a woman, BOTH loves come from the same source, God, so how can it be wrong?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:01:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then re-read what I said at the top, because that comes from Jesus and surely you can place your faith in him. Our latest scriptures (NT) encourage love and understand and compassion on the highest level towards one another, that would include allowing a man to love another man unconditionally and without judgement of being a sinner. Please open your eyes, you're dividing the world.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:04:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will my brother. I implore you to stop quoting from the OT and start quoting from the NT, because Jesus set us out a nwe way of living. Love your neighbour unconditionally and without judgement, please open your eyes, bye saying the love between 2 men is less than the love between a man and woman is dividing the world, and doing the exact opposite to what Jesus has told us to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:06:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>But I'm saying that homosexuality is not a sin at all, so I'm not condemning anyone, because love is God and God is just.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:07:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're doing it backwards though, the OT mentions homosexuality but that all ends at the NT. Jesus set a new way of living, which is to love each other and to spread love and the word of God. Telling homosexuals that their love is less than the love of a man and woman is WRONG.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:10:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>No but adultery has been named a sin and addressed directly by Jesus. The fact you're saying the love between 2 men is less than the love between a man and woman is wrong, on every level. You hurt their feelings, you make them wonder why they're born, you make them hurt and often commit suicide or become a drug addict. If trying to convince them that their heads are messed up, and that they should love woman and not other men, is driving them to these outcomes, then how is it love? It's not, it's WRONG. The love between 2 men is the same as the love between a man and a woman, neither is suprior or inferior to the other, for they are the exact same thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:13:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, so God intentionally wires these 2 men to be attracted to each other and not woman. The loving Christian attempts to tell them that they're sinners, it makes them question their existence, why was I born, if I was made wrong? It causes depression, suicide, it creates drug addicts and confusion. It is the exact opposite of what Jesus has commanded us to do. Jesus has commanded us to just accept and love each other unconditionally and without judgement, for the judgement must be left to God. The love between 2 men is not less than the love between a man and a woman, it is the exact same recipe that comes from the exact same place and it has come from that place intentionally, because God is perfect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:19:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>But I'm sharing Gods word with you, from the most up to date scriptures, you're just ignoring it. You're like the Jews in the Bible, your eyes are shut and you aren't accepting the truth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:26:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>So many OT scripturs being posted. Why can't you all just do what Jesus said? Show unconditional love and compassion towards your brothers and spread the word of God. Telling a gay man he popped out wrong and his head needs fixing, makes people depressed, suicidal, turn to drugs... How is forcing a person to wonder why they were born WRONG, a good thing? It's wrong, it's dead wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:28:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>But you're okay with telling them that God made a mistake, and made them come out wrong.. That their heads are defective and they need to be saved, despite that's how God made them and God makes no mistakes? You think it's okay to make them depressed? To feel unwanted? To drive them to suicide? To turn perfectly good people into drug addicts by excluding them and telling them that their heads are wrong? You want that blood? I think it's easier to do what Jesus said, and just love them for who they are and accept them for who they are, to bring the world closer together and to spread the word of God together as a race.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:32:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not trying to mudsling brother I'm trying to have an intellectual conversation and perhaps even be convinced why I'm wrong, but so far no one has offered me a single piece of evidence as to why I should accept that being homosexual is wrong. I'll tell you what's wrong, my friend, and I hope it opens your eyes. Telling a person that God made a mistake withtheir head, that they are meant to love a different gender, one they aren't attracted to. Making them feel excluded, making them feel worthless and weird and wrong, driving them to depression and suicide, creating drug addicts and making people wonder why they were even born in the first place, if they were born wrong... Jesus says just love one another unconditionally, with compassion, just like you love yourself and with no judgement. The world would be a closer, more loving place with a lot more of Gods good word in it, if people like you would just stop and open your eyes to what you're doing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:38:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't read it because it was long and pointless. A man who argues with me that it is okay to tell another man he was born WRONG, is not worth reading. By saying homosexuality is a sin, you are telling people they were born wrong, that god made a mistake with them. That makes people feel excluded, it makes them feel unloved, it makes them question their existence, it makes them get bullied, it drives them to depression and suicide. You are creating drug addicts. Jesus gave us one simple job, to unconditionally love our brothers and sisters, with ultimate compassion and judgement free. It's a \*very\* simple task he has left us with but a lot of you Christians don't understand the point, you're exactly like the fake Christians Jesus warns about in the NT. How hard is it to just unconditionally love one another, draw the world and its people cloer together, create more love and encourage it, and have more of the good word of God? You make no sense to me, that's why I stopped reading your response so quickly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:41:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not gay, just so you know. I don't want to fight either, I'm here to be educated, maybe I can be convinced being homosexual is wrong, but so far nothing worth mentioning has come up.. At the core, all I've been presented with is crap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:48:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude, people are bornthe way they are born. God does not make mistakes, if a man comes out and is attracted to another man, it's not a mistake it is because he is gay, heisn't confused or like, curious or anything, he's just GAY. He's DIFFERENT to heterosexual men. The OT says it's a sin sure, but I dont care about what Moses wrote even if it was "from god" because Jesus came and he said... Love your neighbours unconditionally, show ultimate compassion and love towards each other and don't judge each other... By telling a gay man he came out wrong, you're bullying, you're making them feel excludedand outcasted, make them feel wrong and they question their existence, it can lead to depression, suicide and you're creating drug addicts... It does not take a genius to work out that by just loving each other unconditionally and showing compassion and encouraging a man to love another man, we are bringing more love into the world, we are bringing the human race closer together and we are spreading the word of god with a lot more ease because there is not divisions... God is right, God is Just, God is Love. God is also homosexual love.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:49:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude, people are bornthe way they are born. God does not make mistakes, if a man comes out and is attracted to another man, it's not a mistake it is because he is gay, heisn't confused or like, curious or anything, he's just GAY. He's DIFFERENT to heterosexual men. The OT says it's a sin sure, but I dont care about what Moses wrote even if it was "from god" because Jesus came and he said... Love your neighbours unconditionally, show ultimate compassion and love towards each other and don't judge each other... By telling a gay man he came out wrong, you're bullying, you're making them feel excludedand outcasted, make them feel wrong and they question their existence, it can lead to depression, suicide and you're creating drug addicts... It does not take a genius to work out that by just loving each other unconditionally and showing compassion and encouraging a man to love another man, we are bringing more love into the world, we are bringing the human race closer together and we are spreading the word of god with a lot more ease because there is not divisions... God is right, God is Just, God is Love. God is also homosexual love.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:50:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude, people are born the way they are born. God does not make mistakes, if a man comes out and is attracted to another man, it's not a mistake it is because he is gay, heisn't confused or like, curious or anything, he's just GAY. He's DIFFERENT to heterosexual men. The OT says it's a sin sure, but I dont care about what Moses wrote even if it was "from god" because Jesus came and he said... Love your neighbours unconditionally, show ultimate compassion and love towards each other and don't judge each other... By telling a gay man he came out wrong, you're bullying, you're making them feel excludedand outcasted, make them feel wrong and they question their existence, it can lead to depression, suicide and you're creating drug addicts... It does not take a genius to work out that by just loving each other unconditionally and showing compassion and encouraging a man to love another man, we are bringing more love into the world, we are bringing the human race closer together and we are spreading the word of god with a lot more ease because there is not divisions... God is right, God is Just, God is Love. God is also homosexual love.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:50:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then why does he make them chemically different? Why does he intentionally create them to be attracted to each other?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:53:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahahaha, it would seem that way but they aren't doing it right. What Jesus preached was true man, unconditional love, no judgement, ultimate compassion... How is telling people they came out wrong being a good christian? Where is the love in creating exclusions, makingthem feel weird and doubt their existence, causing depression and anxiety within people about the way they were born, driving them to suicide and creating drug addicts. I consider myself Christian but I'm wondering how the rest of these people can call them self the same, when they don't even understand the super simple concepts Jesus preached...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:55:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uhh, I haven't answered anyone rudely :L</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 09:00:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>So why does God make homosexuals? Also, that pedophile reference is disgusting. A pedophile has sex with children out of (a disgusting) form of lust and or violence (if they are a rapist too), the 2 are not comparable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 09:05:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Show me where then, I'm asking to be educated. I haven't found a place yet where it says it's not okay directly, and I certainly have found nothing in the entire Bible that has more authority than Jesus saying "Love your neighbour unconditionally" "Judge not lest ye be judged", all his lesons were about love and compassion and spreading the word of God... Telling people that God made them wrong, only makes them feel excluded, different, weird... Turns them to depression, suicide, creates drug addicts, how is that Christian methods?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 09:06:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bro, I'm just genuinely mind boggled that so far you're the only person who gets it, it's actually really sad...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 09:11:53</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Homosexuality is not a disease, it #8217;s part of natural human variation. I think we #8217;ve reached the point that we have enough evidence that there #8217;s a biological basis for sexual orientation, #8221; Margaret McCarthy, a neuroscientist at the University of Maryland told" There is also studies that show, people who believe people are gay by choice are less tolerant, while people who believe people are born gay are more tolerant. Science definitely has documentation and evidence to suggest people are born gay and there is nothing they can do to change it. Sounds to me like you're just an intolerant homophobe, bro.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 09:14:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I'm not gay and Christian and I got your back, brother (or sister). Don't turn your back on something beautiful (Jesus) because of bigots, take the advice you just gave to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 09:16:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't bothered to look at studies like I have for homosexuals regarding whther or not they're born that way. If pedophiles are born that way though, we can take you back to my third point. It is clearly immoral and indecent to have sex with a child who is not even matured to the point where she can bear children, this is an act of aggression and lust and therefore a sin... It doesn't take a genius to work out that if a kid doesn't have ovaries you shouldn't be having sex with it, that's built into our subconscious, unless the person has suffered significant trauma's in their own life and can't see clearly...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 09:24:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>No problem!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 09:30:41</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Dude, people are bornthe way they are born. God does not make mistakes, if a man comes out and is attracted to another man, it's not a mistake it is because he is gay, heisn't confused or like, curious or anything, he's just GAY. He's DIFFERENT to heterosexual men. The OT says it's a sin sure, but I dont care about what Moses wrote even if it was "from god" because Jesus came and he said... Love your neighbours unconditionally, show ultimate compassion and love towards each other and don't judge each other... By telling a gay man he came out wrong, you're bullying, you're making them feel excludedand outcasted, make them feel wrong and they question their existence, it can lead to depression, suicide and you're creating drug addicts... It does not take a genius to work out that by just loving each other unconditionally and showing compassion and encouraging a man to love another man, we are bringing more love into the world, we are bringing the human race closer together and we are spreading the word of god with a lot more ease because there is not divisions... God is right, God is Just, God is Love. God is also homosexual love.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 09:39:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>See man? You'r just a homophobic bigot.. "Anal sex reverse engineers this entire process to produce pleasure. The penis stretching the sphincter open and giving sensations of fullness in the rectum stimulates all the nerves that makes pooping feel good. Unlike pooping, however, which lasts for a short time, anal sex continues on for some length of time, flooding the brain with pleasurable sensations. The proximity of the anus and rectum to the crura (legs) of the ciltoris and G-spot in women and the prostate gland in men also means that pressure and thrusting in the rectum produce additional pleasure." There is pleasure/intimacy for gay people in having anal sex.. Your arguement of a pedophile having sex with a child is completely different. 2 Males having sex is a show of affection and love and also feels good because there is receptors in the anus to make it feel good... A 40 year old man having sex with an 8 year old who has no ovaries or any means to even make a baby, is violent and disgusting and clearly morally wrong.. Your point is invalid. Also, I'm not gay... I'm just not a judgemental asshole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 09:47:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>nah, you're wrong... it's immoral to make a man or woman feel unwanted, not normal in the head like they were born wrong, rejected by society, it drives people to suicide, depression, they question why they were even born, it creates drug addicts and most of all, why would god make them that way if it was wrong? it's scientifically proven that people are not gay by choice they're born that way, so you're saying god makes mistakes? it does the opposite to spreading love which is the number 1 thing Jesus carried on about... Love your neighbour, don't judge and show compassion is literally all he cared about... Causing people to kill themselves and turn into drug addicts, or even not at that extreme, just making people doubt the reason they were born - is not right. it does not take a genius to work out how its wrong.... by accepting homosexuality it only does 1 thing - encourage MORE love in the world, brings humans CLOSER and would make spreading the word of god easier. you need to think for urself a little bit, maybe god told moses to write all that stuff, maybe he didn't... but i know 100% without doubt what jesus said and he said to be a decent human</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 09:54:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>maybe moses wrote down gods laws, maybe he added a few of his own... i really dont care about the OT anyway, because the new testament is the newest scripture and the NUMBER ONE thing Jesus said, was to show unconditional love to your neighbour, compassion and to spread the word of god... being homophobic does nothing but divide the world and cause depression, anxiety and suicide among a large % of the world... all jesus wanted you to do was be a decent person, i don't understand how you can't see it but i'm done trying to convince you, it's like talking to a wall... you have 1 job so just do it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 09:55:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>that's what i thought</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 09:55:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah well i mean, 99% of marriages are that way aren't they</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 09:57:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>i said i haven't researched much into why people are pedophiles, have you? there is scientific data to back up my saying homosexuals are born gay, but i can't find anything to say pedophiles are born pedophiles, its a crude, disgusting and violent act that is probably caused by trauma to the person as a kid themselves</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 09:59:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>and so is causing a mass population of people to doubt their existence, to make millions of people suicide every year and to drive them into drug addiction by telling them they were born wrong, that god made a mistake... 1 out weighs the other, even if it were sinful the repercussions of telling people they're sinning and are born wrong in the head is not worth it and not what jesus would want</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 10:00:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>tell me what it means then, i'm here to be educated... its just that no one has a argument that seems worthy of causing mass suicides and drug addictions and depression/anxiety by telling them god fucked up and made them be born wrong, that their heads are wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 10:01:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>i said you resemble them and their ignorance, bye</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 10:12:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Link please, I'd like to check the persons credibility and see if it's peer reviewed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 13:27:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the resources, I'll start educating myself and make a decision on where I stand. One question though... Don't you feel mean treating gay's like outcasts? That's what I would struggle with the most if I changed my opinion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 13:29:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're intolerant toward homosexuality.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Am I allowed to be Christian, but have zero care or thought about the whole homosexual thing?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 13:33:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to be Christian, but I struggle with the whole homosexual thing. I'm not gay btw, but I just struggle with the whole thing that God makes people that are born gay, and then they are sinners because of something they were born with... So can I just like, ignore that bit? Cause I'm cool with gay people, they don't bother me and their shit is not my shit so I just wanna be a Christian and let them do their own thing... Or does it not work like that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 13:43:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's indirect out-casting though. As a gay man, if I was told that I've been born a gay man, placed on this Earth as a born gay, naturally I'm just gay... That I have to try and fight my core beliefs and my natural instinct and sexual desires other wise I'm a sinner, and god will not accept me unless I spend my entire life fighting the essence of who I am, does that make sense? They are excluded because they are forced to fight their natural sexual orientation, I mean... Can you imagine being forced into being with a man or you go to hell? Of course they feel out casted and excluded. It also says in the Bible it's my job to save sinners, so every time I meet a gay man, I have to try and convince him that his head is wired wrong and he needs to stop doing what is natural to him and what makes him who he is, and who he was born to be, or Jesus will not accept them... Does this make sense? I'm struggling with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 13:49:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>But, in an earlier post I had a bunch of Christians flaming on about how, it's a duty of care to bring the sin of people to the persons attention, like.. If we see someone being raped, we run over and stop that shit because it's obviously the right thing to do, we need to stop that sin. If we see a gay man, it's a Christian duty of care to convince him that he needs to repent and stop trying to be gay or he can't ever go to heaven... This is conflicting within me, because honestly, I don't give a shit about whether or not they're gay... I feel like the more love in the world the better, you know? But everyone tells me I'm wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 13:55:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah so like... We have to tell them that being gay is a Sin, that's obviously going to piss people off. It will piss people off, MASSES of people, millions and millions because they're born that way, that's the way God made them. Then all of a sudden, the way they're made is a Sin and the church will ot accept them and they will burn in hell forever, unless they spend their entire life fighting the essence of their being.. It's like, someone telling me I have to sleep with a man every night for the rest of my life because God made me like woman.. And if I want to get to heaven I have to pretend I like guys and I have to force myself to be someone I'm not... See how I'm conflicted? We're actively making people outcasts from the Christian community by aggravating them, we're attacking who they were naturally born to be how is that right? Why would they want to be apart of something that does that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 13:57:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but like, being born to be chemically wired to be attracted to a Man, then being told you HAVE to like woman, that's a big thing. Like, I wouldn't handle being told I have to sleep with men forever.. So I feel like that's a bit different to like, working on my jealousy and lust or what ever.. It's literally asking you to live a lie your entire life or you burn in a lake of lava forever. See what I mean? It's pretty rough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 14:00:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes that was me, but the context is incorrect. I just heard nothing that made sense to me, so rather than sitting there pissing off the Christian community, I've decided to hit it with a different approach. I'm trying to educate myself and understand how this is right, still struggling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 14:03:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is scientific data and tons of evidence supporting the fact that sexual orientation is decided within the womb. If people just suddenly decided they wanted to get with men instead of woman, I'd understand why it is sin. That's just not true though, they're born, predestined to turn into a gay person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 14:04:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't see a victim in a loving relationship :L</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 14:05:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>But... Whyyyyyyyyyy does God create gay people, and then force them to be not gay? Why not just, everyone that's born is straight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 15:05:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course, this is Reddit after all, apologies. Here is some I found in about 3 or 4 minutes, try yourself if you want more proof... I'm open to your idea's, have a read and maybe be open to mine.[1](http://www.sciencemag.org/news/2012/12/homosexuality-may-start-womb), [2](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3138231/), [3](https://www.berkeley.edu/news/media/releases/2000/03/03-29-2000a.html)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 15:10:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Source 1](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3138231/) [Source 2](https://www.berkeley.edu/news/media/releases/2000/03/03-29-2000a.html)[Source 3](http://www.sciencemag.org/news/2012/12/homosexuality-may-start-womb). A few quick peer reviewd articles with evidence suggesting that sexual orientation is determined in the womb. Only took a few minutes to find those I encourage you to search for more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 15:12:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, but if I see someone telling a lie, and I know it's a lie, I can pull them aside in private and say hey that was wrong, you should apologise to that person and do the right thing, bro... But if I see a man who loves another man, and I say hey man, god made a mistake with your brain you're meant to love woman, go to a retreat and get your head fixed because you won't go into heaven, it doesn't go down well... You see what I'm saying?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 15:15:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>But god literally makes them gay, they don't just magically turn gay.. Why would he do that? There are peer reviewed articles and evidence to suggest that sexual orientation is determined in the womb [1](http://www.sciencemag.org/news/2012/12/homosexuality-may-start-womb)[2](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3138231/)[3](https://www.berkeley.edu/news/media/releases/2000/03/03-29-2000a.html). Why would God make them gay, then force them to spend their entire life fighting against their very own core, lest they be sent to hell? :L</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 15:18:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because you may not have found the source, it wasn't posted to you. I'm a little confused, it's data you asked for. Why change the subject? EDIT: Okay it was you, I'm repeating myself because you said at the top " How do you know that? From what I've seen, that's one theory but not the only way to interpret the data. " and I can't be bothered finding you fresh articles, you seem intelligent can you please find some yourself?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 15:25:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I edited. My inbox is being blown up, apologies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 15:30:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay fine. Answer me one single question. Sexual orientation is determined in the womb, right? There is scientific data and evidence to back it up. Why would god pre-determine someone to be gay, only later to have them spend the rest of their life living a lie, trying to force themself into a sexual orientation that makes them sick. Can you imagine having to sleep with the same sex for the rest of your life,lest ye be damned to the eternal lake of fire? It makes no sense for a loving god to intentionally make people suffer like that. [1](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3138231/), [2](https://www.berkeley.edu/news/media/releases/2000/03/03-29-2000a.html), [3](http://www.sciencemag.org/news/2012/12/homosexuality-may-start-womb).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 15:43:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>God breathe's the breath of life into all living beings, why would he create a living being, then have it chemically wired to be gay, and then punish it for not spending it's entire life trying to be something it's not? I've posted multiple peer reviewed articles on here tonight backing up the fact that sexual orientation is determined in the womb.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 15:46:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I know we're all sinners. To breathe the breath of life into a child, to have it start growing inside a womb, and then have the hormones of that baby's mother determine it's sexual orientation as gay... And THEN to punish that baby if it doesn't spend it's entire life trying to be something it's not seems like a cruel and unjust God. This is on another level to me being born with temptations of lust and jealousy, try to imagine yourself sleeping with the same sex every night and having to pretend you enjoy it and even have to try and convince yourself that, that's the way you are. It's cruel, it's punishing and I feel like it's not a very Godly thing to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 15:50:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think if people ask me, my response would be more like "Oh you're gay? Nice man, how's your relationship? I'm so happy for you my brother.. Yeah I'm Christian. Nope, never put any thought into whether or not you're a sinner... Lol yeah I know the Bible says that but none of it makes much sense to me so I just over look that, I concentrate on what Jesus taught and that's just to love other people and be decent, basically so yeah... I do that, hey good on you for being gay :) Hope it works out for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 15:52:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>You sound chill, I like you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 15:53:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>But what if I know gay people that want to be Christian? I have to say Oh sorry, while you were there in womb, god made your sexual orientation gay.. Unfortunately you have to spend your entire life pretending you're something your not or, lol, lake of fire, soz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 15:58:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have to see the flaw in trying to convince someone that's gay that being gay is not okay though, especialliy if they were indeed born that way. It's insulting, rude, belittling. You're making them question their place in the Universe because thir sxual orintation which they have no control over, is of the same sex. These feelings of confusion lead to suicide, deprssion, anxiety and drug addiction to name a few, how can my bringing of these feelings over people be Christian? I'm not challenging you, I'm genuinly curious on an answer I want to piece this together... It seems like the whole homosexuality thing does nothing but create pain, and distance us from each other when Jesus wanted the opposite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 16:01:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>People are born gay though, there's literally hundreds of peer reviewed articles with evidence backing it... Why would he do that, then make everyone tell them for their entire life that they were born wrong and have a problem with their brain. Making someone doubt their existence in the Universe is a very lonely and cruel thing to do from my point of view.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 16:03:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but, being born with no legs is a lot easier to deal with, than having to be forced to sleep with someone you're unattracted to. Imagine yourself being forced to sleep with the same sex for the rest of your life and having to convince yourself and pretend you like it lest ye not make into into heaven. I'd much rather live in a wheel chair and know who I am and know that I was created right, then doubt my very existence.. How lonely and sad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 16:11:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have nothing to reply to with this yet, you've given me a few things to think about. Take your up-vote.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 16:36:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please don't use wiki links as a source, it's unreliable. What I linked you are peer-reviewed articles which means we are able to replicate them to verify their validity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 16:40:48</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; It is not a sin to be gay or to have attraction to the same sex. It is a sin to have a sexual relationship with someone of the same sex. God designed sex very intentionally, and the purpose is for unity/intimacy between a husband and wife, and also for the possibility of creation of a new life. I see, this actually makes a lot of sense and I'm glad I read that.  gt; Additionally, psychology has not yet been able to determine if homosexuality is innate from birth. Most likely, it is caused by many factors including childhood environment, possible trauma, and maybe even factors affecting development from outside the womb before birth (i.e. music or television that can be heard by the unborn child). It may even be affected by the mother's activities during pregnancy. Incorrect, I've posted 3 peer-reviewed articles on here today indicating that sexual orientation is pre-determined within the womb, but good on you for the first part. I have a genuine appreciation for having been able to read that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 16:46:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is the sin the act of sex between 2 men, or is the sin the act of loving another man?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 16:49:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah okay, I've just recently (within the last 10 minutes) came to the same conclusion, and finally it's does make sense to me. THIS, makes sense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 16:51:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love ya mate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 16:57:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>It has taken me uhh, over 12 hours of constantly asking questions and debating with Christians on this subreddit today, but I found my truth. Thanks for your contributions :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 16:58:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have spent over 12 hours today on this Subreddit, debating and asking questions, and finally found my truth. Thanks for your contributions, God bless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 17:01:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have spent over 12 hours today on this Subreddit, debating and asking questions, and finally found my truth. Thanks for your contributions, God bless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 17:28:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I already made my mind up on the subject :D Man can love another man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 17:35:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>It helps, I wish I could up-vote you twice. Thank you for taking the time to write this for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 17:35:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 17:38:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have found some answers I've been looking for, very glad I made this post and had a lot of very helpful responses, thanks for taking your time to reply to my post! I'll definitely continue searching to understand my beliefs and challenge them for the rest of my life! God bless mate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 17:39:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hear, hear.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 17:57:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>All good, I found my answers :) God hasno problem with a man loving another man, the problem is with the lust and in-celibate sex. This is the truth for me and I finally found it, thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:19:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>lolol ok</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I find no reason to believe God has a problem with a wo/man loving another wo/man, I think it's a beautiful thing to be encouraged and would only bring the world closer together. Though, like heterosexual in-celibate sex, homosexual intercourse I would think to be deemed a Sin, only because it is purely based on lust and intercourse was made by God to produce babies between a man and a woman. Seriously though, in saying that, 2 people of the same sex, wanting to have sex, has absolutely nothing to do with me and I'm not going to go around telling homosexuals that they should avoid sex, because to be fair that's a very personal thing and none of my business.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:24:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, but it's respectful to not make people chase up the sources at the bottom when it's super easy to just find a peer-review journal or something online, they're everywhere. That's my own standard btw lol, no1 else has to do what I do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:26:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, but I found you peer-reviewed articles, if you're providing me evidence of something you could have spent the extra 5 seconds to just find a direct link for me rather than making me sift through links for 5-10 minutes, to verify your publicly editable source.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:29:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've came to my own conclusion after spending like 12 hours on this subreddit today :) I find no reason to believe God has a problem with the love between 2 people of the same sex, I think it's a beautiful thing which can only result in the people of the world bonding together in a closer way. I do agree though, that like in-celibate sex between heterosexual people, sex between 2 gay people is purely lustful and therefore a Sin, even more so when you consider that man and woman have sex in marriage to produce babies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:32:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>[1](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3138231/), [2](https://www.berkeley.edu/news/media/releases/2000/03/03-29-2000a.html), [3](http://www.sciencemag.org/news/2012/12/homosexuality-may-start-womb) I've already posted them a few times, I only bothered getting 3, but it took me like, 60 seconds? There is plenty out there, friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:32:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:37:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey mate! The conclusion I came to is that 2 man loving each other = NO SIN :) The love between any 2 humans on Earth is a beautiful thing to be cherished, and can ONLY bring the world closer together. Jesus did nothing but preach love and compassion and I believe this is the most important part of being a Christian.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:39:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, I was talking about in-celibate couples being lustful. Sex within marriage is fine! Though, I am new to this and don't know much, I'd like to learn more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:40:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I found the truth that makes sense to me now, thanks for trying to contribute though. God bless you too my friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:41:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, that was really profound. I wish I could up-vote you twice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:42:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol, there's plenty of scientific articles spread across this thread showing that sexual-orientation is pre-determined in the womb. If people woke up one day and were like, hmm might try having sex with a guy this time, just for fun... Then I would agree it as sin, but this isn't true, gay people have no control overtheir sexual orientation and you're very closed minded in thinking this way, I'm sorry to say. I hope you find some of the articles I mentioned and educate yourself, and challenge your belief systems.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:43:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you Christian btw?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:44:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sweet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:45:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree brother, leave the world in better shape than we found it, and if we have nothing nice to say to another human, at least don't say anything mean :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:47:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>And I suppose one could argue that, the difference between a gay marriage and a hetero marriage is that, the idea behind sex is to produce babies, where as in a gay marriage it is to embrace in an act of lust... Like I said though, this is an ever evolving thing for me and I feel like this needs some world, because it still doesn't quite feel right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:53:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol mate, i found my answers i'm after... you're full of a lot of hate for a christian and you're coming at me with aggression not an intent of love and teach, ending communication with you now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:53:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, how do you go with following Christ only? Do you go to Church or worship from home?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 19:00:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's your demeanor, you're here to cause trouble. I've found my answers, and told you more than once that I've made my mind up, so let it go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 19:06:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've started a chat with you :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 19:07:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I started a chat session with you :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 19:08:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, woah, calm down. I haven't sent you any such thing as a slew of insults I simply misinterpreted you. So you decided to be gay instead of straight at a certain age then? I'll gladly find you some more resources, I mistook you for a troll. You need to relax I'm not here to hurt anyone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 19:15:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I can't argue with that either :) Thanks for helping me, you're contributing to forming my ideologies around the entire thing. I agree with what you say now that you put it like that. You see, for me at this stage, it's about gathering information from all different sources, be it die hard Christians or LBGT community, I really appreciate your input so thanks a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 19:16:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was talking about couples that aren't yet married then :) Sex within marriage is fine! But God tells us not to have sex before marriage, so gay or not, I dunno, it must be a Sin I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 19:20:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>[1](https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S019188690200140X), "Genetic evidence suggests a heritable component and putative gene loci on the X chromosome", [2](https://www.newscientist.com/article/2155810-what-do-the-new-gay-genes-tell-us-about-sexual-orientation/) "What genes did they find and what do they do? One of the genes, which sits on chromosome 13, is active in a part of the brain called the diencephalon. Interestingly, this brain region contains the hypothalamus, which was identified in 1991 as differing in size between gay and straight men." There's 2, It's 3am I'm going to bed. Good night :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 19:38:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to bed guys, thanks to all who got involved with sincerity. God bless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 05:16:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anglican ;) FOUND IT! At least, this Church I found, very accepting and don't even consider a man loving another man as Sin. Start tonight at 5:30pm.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 05:17:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>All good mate, I will find the truth but I have to start with my own truth or I find no satisfaction within Christianity and it will cause me to turn a blind eye. I found a Church denomination that shares the same views as me and I have my first sermon tonight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 05:18:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah brother, nice. I agree, I found a Church who shares my views I start there tonight! God bless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 05:19:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahahahah! Found a Church that is in alignment with my views it feels so relieving to be able to have Christ as accept homosexuals this has been bothering me for years. Love you bro! or sis.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 10:47:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah anyway moving along lol i've made my mind up on the subject</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 10:48:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>What makes you think I'm not in the middle of my 200 hours of analyzing both sides of the story, and that's what I'm doing right NOW? Don't be so closed minded.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 10:50:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah brother, I'm done with this thread lol, it's nothing but an act of hate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 14:09:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol na mate, sexual orientation is pre-determined in the womb by hormones and other crap, argue the bible with me but not science.. people are born gay they don't choose it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 14:12:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol what, science has known for decades thaat sexual orientation is determined in the womb by hormones and stuff... why would he create something gay then tell it that it's wrong.... also, telling people that they are born to love something that makes them a sinner creates suicide rates, drug addicts, depression anxiety... oh hell yer that's love lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 14:13:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol telling people that being gay is a sin creates statistics of suicide, depression, anxiety, loneliness and separation bla bla bla, that sounds 100% like what jesus preached don't you agree</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 14:15:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol ur a joke how can u say u love people when literally just telling them that being gay is a sin creates depression, anxiety, suicide, drug addicts the list goes on, it's not an act of love to make people feel like that it's hate haha, i think jesus left it a grey area so we can figure it out ourselfs... honestly doesn't take a genius to realise that making people feel lonely and suicidal and depressed and all this other crap is not love lol, it's laughable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 15:02:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>i've posted 5 peer reviewed citations on this thread to prove being gay is determined in the womb... go have a look lol, also your wife isn't studying hard enough if she doesn't know about the incredible, no, STAGGERING difference in suicide, depression, anxiety in the gay lesbian and trans community [here](https://lgbtihealth.org.au/statistics/) is a website it's a .org so yes it's legit, go have a look at these statistics and tell me that this is love... jesus wanted us to love each other and have compassion above anything else, this whole homosexuality thing is some kind of stitch up, it isn't hard to see it's wrong buddy lol EDIT: as for paul, he's just saying what the OT says and people make mistakes, paul isn't god, jesus is god and jesus gave us a really simple task lol EDITEDIT: there isn't even anything to debate here, cant really be bothered replying to you cause i know you're just gunna display ignorance to everything i just presented to you anyway</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 16:08:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's super grey man you are just focusing too must on the testament which is old, rather than Jesus. You are letting knowledge blind you. Jesus gave you 1 job and you can't even do that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 16:13:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not saying that you want to make people feel like that but the facts are that they do anyway. Not just because of Christians, but the whole of society. They are bullied and harassed, even bashed and kill because they're gay, they spend their entire lives being told that they're weird and wrong and then the ultimate being of the Universe who is promised to love everyone - His followers also tell them that they're Sinners (You need to understand that when you're in a place of hurt like they are, they aren't going to understand or want to even TRY to consider things from your point of view, it's human nature to be straight on the defensive and close their mind when people are telling them that they were born weird). They are alone, they are depressed and they are hurt. [Here](https://lgbtihealth.org.au/statistics/) is statistics on the gay lesbian and trans community, whether you want to or not you are part of these statistics, it doesn't matter if you're coming from a place of "love" the real truth is that it's hate, because only hate can cause those statistics. If what you did was love them, then you'd be contributing towards savings lives, not contributing to convincing them that the God of the Universe thinks their brains are wrong. You see what I'm saying? I'm not being aggressive by the way so if that's how you're reading it, go back and re-read this in a sympathetic tone. It isn't hard to do what Jesus said, and that is Love one another. To love a LGBT person would be to encourage them to be themselves and to not try and force them to live their lives being someone they're not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 17:13:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah you already quoted Corinthians, and i told you that you're blinded by knowledge... At the end of the day bud, you, along with many many other Christians and Catholics and other religious folk, AND a large percentage of the population, are isolating the LGBT community and causing mental health issues. Jesus gave you 1 job which is to encourage love in the world, the love between a man and a man is still love and love comes from God, love IS god so if there is love between a man and a man than God has something to do with it. I'm bored and it's 2 am, hopefully you wake up to what you're doing one day. Cya</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 17:25:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems like you need more meditation, awfully quick to let yourself jump to conclusions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 19:13:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>reworded? i added "atleast, i can't tell the difference", i feel like you're the troll</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 14:34:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>yer anyway enjoy adding to suicide statstics, psycho</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 14:36:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>scroll to the bottom, there is references to every single statistic, and hell yes jesus is god, and jesus told you to just love one another and support each other with compassion and bla bla bla, im bored talking with u this has been going on for days lol, enjoy contributing to suicide statistics cya man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:41:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>well you don't look like him so relax</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>also you dont look to be a healthy weight</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 15:29:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Recently lost weight doing martial arts, NO idea where I stand. Honesty please.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 15:43:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>5</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 17:09:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>6.5</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 02:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol I'm only person to be honesthere, if 10 is the hottest you can get and not a single bit hotter or you'd die and 0 is a slug, you're a 6.5 that's pretty good, down downvote me. Get over yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 15:59:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>5.5</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 16:08:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so god damn gay, why are we pretending this is real? There's so many people in the world with better talents than pretending to get beaten up... I mean pros for the technique to take that fall without damage, but seriously... Fuck off with WWE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[28M] lost weight doing martial arts and I'm curious, rate me honestly!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 16:12:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>[https://imgur.com/a/GZlWBtk](https://imgur.com/a/GZlWBtk)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:39:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>His tooth when through his lip, that's it. There is an article here where he literally says he decided to stay down and keep pretending for the fans. [Please](https://prowrestlingstories.com/pro-wrestling-stories/undertaker-and-mick-foley-talk-about-their-legendary-hell-in-a-cell-match/) stop pretending wrestling is cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:45:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>6</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:46:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>6</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:46:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>5</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:46:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>5</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:46:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>4.5</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:47:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>5.5</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:48:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>5</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:49:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>6.5</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:49:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>6.5</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:49:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>4.5</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:50:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>6.5 almost 7</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 20:39:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am unsure of myself that's why my face looks that way lol, very unconfident person. In saying that, I have a girlfriend and stuff but, just wanted to know where I stand, you know.. Just for social confidence etc. EDIT: beard isn't intentional, it's just a thing that's there because I haven't shaved for a few days, work etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 20:45:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because it's hard to hold the phone lol xD Also, lack of confidence. https://imgur.com/a/atuMJa3 Maybe that might help, best I can do without taking more photo's.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 06:38:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because it's all a sham and we don't really get to vote on anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 08:18:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Th... That's the whole joke. The boss has more karma because he is doing Reddit wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Who is the dumbest co-worker you've ever had to share space with?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 12:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 12:40:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sure this will be a re-post but I mainly wanted to get these 2 stories out, they both happened today and I'm just fucking gobsmacked with this guy. Don't get me wrong, he's really nice and I kinda feel sorry for him, because he wants to be a good worker, he's just so fucking bad. We need to put in leave forms for scheduled days off, first story is that he put in a scheduled day leave for 3 months time, for a funeral. I get it like, maybe there is some way that this could be possible, like, there is a time frame or something that a person who's been given to live or something I don't know. I have a lot to learn about the world so maybe there is a way to predict a funeral 3 months away to the exact day, but what happened next confirmed that he's just dumb. We work in a factory, process workers, are working in sync with forklift drivers. The forklift drivers take our stuff outside then bring it back in, for reasons I can't be bothered explaining. Sometimes there is lifting involved for the forklift drivers and if they've swamped and busy, a worker or 2 can be asked to help them. So this guy gets asked to help the forkies (That's Australian, for forklift operators) and I'm not fucking lying, he went up and started trying to push the forklift... Who's work mate can top this? Is there anyone out there that is dumber than this I just... I fucking want to know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 12:46:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahahahahahaha. Oh shit, that's fucking great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 13:30:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 14:52:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>That dog is scared to be beaten. Currently a student in dog psychology at the University of Queensland and this dog is terrified.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 14:55:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reality check, you're probably not the best employee; get off your high horse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If I want to quit my job and start a small business, can I write my cert 4 in small business off on tax?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 16:19:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to quit my job and start a small business, I already have an ABN from another small business I tried to start but didn't have the knowledge to do it. So this time I want to study while I start the business to assist me with getting it off the ground. Can I pay for the course and write it off on tax? Or is it not tax deductible?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 06:35:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stab her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 08:23:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>For perspective, he's flipping out because someone threw a full bottle of beer at him from the crowd.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Grandma wanted to let the world know how much she loves dogs with a personalised plate.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 03:02:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://i.redd.it/rq5v239qlke11.png</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 06:11:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is me doing my "Wow my grandma is stupid" face.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 06:11:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is me doing my "Wow my grandma is stupid" face.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 17:18:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read in another comment he couldn't get to the shop. He was a dedicated Christian though and made sure to never miss a sermon, a few times he even, despite his age made the 15 mile walk to church and back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 02:46:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Give it a go once, so you know what it's like and then listen to them and don't stick your leg out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>With an outdoor grow, how cold will stunt and/or kill my plants?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 14:57:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's going in to spring here in Australia, temperatures are still ranging from about 42-53 degree's Fahrenheit or 6-12 Celsius.. Should I wait another week or 2 until it stays over 50 throughout the night? Or is this okay? Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 15:31:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>