<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject671</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 04:56:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>there's a pizza place a couple doors down and a couple of the kids working there come to my store on their breaks. sometimes they bring us leftover pizza and bread sticks.  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 05:06:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>i pour hot water into a pitcher while my americano shots are pouring if i'm not super busy. then i don't risk my shots dying if someone else is using the hot water tap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 06:04:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>ombre pink drink has cool lime base too. i think a lot of customers/people think it's the very berry base. have to remake so many of these</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 07:08:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>tall americano double sleeve no cup</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 04:16:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>we print blank receipt paper, write our closing list on it, and clip it to the schedule we keep by the register. when the shift sends someone on a break she checks the list and if we haven't kept up with it gets us back on task. it's mostly cleaning and at the bottom a few shifty things. usually goes close drive bar-clean cold bar/syrup stand, pull mats, bathrooms, sinks, wipe down +restock fridges, behind counter floors, BOH floors, whips/mocha/caramel, preclose bars, oven(at 8:30) cafe floors... anything else i missed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 04:26:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>i believe in us</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 05:14:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>ohhhhhhh my goooooooooooood as soon as i saw the blep i actually died of joy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 18:35:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>exactly and i think they've been added to the core menu as if we have TIME in the day to keep making that shitty cold brew whip it's so goopy it doesn't work</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 18:38:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>omg right w/ crystal ball i was constantly putting peach whip on regular frapps hy accident at least with the cold brew it's kind of brown but still</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 20:20:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL what</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:53:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>yez, i bought one a couple weeks ago but they sold out really fast</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>subtle teefies</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 02:49:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 06:04:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>"can i get the triple mocha frapp... decaf?" "so you want a cream based mocha with no whip?" "no i want the new one"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 06:09:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>every once in a while some douchebag puts their big ass hands behind the bar and tries to like wash their hands with our taps and this one guy burnt his hand with our hot water and it honestly scared the shit out of me i turn around and this guy is fondling the hot water tap and saying "oh shit, that's hot" i was like uh YEAH like omg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 17:30:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>we haven't had the dark mocha sauce since it came out. so that would literally just be a decaf mocha frapp with no/regular whip. why would you want the new one if you don't actually want it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 22:39:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>we didnt have strawberry acai until 5 minutes ago. when people ordered the pink drink before that they meant the violet drink so to reduce confusion that's the new name</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 22:43:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>the button for sugar free simple syrup appeared in the syrup section of the registers at my store but i see it nowhere</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 04:52:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>canada. man. that's how it is here. or at least in my store. before the actual pink drink launched we called the violet drink pink</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 05:05:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank u vmuch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 05:27:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>SOME LADY SAW THE VERISMO COFFEE MACHINE ON TOP OF THE MERCH SHELVES AND ASKED ME, THE SHORTEST EMPLOYEE ON THE FLOOR, TO GET IT DOWN SO I HAD TO HAUL THE LADDER OUT THERE AND DROP IT ON MY HEAD TO TELL HER IT WAS ON SALE FOR 179.99 AND THEN SHE BOUGHT IT AND ABOUT 6 OTHER THINGS AND PAID FOR IT ALL WITH ABOUT 7 GIFT CARDS AND IT WAS TERRIBLE AND TOOK UP SO MUCH TIME</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 05:28:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>SOME ASSHOLE LADY TRIED TO GIVE US A HALF FULL STARBUCKS CUP THROUGH THE WINDOW AND WE SAID NO SORRY SO SHE LEFT IT ON THE FUCKING HANDOFF PLANE OH MY GOD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 17:37:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh i do. upselling isn't a huge problem, not for me at least, i usually work nights and people don't want breakfast sandwiches at 8pm, but the night crew still gets shit for not selling enough food as if it's within our realm of control</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 22:01:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>also a 16 yr old barista. i've been here for 5 months or so and what i've learned is no one gives a shit how old you are as long as you're kind, helpful and capable of working and being willing to learn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 04:00:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>ME TOO BITCH ANF IM EVEN YOUNGER I SHOULD NOT BE HAVING ANY PAINS BUT HERE I AM HOBBLING AROUND AAAAAAAHHHHHHH</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 04:48:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>we were open on xmas and someone came in and ordered 25 drinks. twenty. five. in one order.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 20:42:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>sounds like a whole gertrude. but don't you pull long orders to the front? the 5 min tanked your window times no?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 20:42:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>except bananas</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 08:12:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh trippy. our dm is always yelling at us about times so if the order is more than 3 drinks and the 3rd isn't started by the time payment is taken we pull them. i take a lot of trips to the parking lot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 08:21:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>iced/caramel macchiatos are probably the most popular. also caramel frappuccinos. and blonde vanilla lattes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 08:25:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>when i started i loved bar and was always jealous of people who got it more than i did, but now (note i am a closer) i like pos and dt a lot more. when you're on bar at night you have to clean so much more shit and it's just ugh. so yeah i'd say i like dt best</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 08:30:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>blonde triple caramel macchiato with soy milk, half sweet, but i wouldn't get it iced. my iced drink is strawberry acai w/ coconut(call me basic) or white tea w/ peach and raspberry. or a matcha frapp w/out sweetener if the bar isn't busy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 08:32:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>isn't willow blonde roast? we have true north in canada. it's pretty good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 18:02:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>my store doesn't allow more than 10 shots to one person per day. heart palpitations and all that. but our add shot+quantity button allows adding 99 shots and it doesn't take more than 6 seconds</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 18:32:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>oooohhhhh that makes so much more sense</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 06:28:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>one time this guy ordered like 48 coffees all in personal cups through the drive through. which is fine. but when i handed to them every single time he stroked my hand so creepily that i eventually spilled hot coffee all over his gross creepy hands. i didn't do it intentionally but if he had kept doing it i might have. he held his hands out as if he expected me to clean them too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 06:39:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>there's this one guy that comes through sometimes and he specifies the number of ice cubes(5) very rudely. counts them, and will send it back if it's not 5. like, lol. how ridiculous</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 05:10:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>bagels, but we're always sold out. grilled cheese. i recently tried the hummus box and the salad was tasty but the hummus was strong enough to clean floors with, lol. it was expensive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 05:12:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>when i'm on hot bar and i'm steaming milk sometimes it smells so good i could die</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 07:19:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>considering i have no idea what that means, i doubt it. we just have a few things in our back fridges (very low stock) and hummus box is there. no one but employees order it usually cause no one else knows they exist lolol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 07:28:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>i wish it was bigger lol. it's so expensive for four tiny portions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 07:30:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>why the fuck would you ever</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 01:49:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>i don't even bother trying to anymore. my manager makes you provide a doctors note if you call in more than twice within any time period. if i can't find coverage, sucks to be me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 01:50:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>we have a rule for people who order water in the cafe that unless they're ordering said water as part of a larger order and they are a paying customer, they get their water in a to-stay cup anf they can sit in the cafe and drink it. otherwise, no water. cuts down on waste</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 05:43:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>i'm a canadabux partner, so we're not going to get sued for refusing water to people who can go across the parking lot and get a bottle of water from the corner store. our biggest thing lately has been reducing waste, so partners are not allowed to use the throwaway cups if they're on the clock, we're recycling more, upselling the reusable cups. if someone comes into the cafe, they can have water. they just get it in a to stay cup.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 17:11:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>wait what don't you take the wand apart at night and soak it w/ the cleaning tablets?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 17:21:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>ok, so, for closing, you generally have a precloser, right? (someone who works just before close. so until 9 or 10 or whenever you close). utilize them. get them to do cafe floors, bathrooms, sinks. when you close you should just be doing dishes and cleaning behind the counter. your shift will be busy with shift things. it's up to you to get the store sparkling in the half hour you have. it'll get easier. no one trained you to close?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 19:24:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>ohh gotchya. either way i think it's a dumb idea to do that with the pitchers. you do wipe down the wand with sanitizer and blow it out between drinks, which is more than you can say for pitchers, which you just rinse. it takes no extra time to use the pitcher that says dairy for dairy and soy for soy lol. i think i'd feel lost in bar without the labels anyway</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 19:26:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>well, get the precloser to do everything they can fit into their shift. preclose your bars at some point near close, too, it'll help a bunch. also, it's summer now so you might be able to get away with just sweeping the cafe. are you a drive thru location?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 22:29:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>wot the hell. we put a venti cold cup in a grande hot cup when we close the bars and put a tablet in hot water and soak the wand and little yellow cover part overnight. we only do it to the drive and cafe bars though, the decaf bar in the actual drive area will rust because we don't use it. we get so much gunk and shit. i didn't realize other stores don't do it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 22:29:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>is this not a normal thing omg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 22:32:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>that is super weird... we have lids and things on the handoff plane for cafe because #canada but i still think the unlabelled pitchers is counterproductive. why not just have four(or five, two dairy) for each bar(dairy, nondairy, coconut/almond, soy) with the labels on still?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 22:47:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>what? why would you throw away any contamination prevention just because it won't get rid of the problem completely? you blow out the steam wand and wipe it down, which cuts down most residue from the previous milk steamed. but all you do is rinse the pitchers, which is why they are labelled. i understand for your store that it's complicated, but there's still valid reasoning for having labelled pitchers. i know a lot of people with bad allergies to dairy or almonds and if they knew a store did that i think they'd avoid starbucks all together</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 01:38:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>5</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 01:41:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>defense tea. or medicine ball(i think it's called citrus defense now)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 02:01:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL this isnt even a flat white</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 07:39:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>the steam from the sanitizer melts my whole face off and it makes me sad cause i spend half my morning crafting this perfect smokey eye</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 06:16:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>i use powder. my face just comes right off lol melted mascara is part of my look now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 06:17:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>that is fucking hysterical oh my god</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 06:21:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>are dudes really that shitty to taller women?? i always thought they liked a girl with long legs. my little stubby ones are very unimpressive. also, for the things that don't fit, it's very surprising what you can do with a needle and thread and make things look amazing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 09:01:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>disagree. love gina.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 09:02:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>not a huge fan of the scenes where someone(usually jake) overreacts and then screams something(usually no) but for a super long time before the scene cuts just argh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 20:06:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>omh my life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 20:09:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>just puked in my mouth a little bit. how the fuck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 20:13:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>when i first got hired "garbage and cardboard run" confused the hell out of me. i thought it meant someone had to go get cardboard and garbage bags. also, whip. and espresso shots "dying". food "going out". green beans</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 20:14:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>i think it's a dumb idea. glad my store isn't doing it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 22:15:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>because while the wand does touch every single milk, you still wipe it with santized rags and blow it out for two seconds after each use, which is doing way more between drinks than just rinsing a pitcher, and half the time you don't get all the milk off of said pitcher. i think it's dumb because it's throwing away what little we do do to prevent cross contamination JUST because it "doesn't get rid of it completely". what kind of logic is that? my stepmother, while unbelievably annoying, is very allergic to almonds and she says she can tell when her milk has been steamed in the wrong pitcher(an almond pitcher, because green beans tend to grab the first one in sight whatever the label is) because she gets SICK. but she's just fine if it's steamed in a clean one with the right label. this is literally proof that having labels helps. obviously if your bar person is not blowing out or wiping the wand then it's pointless, but they should be. and if i was on bar and all my pitchers had no label i think i'd go insane.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 22:15:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>canadabux we're not doing it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 22:16:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>lool sorry for the essay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 22:20:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>also, communication. my decaf bar is actually not in my bar area, so i'll steam my milk and run over to the decaf bar to pull my shots. bar2 person might want to finish my drink for me, but the pitcher doesn't have a label so he has to take valuable time to ask, or wait, but if there was a label he could just put it into the cup that's asking for soy. i just see everything that's going to backfire for this new idea and i really hope canada doesn't catch on and do it too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 22:35:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes, we have two sanitizer dishes under each bar. one is for wiping the counters and cleaning up spills and the other is for wiping the steam wand</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 22:56:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>i'm wondering if the places all this weird shit is at is just low volume stores lol. i would not be able to keep track of 3 different rags during peak. i'm sure i could learn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 22:58:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>that's a lion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 23:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>for the starbucks cascara cold brew, there's vanilla syrup in the cold brew and cascara syrup in the foam. just saying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 04:23:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>exactly omg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 09:09:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>she probably hates coffee and adds all that sugar so she can drink it and tell people she likes americanos</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 09:12:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>we all went out for dinner right after lol. i had to close so i was late but it was fun</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 08:08:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>hey listen. most of the posts on this sub are just venting. being a partner is hard, especially at first-- i'm also anxious and depressed, but my teams are almost always very supportive and helpful and once you get the hang of things it is much easier. and learning everything at the beginning is fun. there are perks, too- coverage for healthcare, reimbursements for post-secondary school fees, free drinks, weekly markouts. the parts of the job that suck aren't supposed to be complained about while on the floor, so this sub is a good place to purge the negativity. trust me, being a partner is much more than what it looks like on here. i love my job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 08:11:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>also, working here has taught me how to be confident(or act that way) and project my voice and take charge. the shyest person can start here with a tiny voice and sad looking posture and a month later you can hear them across the store and know just by looking at them that they are hot shit and they know it too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 08:12:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>the amount of times i've asked someone who is serving ME, whether it's at starbucks or anywhere else, if they want their receipt, is embarrassing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 08:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>one time my ssv dropped the tills in the back and we still got out early i was shocked to my core</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 19:35:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>sometimes i have so many stickers on my apron you can't tell where the pockets are</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 19:36:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>to keep drive times down, you start making drinks as they're being ordered, before the sticker comes through. most of the time i/we forget to put the sticker on the cup before handing it off soooo it goes on the apron</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 19:53:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>i'm 6 month partner. i don't mind when veteran partners do things for me, most of the time they're doing it for a reason. what bothers me is when partners that are newer than me try to help me, or even worse, tell me what to do. lol it grinds my gears so much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 23:06:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>lololol my partners r such trolls sometimes i'll find my back covered in stickers or on my hair or my arm like lololol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 18:08:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>i just closed last night for refresher happy hour. it wasn't too bad.. assuming you have a partner coming in at 2 or 4 (when do you close?), just make sure you start the big jobs like cold bar and syrup stand at 4 of 5 so they are out of the way. you can do this. when you're on a break, go outside for some fresh air, stay hydrated, make sure you eat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 18:44:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>no, canada. my advice is to discourage the closer/s that you do have from deep cleaning. i doubt they would anyway, but if you can put it in their head that they just need to do a quick clean(rinse and sanitize cold bar, mop the busiest part of the cafe if you have one, etc), they might be more eager to get it done. and when doling out breaks get them to finish doing something first(finish sweeping behind fridges and go on your 15. finish cold bar and go on your half. you know how it goes). whatever happens, happens. you can get through it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 20:35:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>would you like a spill stopper, sir?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 20:37:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>on monday canada had the racial sensitivity meeting and most people just drove right through the lane when they read the flyers but a few people said "aww" or "see you tomorrow" and it was sweet lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 22:04:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>i have no idea. even though i had shitty family and shitty upbringing i still was taught that i should be kind to people especially workers, and i think that's part of canadian values. dont get me wrong we have irrational assholes but i don't run into them far as much as i see on this sub</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 03:18:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>one of the locations in my town ordered so many oat fudge bars they couldn't fit them all in the fridge, lol. they gave so many away</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 03:46:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>one time this old guy ordered like 6 coffees all in personal cups through drive and as i handed each one to him he stroked my hand so gross and creepily so i spilled hot coffee on him. oops.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 03:50:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh my god i thought i was the only one it makes me feel like i'm choking</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 17:33:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>triple blond anything. i drink cold brew when we have it but i work evenings and we're usually out by then. i also won't reject a regular cup of pike</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 19:52:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>damn that shit is beautiful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 09:10:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>it was explained why, because of gossip and stuff, but it's really only a few people who made it an issue. and it's so annoying because there's always at least 2 people that have no idea wtf is going on because they're not allowed to have a fucking headset on. i'll ask my shift for the shift keys but oh, she doesn't have a headset on. i'll ask someone to let me in because i just went on a cardboard run and it's raining but oh, the only two people with headsets on are in bar and in drive and they can't leave so lil ol me has to go all the way around this bigass strip mall and go through the front. it's just... our whole thing had always been about communication but now we're not allowed to communicate. i'm so irritated</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 09:11:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>exactly... i feel so disconnected with only 3 sets. and i'm very soft spoken so it's not like anyone can hear me(unless i'm calling out to a customer or screaming in the back room) if i'm not speaking into the headset</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 09:14:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah. to answer the box, and then the rest of us have headsets to communicate, "oh, this car is at three minutes, do you have the iced latte?" especially if we're slammed, it saves time to ask over the headset rather than go and take up space in the bar to ask. but now 3 out of a 6 person play are disconnected. i'm just ugh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 11:38:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>i think probably gossiping on the floor, having customers hear it... the night crew is bad for it(i assume the opening crew it too, usually when i open they talk shit about the closers but no one is around) but i'd much rather have had a sit down talk about it rather than just completely cutting off half our communication system.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 21:32:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>we generally only have one bar person, and they wear a headset so they can make orders as the person at the box is ordering. because window times. then the dt person is wearing one, and the shift should wear one because right now half my store is green beans. the issue is if i, the bar person, am out of trenta cups and someone just ordered 3 trenta black teas, but i already have 45 drinks lined up for cafe, i can't go get them, and my dt is still taking orders and trying to do window at the same time. the shift is doing a pull or a count or what the hell ever so i have to abandon my bar to get those dumbass trenta cups, unless by the grace of god the cs person is nearby. but when we all had headsets i could just ask someone to get them for me. or frap roast. or whip. or literally anything i don't have time for. i feel like this is counterproductive and i'm just hoping we revert back. plus the germs of giving your headset away and taking it back without sanitizing it it's just ugh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 21:34:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>i know and i'm night crew so we do a lot of cleaning and while we're cleaning we like to talk. we still get everything done in record time, so is it so wrong? it's just the people that start talking shit about a customer or another barista before they've even left the damn store that ruined it for everyone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 21:36:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>i know. it's just so much easier WITH the headsets. and i feel like my store is sort of big, i can't just turn to my right and be like oh hey joe whats up. joe is across the store. when i first started i never used the headset to talk because i was nervous lol but i was literally taught that if someone is too far away for you to take a few steps and be near them then you talk into the headset. fuck that i guess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 21:38:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>exactly, right? so all of that falls on the order person and that's exactly how orders get fucked up because they're too busy putting 7 bacon goudas in the oven they didn't punch in the extra hot chai and that first, looks bad for us, and second, tanks the stupid window times. ugh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 21:41:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>no one would dare use their phone on the floor unless to check the time or date. but the thing about my store is while we do talk a LOT we always put customers first and we always get everything done. one time we had no orders and nothing really to do so a few of my partners were just wiping counters and talking about something or other and a guy leaned over the bar and was like "oh my god, imm sorry to interrupt your super important conversation, but i want a water" or something like that and i bet my hat that a customer complained because s/he saw some people talking and thought it was outrageous</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 21:42:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>i'm assuming district wide. i haven't asked if other stores in my district ARE doing it but it's definitely brand new to my store and i already hate it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 21:42:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>right? i really hope they're not making the morning crew do this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 21:42:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's new to me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 11:21:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>we use blue spray for cleaning bar stuff that we don't take to back to sanitize (counters and syrup stand and crap) and for mirrors and the pastry case and handoff planes, tables, windows... we use restroom cleaner for restrooms and mats, liquid bleach for sinks(though only half of us use it the other half uses bathroom cleaner because it's "easier") and then oven cleaner for the oven. what else would you use blue spray for.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 23:07:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>well on the bottle it does say multi surface cleaner i think. closers clean a lot more things in kind of a tiny amount of time and blue spray gets the job done</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 08:30:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>make this into a spotify playlist and i'll love you forever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 08:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>same. it's usually right before my period and i just get everything done in record time. not so much lately though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 20:10:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>one time this guy made me put "the man" on there, so i just called out the drink for him. he looked me right in the eyes and demanded i call out the name, loudly. i was so comfortable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 09:29:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh you know, the usual. what up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 09:32:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>well i mean not really but who's alright on this sub am i right</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 09:38:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you  #10084; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 21:10:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>this is so cute i might die</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 02:21:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>my eyes are burning</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 05:06:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>why was it removed i want to know too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 05:07:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>i'm so sorry you're going through whatever it is you're going through. i would do anything to help you, but unfortunately from a distance all i can do is offer my ear to listen if you need it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 08:54:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>our water spout has been like that since before i started working there. one time it fell off into fresh made frapp roast</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 08:54:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>omg the last one makes my heart hurt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 09:43:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>happy saturday!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 07:12:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>valerian root. you can get special dog treats made with them(i think theyre called mellow) or you can buy them in capsule form and put them in his food. my golden has severe separation anxiety and he destroys the house when i'm gone. valerian root helps to relax him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>he's got white socks</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 12:13:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 01:42:36</DATE>
    <TEXT> #9829; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 04:51:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>that's so insane because i got my period this morning. i knew i would soon because i started cleaning my house and craving pizza but i didnt know clumsiness was apart of it too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 10:36:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>same. we did some troubleshooting over the phone with the.. music fixer people.. and it worked and then it didnt and then i think it was fixed today for good. i answered the phone and the guy was trying to get me to get a new player and i was like dude stop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 10:39:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>delete this now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 00:36:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's better to get them out. stay strong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>