<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject4392</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I now know who was the inspiration to Ronaldo's Golden Shoe speech</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-17 21:10:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 09:16:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes that is completely normal! I've had ocd for the last 7 years and comparing my rituals than and now, they're completely different. Most of them still based on counting but very different. I know it's strange because when you have a compulsion you think you'll never get rid of it...but sometimes it happens which can be good or not, because sometimes you just replace for other tic... (at least in my case). Wish you the best (:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anyone else sometimes "forget" why you're doing your compulsions?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 09:39:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I go travelling my ocd gets really, really worse. Last week I was supposed to go on a trip but I got so anxious, I was thinking about all the things that could kill me on that trip for every second I was not sleeping, and my compulsions were on the edge. I touched everything, counted non stop, I couldn't do anything but stay still on the couch crying. So I decided not go on the trip. I also decided to see a psychologist for the first time in 7 years battling with ocd. The suddenly, when I decided not to do something that made me really anxious, my obsessions almost disappear. And I still do a lot of compulsions, counting and touching, but I'm not thinking why I'm doing them, and causes me much less anxiety. I know this is probably just a phase were I'm less nervous and therefore better...but has this happen to anyone? Also, I'm afraid now my psychologist thinks this is nothing serious...but it is... Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 12:06:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes!! For example the sound of someone chewing gum kills me but just to see the motion of the mouth makes me wanna punch myself. That also happens for example with someone bitting their nails, I can't stand not only the sound but also the image. And there are many other visual triggers for me...it's great</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can't stop counting subtitles, words and lines from books</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 15:30:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my compulsions is counting and in the past weeks it has been almost impossible for me to watch a movie or read a book. I start counting without even noticing and than I can not stop until I reach a certain number (which is usual big...). I now avoid doing this things since it can become quite unbearable. Anyone else?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 01:21:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reading this really helps, thanks! I'm gonna tr #253; your suggestion, hopefully it will help. Thanks again (:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 01:28:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh. I can't watch my phone turn black too, I have to block it myself every time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 01:35:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so stupid, but that's your question so. When I'm eating, for example a cookie or a sandwich, I have to take 3 little pieces of that food and put on trash, otherwise I'll get fat, or the same thing but with 5 little pieces, otherwise something bad will happen to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 11:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel you. When I was little I used to count the stairs and other things, but nothing special. Than when I got older I start developing this obsession for couting. I count everything: i stoped reading books or watch movies with subtlties because I cannot stop couting. It's horrible. Edit: but do you just count with no specific "propose"? I mean, I can only stop when i reach a certain number. Does this happen to you too?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 19:37:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just can relate. I once freaked out at dinner table. When I start getting really anxious because of some sound, I tend to copy the sound myself, and my mum called me rude when I started copying the sound my dad was doing while eating. When I tell her that this is an actual condition she just gives me contemptuous look, like I'm making this up and, again, I'm just being rude. I wish she would feel what it is to have misophonia.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 16:49:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>The first person I told I had ocd (we were like 15 or 16) ask me "What's that?". For some time I was kinda sad/ frustrated because people had little awareness of what is ocd. But now I realise that I prefer them not to know what it is, instead of saying things like that person told you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 12:07:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't know if you talking about something like this, but for example I have this compulsion of couting the words when I'm reading a text, and sometimes I don't have the need to do that, but I start feeling anxious wondering why I'm not doing that instead of appreciating the fact that I'm not doing that uh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 11:35:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I have a similar I guess...I have to blink my eyes a certain number of times when I look at something dangerous like a knife or a heater (because it could cause a fire at the house or something like this eh) in order to be safe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Obsessions with spirits/ paranormal stuff?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 12:00:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've always had obsessions with things that, although unlikely to happen, actually could happen (someone killing me, someone burning my house, me and my family/ friends having and accident and die). But 2 days ago I had this stupid dream were there was a psychotic girl outside of my house who wanted to kill me and my family. The next day I start having obsessions/ compulsions about the girl/ the spirit of that girl, like she is going to burn my house and stuff like that... I don't believe in spirits and thats why this is stressing me out. Usually the thoughts are about something "real", but this doesn't make any sense to me. Anyone else?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 01:44:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I started cuting when I was 15 and I totally see what you mean. When I was about 18/19, I practically stoped cuting for some time, and I thought: "well, I actually ended up getting over it". I'm 21 and I still do it. Sometimes I don't even have a "reason" to do it, I'm not sad or frustrated. Sometimes I just want to do it. It is an addiction that we developed at some period of our lives and like any other addiction it's hard to stop. And at least for me, I don't have any 'motivation' or reason not do it if I feel like doing it, so that's probably why I still do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>