<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject2922</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 23:06:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is actually hilarious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is wrong with this page?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 06:10:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been on this page for over 20 seconds and haven't seen a single reference to #taxationistheft. We need to pick it up people. More memes would be nice too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Eco nom nomics  #127836;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-01 02:43:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #128175;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-01 05:40:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #128293; #128293; #128293;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-01 07:51:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why Government Matters:</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 04:47:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Discussion/Question Thread: Children</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 06:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's everyone's take on ownership of children in an anarchist society? At what point do humans get to assert self-ownership and to what degree? Is there an implied contract in parenting?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 06:49:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would you say that the children are subject to the orders of their parents? If so, to what extent and until when?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 06:59:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that establishing anarchy from an already existing society, such as the one we're living in now that downplays the importance of community, would create problems like this. One of the anarchist arguments against a situation like this arising is as follows: individuals would be so afraid of an instance like this occurring that they would only surround themselves with companions and like-minded people to create a community. This tribe-like arrangement would work in such a way that social norms would disincentivize this behavior. Also, communities would come to the aid of a person in this position(possibly rescuing them by helicopter or whatever). In the case of these communities still working to be established and a freak kind of occurrence like the one you described, the person must either attempt to get aid from the outside world, live in self-subsistence, or agree to the neighbor's terms.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 07:02:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm thinking that "social norms" are probably the best way to enforce those types of laws in an anarchist society. Would you agree?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guardians of the Galaxy actress says Hollywood "bullied" Trump</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-14 23:59:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nature is beaming with the beauty of anarchy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 20:20:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Refute "Taxation is not theft because you can leave."</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-19 06:01:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's the refutation to "Taxation is not theft because you can leave"?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-19 07:40:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for this link. You're wonderful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You can always leave</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-21 01:36:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-21 07:19:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's true. It'd be good to have the foundations of the rights at hand as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I said, "How tall are you?" He handed me this:</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-21 05:19:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you get to the touchy subjects... #11015; #65039;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 20:03:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 23:28:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>The way I defended it was through saying that #1 that might not be the case, #2 it would look a lot different than it would in our society today. Communities would have social norms that would self-regulate this kind of behavior and ensure nobody sold their kids to idiots.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tale as old as time...Song as old as rhyme...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 07:35:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 08:31:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Drawing similarities between a person growing up on their parents' land and taxation is misguided. The parents have rightful ownership of the property through homesteading. The government does not have rightful ownership of the property it occupies(imposes restrictions upon).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 15:55:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's irrelevant...the people who are renting it out to their parents have proper ownership. It would be just for them to impose controls and fees on property that they rightfully own, and it would be unjust for them to impose controls and fees on property they don't own. The anarchist argument is not that people can't impose restrictions on land period. The argument is that an entity must have proper ownership over a scarce good for them to impose controls on it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 16:03:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Many of the objections raised to "Taxation is theft" in this post can be dispelled by a simple video: https://youtu.be/fasTSY-dB-s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 16:07:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 22:26:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>The government doesn't have proper ownership of the goods which they claim you owe them. "You stayed here, so you pay" assumes that they own the place you're staying on and thereby have the right to impose restrictions on you for residing in that area. They don't actually have that proper ownership because they didn't obtain it through a voluntary transaction or through homesteading. https://youtu.be/fasTSY-dB-s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 22:27:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>You just presented a really good argument right there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 22:31:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not "just" mine. It's the Labor Theory of Property developed by John Locke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 22:35:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not an argument.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 00:08:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>You said,"This is just your opinion." I provided evidence to the contrary. I showed that it is in fact not "just" my opinion. I never would've appealed to authority unless it had answered the particulars of what you said. You appealed to the masses as if it somehow debunked the truth of the theory. I'd much rather stick to real arguments, but you stooped to "this is just your opinion."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 00:14:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's cute how you decided to reduce well-developed rights theory to "norms." Yes, anything that doesn't conform to the "norm" of NONAGGRESSION is AGGRESSION. Yes, throwing someone in jail is violence. I thought maybe I'd get real arguments and thought provoking material from you, as many people trying to debunk "taxation is theft" have given me. Unfortunately, you haven't. I'm all ears if you have any actual arguments. P.S. I would actually love to hear opposition to Locke's theory and why it's incorrect. I'm not being sarcastic. I'd enjoy hearing some critiques of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 04:25:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>So True! The government provisions given to banks are evil!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 19:57:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have 4 ps4 controllers plugged into my computer currently running the latest version of Ubuntu. All of the controllers work when I am in steam. However, one of them does not work when I open up the game. It is the same controller no matter what port I use. It has full functionality in steam, but does not work in games. I'd appreciate any insights you have!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 20:03:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok, I'm having two reoccuring problems that seem to occur randomly, but I've never had an instance where neither of them occur. Either the above happens, or the controller that doesn't work above works, and another controller, which was fine before, registers two inputs instead of one. Essentially, I either have 3 or 5 controllers when I only want 4.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 20:10:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have 4 ps4 controllers plugged into my computer currently running the latest version of Ubuntu. I'm having two reoccurring problems that seem to occur randomly, but I've never had an instance where neither of them occur. Reoccurring problem #1: All of the controllers work when I am in steam. However, one of them does not work when I open up the game. It is the same controller no matter what port I use. It has full functionality in steam, but does not work in games. Problem #2: Either the above happens, or the controller that doesn't work above works and another controller, which was fine before, registers two inputs instead of one. Essentially, I either have 3 or 5 controllers when I only want 4.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 15:22:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Both of these problems occur even if I have Bluetooth turned off and plug the controllers in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yo mama so statist she made you get a building permit to play with legos.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 01:24:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 21:37:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this posted on an AnCap page ironically or nah?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 21:45:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m getting an error message when I try to load the video, but I #8217;m assuming this is a That Guy T video.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 22:00:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also, charities don #8217;t earn profit. The communist would say that, rather than someone taking the value of their labor by  #8220;earning #8221; a profit, in the case of charity, they #8217;re giving the value freely to the recipient of the charity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-26 17:47:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>The free market is the absence of intervention, which, to the best of my knowledge, hasn #8217;t been realized completely. Even many  #8220;anarchist #8221; examples, such as the Eskimos and the like, contain anarchist law, but have other interventionist tendencies. I #8217;m an anarchist, but I #8217;m not sure I like Milton #8217;s quote. Even if anarchism hasn #8217;t been tried in its purest form, given that it #8217;s the most sound political philosophy, we should try it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hoppe New Year</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 06:03:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If you #8217;re having trouble with steamVR games on WMR(lag/shuttering), do these two things:</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 19:31:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 20:48:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Press in the joystick on the left controller, go to settings in steam from there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If SteamVR isn #8217;t working(lag/shuttering) in WMR, try these</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 20:49:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 02:01:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not sure, but these settings helped me a lot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 03:30:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Press left joystick in game and go to steam settings</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 01:44:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Navigate to the settings through the steam page, not the settings button you see right after pressing the left joystick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 04:15:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome! You #8217;re welcome!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 01:38:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wyatt, I don #8217;t appreciate the shoutout you freaker!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>