<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject1617</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Most people still think of the world as being divided between  #8220;developed #8221; and  #8220;developing #8221; countries. In Hans Rosling #8217;s latest video, he uses the example of Ethiopia and it #8217;s amazing progress in reducing child mortality to explain why we all need to update our thinking.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-10 20:08:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;m Bill Gates, co-chair of the Bill  amp; Melinda Gates Foundation. AMA</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 18:40:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi, I #8217;m Bill Gates, co-chair of the Bill  amp; Melinda Gates Foundation. Ask me anything. Many of you know me from my Microsoft days. The company remains very important to me and I #8217;m still chairman. But today my full time work is with the foundation. Melinda and I believe that everyone deserves the chance for a healthy and productive life  #8211; and so with the help of our amazing partners, we are working to find innovative ways to help people in need all over the world. I #8217;ve just finished writing my 2013 Annual Letter http://www.billsletter.com. This year I wrote about how there is a great opportunity to apply goals and measures to make global improvements in health, development and even education in the U.S. VERIFICATION: http://i.imgur.com/vlMjEgF.jpg I #8217;ll be answering your questions live, starting at 10:45 am PST. I #8217;m looking forward to my first AMA. UPDATE: Here #8217;s a video where I #8217;ve answered a few popular Reddit questions - http://youtu.be/qv_F-oKvlKU UPDATE: Thanks for the great AMA, Reddit! I hope you #8217;ll read my annual letter www.billsletter.com and visit my website, The Gates Notes, www.gatesnotes.com to see what I #8217;m working on. I #8217;d just like to leave you with the thought that helping others can be very gratifying. http://i.imgur.com/D3qRaty.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 19:46:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are two things this could reference. One is the free/pay for software mix. The Internet has benefited from having lots of free stuff and lots of commercial software. It has been interesting see people inventing hybrid models. Even stuff that is pretty commercial often has free versions for some audiences. Even the most open stuff often have services people choose to pay for. The second thing is the anonymous versus identified tension. This is another one where both will probably thrive since you want anonymity for some things and full identity for others. I am surprised how little progress has been made in the identity space but it will improve.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 19:47:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Free software. Just kidding. Books actually.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 19:49:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>We had a rich database as the client/cloud store that was part of a Windows release that was before its time. This is an idea that will remerge since your cloud store will be rich with schema rather than just a bunch of files and the client will be a partial replica of it with rich schema understanding.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 19:50:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kids. Cheap cheeseburgers. Open Course Ware courses...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 19:51:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have enjoyed meeting other philanthropists and talking about what they work on. I think there is a movement to do more, start sooner and be smarter about giving. Philanthropy is mostly about a broad set of people giving but it helps if the most wealthy set a strong example...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 19:52:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I definitely think leaving kids massive amounts of money is not a favor to them. Warren Buffett was part of an article in Fortune talking about this in 1986 before I met him and it made me think about it and decide he was right. Some people disagree with this but Melinda and I feel good about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 19:54:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not as much as I would like to. I write some C, C# and some Basic. I am surprised new languages have not made more progress in simplifying programming. It would be great if most high school kids were exposed to programming...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 19:56:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favorite of the last decade in Pinker's Better Angels of our Nature. It is long but profound look at the reduction in violence and discrimination over time. I review a lot of the books I read at gatesnotes.com (is that too self-promotional? http://b-gat.es/12GKLyN)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 19:58:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>The stork.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:00:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The violence against the vaccinators in both Pakistan and Nigeria is a terrible thing. However both countries are committed to finishing the eradication. This is the project I spent most of my time on. We should be able to finish by 2018 although that will require raising funds and some great execution. We have some innovations like the way we use satellite maps to find all the villages and GPS tracking to make sure the teams go to every hut that are helping out. Polio is a harder disease than smallpox was but it is doable. (I discuss this more at www.billsletter.com and you can learn more about the progress against polio with this infographic: http://annualletter.gatesfoundation.org/#nav=section4 amp;slide=2)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:02:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just got my Surface Pro a week ago and it is very nice. I am using a Perceptive Pixel display right now - huge Windows 8 touch whiteboard. These will come down in price over time and be pervasive... (http://i.imgur.com/1JqrLVc.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:03:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Correct!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:04:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vista was what eventually shipped but Winfs had been dropped by then.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:06:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Less than I used to. It was part of exercise for snow skiing. I still ski but I am not as hard core...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:08:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seriously Bing is the better product at this point. Try the challenge. I am biased but the work to make Bing better has been amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:09:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Robots, pervasive screens, speech interaction will all change the way we look at "computers". Once seeing, hearing, and reading (including handwriting) work very well you will interact in new ways..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:10:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>He and I respected each other. Our biggest joint project was the Mac where Microsoft had more people on the project than Apple did as we wrote a lot of applications. I saw Steve regularly over the years including spending an afternoon with him a few months before he tragically passed away...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:12:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Polio is the first thing to get done since we are close. Within 6 years we will have the last case. After that we will go after malaria and measles. Malaria kills over 500,000 kids every year mostly in Africa and did not get enough attention until the last decade. We also need vaccines to prevent HIV and TB which are making progress...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:14:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>It would be nice if all governments were as rational as the Nordic governments - reaching compromise and providing services broadly. The Economist had a nice special section on this last week. Africa governments have often been weak but you can't write a check to change that. Fortunately the average quality is going up. Mo Ibrahim tracks this in a great way. (http://www.moibrahimfoundation.org/IIAG/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:16:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>If the microprocessor had NOT come along I am not sure what I would have done. Maybe medicine or theoretical math but it is hard to say. Most giving is done by the middle class so it is the backbone of generosity particularly in the United States. A key thing is to support government aid which is only 1% of the budget but helps poor countries in incredible ways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:16:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am glad you kept it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:19:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Our goals are focused on helping the poorest (globally) and improving education (in the US). We spend half of our money on global health. One metric to look at is reducing the number of children (under 5) who die. My annual letter talks about the amazing progress that has been made on this. Amazingly as health improves families choose to have less kids so paradoxically population growth goes DOWN as you improve health helping with almost every issue - from stability to the environment.. The Rosling video I posted on Sunday talks about this: http://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/189bwr/most_people_still_think_of_the_world_as_being/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:20:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>So far our biggest impact has been getting vaccines for things like diarrhea and pneumonia out which has saved millions of lives. Polio will be a great achievement along with key partners when that gets done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:22:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Weezer.... Actually U2 is a favorite.. I keep waiting for Spinal Tap to go back on tour...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:24:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vaccines are very important in all countries. Some of the bad rumors have lead to kids dying of measles and pertussis. We have backed some information campaigns on the importance of vaccination even in the US. The Nordic countries do a good job on health like they do on many things...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:26:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>India is making progress but there is still a lot to do particularly up in the North. They still need to add some of the vaccines that poorer countries are already using and saving lots of lives. India did a great job on polio and is increasing the health budget. We work closely with the federal and state governments to help out...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:28:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love playing tennis. I am an avid bridge player (a card game if you have not heard of it - it was more popular in the past!). I like to tour interesting things with my kids like power plants, garbage dumps, the Large Hadron Collider, Antarctica, missile Silos (Arizona),... I read a lot and watch courses (online or the Learning Company)..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:30:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hopefully we won't have terrorists using nuclear weapons or biological weapons. We should make sure that stays hard. I am disappointed more isn't being done to reduce carbon emissions. Governments need to spend more on basic energy R amp;D to make sure we get cheap non-CO2 emitting sources as soon as possible. Overall I am pretty optimistic. Things are a lot better than they were 200 years ago..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:31:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>That portrayal was reasonably accurate....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:31:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is a huge advance for Windows which people will see even more as the great applications and hardware come out..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:32:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't die...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:32:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Microsoft does a lot of software for the Mac. I mostly use Windows machines but from time to time I have tried all of Apple products.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:33:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Higher is better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:34:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did a TED talk about the climate crisis. Over time we have to dramatically reduce CO2 emissions so using fossil fuels will require us to do carbon capture and sequestration. There has been far too little work on this. (http://www.thegatesnotes.com/Topics/Energy/Talking-About-Energy-Miracles-at-TED)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 20:36:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>The ability to test your knowledge and get refreshed on a topic you are making mistakes on will personalize a lot of the learning experience. People like Sal Khan are out in front figuring out how to do this well. My foundation has funded a lot of MOOCs focused on community college kids or kids who have to take remedial math. I am optimistic these will make a big difference.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL that humans and domesticated animals now outweigh all wild terrestrial vertebrates by an order of magnitude.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-29 21:07:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How much of the Earth are humans consuming? It's a huge question. My favorite author tried to answer it. (sorry for the repost)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-31 19:23:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-14 00:56:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>You raise good questions about meat consumption, but I see it slightly differently. Incomes will continue to rise over the coming years, especially in middle-income countries, which means that more people will be able to afford more meat. In fact global demand for meat is likely to double between 2000 and 2030. It #8217;s good news that people #8217;s incomes will go up. But producing meat takes a lot of land and water and also increases emissions of methane, a potent greenhouse gas. So we need more ways to satisfy the growing demand for meat without depleting our resources or worsening climate change. That #8217;s why I #8217;m interested in companies that are finding innovative ways to turn plants into foods that look and taste just like real meat and eggs. ICYMI, my review links to a neat feature about some of this work (http://www.thegatesnotes.com/features/future-of-food).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-14 01:02:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s great that you read Smil in school. I know it can be tough going but I really learn a lot from reading him. I wish more people knew about him... I agree that looking at big systems is crucial. If you want to understand something as complex as humans #8217; impact on the biosphere, you have to look at a huge range of factors. Smil does that better than just about anyone else. In Harvesting the Biosphere he has a bulleted list of recommendations that range from cutting food waste to promoting best practices in agriculture (optimal fertilization, crop rotation, etc.). But like most scientists he is more interested in understanding and explaining the facts than in making predictions or policy recommendations.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-14 01:11:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually Smil isn #8217;t a Malthusian and neither am I. Malthusians make the mistake of underestimating the impact that innovation will have in raising crop productivity and other improvements. One example that Smil cites: roughly 12 percent of the Earth #8217;s ice-free land is devoted to farmland, but the number would be close to 50 percent if it weren #8217;t for innovations in agriculture since 1900 #8230; Markets can drive a lot of these innovations, but they don #8217;t work well for the poorest, who can #8217;t afford to pay for the innovations. In those cases, philanthropy and rich country governments can step in to create incentives for private companies to work on those problems, whether it #8217;s developing new seeds or vaccines for diseases that disproportionately affect the poor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wars account for just 0.05% of the years of human life that are lost annually.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-18 20:14:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-04 01:01:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think everyone has their own reason for giving. For Melinda and me, it #8217;s pretty simple. We know we were very lucky to grow up where we did and when we did, and we want other people to have the same chance to make their most of their talents. I #8217;ll be curious to see what other Redditors have to say about why they give #8230;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-21 00:51:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi Rachel - I'm glad you enjoyed the travel book. There are some magical places in there. And thanks for recommending Heifer  #8211; it is a terrific organization to keep in mind during the season of giving. Merry Christmas!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hello Reddit  #8211; I #8217;m Bill Gates, co-chair of the Bill  amp; Melinda Gates Foundation and Microsoft founder. Ask me anything.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 18:10:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had a lot of fun doing last year #8217;s AMA and am excited to come back for another round of questions about everything from philanthropy to technology to how to lose a chess match in less than 90 seconds (http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=84NwnSltHFo). (Step 1: Play the world champion. There is no step 2.) I hope you #8217;ll read my annual letter (http://annualletter.gatesfoundation.org/). Melinda and I talk about three myths that block progress for the poor. I #8217;ll be answering your questions live from my office, starting at 10 a.m. Pacific time. Proof: http://i.imgur.com/iqvPs7N.jpg UPDATE: I #8217;ve responded to a few myths ahead of time, including one that involves me and a $100 bill. Take a look: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YZnmpDrjtDc UPDATE: This is great #8230; though I have to admit I #8217;m a bit surprised by the turnout. http://i.imgur.com/U5PNnZi.jpg UPDATE: Thanks for hanging out with me today, Reddit: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ynQ5ZhxYAss UPDATE: OK, final update. Thanks for all the great questions  #8211; this has been a lot of fun. I hope you #8217;ll read the Annual Letter, www.gatesletter.com, and check out my blog, www.thegatesnotes.com.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:06:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a complex issue. Privacy will be increasingly important as cameras and GPS sensors are gathering information to try and be helpful. We need to have trust in the way information is protected and gathered. There is a role for the government to try and stop crime and terrorism but it will have to be more open. I do think terrorism with biological or nuclear weapons is something we want to minimize the chance of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:07:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did answer unless the NSA deletes my answer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:09:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am excited about how the cloud and new devices can help us communicate and collaborate in new ways. The OS won't just be on one device and the information won't just be files - it will be your history including being able to review memories of things like kids growing up. I was thrilled Satya asked me to pitch in to make sure Microsoft is ambitious with its innovation. Even in Office there is a lot more than can be done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:11:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>The ultimate is computers that learn. So called deep learning which started at Microsoft and is now being used by many researchers looks like a real advance that may finally learn. It has already made a big difference in video and audio recognition - more progress in the last 3 years than ever before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:12:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes - the terms are a little confusing. Learning can mean a low level thing which all machine learning algorithms do or the high level idea of reading a book and understanding what it means.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:13:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I make sure we pick ambitious scenarios and that we have a strong architecture to deliver on them. I encourage good work (hopefully).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:13:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think this was supposed to be sarcastic...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:15:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just creating an innovative company is a huge contribution to the world. During my 20's and 30's that was all I focused on. Ideally people can start to mix in some philanthropy like Mark Zuckerberg has early in his career. I have enjoyed talking to some of the Valley entrepreneurs about this and I am impressed and how early they are thinking about giving back - much earlier than I did.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its called shorting a stock.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:17:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Owning a plane is a guilty pleasure. Warren Buffett called his the Indefensible. I do get to a lot of places for Foundation work I wouldn't be able to go to without it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a sensitive topic. The idea was that men don't like the current design so perhaps something they would be more open to would allow for less HIV transmission. We still haven't gotten the results. One grantee is using carbon nanotubes to reduce the thickness,</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:21:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>The foundation is involved in digital money but unlike Bitcoin it would not be anonymous digital money. In Kenya M-pesa is being used for almost half of all transactions. Digital money has low transaction costs which is great for the poor because they need to do financial transactions with small amounts of money. Over the next 5 years I think digital money will catch on in India and parts of Africa and help the poorest a lot. (http://www.impatientoptimists.org/posts/2011/01/mobile-phones-savings-a-powerful-pair)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:23:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Education would be the top issue since it is key to individual opportunity and to the country as a whole and we are not doing as well as other countries. After that I would say immigration since the injustice of the current system is incredible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:25:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>We need low cost energy that is totally reliable. Most renewables will require storage which is expensive to do this. Nuclear will make a contribution if we can make it safer, cheaper and deal with waste better. Terrapower has a design (on paper) that addresses all of these issues so now we are talking to countries about building it. It is a 4th generation reactor design that uses depleted uranium.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:25:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>20 years ago I would stay in the office for days at a time and not think twice about it - so I had energy and naivete on my side. Now hopefully I am a bit more mellow but with a little extra wisdom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:27:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Terrapower is like most fast reactors which use Sodium cooling. We tried to stick to proven approaches wherever we could. There have been about 10 Fast Reactors. By using this approach we have no fuel problems and very limited waste generation. Most important is the inherent safety - no human involvement for shut down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:28:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>My time will be about 2/3 Foundation and 1/3 Microsoft. I will focus on product work mostly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:31:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well Smil keeps writing great books like Made in the USA and Making the Modern World: Materials and Dematerialization. Paul Farmer has 3 books recently - to Repair the World is very accessible. In the Company of the Poor is a harder read but also good. www.gatesnotes.com tracks my reading closely. (http://www.thegatesnotes.com/books)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:35:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>The greatest tragedy is kids who die or never get enough food to develop physically or mentally to achieve their potential. We need vaccines and nutrition to solve this. We are making progress but not fast enough. Cynicism is the biggest barrier - www.gatesletter.com talks about this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:36:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>No I cannot. I can still jump but not over a full sized garbage can like I used to be able to. Be careful - it can hurt if you don't succeed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:37:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Melinda would probably watch that version.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:37:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. A small enough chair I can still jump over.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:38:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am using a Surface 2 PRO which works well for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:40:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Windows project which required a lot of patience was great. Office was also great. Together they defined the big success of the 1990s for Microsoft. Office connected to the cloud has a LOT of potential and we are off to a good start. Cloud Storage needs to be a lot richer though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:41:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>The boundaries between form factors is blurring but the range of screen sizes and different input techniques will still mean there are desktop devices and wall devices. However applications will be able to run across multiple devices including the whiteboard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:43:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>A lot of our failures have been backing science that didn't work out. One thing that is tough is when you think the government will take over something you start but they don't - we had that with a school lunch program. It might have been better if we hadn't done it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:44:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Invest in your education.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:44:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never went for a big salary but your basic point is correct.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:47:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think in the next 20-30 years we will be able to almost eliminate gross inequity like the fact a child in a poor country has 30x more chance of dying than a child in a middle income or rich country. Literacy, nutrition,... These are basic things that we can afford to give to every child. In the meantime the rich world needs to make sure we handle the environment and the diseases of the rich.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:49:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love college courses. I still watch a lot of them. I read a lot about people who had been successful. College was fun for me. So the part of the higher education system I got to experience was amazing - unfortunately most people don't get to go to Harvard or the equivalent. It is strange to call me a college drop out in all but the most literal sense. I went for 3 years and took enough courses to graduate. So I am kind of a failure as a drop out and I don't have a degree....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>No I don't. Other people think about that but I wouldn't want to extend my last few years unless that is happening for most people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:52:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are very close. India just went 3 years with no cases. Pakistan is our toughest location right now because some parts of the Taliban have not allowed vaccinators to come in and have even attacked vaccinators. We are hopeful this will get resolved since no one wants their kid to be paralyzed. I spend a lot of time making sure the polio campaign is doing the best it can. We have great computer models that help guide our activities.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:54:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow. That is a nice thing to ask. I wish the debate about education would focus on helping teachers improve and what we know about that. Right now it is caught up in state versus federal and testing versus no-testing. In general politics needs to focus on the problems rather than attacking the other side. Asian countries are helping their teachers improve and the impact is huge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:55:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am not a huge gamer. My son knows a LOT more than I do about what is cool on Xbox. I played Halo but the sports games that the whole family can use are the things I use the most. I threw the javelin very very far!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:58:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Satya is taking a fresh view of where Microsoft is - strengths and weaknesses. A new person gets to step back and change the focus in some ways. He is off to a great start. In terms of the Foundation we fund vaccines that save childrens lives. The majority of those are made in India. In fact ironically India makes a lot of vaccines that are used in other countries but not in India. The Foundation is not trying to help anyone make money - simply to reduce the number of children who die from things like diarrhea and pneumonia.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:59:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I considered law and math. My Dad was a lawyer. I think though I would have ended up in physics if I didn't end up in computer science.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 20:00:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kids getting hurt or sick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 20:02:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>People who devote their lives to working in poor countries are doing amazing work with very little visibility. I have gotten to meet some of them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 20:03:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>In all countries vaccine rumors seem to always get ahead of vaccine facts. This is unfortunate since it has meant measles and pertussis deaths in communities where enough kids don't get vaccinated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 20:04:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Playing Bridge is a pretty old fashioned thing in a way that I really like. I was watching my daughter ride horses this weekend and that is also a bit old fashioned but fun. I do the dishes every night - other people volunteer but I like the way I do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 20:05:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Burger King and McDonalds are fine but In-N-Out is a very good burger. Dicks and Burgermaster are the local special burgers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 20:08:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I favor improving the health of a country to enable them to be self-sufficient. I will be interested to see how cash transfer works out - in some cases like helping someone pay a school fee it could be catalytic. Our focus is health and agriculture which can transform a country. As long as kids don't have enough nutrition a country won't be able to support itself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 20:10:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love him but any similarity was not intentional. One of my favorite movies is Brainstorm - I highly recommend it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 20:21:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tried to answer as many questions as I could, but I #8217;ve got to go. I do have one question for you: How can we help more people understand that foreign aid isn #8217;t 25% or even 10% of the U.S. federal budget, but less than 1%?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>On my recent trip to Indonesia, I got to feed the world's deadliest animal. Here's a picture.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-30 13:11:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-30 19:23:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're right! I visited Gadjah Mada University in Yogyakarta where they're working on an amazing project to control the spread of dengue. I posted a bunch of photos and video on my blog: http://www.gatesnotes.com/Health/Why-I-Gave-Blood-to-Defeat-Dengue-Mosquito-Week.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-01 03:23:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t think we can get rid of all mosquitoes everywhere. But here #8217;s one example of some cool work being done by a researcher in Tanzania to kill the larvae of mosquitoes that transmit malaria: http://b-gat.es/1n0F0Xa</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-01 06:26:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d give my right arm to stop these diseases... If you #8217;re looking for a way to get involved #8212;that does not require getting bitten by mosquitoes #8212;I recommend checking out Malaria No More: http://b-gat.es/PSeOzi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Warren Buffett and I discuss our favorite business book of all time</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-15 13:33:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-15 13:34:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Warren lent me his copy of Business Adventures twenty years ago and I never gave it back. It went out of print in the  #8217;70s but I thought some of you might be interested in reading it. The author #8217;s family was kind enough to [give away a chapter for free](http://www.gatesnotes.com/Books/Business-Adventures-Free-Chapter-Download?WT.mc_id=07_15_2015_FreeChapter_rd amp;WT.tsrc=Reddit). I hope you enjoy it as much as I did.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I wanted to know what Neil deGrasse Tyson thought the world could accomplish in the next 15 years. Here's what he said.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-27 14:14:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hi Reddit, I #8217;m Bill Gates and I #8217;m back for my third AMA. Ask me anything.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:19:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m back for my third AMA. I #8217;m happy to talk about anything. Philanthropy, technology, what it #8217;s like to drink water made from human waste... (Short answer: Just like drinking any other kind of water, except that people get a little freaked out by the whole idea.)  #160; I hope you #8217;ll take a few minutes to look at the **annual** **letter** that Melinda and I just published ([gatesletter.com](http://gatesletter.com)). This year we make the case that in the next 15 years, life will improve faster for people in poor countries than it ever has before.  #160; **Proof:** http://i.imgur.com/lBMmhsA.gif  #160; https://twitter.com/BillGates/status/560503503274008576  #160; **UPDATE:** I have to go. But thanks for all the questions. This really is a fantastic community: Thanks! http://i.imgur.com/aHGlmuI.gifv  #160; I #8217;d like to sign off with one last plug for the Annual Letter, www.gatesletter.com, and my blog, www.thegatesnotes.com.  #160; **FINAL UPDATE:** Thanks for joining in, Reddit. I knew all that time I spent writing signs would pay off: http://youtu.be/9p4bm-RAlLA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:30:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bitcoin is an exciting new technology. For our Foundation work we are doing digital currency to help the poor get banking services. We don't use bitcoin specifically for two reasons. One is that the poor shouldn't have a currency whose value goes up and down a lot compared to their local currency. Second is that if a mistake is made in who you pay then you need to be able to reverse it so anonymity wouldn't work. Overall financial transactions will get cheaper using the work we do and Bitcoin related approaches. Making sure that it doesn't help terrorists is a challenge for all new technology.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:32:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel pretty stupid that I don't know any foreign languages. I took Latin and Greek in High School and got A's and I guess it helps my vocabulary but I wish I knew French or Arabic or Chinese. I keep hoping to get time to study one of these - probably French because it is the easiest. I did [Duolingo](https://www.duolingo.com/) for awhile but didn't keep it up. Mark Zuckerberg amazingly learned Mandarin and did a Q amp;A with Chinese students - incredible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:34:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Technology is not making people less intelligent. If you just look at the complexity people like in Entertainment you can see a big change over my lifetime. Technology is letting people get their questions answered better so they stay more curious. It makes it easier to know a lot of topics which turns out to be pretty important to contribute to solving complex problems.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:36:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Research is very underfunded compared to the ideal. Society captures so much benefit from innovation that inventors don't so there is not enough risk taking. Government (and Foundation) funding of research helps but it still should be more. The United States funds a lot more than any other country even relative to its success. It should do more medical and energy and educational and other research. Politicians often think short term unless the voters tell them to avoid that. Perhaps the most outrageous thing is we have not raised Energy research funding to help solve climate change!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:39:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Government aid funding from rich countries to develop new seeds and help the countries educate their farmers and provide credit to them can make a huge difference. Canada does some of this like the United States. We need to raise African productivity by 1.5 to 2x in order for them to avoid malnutrition and be able to lift themselves out of poverty. It is strange a continent with 70% adults as farmers imports food from countries like the US with 2% farmers. Africa spends $50B net buying food today. With productivity improvement they can offset the weather getting worse and feed their children enough to thrive.  #160; **EDIT**: You can read our letter here: www.gatesletter.com</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:40:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vaccines make the top of the list. Being able to grow up healthy is the most basic thing. So many kids get infectious diseases and don't develop mentally and physically. I was in Berlin yesterday helping raise $7.5B for vaccines for kids in poor countries. We barely made it but we did which is so exciting to me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:41:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have two dogs. One is Oreo and the other is Nilla. I will say I spend less time with the dogs than the kids do but I really like them (when they are not barking at night and not eating things they are not supposed to and when they are well house trained). I have resisted getting a third dog.  #160; **EDIT:** Here's a photo: http://i.imgur.com/oKUbosZ.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>There will be more progress in the next 30 years than ever. Even in the next 10 problems like vision and speech understanding and translation will be very good. Mechanical robot tasks like picking fruit or moving a hospital patient will be solved. Once computers/robots get to a level of capability where seeing and moving is easy for them then they will be used very extensively. One project I am working on with Microsoft is the Personal Agent which will remember everything and help you go back and find things and help you pick what things to pay attention to. The idea that you have to find applications and pick them and they each are trying to tell you what is new is just not the efficient model - the agent will help solve this. It will work across all your devices.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:45:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sauce. Lots of sauce. I always spill a bit so I avoid BBQ before TV appearances.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:46:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nathan Myhrvold has some amazing modern cuisine stuff that is super tasty. I am not a foodie but his new concoctions are amazing. I also like Thai and Indian food but it doesn't have to be expensive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:47:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>So far we have not being able to use technology to connect people to the needs of the poorest in countries that are far away to tap into their empathy. I think this can be done but it needs some missing creativity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:48:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am in the camp that is concerned about super intelligence. First the machines will do a lot of jobs for us and not be super intelligent. That should be positive if we manage it well. A few decades after that though the intelligence is strong enough to be a concern. I agree with Elon Musk and some others on this and don't understand why some people are not concerned.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:51:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are a lot of great causes. It is important not to be frozen trying to pick since it is important to specialize and really learn the area you are trying to help. We picked health inequity as our global thing and educational inequity as our national thing and most of our projects fit into these areas. Part of the beauty of philanthropy is the diversity of causes and approaches that get tried. It is far more risk oriented than government or private sector spending which makes it special when it is done right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:52:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is safe for now! It is also a lot of fun and helps shape your thinking on all issues to be more logical. There is a prospect for change in this area for the next generation but that is true for most fields and understanding how to program will always be useful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:54:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is quite a coincidence but my gift arrived this morning. I got three cool things - a great quilt that a group of people did with a Snoo on it. A great jug of maple syrup and the book The Promise of a Pencil. All very thoughtful. Last year I waited and nothing came. **EDIT:** More to come soon: http://i.imgur.com/pg8ZbLQ.jpg  #160; **EDIT 2:** Reddit just let me know that I did get a gift last year: a generous donation to [Heifer International](http://www.heifer.org/), a great non-profit that helps fight poverty and hunger around the world. So, thank you /u/SailorKingCobra, my Secret Santa! #160; **EDIT 3:** I #8217;m jumping back into the thread to thank /u/bfarnsey for the generous gifts. The quilt is amazing! /u/sillygirlsarah made it in just a week #8212;I don #8217;t know a ton about quilting, but I understand that #8217;s really fast. The Snoo on there is a very nice touch. To show my appreciation, the quilt is being featured as my cover photo on [Twitter](https://twitter.com/BillGates) and [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/BillGates). The Promise of a Pencil looks interesting. It touches on two key areas: improving education in the developing world and inspiring talented young people to get involved with global issues. Adam Braun #8217;s story is a good one and I #8217;m eager to learn more. Who doesn #8217;t love maple syrup? Especially from Vermont. A nice personal touch given that this is the kind /u/bfarnsey grew up with. Thanks again to a terrific Secret Santa.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:55:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>The currency work we are doing is attributed to a person like a credit card is unlike currency or bitcoin. This has some pluses and minuses but for the poor we think it is the right approach since they can reverse mistakes. Anonymity does allow bad guys to be less visible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:57:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are far closer to getting these [digital currencies](http://www.gatesnotes.com/2015-Annual-Letter?page=3 amp;lang=en) into the poor countries. It was a year of great progress. We are hoping to have India and Nigeria going in the next 2 years if things go well. Kenya and Tanzania and Bangladesh have grown a lot although those systems still need some improvements.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 19:59:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I won't have time for all of these. My book reports show up on www.gatesnotes.com The Hololens is pretty amazing. Microsoft has put a lot into the chips and the software. It is the start of virtual reality. Making the device so you don't get dizzy or nauseous is really hard - the speed of the alignment has to be super super fast. It will take a few years of software applications being built to realize the full promise of this. If you study programming and biology and see how the programming can help biology you will stay out on front!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 20:01:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Polio eradication is a big focus for me. Our last case in Africa was 6 months ago and we are hoping no more show up. It takes over a year to be sure. We still have cases in Afghanistan and Pakistan. Until we get rid of it there it can spread back to other countries. Pakistan is starting to take this seriously including the army and the government. They need to do the same things that were done in Nigeria. The Taliban makes it very difficult. They have killed women going to vaccinate kids many times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 20:03:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sewage is a problem. Since it costs money to process it just gets dumped in slums in poor countries. The system the rich world uses of pumping in clean water and pumping it to a processing plant is too expensive. I challenged engineers to create a processor of sewage where the costs could be covered by the energy and water (clean water) that it outputs. We have made progress on that. One team, Janicki, which was written up in Wired, is send a prototype machine to Senegal later this year. Getting rid of sewage helps a lot to reduce disease and improve living conditions.  #160; **EDIT:** Speaking of the OmniProcessor. You inspired me to post a photo over in /r/photoshopbattles. Have a look: http://www.reddit.com/r/photoshopbattles/comments/2tzqlh/psbattle_drinking_poop_water/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 20:05:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right now there isn't enough R amp;D going into safe and cheap nuclear energy. I am supporting Terrapower which has a 4th generation design that looks good. It doesn't use Thorium - it uses the 97% of Uranium that normally can't be used for a reactor by breeding and burning. This means fuel will always be cheap. There are a lot of innovations but the key one is that it is far far safer than anything today - not relying on human operators.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 20:06:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>The timeframe is longer than I would like. Probably 5 years before we have hundreds of them out in dozens of cities but we can scale up fast after that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 20:07:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fortunately as people get healthy they choose to have less kids. We have already had the maximum number of births - that number is starting to go down. We still need to help provide health and contraception in poor countries but all of the global population growth is coming from people living longer. Hans Rosling talks about this in the clearest way at http://vimeo.com/79878808</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 20:08:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is an easy question. I am good friends with Paul Allen who owns the Seahawks and I live in Seattle. The playoff game was amazing to watch. Go Seahawks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>PsBattle: Drinking Poop Water</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 20:09:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 20:09:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Butter? Peanut butter? Cheese spread? Any of these.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 20:11:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have some tough scientific challenges like an HIV cure. However the toughest thing is helping teachers learn from the best teachers. There are great teachers and the kids who get them are lucky. We should be able to spread those skills but the current system doesn't do it very well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 20:12:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't stay up too late even if the book is really exciting. You will regret it in the morning. I am still working on this problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 20:13:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>It seems pretty egocentric while we still have malaria and TB for rich people to fund things so they can live longer. It would be nice to live longer though I admit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 20:15:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am pretty basic when it comes to clothes and food. My big splurge is having a plane to fly around in. I play tennis so I invest in shoes and racquets to help but they don't make a big difference.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 20:15:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>A shorter chair every decade I am afraid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-28 20:16:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would probably be a researcher on AI. When I started Microsoft I was worried I would miss the chance to do basic work in that field.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-06 18:44:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>According to one test we just ran at the office, I #8217;m getting a download speed of 65.96 Mbps and uploading at 12.41 Mbps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-22 01:37:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>The list is a subset of things I have read over the past few months. I thought it might be good to focus this time on a few of the lighter books since most people don #8217;t want to carry around a 700-page economics text while on vacation. I discovered the XKCD book first and that is how I got to know about the comic. It is great that he is still doing the comic so hopefully there will be more books in the future. There is certainly plenty of material for Randall to draw from given his interests #8230;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>80% of deaths of children under age five are preventable.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-17 15:36:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-17 15:39:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>We #8217;ve seen an amazing drop in child mortality since 2000 #8212;most of them in that red box. [The Global Goals]( http://www.gatesnotes.com/Development/UNGA-2015-Setting-Global-Goals?WT.mc_id=09_17_2015_IHMEpost_BG-RE_ amp;WT.tsrc=BGRE) being adopted by the U.N. this month are aimed in part at shrinking it even more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 22:19:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, if you liked Randall #8217;s relativity piece, definitely check out Thing Explainer. [I loved it] (http://www.gatesnotes.com/Books/Thing-Explainer?WT.mc_id=11_19_2015_Thing-Explainer_BG-RE_ amp;WT.tsrc=BGRE).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Here are some questions I get asked a lot... I #8217;ll answer yours at 10AM PST.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 13:44:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;m Bill Gates, co-chair of the Bill  amp; Melinda Gates Foundation. Ask Me Anything.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 18:38:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m excited to be back for my fourth AMA.  #160; I already answered a few of the questions I get asked a lot: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GTXt0hq_yQU. But I #8217;m excited to hear what you #8217;re interested in.  #160; Melinda and I recently published our eighth Annual Letter. This year, we talk about the two superpowers we wish we had (spoiler alert: I picked more energy). Check it out here: http://www.gatesletter.com and let me know what you think.  #160; For my verification photo I recreated my high school yearbook photo: http://i.imgur.com/j9j4L7E.jpg  #160; **EDIT:** I #8217;ve got to sign off. Thanks for another great AMA: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZiFFOOcElLg  #160;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 18:44:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here #8217;s the link to my AMA. I #8217;m getting started shortly #8230; https://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/49jkhn/im_bill_gates_cochair_of_the_bill_melinda_gates/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:06:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think there needs to be a discussion about when the government should be able to gather information. What if we had never had wiretapping? Also the government needs to talk openly about safeguards. Right now a lot of people don't think the government has the right checks to make sure information is only used in criminal situations. So this case will be viewed as the start of a discussion. I think very few people take the extreme view that the government should be blind to financial and communication data but very few people think giving the government carte blanche without safeguards makes sense. A lot of countries like the UK and France are also going through this debate. For tech companies there needs to be some consistency including how governments work with each other. The sooner we modernize the laws the better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:09:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I recently saw a company working on "robotic" surgery where the ability to work at small scales was stunning. The idea that this will make surgeries higher quality, faster and less expensive is pretty exciting. It will probably take a decade before this gets mainstream - to date it has mostly been used for prostate surgery. In the Foundation work there are a lot of tools we are working on we don't have yet. For example an implant to protect a woman from getting HIV because it releases a protective drug.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:09:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since our Foundation can basically save a life for every $1,000 we spend I would pick it up since that would be enough to save 40 lives which is a big deal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:10:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not much. Jimmy Fallon had me dance in a video but the hard stuff was not done by me. When I am at weddings I get to dance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:12:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>The problem of how we prevent a small group of terrorists using nuclear or biological means to kill millions is something I worry about. If Government does their best work they have a good chance of detecting it and stopping it but I don't think it is getting enough attention and I know I can't solve it. I love both sushi and thai food. Since I like them better than my family does I have them for lunch a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:14:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Microsoft and others are working on quantum computing. It isn't clear when it will work or become mainstream. There is a chance that within 6-10 years that cloud computing will offer super-computation by using quantum. It could help use solve some very important science problems including materials and catalyst design.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:15:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Politics operates in 4 years cycles and climate change is a challenge that needs decades of work to reduce green house gas emission. I am disappointed that the US is where the debate has been the most difficult. November in Paris was a positive milestone with a commitment to reductions and a commitment to innovation by the [governments](http://mission-innovation.net/) and [private sector](http://www.breakthroughenergycoalition.com/en/index.html).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:17:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the value of getting a great education - that is going to college - is easy to underestimate. The most interesting jobs require a college education. The STEM related jobs are probably the most interesting although they are not for everyone. The value of staying curious - reading a lot and learning new things even after college is also underestimated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:21:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree that our schools have not improved as much as we want them to. There are a lot of great teachers but we don't do enough to figure out what they do so well and make sure others benefit from that. Most teachers get very little feedback about what they do well and what they need to improve including tools that let them see what the exemplars are doing. Technology is starting to improve education. Unfortunately so far it is mostly the motivated students who have benefited from it. I think we will get tools like personalized learning to all students in the next decade. A lot of the issue is helping kids stay engaged. If they don't feel the material is relevant or they don't have a sense of their own ability they can check out too easily. The technology has not done enough to help with this yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:23:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like my current job at the Foundation better than I would being President. Also I wouldn't be good at doing what you need to do to get elected. I thought Michael Bloomberg was thoughtful about why it didn't make sense for him to try and run even though he is a great executive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:23:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Warren also loves his current job too much to give it up!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:24:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think people's spending instincts are set when they are in high school. I don't like spending a lot of money on clothes or jewelry (for me - I do like to buy nice things for my wife).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:27:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it looks easier in retrospect than it did at the time. People thought we were a bit crazy - even leaders in the industry like Ken Olsen said they didn't need a computer at home. Being young allowed us to think about computers in a different way. Today the challenge is to make computers more intelligent. Software still doesn't understand what thing I should pay attention to next - in fact the proliferation of various tools like texting and email and notifications mean the user has a lot of complexity to deal with. Eventually the software will understand what you should pay attention to by knowing the context and learning about your preferences.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:28:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>VR is the extreme case of AR when nothing from the real world gets mixed in. It can be tricky if you are walking around that you might run into things. Mixed systems which seems like VR but when you might hit something it shows you that seem better than pure VR. So I don't think these two things will stay as separate as they are now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:29:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it shows Satya looking at how the market is changing and being willing to change how things have been done. His embrace of the cloud and mobile including doing software on other people's mobile platforms are also great examples of that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:30:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometimes you just get very lucky based on the configuration. I forget the exact time but I think I had a time below 10 when it was just right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:31:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't seen any concrete proposal on how you would do the regulation. I think it is worth discussing because I share the view of Musk and Hawking that when a few people control a platform with extreme intelligence it creates dangers in terms of power and eventually control.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:34:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I decided that I would be different and never attend any class I was signed up for but always attend a class I wasn't signed up for. This worked out in a funny way when the final exam for a Combinatorics class (which I signed up for) was given at the same table as my Brain studies class (which I attended and did not sign up for). My friends from Brain studies thought it was very strange that I sat on the wrong side of the table and took the Combinatorics exam even when I was the most vocal student in the Brain class.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:34:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>To read? To type? To think before speaking?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:36:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe they could propose an overall plan for striking the balance between government being able to know things in some cases and having safeguards to make sure those powers are confined to appropriate cases. There is no avoiding this debate and they could contribute to how the balance should be struck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:39:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will mention three things. First is an energy innovation to lower the cost and get rid of green house gases. This isn't guaranteed so we need a lot of public and private risk taking. **EDIT:** I talked about this recently in my annual letter: https://www.gatesnotes.com/2016-Annual-Letter Second is progress on disease particularly infectious disease. Polio, Malaria, HIV, TB, etc.. are all diseases we should be able to either eliminate of bring down close to zero. There is amazing science that makes us optimistic this will happen. Third are tools to help make education better - to help teachers learn how to teach better and to help students learn and understand why they should learn and reinforce their confidence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:41:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is worth learning how to read a bit faster. I am not sure what the best course for that is nowadays. I had a friend who took Evelyn Wood and told me what they said. I have a rule that I always finish a book once I start it. This might now work for everyone. I only read 2 books at a time - in fact usually just one unless one of them is so complex I need to mix things up. I read a lot at night and my biggest problem is that I stay up to late and regret it the next day when I haven't had as much sleep as I would like.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:43:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love my work. I love meeting the scientists and field workers. I have the flexibility to work less if I wanted to and I do take vacations now. When I was in my 20's I didn't believe in vacation so I have mellowed. I feel super lucky that I can be involved in the Foundation work with Melinda for another 30 years assuming my health holds up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:44:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think robots that have vision and manipulation as good as humans is a huge milestone that will happen in the next decade and is being underestimated. I think medical advances will also be amazing and unbelievable. Like the robots some of the capabilities like gene editing will bring challenges with them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:45:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are correct! I would put it at the top. Deciding to work on software was a good decision but that just crept up on me rather than being some choice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:46:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will look into this. How many empires do you need?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:47:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you did - sorry I can't deliver an Empire (or an Age) easily.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:49:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am concerned about biological tools that could be used by a bioterrorist. However the same tools can be used for good things as well. Some people think Hoverboards were bad because they caught on fire. I never got to try one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:54:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I studied super hard during reading period and almost always got A's. The big exception was organic chemistry where the promised video tapes of the lectures sometimes had no sound or no video - that spooked me and I ended up getting a C+ in the course!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:55:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just recently switched to the Surface Book. I only detach the screen a few times a week and I like the keyboard better than my previous Surface.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:56:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Programming does help you think logically. I was obsessed with programming from age 14 to 19 and that is a good time to keep trying to improve.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 19:58:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pirates of Silicon Valley was a reasonable recapitulation of the early days of the PC industry. I don't jump chairs at all now. Maybe I should since when I go snow skiing with my kids I need more exercise so I don't get tired by the end of the day. I use the latest version of Windows - always updated Windows 10.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 20:00:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope some people your age take on the need to innovate in energy. Most breakthrough things are done by young people and we need to surprise people with new ideas. The value of cheaper energy is hard to overstate. I also hope your generation focuses on helping poor countries solve their health and education problems. The more people see themselves as global citizens rather than only being focused on one country the better. **EDIT** Melinda and I wrote our annual letter this year to teenagers because you #8217;re the ones who will ultimately be solving these problems: https://www.gatesnotes.com/2016-Annual-Letter</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 20:01:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't study philosophy a lot. Adam Smith wrote a book about Human Sentiments before he wrote the book on capitalism which I like. Some philosophers like Sartre seem a bit depressed to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-16 19:14:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>You and I have talked a lot about what the world needs to do to prepare for the next epidemic. What #8217;s your take on the progress so far? What #8217;s gone well and what do we still need to do?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-03 18:55:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would watch this movie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My parents celebrating July 4 in style (1960s)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-04 06:12:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Washington state's Teacher of the Year showed me why he uses Star Wars in his classroom #8230;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-26 16:25:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>World's Deadliest Animal (with updated data)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-10 20:54:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-13 17:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>In normal reproduction, a mosquito carrying an altered gene passes it on to 50 percent of its offspring. Last year researchers showed that you can pass the gene for females to produce mostly sterile males down to 99 percent of the offspring of Anopheles gambiae mosquitoes. But this research is still at a very early stage. Nothing is ready to be deployed yet. More work needs to be done to figure out whether mosquitoes will develop resistance to the gene and we need to ensure that any gene-edited mosquito is ultimately safe to release. You #8217;re right that many species of mosquito are capable of transmitting malaria. But if we focus on a few species responsible for most of the infections, we have a good chance of knocking down transmission rates to the point where we could wipe out the remaining malaria parasites with a combination of insecticides, surveillance, and treatment. We #8217;re investing in a lot of different approaches #8212;including a next-generation malaria vaccine #8212;because experience has shown the best way to fight malaria is with a combination of tools. In regard to the overall challenge of mosquito-borne disease, I think that outbreaks of Zika and other viruses are a powerful reminder that mosquitoes don #8217;t recognize borders. That #8217;s why the National Institutes of Health and other government agencies are investing in mosquito control efforts for both Aedes aegypti (the mosquito primarily responsible for Zika, dengue, and Chikungunya) and malaria. They #8217;re tremendous partners in these efforts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why I traveled to Switzerland to take a giant whiff of pit latrine odor</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 16:22:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 18:46:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you /u/-PhotogHelp-. This is a really thoughtful gift and I #8217;m glad to hear it #8217;s inspired you to continue to give back. Don #8217;t worry about it being late #8230;I #8217;d say it arrived right on time. Glad you found a great cause to support. Merry Christmas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any Questions? Ask Bill Gates Anything</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 14:06:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;m Bill Gates, co-chair of the Bill  amp; Melinda Gates Foundation. Ask Me Anything.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 17:36:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m excited to be back for my fifth AMA. Melinda and I recently published our latest Annual Letter: http://www.gatesletter.com. This year it #8217;s addressed to our dear friend Warren Buffett, who donated the bulk of his fortune to our foundation in 2006. In the letter we tell Warren about the impact his amazing gift has had on the world. My idea for a David Pumpkins sequel at Saturday Night Live didn't make the cut last Christmas, but I thought it deserved a second chance: https://youtu.be/56dRczBgMiA. **Proof:** https://twitter.com/BillGates/status/836260338366459904 **Edit:** Great questions so far. Keep them coming: http://imgur.com/ECr4qNv **Edit:** I #8217;ve got to sign off. Thank you Reddit for another great AMA. And thanks especially to: https://youtu.be/3ogdsXEuATs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:04:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>A contribution to Rotary to help end polio is a gift I would appreciate. Also any great book you have read and found interesting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:06:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good question. I think having parents and teachers reinforce your curiosity and explain what they are fascinated with makes a big difference. A lot of people lose their curiosity as they get older which is a shame. One thing that helps nowadays is that if you get confused about something it is easier than ever to find an article or video to make things clear.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:07:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>The big milestone is when computers can read and understand information like humans do. There is a lot of work going on in this field - Google, Microsoft, Facebook, academia,... Right now computers don't know how to represent knowledge so they can't read a text book and pass a test. Another whole area is vaccines. We need a vaccine for HIV, Malaria and TB and I hope we have them in the next 10-15 years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:09:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Overall like Warren Buffett I am optimistic about the long run. I am concerned in the short run that the huge benefits of how the US works with other countries may get lost. This includes the aid we give to Africa to help countries there get out of the poverty trap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:10:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am not sure if Steam here means the gaming platform or adding Arts to Science, Technology, Engineering and Math. I have always been a big STEM fan but I have nothing against either STEAM.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:14:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are so many ways to get involved - schools have mentorship and volunteering opportunities. Small gifts to things like Donors Choose have a big impact. I think most people start getting involved in local social service organizations. If you can travel to developing countries and see the needs there that is also great. It is great to start philanthropy when you are young. In the long run the way to avoid refugee problems is to help countries develop by having good health, education and governance - fortunately the overall trend is good despite huge setbacks like Syria, South Sudan and Somalia. Unicef has a lot of good information about how to help with the current refugee challenges: http://uni.cf/2ltdjfr</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:15:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Australia is particularly nice. It is summer there when it is winter here so going there in December and January is especially nice. I spent Thanksgiving there last year. I have gotten to travel to a lot of great places like the Amazon in Brazil which I recommend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:18:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>A lot of people feel a sense of isolation. I still wonder if digital tools can help people find opportunities to get together with others - not Tinder but more like adults who want to mentor kids or hang out with each other. It is great that kids go off and pursue opportunities but when you get communities where the economy is weak and a lot of young people have left then something should be done to help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:20:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just went on a trip with my 17 year old son to see 6 colleges. He is a junior in High School and trying to figure out where he should go. Trips like that have been a great way to spend time together. He reads even more about politics than I do so I let him pick books for me to read. Melinda is very creative about helping me find chances to spend time with the kids. Even just driving them to school is a great time to talk to them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:23:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is super important to improve our healthcare system - both to reduce chronic disease but if we don't do better health costs will squeeze out spending on all other government functions. I agree it is surprising how tough it has been to get digital medical records right and to learn from looking at those records. Still there are some very promising things going on. For example the idea of looking at a blood sample to find cancer very early so it can be treated. We will be able to use genomic data to tune treatments. There are a few big problems like diabetes, obesity and neurological conditions including Alzheimer's that we really need to solve.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:25:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sometimes wear a hat. For example when I did college tours with my son I wanted the focus to be totally on him. A lot less people recognize me when I have a hat on or else they realize I am trying to be incognito. Mostly when people do recognize me they are super nice so I don't feel it is a burden to be noticed most of the time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:28:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Although the Foundation work is super promising and will be the biggest thing over the decades ahead I still think the chance to be part of the software revolution empowering people was the biggest thing I have gotten to do. Right now I am very focused on making sure we successfully [eradicate polio](https://www.gatesnotes.com/2017-Annual-Letter#ALChapter8) - that will be amazing if we do it - as good as shipping even the best software product.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:30:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will be 76 at that time. Hopefully a grandfather. The Foundation with its partners will have eradicated a number of diseases and health in poor countries will be a lot better - specifically instead of 5% of children under 5 dying it should be at 2.5% which is still a lot. I hope I can still type fast enough to do Reddit sessions without someone transcribing for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:33:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a great question. I felt sure that allowing anyone to publish information and making it easy to find would enhance democracy and the overall quality of political debate. However the partitioning you talk about which started on cable TV and might be even stronger in the digital world is a concern. We all need to think about how to avoid this problem. It would seem strange to have to force people to look at ideas they disagree with so that probably isn't the solution. We don't want to get to where American politics partitions people into isolated groups. I am interested in anyones suggestion on how we avoid this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:35:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>One thing to make sure the people who create the first strong AI have the right values and ideally that it isn't just one group way out in front of others. I am glad to see this question being discussed. Google and others are taking it seriously.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:37:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>The main "copying" that went on relative to Steve and me is that we both benefited from the work that Xerox Parc did in creating graphical interface - it wasn't just them but they did the best work. Steve hired Bob Belville, I hired Charles Simonyi. We didn't violate any IP rights Xerox had but their work showed the way that led to the Mac and Windows.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:39:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>We need clean, reliable cheap energy - which we don't have. It is too bad the sun doesn't shine all the time and the wind doesn't blow all the time. The Economist had a good piece on this this week. So we need some invention - perhaps miracle batteries or super safe nuclear or making sun into gasoline directly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:40:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. Perhaps a small chair - a stool. I do exercise and ski but my main sport is tennis which doesn't involve jumping. Some people jump over the net but that isn't part of the sport.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:41:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would say education is the key problem. If you can solve that then it helps with a lot of things. Maybe I didn't understand the question - maybe it supposed to be some idiosyncratic thing that bothers me....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:42:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good question. If you don't have a bun then it absolutely is not. If you slice the hot dog and put it on a normal piece of bread (like [Burgermaster](https://www.tripadvisor.com/LocationPhotoDirectLink-g58622-d9562403-i194997607-Burger_Master-Mount_Vernon_Washington.html)) then it is. When you use a hot dog bun then it is ambiguous.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:45:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would explain that smartness is not single dimensional and not quite as important as I thought it was back then. I would say you might explore the developing world before you get into your forties. I wasn't very good socially back then but I am not sure there is advice that would fix that - maybe I had to be awkward and just grow up....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:46:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Warren Buffett has always said the measure is whether the people close to you are happy and love you. It is also nice to feel like you made a difference - inventing something or raising kids or helping people in need.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:49:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope his administration will decide that funding R amp;D to invent the next generation of energy (clean, cheap, reliable) is a good deal for the US and for the world. Climate change requires cooperation between countries over a period of decades but we don't have much time to waste.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:51:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Over time countries will be rich enough to do this. However we still have a lot of work that should be done - helping older people, helping kids with special needs, having more adults helping in education. Even the US isn't rich enough to allow people not to work. Some day we will be but until then things like the Earned Income Tax Credit will help increase the demand for labor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:54:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Philanthropy is small as a part of the overall economy so it can't do things like fund health care or education for everyone. Government and the private sector are the big players so philanthropy has to be more innovative and fund pilot programs to help the other sectors. A good example is funding new medicines or charter schools where non-obvious approaches might provide the best solution. One thing that is a challenge for our Foundation is that poor countries often have weak governance - small budgets, and the people in the ministries don't have much training. This makes it harder to get things done. If we had more money we could do more good things - even though we are the biggest foundation we are still resource limited. **Edit:** We discuss this in our annual letter this year: www.gatesletter.com</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:55:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:56:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I still find the creation of life and the way the brain works the most fascinating areas. [Nick Lane](https://www.gatesnotes.com/Books/The-Vital-Question) has some great books exploring what we know about how life started. It is amazing how little we know about the brain still but I expect we will know a lot more in 10 years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:57:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheeseburger, Cheeseburger, Cheeseburger.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 19:01:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are so many great TV shows now I can't keep up. I thought someone might ask specifically about Silicon Valley which I love. I can relate to Richard. Silicon Valley captures a lot of how crazy it is to start a new company and the dynamics of success. All the employees of Pied Piper remind me of people I have known. I love This is Us, The Crown, The Knick, Homeland, Downton Abbey, ...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 19:01:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have recommended a book called [Business Adventures](https://www.gatesnotes.com/Books/Business-Adventures) that chronicles some big successes and failures - I learned a lot from that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-13 23:53:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know it #8217;s been ages since /u/le-click began this campaign, but I finally have an answer for you. Hopefully it will be worth the wait: https://www.ageofempires.com/news/announcing-age-empires-definitive-edition/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>U.S. Malaria Donations Saved Almost 2 Million African Children</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 19:33:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I recently found myself in the wilds of the Outback #8212;here #8217;s what I learned.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 17:54:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Every tennis fan should see  #8220;Battle of the Sexes #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 16:31:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 16:31:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m a big tennis fan so when I heard about  #8220;Battle of the Sexes, #8221; I couldn #8217;t wait to see it. The movie was so good, I asked my friend Elisabeth Shue (who plays Bobby Riggs #8217; wife Priscilla) to recreate this famous photo with me last month at the US Open.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 16:50:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>You always do such a good job visualizing the progress we #8217;ve made in a time when headlines lead many people to believe things are getting worse. If you could only use one chart to convince someone that the world is getting better, what would you choose?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 15:53:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, what a clear representation of the toll Alzheimer #8217;s takes on the brain. Thank you for sharing. I #8217;m so sorry you and your family are going through this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just finished reading  #8220;Enlightenment Now. #8221; It #8217;s my new favorite book of all time. Here #8217;s my review (and a free chapter).</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 19:34:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Things I won #8217;t be doing today #8230;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 16:35:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 17:32:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Join me at [r/iAMA](https://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/80ow6w/im_bill_gates_cochair_of_the_bill_melinda_gates/) at 11 o'clock.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;m Bill Gates, co-chair of the Bill  amp; Melinda Gates Foundation. Ask Me Anything.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 19:42:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m excited to be back for my sixth AMA. Here #8217;s a couple of the [things I won #8217;t be doing today](http://www.reddit.com/user/subject1617/comments/80nbcf/things_i_wont_be_doing_today/) so I can answer your questions instead. Melinda and I just published our 10th Annual Letter. We marked the occasion by answering 10 of the hardest questions people ask us. Check it out here: http://www.gatesletter.com. **Proof:** https://twitter.com/BillGates/status/968561524280197120 **Edit:** You #8217;ve all asked me a lot of tough questions. Now it #8217;s my turn to ask you a question: https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/80phz7/with_all_of_the_negative_headlines_dominating_the/ **Edit:** I #8217;ve got to sign-off. Thank you, Reddit, for another great AMA: https://www.reddit.com/user/subject1617/comments/80pkop/thanks_for_a_great_ama_reddit/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:05:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I won't be running for President because I am super committed to the work Melinda and I are doing at the Foundation and outside the Foundation. I agree it is important to have a President who thinks long term about the US role in the world and the research to solve disease burdens and costs and to tackle climate change and improve education. I do think people are expecting too much from Government. Yes Government can do better but local groups can do a lot that government can't - helping out in schools, reaching out to people in poverty. This is also true internationally. I would like to see this civil society sector step up a lot more. Some issues like abortion or even immigration we may never get a consensus on but there are things like better health and better education that we can achieve.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:07:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>The main feature of crypto currencies is their anonymity. I don't think this is a good thing. The Governments ability to find money laundering and tax evasion and terrorist funding is a good thing. Right now crypto currencies are used for buying fentanyl and other drugs so it is a rare technology that has caused deaths in a fairly direct way. I think the speculative wave around ICOs and crypto currencies is super risky for those who go long.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:08:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would be glad to pass along your thoughts on this to the right person at Microsoft - they care a lot about getting accessibility right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:10:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The most amazing thing will be when computers can read and understand the text like humans do. Today computers can do simple things like search for specific words but concepts like vacation or career or family are not "understood". Microsoft and others are working on this to create a helpful assistant. It has always been kind of a holy grail of software particularly now that vision and speech are largely solved. Another frontier is robotics where the human ability to move and manipulate is amazing and experts disagree on whether it will take just a decade or a lot longer (Brooks) to achieve the equivalent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:12:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am not a big beer drinker. When I end up at something like a baseball game I drink light beer to get with the vibe of all the other beer drinkers. Sorry to disappoint real beer drinkers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:15:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are many domains to be successful in. I was a success in getting good grades and test scores in high school. I was a success at writing good code by my early 20s. The dream of the PC being an enabling tool came true by the 1990s. Now I am working on being a good father and the ambitious goals of the Foundation including getting rid of polio and malaria. I think it is always good to have goals where your success is in doubt and I have that in many areas including the work I do on climate change.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:16:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>My solo binge has been season 3 of Narcos. With Melinda it has been season 2 of this is us. With my son it is The Americans. There is so much good stuff to watch now that people tell me great things that I never get around to like Game of Thrones. Partly I leave a lot of time to read so my video allocation is less than most people and partly I watch lectures.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:18:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Allocating time is always tough. Tennis is a big hobby for me and I try and play twice a week (a bit more in the summer). I always try and read a few books every month and a bunch on vacation. Melinda and I look over our schedules a lot to make sure we are balancing things well. I travel about 1/3 of the time for the Foundation which I enjoy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:19:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>GMO foods are perfectly healthy and the technique has the possibility to reduce starvation and malnutrition when it is reviewed in the right way. I don't stay away from non-GMO foods but it is disappointing that people view it as better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:20:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Melinda and Warren are my two favorites followed by Bono. Most celebrities I don't know very well. I do get to meet a lot of political leaders and Nelson Mandela was the most impressive ever. Jimmy Carter is also amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:21:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes - anonymous cash is used for these kinds of things but you have to be physically present to transfer it which makes things like kidnapping payments more difficult.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:23:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that health care costs, education and poverty/mobility deserve a lot more thinking and innovation than they get today. The benefit of getting these things right would be amazing. With all the talk about inequity it is interesting that we still work on vertical areas like health, education, housing, food, etc.. as separate things rather than having a full view of the challenges someone faces.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:25:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the private market rewards innovation in this space quite well. I think electric cars and autonomous vehicles will be great things. The Foundation is experimenting with drone delivery of medical supplies with a grantee in Rwanda and Tanzania. I am not sure the hyperloop concept makes sense - making it safe is hard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:26:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I benefited from having a great education - public schools through 6th grade and then a great private School (Lakeside). So there is a good chance I would never have gotten turned on to software and math the way I did and therefore not as successful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:28:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Malaria is a super important area for the Foundation. The number of deaths has been cut in half using bed nets and spraying and new drugs. For the future we need new tools since resistance is developing to all the current tools. We don't have a vaccine that protects for long enough to help out yet but we are investing heavily in one. We do a lot of modelling to understand which tools would help the most. One that would be new is called gene drive which would reduce mosquito populations for a number of years to make it easier to clear the malaria from all of the humans - this will be ready for field testing in a few years</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:29:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do make myself tomato soup sometimes. It is kind of a comforting food and reminds me of doing the same when I was growing up. I don't make sandwiches much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:31:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I first saw a computer when I was 13 and it fascinated me then. I spent a lot of time figuring out what programming was - first Basic and then machine language. By the time I was 16 I got a job programming at TRW which helped me learn even more (skipping part of my senior year). So I was lucky to have something I loved to do and which became more important in the years ahead. I have had self-doubts about all of my skills but programming is one I have always had a lot of confidence in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:33:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are two amazing books. One is Enlightenment Now by Pinker and another is Factfulness by Rosling. They are both very readable and explain that the world is getting better. **Edit:** I recently wrote about Enlightenment Now on my blog: https://www.gatesnotes.com/Books/Enlightenment-Now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:35:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I spent a month learning the math behind Quantum computing with help from the Microsoft team and a lot of online course material. I wanted to understand how Quantum computers could factor numbers so much faster than normal computers. It is amazing how the matrix math with complex numbers works - nature is doing arbitrary computation but it is tricky to access. These are early days but yes Microsoft is making large investments in quantum - particularly in handling the error problems that most approaches have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:37:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>There have been a lot of failed Alzheimer's drug trials. The good news is that the new tools we have are helping us understand the disease far better - for example the role of the glial cells. I am optimistic that in the next 20 years we will have drugs to help if we stay focused on it including pooling data and helping start ups get funded. I am involved in a number of these areas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:39:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Automation has been driving productivity ever since the industrial revolution including things like tractors and garment making. With software this will continue to accelerate so we need to think about how we educate people for the new jobs that will emerge. Overall automation is a great thing - eventually we won't have to work as much but we are still at least a generation away from a big change there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:41:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is this question so popular? Hello to all the Gills out there. You probably run into someone with the same name less than I do. I don't think my name has affected me much. My formal name is William.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:41:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Capitol Steps albums do this trick of switching first letters and it is very cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:45:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Each corporation has to look at what capabilities it has and how it can use those to help people in need whether it is research or tiered pricing or having employees volunteer. When I was in Scotland I met with people at an NHS hospital there who had paired with a hospital in Zambia and it was amazing how much they helped save lives by visiting and supporting their colleagues. I think creative things like this where individuals get involved can make a big difference both locally and internationally.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:47:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>There was a certain urgency to everything we were doing to stay ahead that meant the speed of activity was very high. I miss this a bit. I had to take Think Weeks twice a year just to step back and see what the longer term trends were. Now I work on things like malaria where I wish there was more competition to solve the problems and things moved faster.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:48:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>My wife Melinda is working with a lot of people on this. Engineering work involves working with people a lot and it is great we are trying to get more women involved. Some professions like medicine have changed to have more women but the hard sciences and computer engineering have been harder to change. There are groups like [Girls Who Code](https://girlswhocode.com/) or [Code.org](https://code.org/) or Anita Borg institute that work in these areas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:51:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is some cool work going on to make meat without using animals which will be far more efficient. The Foundation is funding research on improving photosynthetic efficiency and the potential there is huge. If we can get African productivity up then we will be able to feed the world but we need to innovate to help them have much better seeds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:52:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>President Carter showed us how to work in Africa and how to partner with groups like WHO through his work at the Carter Center on a number of diseases. I have had a chance to talk with him at length to get his advice. He is great at giving credit to partners to help them stay engaged in the work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I code I use tabs because you want the columns to line up. For some word documents I use tabs. You want things to adjust when you go back and edit them and tabs help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>With all of the negative headlines dominating the news these days, it can be difficult to spot signs of progress. What makes you optimistic about the future?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:53:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:54:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes - essentially most resources don't get "destroyed". The elements that were here to begin with are still here. Of course it takes energy to recycle things but I am optimistic we will figure out how to avoid destroying the planet. The number of babies born has already peaked which will help limit the maximum population size.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:54:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>No.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:55:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't snack much. I avoid having candy bars and nuts around since I would grab almonds (salty) or M amp;Ms if they were just sitting there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:57:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the Foundation reducing childhood death and malnutrition and ending polio would be the biggest 3 things. For innovation it would be an energy breakthrough and improving the way we educate kids. For my family it is making sure the kids are ready to go to college and have a great experience there. That is more than 3 and I didn't mention my tennis goals yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:58:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Politicians have been nice about the Foundation work. Many have done great work to make sure aid levels stay strong including in Europe and the US. I wish some of them had more time to dig into the specifics. Sometimes Melinda and I travel with politicians to go see the work in Africa.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:59:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the safety net and equal opportunity need to keep improving. 100 years ago there was basically no safety net at all and it is getting stronger. I am surprised more countries don't have Estate taxes since they redistribute wealth and avoid dynasties. Our economic system has created the wealth that we can now do a better job sharing in an equitable way so our system has done amazing things during the last 200 years despite its flaws.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 21:01:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. It is hard to say when but this is a certainty. Fortunately we got through that one reasonably well. Warren has talked about this and he understands this area far better than I do. Despite this prediction of bumps ahead I am quite optimistic about how innovation and capitalism will improve the situation for humans everywhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thanks for a great AMA, Reddit.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 21:03:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Precision maps (like this one from Senegal) reveal significant health and nutrition gaps within African countries [GIF] [1080 x 1080].</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 18:12:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 18:13:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cutting-edge mapping efforts (produced by the University of Washington #8217;s Institute for Health Metrics and Evaluation) have helped us understand the burden of health and education disparities. These maps will enable us to reach the people who need help the most: https://www.nature.com/articles/nature25760</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 18:38:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>This makes me optimistic, too. Given the intermittency of solar and wind energy, storage is critical to make them a truly viable part of the electricity grid. That #8217;s why I #8217;m excited about (and investing in) breakthroughs in storage, which would help make today #8217;s renewable technology more practical and affordable: http://www.b-t.energy/ventures/areas-of-focus/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 18:39:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m glad that you found this list. If I could use only one number that proves how life is getting better, it would be the first one  #8211; 122 million. I wish more people knew about this mind-blowing success. Thanks for sharing it here!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 18:39:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s great to hear that you are so passionate about the intersection of health and technology. To me, the ability of science to prevent and cure disease is magical. Last year I saw some amazing work at the CDC using virtual reality to help develop a universal flu vaccine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A fascinating framework for thinking about the world</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 16:31:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 16:38:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I recently read Hans Rosling #8217;s new book  #8220;Factfulness. #8221; In it, he rejects the idea of dividing the world into  #8220;rich countries #8221; and  #8220;poor countries. #8221; The framework he suggests we use instead was a breakthrough to me  #8211; and I #8217;m going to try to use this model moving forward: https://www.gatesnotes.com/Books/Factfulness</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Forget Shark Week. This animal kills more people in a day than sharks do in a century.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 16:02:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 16:03:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jaws is nothing compared with [the flying terror that is a mosquito](https://www.gatesnotes.com/Health/Mosquito-Week-2018?WT.mc_id=04_24_2018_06_MosquitoWeek2018_BG-RE_ amp;WT.tsrc=BGRE).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 20:29:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you #8217;re looking for practical advice for how to overcome this innate bias, I highly recommend reading  #8220;[Factfulness](https://www.gatesnotes.com/Books/Factfulness?WT.mc_id=04_24_2018_11_MosquitoWeek2018_BG-RE_ amp;WT.tsrc=BGRE). #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 20:29:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I couldn #8217;t agree more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 20:31:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s great to hear that you are thinking about becoming a doctor. Here are [four good disease books](https://www.gatesnotes.com/Health/4-Good-Disease-Books?WT.mc_id=04_24_2018_12_MosquitoWeek2018_BG-RE_ amp;WT.tsrc=BGRE) you might like.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Puppies and books. What #8217;s not to love?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 18:41:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bright ideas needed</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 13:44:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 13:48:09</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;[Factfulness](https://www.gatesnotes.com/Books/Factfulness?WT.mc_id=05_24_2018_4_Factfulness_BG-RE_ amp;WT.tsrc=BGRE) #8221; is a worldview that will help you see the world more clearly. My late friend Hans Rosling described it as  #8220;the stress-reducing habit of carrying only the opinions for which you have strong supporting facts. #8221; What are your best ideas for encouraging factfulness in the world?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Which book do you think every new college grad should read?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 18:32:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yesterday I asked Redditors which book they think every new college grad should read</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 17:01:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 17:02:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for all of the great suggestions. If I had to choose just one book, I would recommend  #8220;Factfulness #8221; by Hans Rosling. Although I think everyone should read it, it #8217;s especially relevant for new college grads. Graduates from U.S. schools can actually [download a free copy of  #8220;Factfulness, #8221;]( https://www.gatesnotes.com/About-Bill-Gates/My-gift-to-college-graduates?WT.mc_id=06_05_2018_08_FactfulnessGift_BG-RE_ amp;WT.tsrc=BGRE) and everyone can [download a free excerpt from my favorite chapter](https://www.gatesnotes.com/Books/Factfulness?WT.mc_id=06_05_2018_08_FactfulnessGift_BG-RE_ amp;WT.tsrc=BGRE).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Global child mortality: it is hard to overestimate both the immensity of the tragedy, and the progress the world has made</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 19:24:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 19:27:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>/u/max_ourworldindata created one of my favorite data visualizations, which charts the decline of child mortality across the world. He is also the founder of one of my favorite websites, [Our World in Data](https://ourworldindata.org/).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>