<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject5603</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I hear Reddit likes seeing paraplegics defy the odds...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 01:24:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 01:29:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>The couple in this pic are good friends of mine and this was how they announced they are expecting! They will also be getting married, so if you want to help pull off a reddit miracle, go to [this link](http://brideslivewedding.brides.com/MeetCouple.aspx?coupleId=5730 amp;shareClickGuid=bc20a110-12e8-40ca-a543-07ef4b602ad1) and vote to help this awesome couple win their dream wedding! EDIT: Breaking news! [it's a boy!](http://i.imgur.com/yNrVemy.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 01:56:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha well I wasn't there to witness the act, but based on the writing on the wall i'd assume it was all natural ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 02:27:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>took me a minute to get this one. Bravo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 02:31:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>that's him!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 18:16:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>hi! sorry, if i would have known who took the pic i would have given you a shout out.. i knew this post would be popular, i just didn't know it was going to be THIS popular!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-09 16:19:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awe I'm sorry :( I'll take it down asap</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Paralyzed former olympian walks wife down the aisle 15 months after spinal cord injury. Story in Comments.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 16:45:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 16:45:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>The man in the photo is Jaime Nieto, a two-time olympic high jumper who was paralyzed from a spinal cord injury that he sustained in April of last year. Doctors were unsure if he would ever walk again, but after 15 months of intense physical therapy and working out on his own, he was able to fulfill his promise of walking his wife down the aisle at their wedding. [Story here](http://www.nbcbayarea.com/news/california/Injured-Olympic-High-Jumper-Jamie-Nieto-Walks-at-Wedding-in-San-Diego-436029563.html).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 17:05:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>He is still partially paralyzed from the shoulders down but he is getting stronger everyday. Paralysis isn't so black and white.. it is not an all or nothing type of thing. He still has a long road ahead of him to regain as much of what he lost as he can..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tortie with her teddy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-26 00:07:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tortie with her Teddy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-26 00:59:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tortie with her Teddy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-26 04:53:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 20:43:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha.. as I stated in the original post, I am a friend of the couple in the "it still works!" photo.. but yes, they had their baby boy in August!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My cat's reaction to finding out she will no longer be the only cat in the household.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 15:02:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Reddit, meet my new rescue Beesly.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 15:15:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>16 Good Things that are Increasing in the World</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 05:18:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 06:04:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand, but im curious as to why my post got removed while an almost identical post displaying graphs is currently at the top of 'Hot' posts on r/pics?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not only are a lot of bad things decreasing, there are also a lot of good things increasing!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 19:04:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>