<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject187</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Take all chest option?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-04 01:59:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry if this is already in Minecraft (Im pretty sure it isn't but theres a similar thing just for items that are the same) but this mod adds a lot of useful chest sorting options uncluding a "Deposit all" Option but its suprising to see theres no "Take all" Option, im used to having this in Terraria wheres its very useful for quickly moving contents from one chest to another.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-04 17:16:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess to prevent that it could be disabled in config.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 00:10:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Simple but good so its really good for this mod.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ender Moon - Overworld event at night</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 21:08:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had the idea of having a chance of the moon being purple and the overworld would be covered with a purple tint,making the overworld spawn much more endermen than normal, this could also block out other enemy spawns and could still be slept through as normal. This would be useful for getting Ender Pearls and would fit into Minecraft pretty well. This could be disabled in the config if players didn't want this happening.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Time Sensor - Different than the daylight sensor</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 13:55:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking since this adds a weather sensor, a time sensor could be added. At first this seems to be a daylight sensor but this would be a bit more specific, you could put in a specific time and it would output a redstone signal at that time. The sensor could look like daylight one but with the minecraft clock on it with a the corresponding time so its clear what time it will go off. It could also have the added bonus of not needing to be outside. Crafting it could be as simple as a clock and a daylight sensor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Chests Have Names</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 22:51:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>In the new snapshot beacons now have names by default, this would be very useful for chests since i always have to put a sign on them to know whats in them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-08 13:53:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shift + L or whatever you set lock to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-08 17:10:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think they could just shed them over time, killing parrots seems a bit bad plus you haven't had to kill any other tamable mobs for items.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 17:23:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like how it does stick out in a way, like a pure white temple in the nether? Surely it can't be that friendly right? Then you get there and its just spawning bunnies which are friendly too and then they attack. Its deceptive and perfect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 22:44:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was gonna say "Uh they're already in" but I was thinking of wool and now im just surprised as this would easilly add some more decoration blocks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-10 05:51:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im suprised this isn't in already, I mean Sugar Cubes are a real thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Armour that breaks says so on screen similar to sleeping at day.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 23:24:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just something simple like "Your Diamond Helmet Broke."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tree Leaves Sometimes Drop Sticks When Broken</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 18:41:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought it'd be neat since real trees drop sticks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-13 03:04:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could have Blaze rod arms instead of sticks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-13 16:33:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dynamic lighting like that probably wouldn't work very well, the closest to something lighting up everything as you go would be nightvision though it won't stop things spawning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Chest Options For Shulker Boxes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-13 17:38:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure if it was forgotten or its not possible but Shulker Boxes don't have the chest options other storage things have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 04:21:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>It'd be even cooler if it could be made into like a sentry somehow, like how people use guardians as sentries but as its own specific block thats much simpler to use.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Whistle Emote (With Gameplay Uses)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 03:21:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking that a whistle would be pretty useful in some scenarios, it could have some uses: - Alerts enemies from far away if you want to get their attention and draw them close - Players can hear it so its a little easier to alert people where you are - Summons your horse (This one would probably be harder to do as you can have more than one horse, maybe it would be your last interacted horse, as well as maybe something to not spawn them unintentionally, whistle while holding hay?)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shulker Display Stand</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 03:31:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another use for the Shulker Shells, this would be half a Shulker Box that has an item levitating over it, to display it. Basically acts like an item frame but its placed on the ground and displays the item in 3D while rotating it. Took inspiration from the fact Shulker Boxes hold items and the fact they levitate things. Crafting recipe could be something like an enderpearl and a Shulker Shell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Iron Golems follow players holding Emerald Blocks.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 23:18:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would be useful for moving around Golems, maybe could even make them try to get out of water?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Village Priests can "Revive" used Totems of Undying for a high price trade</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 03:30:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Using a Totem would get a "used" Totem that is useless, but a priest would be able to give it back power. The trade could be something expensive, maybe a certain amount of blocks of Emerald.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cave Crystal decor</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-20 12:48:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cave crystals are really cool but its kinda sad theres not really anything like slabs or stairs so I can't make much with them. Maybe could even be some nice clear doors?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 22:52:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know they are but other than that there isn't much to them sadly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 02:05:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah there is a lot of potential still with maps, my favorite being a space themed one that was similar to rd_asteroid in terms of aesthetics. I at least appreciate them making the gas passer a pretty fun thing in MvM since it means they technically added SOMETHING new to MvM.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Grates - Built in mind for the new Magma and Soul Sand Bubble Mechanics</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 20:34:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I LOVE the new bubble mechanics added to these blocks, it adds brand new uses to them and the use for them is very cool, however, I think it just needs a little addition that should fit naturally. Grates. These are made in mind with the bubbling mechanics where you can place these on top of these blocks and they will still work. What does this add? It means you can have Magma Blocks that can work normally but wont damage something when pulled down, combined with the fact this gives air this could be used for cool air restore areas (Sonic the hedgehog style). Another thing to note is that these shouldn't have to be placed directly on top to work so you can build a deep enough area for the bubbling mechanics to work but so you can basically use them at any height. And lastly, grates naturally should let water go through them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 22:09:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think thematically having this as a new thing could work well and could have more new ideas added onto it such as maybe letting items be able to pass through it, could have the option to open and close via redstone and it can give a new crafting use to iron bars rather than just using iron bars themselves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 03:23:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I forgot to put the key on here apparently: Green = At start Yellow = During days before release Red = Near/At release</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Here is how I think they would show off returning Smash 4 characters in Smash Switch (Assuming they come back.)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 03:58:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 04:15:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mainly put so many as shown first because its going to be E3, theres a ton of characters if they all come back and there isnt a ton of time between E3 and the holiday season so I dont think there would be as much time to show off characters as 4.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 04:56:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>If they do, I hope they actually work on those maps again, having them back would be amazing but having them there brought back and never finished would hurt too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 22:04:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Slimes have been shown to be really stretchy in games like Mario Sports Mix to the point that itself could make a unique moveset, plus slimes have been able to use magic which would work easilly for specials.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 00:14:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>This doesn't look like a list of characters that were cut for a logical reason but more of a personal dislike list, removing the new pokemon and the new mario characters despite their popularity and importance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ARMS was already in Smash.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 02:06:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 20:20:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eternaweenifier come on Valve let me use Mr. Mundee's Wild Ride 24/7</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Atomizer Nerf/Bugfix, should it be reverted?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 20:27:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just wondering what the community thinks since personally I liked switching it to use it straight away but now it feels kinda clunky to deploy the jump, as far as I know it wasn't too polarizing but im not exactly a pro scout. If it was too good like that do you think you could think of a stat to help balance it out without making it slow like how it is now?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 23:49:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I get that, thats why i was thinking maybe a new downside could be added to it to help fix that, I think the sandmans HP downside seems like a more fitting thing here than that considering all you get there is a kinda mediocre projectile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 01:15:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe a specific nerf to that specifically, like more bullet damage taken during switching it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 04:13:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Themed as fuck, godly price incoming.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 14:15:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe a holster penalty to counteract that? That way it would still have quick access to it but it require some actual time to put it away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 14:57:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>A holster penalty would put emphasis on not using it mid combat though, a quick switch speed would let you pull it out in a dire situation but you would need time to put it back to use anything like a gun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 15:16:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking very polarising holster times like thermal thruster but yeah I can see downside of him being able to pull it out and use it straight away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 22:20:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly Hades from Kid Icarus Uprising is the perfect Ganondorf replacement, he even does similar moves to him already, along with Kid Icarus Uprising being something Sakurai loves so more likely than Black Shadow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 22:46:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bare in mind the clone is Ganondorf in the first place so it being tied directly to Falcon isn't needed. Also Hades does an attack similar to Ganondorf's dropkick move so that helps. Size has been brought up as an issue but Hades scale can be changed fairly easilly with no issue, not like he has big wings or anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cohesive vs Canon movesets, Explaining why Link or Pit don't use every weapon they have.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 19:37:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>So this is just something I want to bring to light, I've seen a lot of discussion over movesets for characters who have a lot to choose from such as Link and Pit and why they don't use more from their games, I want to bring to light why them being 100% canon may not be right. Weapon users: Link and Pit are characters who have a main weapon, this is a clear cut reason as to why its used in most of their moveset, many times I've seen people question why doesn't Link use a hammer or why doesn't Pit use more KIU weapons. Cohesiveness. Just because a character HAS tons to choose from doesn't mean they SHOULD. The way you would play Link is how he is in Zelda games, you don't literally pull out a ton of weapons every 5 seconds, you'll be using your sword and occasionally using an item (special move) to deal with the enemy. Making specials, special: Both Pit and Kirby fall into this, Pit uses other weapons for special moves and Kirby uses more drastic copy abilities that don't involve basic brawling moves. It's not like Kirby is lacking in stuff to choose from, far from it and Sakurai obviously knows this. If Kirby is pulling out a sword for a back air, whipping forward for a forward air and shooting a bow upwards for an up air Kirby's special become less special as well as cohesiveness being lost mainly just for it to be canon instead. The ones who AREN'T cohesive on purpose: Mr game and watch and Villager, 2 characters who use a ton of different weapons making their movesets appear almost random but lets look at what these characters are. Mr Game and Watch is a character who is 2D stick man and moves at a choppy frame rate and body wise doesn't exactly seem like a fighter, he's weird so his moveset being weird fits perfectly. Villager is a character from a game where you're always using everything and the kitchen sink, none of which are weapons (well there is an axe but you literally use it just for trees) so using many different tools fits how Animal crossing plays while staying true to the character itself. A character like Pit being weird in the same way game and watch is just isn't fitting to the character, no matter how many of the moves are canonically used. The main reason I've brought this up is because I think people just see Link using a sword strike as boring and wondering why he doesn't just pull out something else, to the point of calling Sakurai lazy for not using more from their games. I've also seen people say "Dark pit should just use weapons only from KIU" which is unfitting for how he is, the ideal way Dark Pit would be is to be a Lucas style Semiclone to Pit, still using his 1 main weapon the silver bow but with different strikes using that weapon, along with maybe a different down b (side b already uses a different weapon). I get this loses "potential" but when that potential can turn the character into something they're not, you're just making a character into references more than the character.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 19:53:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I forgot to mention the Dark Pit Staff, yeah it could work as his default weapon however I think the Silver Bow is still his main weapon as shown in the game and how theres other character based weapons like Palutena Blade not being used by Palutena. Additionally Dark Pit lost the ability to fly freely and thats who is in smash as seen with up B being done by Viridi. As for Inkling I think the other weapon archetypes would work well for specials.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 20:03:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Dark Pit Staff is only used once like it says there though for a single shot, where as his battles are shown with the silver bow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 20:11:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Silver Bow itself is a flawed version of the Palutena Bow so it fits him 200% there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What other classes should have access to the Burly Beast?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 20:22:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Important Question I need to know what the TF2 community thinks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 02:58:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think DLC would be his and maybe even Spyro's (considering they basically confirmed his trillogy coming to switch) chance at being added, I only think of these though because DLC 3rd party wise its REALLY hard to top Ryu, Cloud and Bayonetta.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 12:38:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pit wasn't made in smash 64 and was even updated in 4 and he follows the same philosophy as Link</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Items you expect to be removed next game?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 16:25:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Easy picks for me would be the Gust bellows and Beetle because they're from Skyward Sword. (and no one likes the gust bellows.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 17:04:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think Sakurai would be so quick to kick them out considering it was his game, I could see the eye turret going though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 17:16:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>No rage No hitstun canceling No untechable spin No magnet hand recoveries (no 2 frame if this happens) Next to no RNG in character movesets (I cant think of a way judge can lose RNG though)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 19:35:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I dont think ive met one person who legit likes them so its good its seemingly on the chopping block anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 19:36:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>There honestly might just not be one this time. Brawl technically didn't have one but DID have mario spin off characters like Wario and Diddy, so maybe its their chances to shine again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 19:47:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really don't think Yoshi has anyone to choose from except like Baby Mario but Baby Mario in Yoshi island games just rides Yoshi.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 20:28:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry to say but its more than likely gonna stay if diddy stays.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 21:17:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mega mans mostly works naturally with him using an arm canon to shoot out stuff as well as not using physical items for bair and fair, Kirby would have to pull out tons of different items or do something really strange like spit out ice. There used to be one stand out move kirby had and that was dash attack in melee, it didn't fit in with the other moves he had and was just kinda basic for what it was based on so it became the yoyo breakdance to fit with kirbys mostly basic moveset while still being canon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Kinda out of the loop but, Why doesn't Valve bring back some old strange weapons?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 21:43:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mainly made this because of the strange Gunslinger which as far as I know is only in a crate worth 14 keys? Surely this isn't right for something this common.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 22:00:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>They could probably gain a vintage or something similar quality to technically separate them while still having a not absurdly priced strange version.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 22:01:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only really peach does that for basic moves, that being her f smash. Corrin uses their body parts which is still fairly natural vs pulling out an entirely new weapon. Kirby could transform in Kirby 64 which could've been done for smash but would've more than likely made kirby not look so good when doing that with a hat on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 22:07:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, I dont think this should've even became a problem in the first place though, theres no way a strange for a commonly used weapon should've been in 1 now rare crate. I could understand like a strange reskin being very rare but this is just bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 22:10:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get the joke an all but they probably wouldn't make one because of the colour being important to tell what weapon it is since he has two pick weapons.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 23:13:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean you could just turn on only those items and turn off any new ones off using the item switch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 01:24:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like Crash and Spyro would still work as curveballs considering they're western made characters and are mainly connected to Sony more than anything so they stand out in that way while still fitting aesthetically to smash.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 17:19:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because Kirby uses weapons or the hats themselves for a lot of abilities, where as he has his feet and fists always. Kirby's moveset is mostly moves he actually does anyway and they flow together naturally.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 00:47:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>There really isn't no reason Olimar can't have access to Rock Pikmin and have EVERYONE be an alt. Olimars changes in 4 I feel like were both a technical reason and a gameplay reason, Brawl Up B was not very good and all tether recoveries were removed in general. Plus canonically Olimar gets access to all types of Pikmin. Rock Pikmin can easily be added on to make Pikmin pluck order Red, Yellow, Blue, White, Purple and Rock.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 01:10:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder if scouts baseball can get stuck in the door?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 02:06:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scot Blocked</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 03:01:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I honestly just want to be able to use a sandvich and a shotgun, if people can provide legit reasons as to why this is too much please tell me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 03:07:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like no one uses the shotgun seriously becuase of how godly a sandvich is though in comparison, theres no way you should really ever not have a food item. As well as it not really being as crazy as say solider being able to wear boots as well as a shotgun, its a different scenario because of how the classes work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Gas Passer: How is it?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 19:30:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't seen many people use it since the jungle inferno stuff ended, me personally have found it just a chore to use but power wise it seems fine, what changes could be made to make it more fun but still balanced?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 21:01:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think cause the point is to throw it on and let team mates deal with it (thats why any damage lights them up, not just fire) but the way you get it is more encouraged to just rush in and build up damage for another one but getting just 1 is a pain and the reward is just for a support thing, it can block an area but honestly not for long for something that takes so long to get.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 21:55:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess being too simple can be an issue, considering how much I like the modern one much more than the original both in use and fighting it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>With swimming into 1x1 holes being a thing, I think Crawling needs to be done for land based 1x1.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 00:50:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just feel like this would help a lot, it doesn't even have to be a new function, just the bare minimum of having your character crawl when in 1x1 space.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 02:36:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think they're meant to be rare but drowned do supposedly drop them rarely so they aren't exclusive to monuments now anyway so im for this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Something strange about the Crusaders Crossbow stats</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 02:53:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>It mentions no headshots like that needs to be pointed out, how come? I mean Medic isn't a sniper so it'd be strange to assume it could headshot, it seems like something that would only need to be pointed out if medic had a weapon that could headshot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Since Ice biomes can't have Dolphins, Seals instead?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 05:09:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seals are really cute and would help add more life to that area, if wanted to make them more useful they could act literally like dolphins but for ice biomes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 21:18:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that ANOTHER new pyro kill taunt?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 02:36:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think gas passer afterburn ever happens enough for that to be useful, especially since that requires a kill for a health kit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Phantoms drop a material to craft a cursed bed that lets you sleep during the daytime.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 16:56:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like it fits their theme and would be a cool option to have. Maybe it could also not reset your spawn point since its cursed and can't be used to skip the night anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Simple Farm using waterlogged slabs</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 12:54:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 19:51:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bit different fixing a hat vs buffing a weapon again but yeah I never thought "this needs nerfing" but I think its cause they want to make heavy not just have a faster movement option thats not as detrimental as the current designs. Probably because they'd easilly become the meta as speed is an issue for heavy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 23:06:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty sure that just turns it into a dirt block again im afraid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 01:37:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make holes with water in it, put slabs on top.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Weapons you'd like to see a complete redesign in rather than simple buffs/nerfs?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 15:42:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>For me I think the Eviction Notice is just kinda in a boring and bad place as is, its design clearly should be a bleeding weapon but for some reason its even weaker than stock.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 15:52:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thats a lot! Any ideas for them specifically since some of them seem pretty hard to redesign.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 16:07:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>More specifically, the sound it makes on hit makes it sound like a bleed damage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 17:33:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its in a very awkard state of basically OP in pubs but near useless elsewhere because of how it works. It needs an overhaul.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 19:57:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I mean shotguns in general are already fighting the losing battle against lunchbox items so its just kinda the worst of the worst if anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 21:06:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Slow is probably REALLY strong on Spy, considering he's about being in a certain place close to the enemy and that makes it way easier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Keep the super speed of blue ice but make it so boats brake when reaching a certain crazy speed so you can't outrace the chunk rendering.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 00:00:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>If the super speed gets removed that will make blue ice a lot less interesting. A speed limit thats high to stop the game literally breaking should be fine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Whats the deal with no shields in other versions?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 03:10:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know dual wielding technically is just barely in the other versions but to me the shields seem like weird things to leave out since they are simple to implement and are an entire item missing from the game. Have the developers explained this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 03:34:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought that might be the case, just thought at very least the shield would be added since as far as I know its like the only major item not in other versions and they already have the mechanic of the off hand to make it work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Has there been any offical word on Gyro controls for Switch Minecraft?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 17:43:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really would love this being added, wondering if its been said this might be added when it gets updated to Bedrock.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 18:30:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay thank you, good to know they haven't outright said no to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 01:56:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do miss the caber, it went from a joke weapon that was high risk high reward to a weapon that is a joke because its high risk low reward. Honestly the caber should respawn after time I mean the Darwin's Danger Shield does now and if you've survived after using it and you're out long enough it should just happen like anything else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 01:58:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah whoops I got that mixed by accident.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Slush - A decorative and fitting block for cold biomes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 19:32:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Slush is the middle ground between snow and ice so it seems fairly natural to me, but the decorating comes in with being able to dye it similar to how slushies work which can mean a new set of coloured blocks to use. The block would probably slow you down like soul sand and react to gravity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 22:08:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't have one but imagine darker slightly translucent snow for the default and colored versions of that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 02:03:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idk how realistic that is honestly but sounds like it could work!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 02:07:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It would be cool to see sand replaced since it sticks out quite a bit though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How come Steve in all promo art and merchandise uses the texture from way before release with the in-game Steve being something very different?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 03:08:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its very weird to that this day the current in-game Steve textures are only EVER used in-game with promo stuff never EVER using it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 04:00:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry for sounding nooby here, but what if the sword swipe and axe full power attacks were like bonuses ON TOP of the old style attacks where you could do the classic rapid clicks at the same strength but if you don't attack for a few seconds you can do an even stronger different attack like the sword swipe?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pressure Plates stay stuck to slime blocks when placed on them for more convenient Launchpads and other things</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 14:05:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand there might be some technical issues to this but it is bar none the best when the pressure plate is on the slime block itself its just currently they pop off after bouncing. Pressure plates don't even give you fall damage when they're on a slime block so that is already there to work with this idea. I think they should give a very brief signal when stepped on when its on a slime block.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 14:18:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think to get out of it you should be able to jump repeatedly like many games such as Mario, this will still make it work for mobs and inconvenient for players as a trap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 14:35:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably hasn't been done mainly for ease but you have to remember that these are basically just water zombies and zombies wouldnt be smart enough to swim.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 17:00:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>That serves a use though where as, as far as I know, pressure plates popping off doesn't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 18:01:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could probably make that its own thing, a sticky plate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A kinda bad but realistic idea for unrestricted Halloween Items</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 04:06:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I honestly see Valve releasing "ScreamFortress Classics" Cases that have old Halloween cosmetics but this time, they're unrestricted. This seems like the most likely thing to happen to me since its giving people what they want but at a cost. How would you react?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 15:18:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>u/helenangel Is this a technically possible thing or is limitations stopping it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 19:07:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>The whole thing is a bit much for Minecraft so I can see why people are against it, it being an option when creating a world can work but honestly the most natural thing to me would be cherry-picking the best parts of it that people love.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 19:55:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>If they do this the item should be called gold-plated or iron-plated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An island with a singular tree. (Seed and location in comments)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 19:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 19:59:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seed: 2306155473820946324 Location: -164.72 71.56 640.9</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 22:05:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sniper's head is bloody twelve feet tall</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 23:22:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its in the latest snapshot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cake under a Note block makes a kazoo noise</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 16:47:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wacky huh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 17:25:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah like other note block changing things.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 17:45:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you remember the time you took metal from another engies dispenser and used it on your own buildings</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Inventory Sorting?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 05:20:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am really shocked this isn't a Frequently posted thing, and any posts relating to this are months old, I'd really LOVE basic options such as deposit all, take all, and of course the ability to just have everything automatically go in order. Creative already has items organized by type so that would be the template this "auto arrange" option would do. And if you want to go the extra mile, being able to favorite items from being deposited would just be great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 15:14:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Many Adventure and sandbox games have an "organize" option, managing what items to bring with you is the survival part.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 22:27:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>It would still be a task to sort your inventories especially with as many items as there are, you'd still need to do stuff like make chests for dirt and stone. This just helps out small inventories like your own or just sorting out a small chest, you can sort it and get a rough idea like "ah blocks will always be towards the top but my weapons will be near the bottom" Speeds things up and adds convenience.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Nether Mob that can be everywhere. (Details inside)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 00:08:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's a fairly simple but I think game changing mob for the Nether, it takes the idea of the silverfish but expands it across an entire dimension. This is to address some issues the Nether currently suffers: * 1. Digging in the Nether is boring * 2. Digging in the Nether lacks danger * 3. More hostile life in the Nether It lives inside netherrack blocks that look similar to any others but have *slightly* longer digging time, it will attack you once it is broken to discourage mindless digging through the Nether. They spawn in clumps like ore and if you dig out one it will have many connected to it, breaking all of them at once. They won't have a lot of health or do a lot of damage but breaking open a big clump could cause a instant swarm if unlucky enough, they're not smart enough to call for back ups though. Looks wise I was thinking like the scrapped Mob C, small little chompy guys but with a Netherack like texture.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 00:20:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I legit don't know about it so if this resembles a mod its entirely coincidental.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 01:02:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll be honest, haven't had this as an issue but guess I'm lucky. Lava is an understandable but pretty boring hazard. Another idea I had for this but didn't write down as the post was getting pretty long was these also spawning in Quartz as thats definately a thing thats pretty boring as is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An invisible building block, Phantom Membrane block</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 16:08:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I saw that a Membrane block has been suggested before but its completely different from this idea, check it out [Here.](https://www.reddit.com/r/minecraftsuggestions/comments/8ayk5a/membrane_block/) So this is for something I've been wanting for a while now, a reasonable survival barrier block, however it'll be a little more interesting than just that. It'll appear invisible like normal however when a player/mob is on it or it is being mined, it will reveal its true form, you will also be able to see it when holding phantom membrane like the barrier block. Mining it will be instant similar to a slime block.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 16:56:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holding the block themselves could also work like how holding membrane works.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 00:06:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its very easy to get rid of so you cant be trapped by it and its COMPLETELY clear vs glass being something good for aesthetics like houses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 00:07:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love the mushroom cluster idea, something i didnt think of but seems so obvious now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Snowball can be used to make a snowflake banner</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 02:59:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice new use for snowballs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 17:37:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/bossfight</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to have longer time to reconnect on a server?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 20:57:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen people talk about a command that lets you have more than 20 seconds to reconnect but I don't know it and can't find it when searching.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 23:32:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>The real plot twist is the last part not being the Phlog</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Using a Fishing rod on a Tripwire Hook pulls you towards it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 16:33:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know grappling hook is a frequently posted thing so here is a more reasonable and logically fitting one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 16:39:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the name did kill the idea but Mojang is probably just weary on adding projectiles in general since they can be powerful. Tridents have been added but they're clearly a normal weapon. Maybe its the concept of ammo they dont like and only want bows to be like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 16:40:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah Insta-swoosh kinda thing like when you pull a mob.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 23:50:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shouldn't the parrot be glitching its head way off the image</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The only thing Valve would need to add to make my favorite Scream Fortress update</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 00:59:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 01:21:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly I want bird heads for all but this one is the one I feel is missing most of all. Though Spy did get a cool bird recently.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 04:28:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since Aristotle is the opposite to Archimedes, probably would become Spyistotle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 14:53:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=329804821 Here!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 18:28:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I mean I get why there basically wasn't one since they put out the literal only update out of that year then so trying to push out a full force update straight after that wasnt reasonable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 18:39:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Switching to the Eviction Notice literally makes Heavy stab himself with them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 20:06:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>It should probably be the ball instead of a line, this looks like its just using the zap attack to kill.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 20:36:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe more like the halloween spell its based on would work https://wiki.teamfortress.com/wiki/Kill_icon#/media/File:Killicon_tesla_bolt.png</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 14:44:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you shove with it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 16:32:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't get why this would be needed, just cancel it? Taunts that are longer done after a kill are more disrespectful anyway so pulling off a longer one is more effective.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 01:11:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pootis, Pow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 20:01:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is cool and all but you fucking know Valve is gonna make it ultra rare.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 20:37:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone PLEASE make this a taunt where demo sits down then does this while screaming MEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE- endlessly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The next wtf character choice i'd like to see in Smash</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 01:58:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 03:57:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Obviously not, I mean just as a joke mod like many others.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is this new?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 04:46:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I noticed when someone got 7 refined, instead of saying refined metal in chat 7 times it just said refined metal (x7) instead making the chat much less cluttered.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 22:48:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish you could customise the ka-BOOM taunt to have any picture.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 03:09:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but with the decal tool instead of a mod so people see it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 01:23:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I legit don't see the problem of it having a normal air blast considering it uses up quite a bit of ammo for what it is. It's already different from a normal flame thrower so its weird to have a nerf like this on it. It's kinda like if the gunslinger had a carrying building penalty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 15:29:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wouldn't it be kinda annoying to do this since you're in water? Especially when Ink sacs are an item that has not proper use other than dye.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Small Cacti (Like Sea Pickles)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 22:43:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>So we SORTA already have this with the potted plant Cactus but this would be growing in the desert and would stack together on one block in different amounts. Adds a little something to the desert while still fitting in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 22:50:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, maybe less damage than bigger ones but more or less the same.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 12:48:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would probably be its own type, maybe call it armed Cacti.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If a reskin had stats based on its design - Post your ideas!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 19:10:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>So for example, Bread Bite would now give health back to the heavy on successful hit (Eat their health) but have some kind of downside to that. Scottish Handshake gives you back some health on taunt but makes you more flammable (Alcohol is flammable, maybe demo spills it) . Bat Saber could have the shortstops shove on it (scout,use the force). Post any ideas you have!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Option to toggle spawn eggs icons into the face of the mob instead</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 20:28:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>A simple thing really, this makes it so that there's a menu option to change the spawn egg into an image of the mobs face, this makes it so its easier to pick out which is which mob much quicker than looking at egg colours. Eggs work for simple colored ones like Creepers but with more and more mobs being added and them being similar colours to each other, it can get a little hard to choose from without looking at their names. This would also be an option so texture packs could do the same thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 20:29:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's not a reskin though, that is its own weapon already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 21:05:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>That still means you'd have to mouse over it to check, this option is to so you can see it from the list without having to search around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 21:41:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah it would just be a flat texture, not a model.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 21:44:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>This idea makes it so texture packs can also have the option though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is this parrot a cosmetic?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:42:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 04:51:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Buildings are being scrambled!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Heavy going to hell after eating a Sandvich in front of a burning Medic.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 00:17:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Paintings can be used on the floor with different designs AKA rugs</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 02:15:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or it could be its own item, be either way some floor decor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 19:38:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>SPY CREEPIN AROUND HERE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Seagrass is animated very nicely, what about subtle animation for normal grass?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 17:23:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Doesn't have to sway as much as the stuff in the water does but it'd make things more lively if it had a subtle movement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 23:03:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be clear I meant sprite animation wise, not how shaders do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Inspecting the Pass Time Jack has odd results.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 23:10:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Shortstop's description of the shove feels as forced as the shove itself.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 00:18:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 01:13:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like the shove as a move idea but no idea whys it on this weapon, this weapon really should just but a basic gun weapon for scout. Could at least give SOME upside to shoving someone like it marking them for death on shove while they're midair from the shove or something its just literally a joke as is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 03:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems like a strange addition to add to scout just in general, he doesn't exactly need it. It should get a change to make it worthwhile on whatever weapon its on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>when you walkin</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 21:23:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 15:08:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would've been against this years ago, but like you said, theres already 2 forms of crawling already, just weirdly specific times to do it, it should be a thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 20:11:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always feel like a coward but I wouldn't mind just turning off creeper explosions separately, pretty sad that you have to turn off villager farming to do it though so yeah this is good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 19:18:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>New Spy Knife: Chair</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 17:10:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sad that this could've legit been a thing if Minecraft was on Steam or at least when Notch played the game a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Surely this has been done before right?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 18:14:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to increase the size of the ammo left on heal patient on the Medic HUD?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 17:41:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I find it really small, I know custom huds do this but I just want the default with this changed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 04:29:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>C'mere, Cupcake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Visible DI indicator on Corrin Neutral B? Intentional or accidental debug?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 21:44:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 21:46:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XFtvh8681Xc Source match</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 19:31:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably cause NES classic character like Megaman was for 4 as well as Konami clearly being fine with their characters in smash.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Very Easy Mode - Middle ground of Peaceful and Easy with some twists</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 19:21:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometimes you want a nice peaceful Minecraft playthrough but not literal no action of peaceful and not just the basic experience of easy, heres some proposals based on some feedback from friends. * Mobs still spawn, but will only do in any darkness created by blocks, moonlight wont spawn mobs meaning walking around in an open field is fine but a roofed forest will be dangerous to be near. * Mobs that grief like creepers, wont break blocks but Villagers can still do so for farms. * Items won't drop on death, but SOME exp will to make death still an issue but not as big of an issue. These are things me and others feel like would be a nice proper easy going mode of Minecraft without it literally just being walking around with nothing to fight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 21:21:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Put this image on an objector</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The REAL reason Random Crits are still a thing.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 18:38:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A character who probably won't happen, Vince from Art Academy Moveset concept</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 18:28:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 21:40:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't put it on the post but the trace would have a low amount of HP, as well as not use special moves as that would be just insane and cause too much to spawn on screen. Also yeah the delay of 2 seconds is like what I meant. I think Zero in MvC has this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 20:08:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly the intel room of 2fort is one of the most iconic parts of TF2.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 18:37:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cardboard Mario?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Something interesting about the blog posts and Ridley</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 18:41:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>So far, all characters who have a drastic alt like Wedding Mario, Koopalings or an opposite gender are mentioned in their blog post. Ridley is an exception to this for some reason and technically nothing has said Meta Ridley is actually an alt. This applies to Olimar and Alph too so when Olimar gets his daily blog post, make sure it mentions Alph or something weird is going on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 18:44:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's understandable, but not even a word on it? That wouldn't need a finished alt to happen, we've seen footage of it so its not hidden either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 01:34:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Steve, this is gonna get hate but you cant argue with how close its been to Nintendo since the Wii U, its a best seller on the E-shop, theres a Nintendo exclusive texture pack, they've embraced crossover play with it, theres an upcoming Creeper 2DS XL and lastly EVERYONE knows Minecraft. But all this is invalidated because people dont like kids playing it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 00:40:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>What makes me a good Legoman?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thanks for saving me a spot in Smash little buddy.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 01:31:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 01:35:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've already seen this render used elsewhere</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Greninja's new water kunai's</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 04:03:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>17 Echo Ideas and reasons they could or couldn't appear</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 20:49:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 20:55:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought about it but Square Enix stingy amount of FF stuff in smash makes me doubt it would happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 21:22:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>How so?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 22:09:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>This doesn't seem to load for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 22:17:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah that, that seems fine, she doesn't do anything on that stage and could easilly be just not there when playable like Toon Link on Spirit Tracks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 22:41:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not the direct colours though, Fox's Wolf alt is now purple fur so its clear they avoid alts like that now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 02:45:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm pretty sure Birdo inhaling people has just never been a thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 17:49:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>She has no problem throwing fireballs at people in Mario Kart, KK slider is the pacifist of the series.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Explaining how an ARMS fighter could work in Smash Mechanically and have longer range than Simon Belmont</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 01:22:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 01:55:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>The thing with echo fighters is that they have to have the same sorta base attributes. If Spring Man had the many jumps and the comeback mechanic while also giving Ribbon Girl these it could work. As a Simon/Richter style Echoing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:17:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>As much as I like all the fighters, especially Dr Coyle as a really good female villain, it would be someone basic to do Arms in smash since they would already have a unique gimmick, like how Ryu is in Smash.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 05:05:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh yeah for sure, 1-upping Simon is definately a DLC thing and I don't expect to see Arms characters till DLC.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 16:16:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why waste a down B charging their arms when shield + B is perfect for it, especially when they can't do it in the air.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Echo fighter with an Echoed Voice</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 16:23:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 22:56:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even same height jumps are extremely powerful for their onstage use.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 17:21:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Olimar Neutral B: This could very easilly be a Shield + B move now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 17:44:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Peach's is at least an actual move though, not some sort of complementary mechanic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 17:51:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pikmin mechanic wise, could be the charge order attack to latch on all your Pikmin at once. Or could bring back the brawl up b but sideways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 17:53:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah the thing with Pikmin is there isnt any NEEDED things but wasting neutral b like that seems unnecessary when it serves no use mid air anyway. I posted some ideas down below though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 17:58:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think for the brawl up b thing, the pikmin could comedically stretch quite a bit to be decent. Lucas' rope snake did in Smash 4.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 23:26:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>They didn't have a trophy in wii u, just 3DS cause it was on the portable based Rhythm heaven, theres a lot going for Rhythm heaven now but for chorus kids specifically, it couldve changed to something more relevant like Tibby.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 03:41:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pikmin throw could be moved there like Kirby does and could gain some kind of new Side b, maybe like brawl's up b but sideways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 06:04:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>This applied for chorus kids too at the time and they aren't even the main character of their game unlike Tibby.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>To everyone who says Isabelle is not a fighter</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 13:12:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 13:48:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Happy Home Designer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 15:37:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Almost have this in the New Leaf update, she's in her camper van and she wears her casual clothes saying shes took the day off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>