<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject280</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Insecure Body Shaming MIL</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 13:43:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could use some advice and DWIL Nation forums were too mean for me. Let me preface this by saying I don't want to cut my MIL off. I only see her maybe x4 a year because my husband has agreed to limit my contact with her. And when I DO see her its in a larger family setting so I do not interact with her much. The issue is my mother in law brings up my weight CONSTANTLY. I am 153 pounds she is about 190-220. My SIL (her daughter) is easily 250-300. Its become quite awkward for me because she will obsess about "my figure" to anyone who will listen to her. Comments include as follows: When I ordered a salad "Oh wait until you are eating for 2!!" "Shes just trying to look good" to my mother when my mother complimented my weight loss at my wedding. My mother was FURIOUS and hasn't spoken to her since. "I'm trying to look like THAT" pointing to me at a family Christmas get together. It was so embarrassing and made her look insane. "Wait until you have a baby!" When I lost 10 pounds one summer for my job (cannot say what I do because it will give me away) Then she'll put down her and her daughter "We only feed the girls in my family" And what really bugged me is they came to my house last summer (this has since stopped) and my MIL pulled me a side and said "Can you tell SIL she looks great? She lost 13 pounds." She gave my husband "leftover" chips cookies cakes and everything she knows I like when I was on a 3 day cleanse. Funny thing was I have IBS and was "fasting" on veggie juice to heal my stomach not loose weight. I didn't eat a bite of it but found it funny she assumed it was for vanity and not health. When I hit 153 last summer and she saw me she kept repeating "You lost weight" "You lost so much weight" and its literally the only thing she talks about. How do I make her stop obsessing about my weight? I've thought about saying "If you worry less about my body and more about yours you would be happier." Or "Why are you so obsessed with my body? Its f***ng creepy." And finally "If you keep talking about my body, I'm leaving." And walking out of the family gathering. Thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shutting MIL down</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 23:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Family picnic is coming up. Last time I spoke to MIl I confronted her and she seems to have backed down However BILs fiance sent out invites to her bridal shower and I RSVP'd "no". How do I handle MILs badgering? She is very much "Give me an explanation so I can argue with you about it insult you and passively aggressively tear you down about it." I have to see her in person for a large family gathering.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Nose in my 'Weight Loss'</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 19:29:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has this been taken as a MIL name yet? Mine is quite nosey and prides herself in knowing things about you. Our family get together is quickly approaching and I've lost 7ish pounds due to my job that's mostly walking as well as eating right and regular exercising to self manage my anxiety. I look like I've lost twice that because I'm built like Rhonda Rousey (muscular). She wants to know what I have done to loose weight. Do I owe her a response? If I tell her what I'm doing she will turn it into a competition and I have no interest in competing with a post menopausal woman, especially not the one who [failed to] raise my husband. How should I respond to the "'What have you been dooingggg's?" DH insists these are complimentary but for the women out there who have bee through this we known better. I want to say "Thinking of you and being unable to eat." But coming out the gate aggressive will backfire since her team of FMs will be there. Will "Thank you for the compliment" work?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MIL sent GFIL to Mow My Grass</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 16:00:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>This took place years ago about 8 months into my brand new marriage husband and I had new jobs, new schedules, a new home, and were still getting "used to" each other and were fighting a lot. I think MIL smelled blood. She would constantly bring up "graaaandbabiezz" and my husband and I would shoot her down. She did group tactics to "shame us" into kids at family reunions, run behind the other's back like a child to "hint" and when I would tell husband and he would call her to yell at her she would say "subject280 is too sensitive I was joking about being at her delivery room and having GFIL film it!!" So now we have FMGFIL. He is MILs father and is basically the Jedi who trained MIL. Hes also the biggest pain in the ads I've ever met. Helpless worthless waste of space. On top of this we had HIS mother GGMIL and his wife MILs mother GMIL. Bot were nasty bitches, codependent on GFIL. Around this time GGMIL and GMIL died 2 months apart. GFIL was naturally devastated and being new to the narc game I DID feel bad. Well MIL smelled the blood and approached husband and I in front of an audience with GFIL in tow and states "He is just SO LONELY and LOVES to mow grass" so husband and I agreed stupidly to let this FM into my home where he would bust up our lawn mower, our septic tank, and as soon as we were alone in the kitchen would hound me about grandbabies grandbabies grandbabies. Basically MIL had HIM coming to my house once a week on a work night hounding me for him. Stupid me allowed this for 2 summers. On one occasion he "accidently" let the dogs out and I had to chase them over 2 miles because they're hunting dogs. On another occasion he dug for information on my "weight" (my MILs obsession) and I finally told my husband "When we purchase a new mower hes out" and husband agreed. Now every holiday when I see this shriveled flying monkey he has the nerve to tell me with a CBF "I miss mowing MY grass". YOUR GRASS? Yours?!?!? You fucking prune...my theory is MIL wanted husband to move him in with us because we have a step in shower and live in a 1 story home. He was also a school teacher so in their heads "if they have kids GFIL can be free childcare because they will neeeeed hiiimmm and he is faaaaaamily and sooo loonneeely"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Time My Husband Flexed His Spine</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 01:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>My MIL once tried to guilt us into a last minute party for her father, and we already had plans for the night. My husband responded "We aren't coming" To which she whined: "But its GFIL's biiirrrrttthhhddaaay!" To which husband replied:"Oh, then we are DEFINITELY not coming." To say it was satisfying is an understatement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Nose At The Bridal Shower</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 13:58:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>This happened 3 years ago when I first got married. I thought this was the place to unpack it. So I did not WANT a bridal shower. MySometimesNo mother decides I was having one. She, her best friend who is like an aunt to me/mother of MY best friend, my sister and even my brother worked and had food done/games planned in 2 days. My mother calls me and states "Your MIL keeps texting me 3 times a day asking to help and won't take "we have it all done" for an answer. What the  #247;* #247;* #215; do I do?" Stupid me says "Ask her to make a dish so she shuts up." MIL invites herself to my mothers house to arrange her dish. Of course immediately starts rearranging things and my mom has to tell her several times "NO" My parents called me. My Dad who is stoic and usually silent was like "This woman is a bitch." The day of my bridal shower MIL invites GFIL "to sit in the back room" since he droce GMIL and GreatGMIL. MIL proceeds to try to make it a day for GreatMIL to get the attention off of me. My friends and family are there all happy for me. MIL is jealous. CBF the whole day. My mothers friend and I do BeachBody workouts and we have both been obease in the past. We were taking about the latest program and my MIL says *to my mothers face* "Oh...LaneAnie is just in 'bride mode'." My mom had watched me struggle with my weight my whole life. My mom gives a speech. Halfway through a teary eyed part my MIL stands up, barks over my mom "We love LaneAnie too." My mom and her friend were speechlessly pissed. GMIL kept mistaking me for "my twin sister" I dont HAVE a twin guys!! Gift opening time. MIL snatches every open gift out of my hands to inspect it despite the fact my friend is keeping track of the gift/who sent it. I got a check, guys, she ripped it out of my hands to see how much her husbands realtive had given me/her son! At the end my moms other friend pulls me aside and says "subject280...What the fuck is wrong with your MIL?" Reports came back from guests that they were extremely uncomfortable with the way she acted the whole time. And of COURSE weight obsessed sister in law "Couldn't get the day off of work." To bother to come. I strongly suspect she was mad because H and I had been engaged and her long time boyfriend was dragging his feet. My mother says "When its time for a baby shower MIL isnt welcome."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MILs Side Get Together</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 23:22:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Date was set. All of The Boss's nosey flying monkeys are assembled. "When are you having kids?" Is all these assholes ask me about.( I wanted to edit this and say I think MIL coaches them to do this. Last year they made a big deal about an old high chair and in front of every one asked loudly if WE wanted it.) My canned responses are "MIL said it would make me fat so I'm afraid to." (Because she has baby rabies this would throw it back in her face) "When people stop asking."(this opens me up to "we haven't asked where are the kids" questions) "That's a strange thing to ask....are you saying I LOOK pregnant? You are SO RUDE!" (This makes me look insane which furthers MILs narrative) Or I could flip the script. Get them to tell me about their pregnancies and then as they're talking cut them off and say "Thats nice" and walk away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 02:02:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>So...how about "you will be 3rd to know...after Husband and MY mom know."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 02:11:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its ALL about control to these people. No SS number no high school diploma no photo ID no record of you and you cant leave.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 02:12:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see it as you did your husband a favor by reminding HIM to do something vs doing something nice for your MIL. After all you are his wife.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 03:32:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have an active imagination</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 03:47:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>What I do is I wait 12 hours to answer a text from someone who is text-until-you-respond-to-me. This "trains" them if you will, to stop harassing you. If you delay gratification *consistently* then they will stop. She sounds like she has anxiety. My sometimes NoMom has it and it went untreated for years. Ive forgiven her and moved on but I trained her this way to quit obsessively calling and texting. It has worked. And you can be kind about it. I said "Mom, calling me constantly scares me because I think something is wrong. How about you wait 2 hours before calling me or texting me in case I am cooking and doing dishes or in the bath and can't get to my phone? Sometimes my hands arent clean enough to text back." And that was enough for her to realize "She's NOT ignoring me. Her hands are covered in raw chicken, dish soap, ECT" and it helped change the destructive obsessive thoughts she was having. (That was a side effect...I'm not promising you that will happen in your case)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 03:48:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm thinking if I spike the punch bowl we would all have a better time.......</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 03:51:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>The louder she gets envision her lighting herself on fire like the human torch. Now imagine you are aquaman and the calmer you get the more water you can summon and before you know it you are as deep and calm and powerful as the sea. It will help keep you calm. And it sometimes unnerved angry out of control people because it shows them you are more collected then them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 03:57:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Report your MIL to the police if she shows up with your ex. She's breaking the law and so is he</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 11:16:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much for this. By saying nothing I can't be accused of saying something mean</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 11:20:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's not wrong from the sound of your post</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 11:23:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need to remember theseadult children are all but hostages under Jim Bob. All they hear growing up is now evil everyone else is and how they are going to hell if they dont obey authority...so husbands. I think Jinger married Jeremy on purpose because in her mind him telling her she can wear pants ect keeps her from going to hell or being cursed "because she is just following her headship."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 11:27:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would have walked away and had husband change her dressing if she insisted on flashing me. I know hindsight and all that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 11:32:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the future: "Baby isnt moving...thats gas" "I said no pictures" then report every single one to social media.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 11:34:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>They will all be convinced I'm pregnant and when no announcements come by Christmas I get to see her have an epic meltdown at dinner.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 11:37:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will be PMing you...I foresee the future now. You are the hero with experience i need!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 11:40:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you are being smart</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 11:52:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everytime she says "How is the new house" and you dont HAVE a new house say "It's great! We love the new sitting room and neighbors." Make her panic. Then after she asks 50 questions say "there is no house I thought we were playing pretend."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 11:53:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell her someone from YOUR family's side gave you guys money  #128520; that way in her mind your family has the power and that will drive her insane</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 11:58:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Leave a torn condom with some yogurt in it on the bathroom floor. If it continues report her comments to HR. That's harassment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 12:03:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think they were always IBLP/ATI because of Jim Bob and Jim Bob's mother talking about it and his drunk dad? Could be wrong....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 22:29:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because she knows her son doesn't give a fuck about her so she targeted you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 22:30:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's when you fart. Loudly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 22:39:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chemical warfare?!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 22:43:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I want to be happy too. What makes me happy is talking to you once a month."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 22:44:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>How vile. That's when you take a step back and walk away from her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 22:55:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I meant the story was vile and since farting won't stop her you walk away</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 23:02:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good for you!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 00:33:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make sure you make it clearer than crystal that you are NOT "hers"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 01:09:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>You obviously know her best but my advice is speak with your actions....not words. Words give these women something to latch onto or twist around and argue with. Actions, there is no guessing to be made about them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 01:13:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Words are useless to her. Speak with your actions. *Show her* that you won't change.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 01:15:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Say nothing to her comment about going overseas. Nothing positive or negative. She's looking to see if you will chase her for validation OR tell her off so she can cry victim.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 01:23:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Answer a question with a question" Her "What's that" You "What's what?" Her "That...thing in your hand." You"What thing?" Her"That" You"Why do you ask?" Her"are you feeding that to the baby?" You"feeding what to the baby?" Her"that" You"What?" Her"THAT" You"Would you like some?" So on so forth. Good rule of thumb with anybody giving you any advice ask questions. Her"You should give the baby breastmilk" You"Did you feed your babies breast milk?" She will either clam up or say "I read..." You"Where did you read that?" Her "in a book" You"What book?" Her"a parenting book You"what was the name of the book?" And keep going like that. Keep your tone pleasent and cheerful like you are chatting with your best friend. To everyone else you will look like you are being polite so she can't cry and whine that you are mean or ignoring her. And she will be pissy because she can't get to you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 01:24:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Act like you cant hear FIL when he talks and have him repeat himself several times...make him doubt the volume of his voice. I'm petty though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 01:27:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never facetime her again. She's playing a game. Let your actions speak. If you don't give her any attention whatsoever then she's going to be less of a problem. Be prepared for an extinction burst....and have your friend send her an invite that is an hour later than the actual party so when she inevitably shows up late or early to make a scene the party will already be in full swing and nobody will care about her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 01:56:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Our guest list has been finalized. No."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 01:58:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should have programmed this subforum into her phone And ps you are my fucking hero</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 01:59:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh and I hope you deleted some of the MIL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 03:00:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ignore her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 03:01:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love me some cotton candy Faygo though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 03:07:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imagine her all pissy all alone just tap tap tappity tap texting away furiously trying to get your goat and you all snuggled up in prewedding bliss feeling loved and supported Hope it helps!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 03:08:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would respond to every one "To avoid further conflict I am planning the shower. Look for your invitations in the mail"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 03:34:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think JB and Mary blamed JLs "lack of faith in God" for his alcoholism</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 11:49:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>My guess is that they have had a miserable childhood/life and they view marriage as "what will cure them" and that fails because no man or woman can undo a bad childhood/make someone happy, so they turn to their kids. Their babies are unconditionally in love with them at first because they need them. But as they grow a mother will stomp out all forms of independence. A DIL or SIL comes along and "steals them" which sends MIL in a rage to see someone else happy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 12:24:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>The problem is that women feel that their children's love should be on demand like that. My dad always told me "Children are all tiny adults" meaning that they weren't puppies who are loyal to a fault, they arent perfect, they aren't robots, and their "job" was to grow up and leave and his job was to make sure I was ready and able to leave and to provide for himself so I didn't have to "keep him" in his old age and I could provide for my children. My Mom asked which room was hers when I bought my house. . . . . .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 12:26:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>DD won't want to be around Grandma. You already won that war.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 12:30:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have always found it strange how our society picks what is "Boy" and what is "girl" clothes...like honestly just about all of my tee shirts are men's smalls. Nobody can tell. And those bullies are probably losers now lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 12:31:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. Or she wants to use the LGBTQ community to justify assigning her grandchild the gender SHE wanted because "I wanted a granddaughter not grandson!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 12:33:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Think of how sick this is. You guys.... Trans children's acceptance is a war that society is fighting right now. They have been bullied and hurt for years..... This bitch wants to piggyback on their struggle to make her "grandbaby sex disappointment" go away so she can have her "yay granddaughter!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 12:37:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>My husband barked at her "granny pod" Honestly my mother is needy but only a sometimes if not occassionally no mother. As the marriage went on one day out of the blue my husband says to me "Your mother has treated me far better than my mother has you. If we ever *had* to I wouldn't mind having her live with us. She always comes over and helps, she never says anything awful about us to each other, and she's supportive." I don't think it will ever happen but I know that speaks volumes of how its possible to express to your kids that you miss them/are lonely without tearing their spouce or marriage apart.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 12:44:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not only all the pockets....but DEEP pockets to fit cell phones...and all my stuff.... I just had a mini little tingle of delight run down my spine. Helpful tip you can purchase mens jeans and have the crotch part tailored. If you don't you look like you have a tiny erect penis from the way the fabric gathers LOL. I have a friend...no lie... Her boobs are literally the size of 2 basket balls and she is a tall woman but not fat (think Amazonian). She gets her clothing from mens big and tall and gets everything tailored. She always looks classy and feminine because they take the shirts in at the waist and they redo the crotch piece a bit. Its a little expensive but she buys quality clothing that lasts years....oh and another gripe men's clothing lasts SO MUCH LONGER than women's!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 12:46:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like she was pissed he was growing up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 13:22:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I called this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 22:28:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Adjust the time to be 1 hour later than everyone else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 22:29:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. Pretend you cannot hear either one of them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 01:23:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love how Grandma is doing the work for you, your daughter hates her and you don't even have to lift a finger! And GREAT job calling her out in front of all those people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 01:46:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a BIG fan of answering stupid texts like this hours if not days later. Also "Thinking of you in Harry Potter land" for an example could have been handled like this "Why?" "Because you like Harry Potter" "I'm not a big fan. Glad you are having fun." This way you show her she doesn't "know" you she can't "get to you" and she doesn't have you "on demand" to feed her attention seeking behaviors.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 03:04:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Outstanding</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 03:06:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Send a book about "Passive Aggressive In laws"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 03:07:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Welcome to her Borg, Incubator</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 03:09:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck with her. Have her feel the baby bump and brag how hard and how much the baby kicks when *YOUR* mom feels the bump. Every little thing she gets you as a gift thank her then talk about the one *your mom* got. Make sure you brag about how wonderful your mother was growing up periodically. Ok. Constantly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 03:09:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not even joking</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 03:10:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly what did your husband do? He should have picked up the telephone and demanded an apology for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 03:12:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Derrick and Jill look like camera crew that wandered into the shot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 03:15:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your MIL has shown you her weak spot by saying " I want to be favorite " that right there was your hint to kiss her ass. Noooooopppppeee! Do the total opposite. To everyone else it looks like "Oh shes making conversation about her great mom she loves." To MIL it drives a big ass fuck you to her violating your boundaries. Also ANY information she "discovers" about your pregnancy reply with "I guess I should have told you about it a week ago when I told *my* mom."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 03:16:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Send her a book about cutting off toxic people</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 04:16:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>"He *has* a job. Pleasing his master. Sexual. Master. *ME*."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 13:09:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>"We were too busy fucking."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 13:17:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Report her threats</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 13:23:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>If she hit him then you could always report to the police and say you are in fear for your safety and the baby's safety</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 13:29:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would actually question if she isn't mean. She was trying to plant a narrative for your man to doubt you and paint you as cheating on him with a woman. If she pulls shit like this again *"Thanks! BFF will love this. Boyfriend can't keep up with both of us. This will help."*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 13:30:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I literally have my favorite toy and blankie in a burn proof box</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 13:34:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not to defend her but for science was she a rural American? I ask because my dads abusive parents grew up in rural America and had similar stories. They viewed things like this as "toughening kids up" Abuse back then was rampant because that generation of parents had survived the Great Depression and World War II and were in fear of it reoccurring so they felt that they had to toughen kids up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 13:37:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Name it "Forgiveness" or "Unity Between Man amd Wife" I have to ask if its common in your culture to name homes because that's really really beautiful!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 13:42:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now you know not to waste words or expect sympathy from her. Now you know to let your actions speak If she takes your stuff out, put it back. If she leaves your food in the fridge leave hers on the counter tops and put yours back where it was. She is *counting on you* talking about things with her so she can twist and manipulate your words. Don't give her anything to pick apart. Just let your actions mirror hers. Let her get upset so when she inevitably flips out you can flip the script "MIL you're so *irrational*" It sucks but sometimes tasting their own medicine is how they know not to fuck with you/shows them you arent going to dance to the tune they're playing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 13:44:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mom was probably terrified of GM so she had to throw that in there so she didn't get the wrath of GM for "losing the ring"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 13:47:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not to defend her OP but I would be scsred to death about watching twin babies on my own too....but of course this would be for the babies health...because I'm a caring woman I am suspicious if your MIL is asking for a window into your routine so she can pick it apart and criticize you. Honestly use your "mom of twin status" to brag up your parenting skills so at the very least your MIL can't say "I was a better mom" because you forever have the right to say "Well I raised TWINS" For some reason this matters to petty bitches.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 13:47:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Maybe you can watch them once they are old enough" Don't give her and old enough age  #128520; #128520;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 13:53:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL keep doing exactly what you're doing. Question her question her question her. She's making an ass out of herself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 14:26:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was about to suggest blinking at her, standing up, and dumping it right in the trash and walking away</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 15:02:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe you. Out of respect I won't even try to guess who you are. Your husband is FAMOUS and paparazzi is evil. Nobody believes any of it here in normal world. If rumors swirl send photos of you and your husband looking blissfully in love to paparazzi to negate the effects. OR you could sell your story of his mother ruining yout life....Ohhh people would LOVE that juicy shit and it would shut her up for-ever!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 15:04:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Text her "I can see why you hate it butthankfully you will never be invited to stay."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 15:06:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Give the money back/mail the ripped check up with a note : "Thank you but I don't like presents that have conditions or strings attached."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 15:08:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was so YOUR MIL can "feed" re:Be a mother to your baby. That's fucking sick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 15:15:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any woman who implies you cheat on your husband is up to no good. I would be very cautious assuming she is just stupid. I think she's smarter than you think and is playing dumb so your boyfriend cares for her (pays attention to her) and she can get away with passive aggressive shit like this. She did this intentionally to pull him away from the party, to hurt your feelings, and to try to cause doubt in your boyfriends mind. Her "me so stupid" act is just that. Her reward was your boyfriends attention. She was rewarded by your boyfriend leaving the party to take her home. So she got 1 on 1 time with him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 16:01:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't mean it to be petty. I mean it to fight fire with fire and show MIL that you aren't playing games.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 16:36:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nutella is so tasty though. Not at all like sex toy grossness. Though I blame nutella on my weight gain so probably better off if you're not going to eat it  #128526;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 17:10:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's awesome! Yea an acronym of her her husband and other son is disgusting. How about an acronym of the two of YOUR names OR an acronym of your surname and his surname?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 17:13:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally go ANYWHERE but her place for thanksgiving.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 17:14:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea that part where you say "She might not seem that bad" She sounds like a MONSTER to ME.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 18:18:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why keep it local when you can go NATIONAL?!?!?!? I remember a few years back Blake Lively s mother in law was exposed for being a Just No in the tabloids because she was pissy that she was young (and lets be honesty young AND hot) and now every photo OP you can practically hear her MIL kissing Blake Livelys ass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 20:16:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even if your mom *doesn't know*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 20:19:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dad's response was always *"What does it matter what I think? You're the one who has to live with him....."*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 20:30:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Allow me to fundy translate: "Fuck no. I have too many but don't want to say that In case I get another one I don't want it to feel unloved."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 20:39:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are Chip and Joanna Gaines fundy?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 20:43:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>So she can make bridesmaids dresses too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 20:46:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>*"I didn't say I didn't trust you. Ive asked you to let me know if my daughter is okay. If you insist on putting words in my mouth then we are turning around coming home and you'll never have to worry about what I think about your babysitting skills again."* *"Well MIL I don't like YOU because you are sneaky manipulative and an asshole."*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 21:01:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Smart to keep ALL texts/emails to show your husband. The more you do that the more he will see this is a *her* thing. Here is how you win against this woman: Maintain your wide eyed innocence with your husband. By getting upset you give *him* something to focus on other than his mother. "Husband, it *hurts* me *so much* that your mother would accuse me of such a thing." ECT. This rips down your MILs sneakiness and collapses her triangulations. Better yet....Let her lie to him in front of you like that and *wait" to show her the text mesages while you are in front of her and DH. Actually sit down for a "discussion" with them, let her dish out her tirade then innocently present the texts and ask "Could you show me which one you are referring to?" Watch her CBF. Watch them try to dance their way out of that. By playing innocent you allow MIL to do this sort of thing more often, and the more often the more doubt DH will have. And next time she gets drunk like that press "record" on your cell phone to play back to him and act all hurt and sad by her words. Act like you *want* her to like you but secretly give 0 fucks.  #128522; hope this helps</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 21:05:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You accidently gave her a "heads up" by discussing it with DH first (which was the right thing to do by normal people standards but we are dealing with an abnormal). Next time say "Why don't *we* talk about this with her...I just feel *so bad*. Let her have the floor and accuse you of these things *then* show him the text messages while she's sitting there all smug thinking she won and ask "Which text did I tell you that?" If you catch her off guard she won't have time to come up with a response likr that.  #128520; #128013; #128128; #128520; #128013; #128128;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 21:08:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>*"Mom. I know you care about me a lot but next time you have a concern please come to me, not my husband."*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 22:26:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I would have preferred him ask my dad, looking back on it, but at the time it just seemed silly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 22:28:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe add on "I wouldn't want him to worry about me" to soften it if she is easily offended There is a time and a place to be direct and blunt but occasional softening of blows I think makes those times of being harder more effective.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 22:52:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need to speak to BIL and SIL. They need to be aware how she speaks about her granddaughter for her protection. This type of negativity can severely damaged your niece and BIL and SIL need to be made aware of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 22:54:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>The police. That way they have a record in case she ever does lay hands on you. Men get royally fucked in domestic situations. If they have a record they will see that she has threatened you in the past if you ever need to call them or she makes a false report against you in the future</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 22:57:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I may...I have vivid memories of my Just No Grandma doing this to me. I would quickly forget about her sleepovers on the car ride home with the promise of a pillow fort popcorn and a movie with my mom. But for real I would sit that bitch down and tell her you are the mom he is the dad and if she does that again that's the last she sees grandkids for 6 months.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:50:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes you go to the department and express you would like to report your MIL is threatening you. In my experience they may press charges. If you feel you are not at that stage yet then you can start a folder on your desktop with saved photos of any texts she sends time and date them. If she ever attacks you do NOT fight back. Run. If you are the one with marks on you and she has none they are more likely to believe YOU over her, especially if you have a record of the threatening texts. You could also report her to Children and Youth Services and explain you don't feel your child is safe around her due to her threats. A counselor there may be a better first step to build your credibility should you ever have a false allegation made against you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:50:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>And typically arrest records are public.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:51:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>WOW</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 01:28:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I think it is what is best for our relationship."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 01:36:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>When she tries to hold him again say "I am sorry but I need you to change clothing first. Also I'm going to have to watch you wash your hands and brush your teeth." If she is reasonable and really wants to hold her grandson she should oblige. If she throws a fit hit her with: "If you truly love my son, you will do as I ask." If she says you're being rediculous say "So are you. You are well aware of the health affects of 2nd hand smoke." Throw every accusation back at her. Calmly. Visualize your baby's lungs vs your frustration with her when speaking to her to maintain an inner deep Zen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 01:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your girlfriend needs individual counseling. That's not good for her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 01:42:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hell yea. My kind of people. I would have trolled her and act like the biggest hillbilly you know. Cowboy boots...say "ain't" a lot...ect Bragged about buying shotguns for baby's first present....LOL.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 01:47:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would demand an apology for the appalling things she has said about you and an apology for your mother who had to hear people speak so unkindly about her daughter. What's going to happen when you have mixed race babies? Racial slurs, stereotypes...comments about "their kind". Edited to add you need to have a sit down with her and let her know you know. And your husband needs to back you 100 percent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 03:02:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like to use my powers for good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 13:06:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm actually impressed by her honesty...even if its wearing a fundy veil.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 13:19:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your mother is a textbook narcissist. Get a therapist for yourself to process all of this. And for your sake put some distance between you and her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 13:22:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>All I can say is my mother did this to my sister and I and my brother waa allowed to do so much. I th I think some moms like to bully daughters in the form of competing with them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 13:25:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>That mug that says "Have a Nice Day" then as you tip it up to drink from it it's a middle finger on the bottom...because its passive aggressive like her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 13:39:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's my question: I'm wondering if they sense you are "hiding" a pregnancy from them *(you're not obligated to tell them of course but this would be their mindset if they are a bunch of justnos)* and they're scared the reason you haven't told them yet is because they aren't as "close" to you as they thought so they are trying to force a relationship/trick you into telling them...if this complaint of not talking often enough is a new one. What are the odds while FIL was over that he saw a pregnancy book or a pregnancy website left open on a browser or a bottle of prenatal vitamins? Do you "look" pregnant? You said you were tired FIL might have noticed and be suspicious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 13:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your husband lost his parents they day they picked the bottle over him. Good on you protecting your children like that Next time you see she's DUI then call the cops and explain she does this all the tume and you're afraid she needs help. A few days drying out in county might save her life. If she chooses to kill herself, which is what she is doing get your husband in counseling so he's alright. Be prepared for a flying monkey or 2 telling you to now let grandpa see the kids because you killed her by not letting her see her grandbaybiezzz *eye roll*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 13:47:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>She had YDS before he passed? I'm tempted to wonder what MIL did in those 3 days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 13:48:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ohhh I would have made sure that bib got lost in the wrapping paper trash. Fuck that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 13:54:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would say: "I heard the 'gay gene' comes from the mothers mother's side and skips a generation." Then tick off "gay" things you have noticed about her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:00:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why do these MILs think its a good idea to call DIL's Mother's? Like do you really think the mother is going to side with you, a total stranger, or her own daughter that she gave birth to and raised? I'm trying to envision a scenario where my blood relative's MIL calls me to try to get me to side with her over something and I just laugh and laugh. Like you really think you're going to sway me? The only response I could think of to that situation would be "Quit causing problems" and hanging up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:04:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think if the show ended tomorrow we would see who they really are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:06:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I cannot IMAGINE giving my MIL a front row seat to my vagina. Ew.Ew.Ew.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:07:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would have been tempted to reply *"Wow. That's really really disgusting that you couldn't give a husband and wife privacy during the birth of their child. You are a gross bitch."*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:08:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Saaaaaame</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:09:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah...that makes 0 sense to me Plus...aren't they going to DIE before the child is old enough to NEED guidance?!?!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:16:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a skinned down version of that horror!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:17:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>*pulls up popcorn and anticipates passive aggressive comments*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:18:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look Isreal in the car seat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:19:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine made me learn and I was making dresses for myself at age 10</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:20:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Starting the buddy system young</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:28:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>...that seatbelt carseat thing....omg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:29:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jill's midwife training was a fucking joke as evidenced in the footage of the show. These people don't believe in mental health issues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:31:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're forgetting Tabitha married a convicted rapist</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:44:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. "I could never disrespect my own mother like that." Is another good one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:46:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's not a coincidence that you're not white and she's saying you're "beneath" him. That's racist as fuck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:56:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's a lying liar who lies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:57:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>You were probably so overwhelemed because people like her are sooo good at being sneaky and manipulative you never see it coming.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 15:01:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>So many many good points in this post</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 15:03:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm right there with you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 15:09:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>HA!! LOVE IT. When pestered about it I think I'm going to say "I used it to pay the neighbor boy to mow my lawn."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 15:17:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Lying is a sin" "Let no curde joking be found among you" that's in the New Testament "I would like to come with you to church." Lecture her congregation on the evils of lying and joking about beating your wife.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 15:17:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also have a sit down with her and he preacher and ask if this is what they teach in their church</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 15:51:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think Sam escaped the car seat and now they can't find him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 15:53:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I say this all the time Happiness is the best revenge And you do more damage by NOT sinking to their level</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 15:59:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holee Molee your mother had you sent to Rikers. Holee Molee. I hope you don't speak to her anymore. Rikers. Holee Molee.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 16:00:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for sharing this. My blood pressure needed that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 16:18:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would make it my personal mission to prove that is false</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 16:20:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Be extra careful. Do they know anyone in your doctors office or at the store you purchased a pregnancy test? The pharmacy that you fill your prescription? JustNos can be VERY connected.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 16:20:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL even BETTER.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 16:27:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>If we were to have a tossing match really its no shock. Jinger and Jeremy are *marketable* Jill and Derek are a trainwreak.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 16:35:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would link this reddit as a reply to her Facebook along with several articles about how tactless the MIL is being.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 16:37:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good good. "But watch out for the flying monkeys because they are everywhere."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 16:38:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like BIL should come live with you guys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 16:46:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wtf are "god parents"? I was protestant and we never had this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 16:47:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>If someone is talking down about you they are acknowledging that you are above them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 16:49:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>*but it MIGHT be twins*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 16:50:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe they hired a handmaid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 23:47:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can report her for harassment. And if you WERE a drunk you would be fatter not thinner.....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 23:47:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>OfMissionaries</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 23:50:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>*THEY RUN IN THE FAMILY*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 23:51:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh didn't see your response I posted the same thing haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 23:52:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>What you do is write down the time date and location. Send her a "Do NOT contact me" email text ect. If she keeps contacting you then you can go to the cops usually.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 23:53:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alternate Caption: "2 Flew Over the Duggar Nest"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 23:58:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are welcome. It might be a good idea to consult with your divorce lawyer or local police for better more accurate info. You can walk into a station and ask to speak to someone. Police log every report/complaint. By doing such you establish a pattern which becomes evidence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 00:00:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now you know why Amazon sells undercover flasks. I recommend the sunscreen tube</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 00:05:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Redditsilver!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 00:07:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ive never read something so beautiful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 00:55:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>No he got out of the seat and now they don't recognize him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 00:57:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because Blessed Be The Self Tanner!!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 00:59:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I know this is your first time as a Grandma....but MY grandma never allowed us to act like this. Thats why we still visit her."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 01:05:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blessed Be The Naked Fruit Cake</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 01:55:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everytime she says about this being "Your first baby" respond with "Advice only works if you ask for it."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 01:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh come now. These would be a smash hit in the hipster community</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 01:56:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that is the light reflecting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 01:57:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>why is Jinger smiling so unnaturally in her wedding photos? She doesn't smile like that in other photos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 01:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>In a yard sale outfit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 02:03:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>The part where you ask what she used in the bathroom because it smells nice... Omg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 02:03:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah ha! Attempted highlights. I see them now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 02:03:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Time to send nudes. Of other men.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 02:52:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>The hair seemed to be a mixture of excessive product for the wrong purpose (like max hold hair spray for curls vs straightening balm), a lack of clarifying shampoo to remove product build up, no heat protectant, no conditioner or excessive conditioner, and improper sized straightener. I remember her having a large paddle when a smaller one would have worked better to get closer to the scalp and been easier to maneuver with her type of curls.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 02:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jeremy admitted somewhere that after seeing *this video* that's what made him like her. Jessa has spoke openly about how she arranged this match. Ben and Jeremy were close and Ben would know what Jeremy would want in a woman. I am wondering if this was an act for Jeremy's benefit as others have speculated before Jinger is more manipulative than we think....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 03:03:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are usually community centers that help people find jobs. You and your husband should go to one of those and speak to a career counselor. At the very least a 16 hour shift at McDonalds beats dealing with this loon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 03:05:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love roasted sweet corn. Tell MIL everytime she says she's allergic "Good! More for me! I am lucky to have a MIL who is allergic to everything I like." She wants you to "jump for her" and bend over backwards to make her special foods is all. Show her you won't and it will stop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 03:06:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even to get out of the house for a few hours, maybe consider 2 jobs? I had 3 at one point...not because I needed the money but because I needed to get out of the house and away from my JustNo sister.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 03:45:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would henceforth send images of male anatomy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 03:51:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>The moment she speaks something cruel you speak something worse. Let her run to your husband, let your husband see how much worse it is when he does not deal with his mother and leaves you to fend alone. Right now in his mind you are the lesser of the two evils so he sends her your way so he doesnt have to deal with her. You send her right back in narc tears and narc rage and let husband deal with the fallout 100 percent. If he tries to fight you say something he would say right back "Well, you know this is just how your mother is." And walk away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 03:52:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love that you stole it and threw it away</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 03:55:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was snarking too. It looks like she attempted highlights</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 03:57:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can picture them literally just shampooing because conditioner is expensive...or worse just bar soap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:00:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't live in fear. Says me who still runs from Jason Voorhees when I have to pee at 2am</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:01:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is to show your husband you are not taking his moms shit. He is using you as a shield so he doesnt have to stand up to her. If by putting her in your path you "cause problems" then he will stop doing this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:11:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. Its late. I am drunk...someone explain</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:14:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there a name that means "Fuck you MIL" but also can mean something else?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:17:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eating is the only thing you look forward to after kids when you're religious and can't drink or do the jiggy jiggy for fear it will result in a baby. #OR MAYBE TWINS BECAUSE IT RUNS IN THE FAMILY YA KNOW!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:19:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn. How about Palace of DH</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:19:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want one of these. Birds not thigh things</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:20:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. My dirty mind took that someplace else entirely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:23:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Austin wants a beer. He doesnt know it because he is too holy for the vile drink but that man wants BOOZE. Fuck I want booze after watching THAT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:24:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>At this point Sam is going to grow up and look like a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle but instead of a shell its a carseat. Cowabunga Dudes!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:24:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aaaand I want one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:29:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>That face you have. I have it too. Once at a department store I had a stranger approach me to help him pick out an outfit for a first date The second time an old man had me help him pick out a gift for his wife Third time I don't remember what happened but its always strangers seek me out. Ive held sobbing strangers in parking lots. It can be a bitch of a curse in the form of coworkers obsessed with you, and BSC strangers like this woman. Stay strong sister.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:30:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm glad I am not alone in my ickiness. I blame the rap music.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:31:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jeremy has his eyes closed and clicking his heels saying "there is no place like Laredo...there is no place like Laredo."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:31:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jinger says "Fuck OFF bitch don't drag me into your weird shit!!!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:32:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blanket Training is so last season. Car Seat Training is the in thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:34:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I raised a few of these. One got full grown still thought I was it's mama and ran across the barnyard to lick me 400 pounds later. If you want to know what it feels like to be loved on by a full grown cow go to the department store, buy a sheet of sandpaper, soak it in wet grass and methane then drag it from your cheek down to your hip. We ate him. Yes I feel like shit about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:36:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can tell they have no fucking clue what to do with that kid. Im not going to diagnose him...but what if he has mental delays due to the traumatic birth and rather than give him a good environment they just strap him down like that? Or what if they just suck as parents?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:36:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>DILs Castle Hahahahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:38:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because in their culture she may not find anyone as rich as daddy and babysitting little siblings is cheap to live in a mansion and have your own garden vs marrying some broke ads who wants your legs spread and your mouth shut</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:39:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>He was something. Bottle fed him and raised him. He used to prance and run.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:40:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup right here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:40:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Respond like this: *"No"*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:41:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just would like to know the story behind this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:51:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why? Don't suppress it. Fuck them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:51:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Report her for a HIPPA violation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:55:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>"DILs *Fortress*"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:56:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Obviously Rome wasn't built in a day. So just keep ignoring them ans venting to us in the meantime.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:56:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know you make a damn good point...there goes all my 2 minutes of speculation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 11:59:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 12:00:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never knew that. Sorry to hear about your dad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 12:01:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who of the 19 is the fiddler? Just curious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 13:32:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>What you do is you whip out the old Catholic Bible and start memorizing what it says. Every time that she slanders or gossips quote the verse about it. There is a verse about "older women being charged with teaching younger women and not being gossips. Quote the one about busybodies. Do this in front of an audience. There is nothing more powerful than using someone's own bullshit against them. Especially as she perceives herself as the ultimate authority spiritually you will also "look like" you know *more* than her. There is no way she cannot agree with you without looking like an idiot Example: "They say so and so had a baby that wasnt hers" You "The Bible (in the book the verse) says 'refrain from gossip as such does not belong in our church. The church is made up of all of us." (I paraphrased but you know how to Google scripture) Watch her try to twist it. Google some more and quote some more. Keep holding her to the ground with that Bible she weaponizes. Ive used this so many times on people who use the Bible to hurt others. When you cant get her to shut up quite the verses about fools keeping their tounge and sniff about how God will separate the true believers from the non. I so wish I could be an ear piece for you. I'm not even Catholic and I bet you and a margarita I know more about that book than she does.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 13:32:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is the "jaw"? I must know</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 13:36:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>To a Just No this is an invitation to keep causing pain so be careful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 13:38:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you have no witnesses and leave no marks....I'm kidding</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 13:39:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ew! Ew! Ew!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 13:39:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aaaahhh! Inbreeding and strict religion seems to go hand in hand</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 13:46:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are trying to make you doubt your experience as a mom. Here is how you flip THAT script: "Look. I know this is your *first* time being a grandmother/great grandmother so you need to just relax enjoy your grandchild and let the parenting up to me and my doctor, the expert." "My DOCTOR has helped raise 100s of babies...youve only raised 3? Yeah I'm going to go with my DOCTOR'S opinion." "I know youre old and forget things so let me remind you they've changed since you've been a parent." "That's the way things *used* to be done." And if they say "My son your husband is fine." Start rattling off all her deficiencies he told you about her parenting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 13:47:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right here. Don't ever let her alone with the baby even to pee.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 13:48:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is no way you can set boundaries with this woman. She will use your health issues as a reason to shove you aside and take over your child.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 13:54:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Start standing up to this bitch. I have panic attacks too but boold on conflict helped me greatly. The more you stand up to her the faster she will stop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 17:26:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Plus words hurt soooo much worse</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 17:29:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you want to shut her up: "You were a shit mother so I don't want your input."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 17:30:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea it confused me too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 17:35:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Id have a friend pretend to be a doctor lab coat and everything and swing by for a visit and criticize all grandma's "suggestions"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 17:36:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hers looks purposefully unnatural. And she has this same smile in a lot od her wedding photos</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 17:42:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>"You'll have years to hear it because she already hates you. I imagine for awhile every visit will be like this."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 17:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>*"Lesbians are also the least likely of people to be around abusive old bitches or bring their grandbabies to see them."*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 22:31:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks like she intentionally smiled this way as in in her mind she was picturing it looked different than what it does.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 22:33:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm protestant so I have never heard of this but it sounds medieval</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 22:34:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>A fake positive pregnancy test then  #128520; #128520;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 22:35:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I do take care of him. Just not in the ways you are thinking." Watch her face</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 22:39:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>You tell them what you told us Sadly what you are experiencing is common. Many people will take your side, many more than you realise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 22:42:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>What I did is I improved my own mental emotional spiritual and physical health by taking gym classes and reading books. Put my energy into self improvement and conquering my own demons vs put my energy into hating/fearing her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 22:44:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love that the fish dress is a thing on this forum</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 22:59:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tread lightly because you just gave her ammunition to use against you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:00:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Start hitting "record" on your cell phone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:01:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought the Bible was enough!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:03:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>People who literally built a television show around being frugal don't wear Apple ones every day!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:04:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>The downvoting on this sub is insane and so random.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:05:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>What if this is an actual maternity ward gown and they're delaying the birth announcement for the premiere? Some fancier hospitals have fancier looking gowns like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:08:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>She looks great but that looks downright painful. That bump must feel like it weighs 50 pounds in the heat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:08:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>OfBabe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:11:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>C Section babies have bigger flatter heads...leave our kind alone we cant help it LOL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Huh. Josiah can smile</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:12:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>DILLY DILLY!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:13:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>People call my husband Mr Myfirst Mylast because I'm a rather butch straight girl...does that count?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:14:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my god. That's so awful to think about isnt it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:15:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry you went through that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:15:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like transgender youth UGH to the thought of skeevy Derrick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:17:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You literally made the last 20 years of my life make so much more sense. I'm astonished I have lived this long without knowing this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:17:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>They lied to you. I STILL have a flat head. Balancing books was waaayyy too easy in manners class.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:19:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Joy looks like her mother in law with dark hair and glasses. . . .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:35:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blessed be the apple watches</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 01:20:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>My head is spinning but I plan to Google more. This is quite eye opening</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 01:21:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's alright. I plan to read into this more</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 01:23:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I literally make Abe Lincoln shout "OUCH" the way I pinch pennies in 4ths. And I do what I can to be minimalist in my Earthly possessions because I think having too much takes it from someone who needs it and dampens our spirits</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 01:26:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Call the cops the second he steps foot on your property. One of the conditions of sex offender registry is no contact with minors.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 01:30:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I prefer debt free virgin men with no tats...does this make me a bad person?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 02:43:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blessed be the clean seed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 02:44:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didnt think the baby shower one had buttons</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 02:46:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm looking in a mirror and its not lying to me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 02:46:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Should I tell him the blow job is from you as well?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 02:48:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was a former fundy and they would open credit cards for small purchases to build credit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 02:49:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Bridge Burner" is my superhero name. I try to use my powers for good though I do loose sleep over what I post on this forum sometimes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 02:53:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pardon my ignorance but is "Dutch Courage" a euphemism for alcohol?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 02:56:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have her figured out. She was super jealous. Now everytime she calls for a visit short notice say: "I am sorry but I already have something written in that pretty day planner you got me. We will have to pick another day!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 02:56:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's so cute</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 03:03:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I LOVE it! And now I want more Australian sayings! More! More I say as I clap my hands in glee</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 03:04:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you imagine that old wrinkled contorted face fumbling for her pearls to clutch?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 03:04:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I need therapy sometimes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 03:08:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>For your sake I'm going to share a little of my own experience. My mom went no contact with her mom when I was 5. I didn't miss her and I don't. Kids don't need that big loving family Hollywood pushes. They DO need a great mom like you. Keep up the good work. What helped MY mom, and you dont have to do this, but she adopted an older woman at our church who was a maternal figure to her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 03:08:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I say that all the time in rural America My favorite is when I say "That dog don't hunt" people have no clue what it means</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 03:09:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I scare myself with the darkness. I think its from living for so long as a doormat that I've given up and just say awful shit now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 03:14:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Answer a fool according to his own folly lest he be wise in his own eyes" that's in the Bible...and I'm probably taking it out of context.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 03:15:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I'm no expert" Oh Jill. Sweetie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:17:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>As long as you love that baby you are doing things right. That baby will become a teen and an adult. No matter how much you protect them they will make mistakes they will mess up. Children are given to us to teach us lessons. Good lessons. Not punishment for our own mistakes. Lessons on love and lessons to learn about ourselves. Never blame yourself for anything. Your job is to love that baby and guide that baby. That baby will be a teen and an adult that needs your love and guidance not for you to be kicking yourself. Don't fall into the temptation of self loathing. Keep treating yourself with the samw love you treat your child.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:20:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>We were all conditioned to take that high road but that high road leads down to a doormat. When someone is abusing you like this there is no excuse for it. None. Anyone who will abuse an adult will abuse a child. There is no high road when it comes to protecting your children. We women are scapegoats for society. We are hormonal and crazy and whatever. No. We are too silent. We take these "high roads" and subject ourselves to this type of social abuse and we need to be the last generation that does this. You don't have to be an asshole but you can be truthful as hell because the truth hurts worse than any insult.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:21:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imagine this then; "MIL. Could I borrow an outfit? Husband and I like to role play in the bedroom."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:22:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Its not the size of the dog in the fight but the size of the fight in the dog."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:22:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:24:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>This has made me realize how bad its going to be for Duggar Grandkids. It was all fun and games when they were babies but now they will be denied proper education as well thanks to the parents.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:27:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>You vent away. Let it out. You don't have to do this but one thing that helped me is envisioning I was holding a rope that was attached to someone else's approval of me. In my case it was my sister. I envision myself physically dropping the rope and walking away from the burden everytime I am around her and I know she will say something that is meant to hurt me. It takes practice but it works. "I am worth more than this. I deserve love peace and joy" is a good mantra to rehearse before bed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:27:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>A good book to read is called You Can Heal Your Life by Louise Hay. It really put things in perspective for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:29:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I'm not willing to expose my chidlren to abuse. My children's mental emotional and physical health strongly outweigh my desire to make your mommy feel good."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:30:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>It emphasizes self love and forgiveness to heal yourself instead of to rugsweep abuse and make nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:37:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it will open with a scene from Josiah and Lauren moving away. Josiah will be trying to run away from the compound but Lauren will have her long veil wrapped around his neck to keep him in check. Jessa will be acting smug as though she is the authority on marriage. And she will say Lauren might have twins. We will see much boring Baaaaabbee footage from a very lame baby shower. John David will be snarky as hell because he knows he is on his way out. Abbie will disappoint us with her Fundyliciousness. Michelle will fucking hate her and be jealous as fuck. Kendra will babble and giggle about the baby. Joy will be pregnant. Austin's dad will say something with an accent like "Dagum Anothern' ? Praise the Lawrd!" Her mother in law will put her fat foot in her mouth again. Josiah and Lauren have a creepy as fuck honeymoon. Josie will sing. A kid we don't even know will suddenly be heavily promoted for a courtship announcement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:37:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>This lady is a survivor of childhood abuse this is a must read for you!!! Good luck on your journey I think all of us have gone through this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 05:00:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>A good book is called nice girl Syndrom</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 05:02:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>On top of that they have no access to credit or outside jobs. They will marry within the cult circle. Israel and Sam will be raised to think they are better than the people Jill and Derrick minister to but in the same token be told they must love them. . .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 05:37:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>The top and back are flat Seriously. Do I need to upload a photo for you lot or what?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 05:39:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>What KILLS me is this is a woman writing this about other women.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 05:43:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so glad you are no contact. I've done martial arts my whole life. I would have dislocated her arm. Good luck proving lil ol ME did that, Bitsy you're old and slipped in the fucking shower like old people do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 06:26:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>And you're a doctor? Nurse?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 06:30:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. Head shape has nothing to do with c sections. . .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 06:31:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>"May the bridges that I burn light my path"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 11:44:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess if you turn back around? Idk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 11:46:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It means that what someone is saying makes no sense or is suspicious. "He said he was late because he had car trouble, but that dog don't hunt."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 13:14:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friend had a narc father. On his death bead he practically ripped his arm off and told him how ashamed he was of him. Now he lives with that final memory of dear old dad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 13:40:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I grew up with "Your gonna have to tie a bone around your neck for a dog to come near you" Meaning ugly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 17:48:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can neighbor cop stand guard at the maternity ward?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 22:28:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dont be afraid to ask a friend to be your backup.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 22:29:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you cross the bridge THEN burn it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 22:34:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Next time she says shit "God made me infertile because He knew an evil witch like you doesn't deserve grandbabies."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 22:38:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>"My experience was worse....women have babies all the time" OH GOOD! Then you understand a woman needs privacy and time to heal. Thank you for understanding you are such WONDERFUL grandparents we will see you in two weeks. See? You can play this game too. And win. Twist their delusion and throw it back at them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 03:38:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>To make yourself feel better go read all of our threads. Now you see what you are NOT missing! Now you have the opportunity to find someone who was taught healthy boundaries. Individual counseling would benefit you greatly after surviving your MIL.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 03:40:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>"MIL. I cannot allow you to hold the baby unless you return her to me when she cries. If you truly love this baby you will do what is best for her. And if you desire a good relationship with her as she grows you will respect ME. You may hold her for an hour but I have her ear 24-7. You can easliy be grandma-we-don't-like."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:13:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>"If you don't like it you don't hold her" When she gives you the "I raised X babies" then respond "Well this is MY baby and you will follow MY rules. If it becomes "Yourrr wifeee is meaannn" tell your husband " I asked her 3 times to do something and she told me she didn't csre about me or what I want that this was her baby and she will do what she wants." Even if she doesn't say that....her actions did.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:17:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Smart girl being fussy with cookware I had to replace cookware 3 times my first 2 years because it would get warped. I think I'm purchasing stainless steel everything in the future.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:20:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>In going to use your story for examples of dialogue BIL "Rabbit food" You "I thought it best to offer everyone a *healthy* option...in case anyone was trying to lose weight." Cue CBF. MIL "I knew it" You "I figured that night you were here and ripped the condom off of DH would be the night we conceived." This serves to get the attention off of her back to you. By saying something dumb like this people laugh at her and put their focus back on you. MIL telling you how to care for him. "You taught him how to be helpless. I'm teaching him how to be a man." Cue CBF</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:21:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just make sure to read the care manual. . . dont be like me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>"MIL. You look constipated. The bathroom is down the hall." "MIL you look unhappy" *let her say something stupid* "It must be hard choosing to be unhappy all the time."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:24:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you happen to have any friends that are buff heavily tatted or look Mob-y in a black suit have them "stop by" on her next visit in a group. Have one say "OP, we have some...business to discuss with you." And have him walk away with you She would shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:29:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Certain medications can cause old ladies to be miserable bitches too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:31:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whaaaat???</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:33:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Frame a few of DH for your room. And by a few I mean all the walls. If YOU frame them in "Your' room it gives mommy a kick in the ass because its las if to say "Since your mommy is mean I will love you, DH. Your mommy is awful. Let wife *your New mommy* (sick but this is how MIL thinks) make it aaaallll bettteerrr."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:36:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>After that you need to sit your hsuband down and explain that because she tried to *poison* you that she is no longer welcome in your home. I'm sorry I know we aren't supposed to say this but this would be an instant cut off for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:41:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would report this to a lawyer or police so that there is an open log. If she escalates you want dates and times and instances. Those cameras need to be focused on your fridge. Get her on camera tampering with your food. Record yourself telling her that you are allergic to citric acid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:43:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>My inner cheapskate is giggling and wringing my hands together with glee at the thought</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:54:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Troll: "Are you pregnant?" "Yes. With quadruplets." "So and such bought this place/is dating this girl I dont know what they were thinking...." "I heard they did it JUST to piss YOU off." "Where are you going?" "To Antarctica."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:56:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Next time, just start talking about pasta and cupcakes again when she mentions divorce.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 13:08:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally no amount of therapy would convince me this woman is safe to be around your son. When she threatens suicide roll your eyes at her and dial 911. If she texts you or calls you and says "I am going to end it." Immediately hang up and call 911. If you respond your words can be used against you. If she does go through with it police pull phone records and can time you down to the second to see how long it took you to call 911. Make it immediate so there is never a legal accusation against you that you waited on purpose. This wasn't to scare you but to make you aware of what I have seen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 23:22:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Watch a few episodes of Real Housewives of Atlanta for inspiration.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 23:25:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just made that up, to give OP ideas of what she could say</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 23:27:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. That's the effect of a statement such as this so when MIL has a fucked up thing to say OP will prove to her that she will go even lower.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 23:42:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>She didn't. I made it up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 02:19:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>To help you play nice: Stop resenting her for being a bad mother to your husband. You can't change it and her failures made your man the man that you love. This doesnt excuse or justify her failures, you just have to accept that as something you cannot change. As for the passive aggressive, no. You do not play nice. You play *fair*. Do not let her have a foothold by allowing her to be mean and just taking her abuse. I will use a common statement as an example: MIL: "MY kids never acted like THAT." You: "Really? How would you know how your kids acted, I was told you were never home." Or, if you want to take a baby step: "Considering I am not you and my kids are not your kids, it makes sense to me that they would act completely different. Oh, MIL! I feel bad you didn't know all chidlren were different....I guess your generation didnt have Google so this makes sense...."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 02:20:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or just dump whiskey or vodka in a glass of coke if you're a cheap lazy bum (Like ME)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 02:22:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make her earn her keep. Ask her to help. When she says "Im a guest" say "I thought we were faaaaaamily and faaaaamilyy helps out. Are you saying we aren't family?" And if she asks you to "get" her anything because you have the vagina yell loudly " HEY HUSBAND....YOUR MOM NEEDS TOWELS GET HER SOME!!!" don't put yourself in the position of being her mother or servant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 02:25:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Send her on fool's errands. Describe baby items that don't actually exist and have her scour the internet for them. "I need this golden diaper genie that has arms and makes a noise when its full. Yea I think Gerber makes one...."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 03:26:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Be prepared for her response. Some passive aggressive old women WILL escalate. "I meant that you're not good with money" "I meant that youre FAT" If she admits this state loudly "I think that is a terrible thing to say. I cannot IMAGINE being that unhappy all the time. I am concerned for you." Put it right back on her. Do not stand there holding the weight of her cruelty. Imagine she hands you a gift with a receipt where you can return it. Return it to her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 03:46:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell your husband the realities of childbirth. Mine just thought it was a woman in some pain snuggled up in a warm hosptial gown with her knees up with daddy holding her hand a blanket draped for modesty across her thighs and grandparents joyfully flitting back and forth asking excitedly "is it heeerrreee yettt?! Is it heeeerreee?!?" and then the woman after breathing heavy and saying "Oh golly me this hurts" and letting out 1 final scream magically a baby emerges. He honest to God had NO idea what birth can be. I Googled "birth gone wrong" and made him look at images and video footage. I explained how "unwanted stress can make birth longer harder and ' go wrong '... Like having a cruel invasive MIL present." His response was "I will stand in the fucking door to make sure you have the privacy you need."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 03:47:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>"MIL. This is MY baby, not yours. I will thank you to remember to call MY baby your 'grandchild'."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 03:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think DH needs to flip the fuck out on ole asshole mommy the moment she says something fucked up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 04:05:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know I'm not supposed to diagnose...but come ON....Stevie Wonder can see your mom has anxiety issues. Obviosly everyone else already said "Find a better sitter" and I agree. But if it means any thing she doesn't seem like a total fucking monster hell bent on ruining your life. You probably care about her a lot and it must drain you to worry like that. I would just encourage supervised visits here on out. You can be gentle about it too. Tell her you love that she loves your kid but you want her to be *grandma* not babysitter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 04:09:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Grandma called an ambulance 20 years ago to check on somebody. I would say mom and Grandma both feed off each other. Or they may have genetic anxiety issues. No judgement. My own family tree shakes like Chicken Little on a cloudy day...unfortunately the nuts didn't roll off and we hit every branch on the way down which is why we are ugly too. Okay I will stop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 04:22:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>The denial is so strong with the Just Nos. That's what makes toying with them o so funny. But please Reddit can I have a brief moment of vulnerability? I would be sad too if my daughter/son did a wedding like this... and I am Kid Rock level white trash. I own so much camo there are days you cant even see me if I walk outside...if I'm drunk I piss off my back porch....and I have been known to drink out of a garden hose. (Sorry...that was a lot...) But dammit when I got married I had a wedding dress and everything looked nice. I am so glad I have pretty pictures of my husband and I to look back on where we are not dressed like extras from East Bound And Down. And don't get me wrong I know one day if I am in that spot and my son marries a tee shirt girl my mouth will be clamped shut and I will sport the most non white tee shirt I can find in support of their decision.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 04:23:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Google some crazy traumatic shit for him to watch and you'll have one yourself  #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 04:25:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>What really did mine in was when I told him babies can tear the vaginal wall and ass cheeks on their way out sometimes ....I totally exaggerated and said "I might even need STAPLES in my VAGINA" He's STILL asking me "How is this possible. What can we do to prevent this, are you sure you even WANT kids? We can adopt...how about a dog?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 04:27:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>She needs a punctuation lesson. That's atrocious. I get that its the internet but come on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 04:30:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope they have gone into CIA witness protection level hiding and she no longer needs us. Kind of sort of hoping too that Gabhead rolled down a flight of steps and her head went "thunk thubk thunk" on every one of them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 04:34:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know this, as the end of my post says.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 12:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometimes I think we are hard on MILs but overall I think if they wouldn't act like assholes they would be able to tell us stuff. Like example instead of yanking babies off of mom asking "Could I hold the baby?" Like honesty manners go so far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 12:31:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why hello good to see ya</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 12:32:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not always, lets not scare OP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 12:34:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jeeze its like trying to keep up with Game of Thrones characters</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 13:48:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think we need more labels than BEC and Just No. I feel like MY MIL personally just reallyreallyreallyreallyreally wants grandkids....i dont blame her...but when she purposely tries to control MY life over it I have issues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 17:36:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 17:37:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your making a c section sound better......</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 17:37:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>True</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 17:40:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, you never want your baby near her again. Call the lawyer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 17:44:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Suggest your parents volunteer at a children's center, foster, or get jobs at a daycare.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 22:29:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>VAGINAL C Section?!?!?! Off to Google I go!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 22:43:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let me clarify: my expectation for all weddings is that there be some sort of "fancy" element to them because I LOVE wedding pictures. I used the white dress as a straight bride example. It doesn't have to be super expensive but I'm a sucker for the couple looking their best. I know...their choice...I also hate when people wear pjs to Wal-Mart but their body their choice. You reminded me of something....off topic but allow me to indulge in this memory: I adore when lesbian weddings involve tasteful "non white dress" wedding outfits. I swoon over a good suit on a lesbian bride. My FAVORITE thing I ever saw at a lesbian wedding is this girl wore kaki capris and a sexy pair of heels with tiny suspenders fitted around her boobs on top of a tucked in tailored to perfection button up top and had her hair braided into a faux hawk. Her wife wore a lacy white dress and looked underdressed standing next to the bride in the capris. Imagine...a pair of capris looked better than a freaking wedding dress thats how good this looked. If I have a gay/lesbian child and they have a wedding that involves tee shirts and jeans mama is stop gon' be psad. But mama's gonna keep her damn mouth shut too  #128521;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 22:48:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>She wanted you to do the gender reveal during FILs 40th so she could control it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 22:49:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>If she's a pissy bawl baby type don't tell her you are considering taking a relationship with "her babies" off the table. This will escalate her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 22:52:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like the woman does this to every one not just you and your partner. If thats so try these "MIL, it must really do a toll on your health to be so nasty all the time." Makes her realize she's not going to "get" to you and have any control over you. Which might shut her up Or just stand there smiling at her. Just smile the kind of smile that goes to your eyes and dont say anything. Like she's a joke. Ohhh they hate this so much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 22:52:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like the woman does this to every one not just you and your partner. If thats so try these "MIL, it must really do a toll on your health to be so nasty all the time." Makes her realize she's not going to "get" to you and have any control over you. Which might shut her up Or just stand there smiling at her. Just smile the kind of smile that goes to your eyes and dont say anything. Like she's a joke. Ohhh they hate this so much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 22:53:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like the woman does this to every one not just you and your partner. If thats so try these "MIL, it must really do a toll on your health to be so nasty all the time." Makes her realize she's not going to "get" to you and have any control over you. Which might shut her up Or just stand there smiling at her. Just smile the kind of smile that goes to your eyes and dont say anything. Like she's a joke. Ohhh they hate this so much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 23:22:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>God bless. That kid better cure cancer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 23:28:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just a caution, because I like you: returning insult for insult isn't always the most effective. Firstly if you are a kind sweet person and it takes you energy to come up with comebacks remember this woman has nothing but years of anger amd negativity inside of her to spout. She will win. Period. She can smell your weak points and knows things about you your own mother doesnt. Her type are crafty. Secondly by handing the situation back to her you avoid being drawn into this negative cycle. This woman wants you to be mean back so she can be a victim. "Must be hard being so critical" brings attention back to her which passive aggressives hate. The smiling and remaining silent avoids dumb pointless conversations with a passive aggressive person. They are vampires. If you give them no energy to suck they get dried out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 23:31:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL. I would have waived "bye bye gramma" and walked to the car with the baby.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 23:36:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another good one to do in these situations is to answer a question with a question "What crib did you get" "What kind of crib did my husband have as a baby?" Let her ramble "What cribs do you like?" Let her ramble then buy the one you were going to buy anyway. Sometimes, not always, sometimes all a JustNo wants is to feel validated. Sometimes if you let them talk and feel important for 5 minutes it shuts them up. Like I said this is a BIG sometimes. You know your MIL better than me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 23:36:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 23:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's fucking awesome. And that gives me hope my MIL won't want anything to do with my grown children</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 23:41:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope to one day be half the mother yours is. My stars!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 00:08:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>"MIL I feel disrespected by your insults and the way you treat me. I would like an apology." Is where I would start.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 02:39:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its for YOUR mental and emotional health as well as for your peace of mind. Ever hear the phrase " You Cant Kill What Is Dead Inside? " that's your MIL. Dead inside.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 02:40:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like to think of myself as Miss Piggy. Loving and kind to the people who matter but put you in your place and karate chop ya ass when need be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 02:55:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>.....I may or may not have read it......</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 12:11:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>You do a squat thing and bend a certain way and 1 hand the patio and 1 hand the shorts I'm awful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 12:12:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>You tune it out as they babble. I forgot to put that in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 12:21:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. Add extra charges. Make it stick so she isn't allowed out. Some states that's a felony and she will get state time vs county time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 12:24:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm LIVID for what she did to you. LIVID. Who in their right mind breaks into a home, attacks a woman, and a PREGNANT woman at that?!? What if your kids had been home and saw that? Or worse what if she targeted them? What if your husband hasn't seen it. What if the neighbor hadn't called the cops? She could have KILLED you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 12:25:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jujitsu and if your state allows it, a handgun lesson. Go over logistics with your lawyer in case she escalates and brings a knife next time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 12:29:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right here, this is exactly MILs problem. In her mind "If my son didn't marry a clone of me, he doesn't love me"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 12:32:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make sure you tell people at work that your in laws are trying to hurt you in case they show up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 16:45:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make her the last to know anything</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 16:54:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>But dont get me wrong by all means if you HAVE to protect your kids then rip it right off the table</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 17:21:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Hey, MIL, who calls you MiMi? You said they're your greatest blessings, does that mean the neighbor kids call you MiMi?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 17:40:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have your gender reveal the day or weekend before the 40th. At your house. Show her who is boss.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 23:58:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make it your profile picture</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 00:11:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so mad for you. If ita safe for your baby try peppermint lavender and eucalyptus oils in a diffuser. Helps me sleep when I get down about the world.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 00:26:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Mom, why do you need to go to church since you don't act like Jesus?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 00:27:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's awesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 01:37:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you feel like stirring the pot: "My father asked for privacy."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 16:56:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell her "Thats a shame....so the gender reveal party is at 6 pm. Come if you can."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 16:58:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>When she says "Fruits and vegetables will hurt them." "Well, MIL, I see how faulty your genetics are so I decided it was best to start healthy eating young." "That's right. Id rather them not have a bond with abusive family members, like you " "My greatest goal is to make my children hate you." Fuck her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 19:26:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>"MIL....I'm too uncomfortable that you saw my boobs to ever be in the same room with you again. Oh, sorry, baby cant be without mom. No your son can't bring him to see you."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 01:10:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>This reminds me of that Amanda Bynes movie where she meets a prince</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 01:14:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Husband dont even ask me to make other arrangements for my kids." When he tries, to "huh!" And walk away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 01:16:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love that literally everyone is on your side on this. That makes me maniacally hyena laugh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 01:18:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can see your MIL with that ring over a volcano like "Masa sayz noo! Da Pwresious!!Screeeeeeeech."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 01:19:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pavlov is screaming "this rings an alarm bell"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 01:20:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>OP it is time for you and DH to get matching face "tattoos" Don't tell MIL yours are temporary ones though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 17:08:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you I could not remember the name....are you sure he wasn't a Prince? I thought their was a Prince</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 17:16:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>That old perfume would have been great...that would have kept the flame burning bright in the crap bonfire on your front lawn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 17:18:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does she want hair clippings for her shrine to your daughter as well?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 17:19:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Send her a cloth doll with DDs face on it. Let her play weird games with her new toy...because your daughter is not her toy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 17:24:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Carry wet wipes with you in your pocket. Everytime they reach out take the baby ever so gently wipe their face followed by their hands with it. Then offer them a face mask, I belive they're called particle masks, and a pair of rubber gloves. "This is how it must be until baby is 2...doctors orders." If they whine then pick up your baby and say "Come quick my little one, we must return to your bubble. Your immune system depends on it!" Lock yourself in the nursery until they leave. Keep snacks in there in case it takes them awhile to take the hint. OR hold out a bottle of Purel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 17:25:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>And hold out a bandaids and say "Cover that THING on your mouth first please."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 17:27:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know in a healthy in law relationship I agree husbands parents husbands responsibility....however to a bullying relationship like this one I feel the one bullied needs to do the standing up. However this is my experience: my MIL doesnt take my husband serious because she believes she can control him. However when I speak she backs down. Just a thought. I'm no expert.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 17:28:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>"That wont be happening. Don't ask again." There is no nice when it comes to people who hint/pester. Shut it down. The fall out from MIL is better than disrupting the sibling bond.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 17:30:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>If she's an "askhole" then a lengthy response such as this will give her ammo for an argument. "Well, SIL did this and HER kids are finneee...you're too picky."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 00:54:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>That implies consent I truly dont mean to be argumentative I just like to present both sides so the OP has awareness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 00:56:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>If she is a pain be careful threatening to remove the grandchildren. You should never threaten this unless they are in danger...and usually after they have been removed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 00:56:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone on here taught me so I cannot take credit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 00:58:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Quote what the Bible says about too much stuff and burn it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 00:58:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is MIL pissing on her territory</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 01:22:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to say this as an effort to give you strength; You met the ex for a reason and you learned what you were meant to from him. Let him go and thank him for the lessons. This helps me when I am hurt by others</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 02:16:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>My guess is she is collecting "evidence" to use against you. You need to block her and if she asks "I found your need to repost everything I post strange. I decided communicating via text is better for faaaaamily anyway."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 02:17:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I didnt have this baby for you" "This child is an autonomous being. They need space." "Save your 'excitement' for when I need a sitter." That may be NEVER but she doesn't need to know that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 13:40:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Threatening can escalate a situation is all I am cautioning against, so they are aware and prepared in the event it does.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 13:41:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, then OP will have a great legal insanity case against her haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 13:42:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Leave a big dildo with a suction cup on one end for her to find  #128520;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 13:51:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Your past addiction issues make me nervous. I'm sorry but my children's safety is more important to me than your feelings." Or Volunterer to go to an NA/AA meeting with her. See if shes actually staying sober.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 13:53:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Say something like: "Please don't "share" my photos. I do not want strangers on your friends list seeing images of my child, for my childs safety. If you really love my child you will understand."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 13:54:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Send her a photo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 23:01:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>ACTUALLY the rings are to be "valuable" because in old times should the wife be widowed she could pay for food by pawning hers. . .not that anyone cares.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 23:07:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>"The rings are pretty...are you and FFIL getting upgraded?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 23:08:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just tell her you "special ordered" yours and its already been paid for if that's all it takes for her to shut up. Every 2 weeks would test me greatly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 23:10:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly stop giving her information too. She offers to pay for flowers? No thank you already have them picked out. Rings? Oh sorry already ordered. What kind did we get? Its a surprise for everyone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 23:46:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's actually happening here is she is not really upset about the picture...the picture just represents the fact that she now has 0 control over your husband and in her mind he can only love 1 woman...which is dumb as fuck. You can love your mom and wife. She wants you OUT and she wants to make your child and husband love HER and HER only. You are dealing with a deranged desperate individual. Get that RO. Invest in some martial arts/gun classes. Read the post about the pregnant woman who's MIL broke a window and attacked her for the same thing "Destroying her family"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 23:48:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>You also need to inform your OBGYN office as well as the hospital you will deliver at of the situation so they are aware of what is going on. They need to know MIL is dangerous to you and the baby at this point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 23:49:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your kid has a stronger spine than me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 23:56:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>My thoughts are this: Your step daughter/adopted daughter was crying at the thought of MIL being her mother and MIL moving in with her moreso than the idea of you not loving her because a child knows who loves them and who is evil.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 00:02:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I woke up early to make breakfast in bed. He wasn't hungry. I about left him. I overreacted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 00:14:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sitting here thinking to myself I've never seen a bride or groom speech. Just maid of honor and best man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 13:16:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't want to come off arrogant lol. I like to know the "why" behind things</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 13:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need to report this to police NOW before she frames it on you. Her daughter is her flesh and blood. Your baby is her flesh and blood. You are the outsider and will 100% be blamed. Trust your intuition.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 13:52:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everytime she says stupid shit like that, go get the Bible and place it on her lap and say "show me where in this book that's written?" I'm telling you challenging the religious types is so much fun!! Especially when there is an audience.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 17:49:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>What goes on in her head?!? "If they dont like to eat toast the way I like to eat toast then they don't love me." It's toast....but its not just about the toast. Its as if they need to control every single aspect of someone's life down to the toast setting. Unbelievabe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 17:50:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Finish it with a "Kids, don't listen to your Grandma. Run along and play now." Watch her face turn inside out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 17:51:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Arent they like 10 bucks on Amazon anyway?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 17:54:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mindfulness is really really great for PTSD. YouTube Louise Hay meditations</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 17:57:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember when I got married I wanted to know why I needed 2 rings and husband only needed 1. Still haven't found that answer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 17:58:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bleach. All the bleach</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 22:48:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Send her links about meddling in laws</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 22:49:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>It makes me laugh how they think they know better than science, religion, health, ECT.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 22:58:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. Not at all. Yea. You will always be her enemy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 23:02:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think she pushed her down the steps. . .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 23:09:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the FUCK? This woman is such an embarrassment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 23:22:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm saying I highly suspect either MIL didn't fall AT ALL or threw herself down steps OR threw her mom down steps LOL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 23:30:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm wondering if the knife under the bed was for the bitch MILs of old</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 23:31:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have never nursed nor delivered....but that makes no sense whatsoever. I hope you never leave your kid alone with her. Yuck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 23:34:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dont set them. Lie to her. ONLY because you only get 1 wedding. Do what you have to to make it peaceful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 23:35:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let me guess: Your MIL is either jealous because MIL is also a large woman OR MIL used your wife's weight to shame/control/hurt her her whole life and is mad she is losing her punching bag?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 23:37:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>"When you stop asking"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 23:38:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ohhh pllllleeeaaaassee please please say this. Please</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 23:39:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>"These are your grandchildren" *gestures to pets* That one shut mine up for a little bit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 23:43:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you sure she has dementia? People can forge medical documents OP this sounds terribly suspicious to me. This sounds like Christmas Cancer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 01:27:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>As long as no pumice stones were around I'm sure she was fine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 01:30:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was a bride to be I tried to include my MIL for the sake of peace too so I can't judge OP. But OP if your husband is on your side sound bites you can have are "MIL. That was rude. I would like an apology." "MIL....I cant have you speaking ill of my mother, the woman who raised me. Please stop." If she throws a tantrum ignore ignore ignore. She may escalate, this is normal, but she WILL stop if you and your mom stop trying to reach for her. It doesn't make you and your mom mean people either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 01:32:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>You say you called "truce" but nothing about your MIL 's behavior was "truce" to me. OP do NOT worry about this cruel woman. She will only treat you the way you allow her to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 01:35:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I fully meant that you and husband were going to purchase a toaster on your own, I just laughing at MIL saying you would be wasting money.  #128521; Yeah no. Bad idea to allow MILs any input on your home.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 01:38:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Thanks for your input but we already have decided on something." Don't give her specifics. If she asks: "Its a surprise"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 01:45:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are NOT a bad person. Lets say MIL was a big dog and she bit you. Ripped your arm to shreds left big bleeding gashes, the works. You had to endure the pain of surgery recovering scarring ect. Pay medical bills...nightmares...everything. Would you let and hug and cuddle that dog next time you see it? No. You would be rightfully scared and cautious and most likely avoid the dog at all costs. Would you say you were a bad person for not cuddling that dog? Hopefully not. I think you are confusing love with trust. You will never trust this woman after what she did to your baby. Her actions show improvement. But once the mirror of trust is shattered once you glue the pieces back together they are still cracked. You can "love" this woman without trusting her. And that makes you a wise person not an unkind one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 01:46:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>The fact you are even giving them a 2nd chance is loving.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 01:50:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>She wanted YOU to come "get it" and take it to the dump FOR her. You're "pregnant" not "helpless" (her thought process). JustNos can't stand when someone else gets presents and new shiny things.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 02:16:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are preaching to the choir. I mean no judgement. I just wanted to make sure you realized that this woman is not being normal gracious or kind. The best way to handle women like her is to allow your actions, or lack of actions, do the speaking. When she says something hurtful, walk away. If she does something stupid/cruel ignore it. If she says or does something kind, interact with her. Say "thank you" or something. Its called operant conditioning. When you dont give her any response positive or negative she gets no reward. When you interact with her you are rewarding her so only reward good behavior.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 02:18:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>*"I can lose weight. I can medicate for depression. But you will always be a lonely old crone."*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 02:21:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to cry. I cannot IMAGINE doing that to someones parents. That's so awful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 02:23:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hair spray works great where pepper spray isn't allowed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 03:31:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uuuuuuuu........</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 09:24:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>If she has that history I would demand a medical report. I'm sorry but that to me is so suspicious. Obviously your life your choice but that is too convenient for her in my mind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 09:26:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't. I would just do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 09:27:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea. Call the cops. And I don't think a PO box is a bad idea right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 09:31:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mil doesn't want your wife to have any "connection" to you so that the marriage is easier to sabotage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 09:56:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jacob wrestled with an angel and was renames Israel. Which is where the country gets its name. Duggars cant have a child who doubts God now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 09:57:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>"J" because "J"imbob. Josh's kids start with "M" for "M"ichelle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 11:07:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hm. I can practically hear the drums looking at him. *"What if I say I'm not just a Duggar. What if I say I'm not just another sonnnn in law. Derrick's a pretender [missionary] What if I say I will never surrender [to Jim Bob]"*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 11:11:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>And why is he standing like he's about to whip his ass?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 13:28:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you switch your medical to all online? She cant throw away emails. You can buy a PO box and make that the address on Ipsy/online shopping without legally changing your street address. You can also have them delivered to a friend's or relatives house.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 13:41:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>No because its reasonable to be angry the woman acts like you don't exist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 13:46:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also to help you take the impact out of this trespass; Remember when DD is hurt she will cry for mom not grandma. When DD is picking out a wedding dress she will want mom not grandma When DD has a DD of her own she will want mom not grandma. DD looks to YOU for an example of how to conduct herself, to YOU for approval, to YOU for love. Grandma is just this person Dad encourages her to preform for. Trust me that won't last. Kids pick up on how MILs treat mom and they dont like it. I speak from experience.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 17:31:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let her bring her shit wine then supply the caterers with the wine people actually like</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 17:35:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you feel lik3 stirring that pot: "MIL our children will serve the LORD not their grandma. You are making an idol out of yourself which is against the 10 commandmenrs. Also, slandering MY name is a SIN. Husband and I prayed for a harmonious relationship with you and instead you have rewarded us with deceit malace slander and evil. The only one who belongs to the dark one is you the wolf in sheep's clothing. We are fleeing from what is evil and clinging to what is good in this situation. We love and forgive you but we cannot trust you around our children after your malace and deceit."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 17:38:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have had nothing but negative experiences with the Baptist church. No offense to any Baptists out there but some of your kind take it over the fucking line. Not to scare you OP but keep your kids as far away from Just No s pastor and congregation</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 17:43:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had a Baptist influenced childhood..I liken it to "recovering Catholics" It wasn't until I read the Bible on my own and saw what it actually said vs what the Baptists told me it said that I saw they skip all the love and forgiveness chapters. I see you are athiest don't take this as me trying to convert you but if you have any sort of anxiety/PTSD reading the Bible on your own can be very healing because for me it affirmed that the adults in my life were nuts/twisted/misquoted things. Just a sharing if experience in not telling you how to live your life I've just been there and know its not fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 17:45:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know hon and that sucks. I'm so sorry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 22:32:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOVE how they glaze over the "everyone is your neighbor love them" parts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:01:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah GOD FORBID we actually live like God tells us to in thr Bible we read.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:07:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make sure to bring this up forever "But MIL...I WAS right about X equals Y...REMEMBER MARGE?!?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:22:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's awesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:24:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>And their mumu</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:25:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>You'll find the books in the closet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:25:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its the "lack of sleep" he gripes about</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:32:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is fucked up of me to say and I will feel bad if there was a legitimate issue but what if they just did it because they wanted to create drama and mystery around the birth for ratings?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:33:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Side Hug Side Hump Side Sex?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:33:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope they elope</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:34:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Engagement Whole Potato Pot Roast</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:36:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's tater tot grease</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:37:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it bad that I have no clue what setting my ring is? LOL.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:39:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not to be a bitch but she's not built for a the shirt dress. Tank dress sure. But I'm gonna give her a pass because she just squeezed a human out her holy hole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:41:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think its disgustingly unflattering. You cant fucking tell me People magazine couldn't do hair wardrobe and makeup on this girl. Baby or no baby. If a magazine was doing MY photos I would demand to look like one million dollars.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:41:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>The highlights are ghastly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:42:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aggressive modesty</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:42:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>If they did they did a piss poor job on Jinger</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:43:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe she even HAS ONE Meant as a joke sorry I camt help it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:44:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>What if he had TWO girlfriends in different states!?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:45:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>They'll have 19 kids by the time we see this footage</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:45:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Git some</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:47:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you think John David will make his groomsmen wear all his past groomsmen outfits?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:48:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see it as the girls "escaping" Jim Bob</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:51:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here are my thoughts: The girls can cook clean be pretty do as they are told and can pop out kids. This translates to appealing for a number of different guys with a side order of TLC fame. For the Duggar boys they have no marketable skills. They all but have to pick a fundy because what non fundy woman would WANT a man who was raised in this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:53:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anna was given to Josh because she was an obedient incubator that gave him and his real wife, Mommy Michelle, babies. Kendra and Joe happened because their both easily manipulated and Lauren was pushed onto Josiah because Jim Bob had to put the "gay" rumors to rest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:54:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can just hear Michelle: SHE IS 26!!! SHE NEEDS TO HURRY!!! SHE IS GETTING OLD DRYING OUT AND HER EGGS ARE FALLING OUT HER HOLY HOLE. QUICK! BABIES NOW!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:55:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was Jordyn's hair</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:56:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Michelle is going to try to take her home to the compound.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:57:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sometimes wonder if Jeremy posts on JustNoMIL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:57:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought it would be pink because "Its been so long since girl grandbaby" moreso than gender roles. Jinger seems like she hates pink.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:58:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think she will have feminine features and grow into a good looking girl.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:01:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to know what Lawsons name was. "Dddoooouuucchheeee"?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:01:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>It reads to me like she just wanted "out" and to feel loved by somebody, anybody.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:05:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know this is in style. I see it at target along with bamboo furniture, those little cactus in glass containers, and other 60s-70s decor. I'm with you. I HATE it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:06:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I grew up in a farmhouse. There were none of these ugly things around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:06:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why bother when its pennies at the Goodwill?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:07:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like this prick doesn't own earplugs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:07:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm thinking its fake. I can't tell but I was thinking the same thing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:08:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>That ugly thing came from the thrift shop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:08:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>They fetch a good price at the flea market... I'm kidding. Enjoy your decor</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:13:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>People magazine couldnt find her a cuter, fresh out the womb, maternity outfit?!?! Really? I call flying bullfuckery. This girl survived Josh. Survived Jim Bob, put up with Michelle Jill's "Hare Yu Phregnant" bullshit, Douchermy, Jessa's condensing "I have two baby's y'all" comments possible fertility issues a fucking cult and just had a baby her FIRST BABY...she deserved to look hot as fuck. She fucking deserved to look like a million dollars and they gave her a grey garbage bag to wear. Call me a bitch. Call me a leg humper. Call me an asshole. I dont give a fuck. This is a SNARK SUB. So which is it? Are we humping or are we snarking?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:14:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>What if they made a side deal and took JBs moolah from him and filmed the elopement!?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:15:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry if I sound mean but Jeremy is so...some thing. Like you kicked a ball around get the fuck over yourself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:16:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>We call that projection</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:18:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>"MIL I wish I was an addcit. It would make being around you so much more tolerable."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:22:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Put a chair under the doorknob and keep the door locked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:24:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would get eyeshadow and Halloween paint and show up to her house with "bruises" Hey if she calls the cops you can wash them off and you have the added bonus of making her insanity public.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:25:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>One that likes takeout</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:30:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate to say it but you need to sell that home and return the money. She will always and forever hold that over your heads.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:33:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>That dress is fucking ugly. Jinger is worth thousands of dollars. She can dry her tears with all her TLC Jim Bob money. I'm sure she gives 0 fucks what I think about her stupid dress.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:34:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I not allowed to make jokes?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:35:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Act all skiddish and nervous. I'm awful. I am so sorry to any abuse survivors out there. But this MIL needs a 'learnin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:36:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>A house is a house. A home is where the two of you find peace and love. Call her bluff. Sell it and have freedom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:38:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im a big fan of "I like messy. It discourages frequent house guests."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:40:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry you saw it that way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:41:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>And another thing...we are here to make fun of Duggars. We are big fat fucking hypocrites if we cant take a shot ourselves now and then.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:46:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just saying...if it were me and I was to be plastered on the internet for eternity I would have suffered a cuter dress for 10 minutes. And demanded hair and makeup.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:47:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe a rebellion to the whole shrill Michelle baby talk about "being a lady" for umpteen years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MIL in Mauve</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 01:06:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think I ever posted this full story. So years ago when H and I were planning our wedding one day The Nose says "Hey subject280 could I show you my 2 top choices for MOG dress." I went into her dining room on my own no witnesses...y'all. She was holding a white lace dress! It was WHITE! I remained calm and she pulled out a purple one and showed me that one as well. Thinking quickly I said "That purple one makes you look super young/slim." Yeah I can be manipulative too. She wore the purple one...and about 2 months later Honey Boo Boo's mom wore the same fucking one in black on the red carpet. No lie. Google Mama June black dress barn dress. Oh but that isn't the end of it. 2 years later I tell H about this on our way to GMIL (FILs Mom) thanksgiving. Husband instantly believes me and I explained I never told him because I was afraid to cause drama. So mind you only Me H and MIL know what happened. So at thanksgiving BIL and SIL are discussing their upcomming wedding. BIL jokes he wants a white tux and SIL wants a black dress because they love trolling MIL. Well AIL...FILs brother's wife...pipes up and says "Honestly as long as MIL doesn't wear white that should be fine becauae thats really disrespectful to a bride." Guys. The look on MILs face wasn't CBF. It was full on panic." I too graciously kept my mouth shut. I regret not calling her out right there. On the ride home H told me "I can tell by the look on her face she did that to you subject280. What the FUCK is wrong with her?" About 4 months later I finally confronted MIL about it. Her response? "I remember it being mauve." I just keep picturing honey boo boos mom when I see my wedding photos. And now everytime I ask for anything white in front of MIL I refer to it as mauve. As in "please hand me that mauve paper plate." Its a joke only she and I are privy to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 01:09:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live to supply fodder for the DILs and SILs of this subreddit. We all need a hobby. And I need an outlet. My husband keeps asking me why I am always in such a good mood lately. I'm scared he thinks I'm having an affair because I'm always on my phone on here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 01:11:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because we are a snark sub. We can make fun of Duggars but when someone interprets any perceived slight we are immediately attacked and downvoted because WE can cyberbully sexual assault victims but we can't have opinions about anything somebody else might not agree with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 01:13:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jim Bob and Michelle are sooo JustNo. Overtly Religious Narcissistic Child Abusers Baby Hoggers Overly Involved/Emeshed Assholes I love the clip where Jim Bob tries to call Jeremy poor and Jeremy doesn't feed the Narc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 01:37:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>She looked like a big ole fat plum. But a YOUNG one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 01:38:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fucking goals</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 01:42:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just couldn't believe mauve in her eyes equals white. Her delusions confound me. Anyway how about that Mauve Man Trump and his immigration tactics? He only seems to cater to his old Mauve voters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 01:43:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mauve can be glaring I know. I am a Mauve woman so I need to put on extra sunscreen when I sit in the sun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 01:46:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe she likes towel lint on her food</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 01:47:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or was she just a bitch willing to latch onto anything to make her DIL look bad? If its not your hair weight appearance style makeup its your wife/homemaker skills your parenting skills some of these fuckers attack your sex life. I dont mean to sound snarky towards you...just MILs in general.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 01:48:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>My husband is this way. I love dishes. I love my pruney hands and the way soap amd water wisk away grease. Oh the joy of scraping that brillo pad across a pan! I'm not even joking. I have issues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 01:49:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Buy her bleach for Christmas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 01:53:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>*"Because we are saving the brick for the lid of your coffin. Can't risk an escape."*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 01:54:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh Id answer *"Yea son is too young to understand you. Goodbye."*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 01:56:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I cannot believe you reward this shrew. See if H can dial it back to once a week...I know its so hard dealing with her kind. I mean no judgement of your methods.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 01:56:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do link</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 02:03:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tighty Mauvies Mauve Napkins Mauve Washing in Hollywood Mauve Christmas Mauve supremacy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 02:05:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a nice night for a MAUVE WEDDING</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 02:48:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>You gotta put the breaks to her. Flip that script. Its the only way they learn respect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 02:52:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get the compromise. You can hang up a phone its harder to kick out a demon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 02:53:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Hes big because I can actually COOK, MIL. How are they doing at Olive Garden? Do you have a punch card?" Flip. That. Script.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 02:54:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>He will cry but also be relieved. He will feel sad for the mother he never had but sad that hes not more sad. Therapy. All of it. Books on Narcs if he's not a therapy guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 02:55:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sure they are both insulated by their massive egos</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 02:55:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tbh this is a snark sub</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 02:56:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. She had a mauve color hehehe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 02:58:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it will be a good 2 years before baby is even big enough to reach it. Either way it looks fucking dumb and should be burned. For the love of God get baaabee Jr something visually stimulating like black and white checker print to develop their vision not a hideous stringed plant</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 03:01:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>All I think about when I see these plant holders are smelly old people who hoard poorly cared for animals, smoke excessively, collect old magazines, bitch about politics, their house smells like mildew, and wonder why their grandchildren NEVER visit them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 03:05:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sit with me for a moment on an imaginary bean bag. You are gripping your favorite drink. Take a sip. What relationship with your family are you destroying? They are assholes and you don't need them. Take another sip. You get to live in fucking Europe. That's fucking awesome. Take another sip. You know who is fat? Ashley Graham and she is one sexy bitch. Take another sip. Order a taxi. Fuck their will. Fuck their money. Go find a hot European partner some adorable pets and a fancy cup for your flat for your favorite drink.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 03:10:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any chance of ever having a relationship with your mother....that's who died</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 03:13:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope she has 3 babies and lives across the road from Ex MIL so she can sit and watch all the joy of the birthdays and holidays she will NEVER have with babies that arent her grandbabies. BWA HA HA HA HA. At the very least add that bitch on Facebook and tag her ass in shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 03:14:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey that dirt has minerals in it!! Seriously Jill be fucking vegan do yoga sell essential oils and be fucking done with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 03:17:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only acceptable comment to a pregnant woman is "You look fantastic. Can't even tell you're pregnant unless you stand sideways."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 03:19:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell her lying is a sin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 03:27:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>There ya go!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 03:30:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, I fucking hate them too. Now it makes sense. They have that fundy lite creep show behind the scenes vibe. Fuck them and their ugly "modern farmhouse" astetic. Shovel some cow shit. Bale some hay. Then come tell me what hangs in a farmhouse you pretentious prick, Chip Gains! I patiently await a scandal in their camp. Seriously. Are we nothing more than a fucking flock of sheep that will buy any disgusting wall hanging because it's sold at Target and somebody on HGTV promotes it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 03:35:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fucking ignore her. Seriously. Shes a little bawl baby bitch. "Waa waa waa I don't get a special party or dress. I'm and old dried out bag. I could show up in a fucking chicken suit and nobody would give a fuck waaa." She can do and try all she wants to "ruin" or draw attention away from you but any thing she does guests will just ignore. Laugh at her making an ass out of herself. Remind her of all her insecurities. If she can dish it out she can take it. If she sends you some thing nasty send this piece back; "I will make sure you rot in a nursing home and never see your grandchildren you disgusting old bat. Test me motherfucker. Test me."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 03:36:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell her "I thought your nationality was dumb old bitty. Silly me."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 03:41:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry but that made me laugh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 03:50:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's an easy RO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 03:50:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mauve dear its mauve</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 03:51:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go to counting on</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:04:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try an original insult.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:04:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm allowed to have opinions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:07:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm allowed to be</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:07:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then she goes to prison forever. 2 birds 1 stone. I see no issues. (I am only kidding)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:13:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>And they say evil never dies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:16:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dear sweet lady I had a flashback too like that before. All I can say is "You Can Heal Your Life" by Louise Hay helped me the most</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:17:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another bullet point on my "talk to therapist about" list</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:21:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>None of us deserve it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:24:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The book my dear. The book will explain it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:25:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh honey I'm being sarcastic. I'm laughing too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:31:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thats actually so fucking awesome. MIL gets ultimate "nosed rubbed in her own shit" karmic payback. I feel bad for the DIL and new husband but hopefully now exDiL gets a good kackle out of it now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:36:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seriously this is fucking crazy. I'm so fed up with this sub. I came here to snark on the assholes that helped invent this sick cult I was raised in and "I'm mean for saying a plant holder is ugly" nevermind these people promoted child molesting, child abuse, spiritual abuse...shall I continue? But oh heaven forbid I make fun of a fucking potted plant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:38:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Women aren't allowed authority in the church per YOUR Bible 'deaconness'."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:40:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I came I snarked I somehow offended you over my disgust for a potted plant</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:41:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>No I have never heard of this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:42:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>God forbid we have opinions I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:43:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish I was tech savvy and link it. Google Mama June Black Dress barn dress</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:45:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do I link an image?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:54:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>If people are upset that an internet stranger doesn't like ugly plant holders and they lose sleep over it we have bigger problems.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:55:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm judging People magazine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:57:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're all rag mags. They're all "People Magazine" to me. Morphed into one giant tabloid you glance at while trying to find your favorite gum at the supermarket.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:59:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because reading books makes you not want kids. . . .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 05:00:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or taking the animals attention away from her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 11:27:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I don't want a mother in law who lets herself into my house amd stares at me naked."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 11:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>"And risk passing on your faulty genetics and undesirable personality? No thanks, MIL."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 11:41:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Keep unhooking yourself from her emotionally. The day she can say wicked things and they don't hurt is the day you've won. The day you can twist her words and throw them back at her is like throwing water on a witch. "Its important for children to have a rebellious stage" "At what age does that end? Becauae you seem to still be in yours Mum." "Eeeeeeeeeeeeeee!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 11:44:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>When she gives dumb advice "MIL. Advice only works when you ask for it. I do not see you as an authority on child rearring marriage homemaking or life skills. Please leta just enjoy this visit and kindly keep your comments to yourself please."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 11:54:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stop making yourself responsible to host her. "you're here? Today? Oh that's too bad we arranged a play date today. Enjoy your time with H. We will be back later."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 12:06:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I cannot describe how wonderful this is</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 12:11:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your grandmother is going straight to hell</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 12:27:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Doesn't matter. There is no excuse to wear a wedding dress to a wedding not your own.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 12:32:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Time to cut the cord</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 14:02:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>They didn't interview my mother in law</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 14:03:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>You keep your daughters/future daughters away from this man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 23:01:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a fucking bitch "You need to allow me to be an asshole amd do whatever the fuck I want. Fuck your feelings Fuck your wife. Fuck your kids." I would never allow this piece of garbage into MY home either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 23:07:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everytime she says " You dont need that " what ever it is, hold eye contact with her the entire time and go "mmmhhmmm. Yummy. This js amazing." It is so incredibly juvenile but it works. I had a friend who is vegan (which I have no issue against I have tried it/studied the benefits of the lifestyle) however everytime she shamed me about animal products I did the above and now she leaves me alone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 23:13:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol. Trash can.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 23:13:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Announce she has cancer somehow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 23:31:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell BIL to ask MIL if her MIL was allowed in the room when SHE was giving birth?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 23:33:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell her if she mentions it again you will elope</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 23:56:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will never fathom how someone can be cruel to a child. An innocent child, just to hurt their parents.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 23:58:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>May be you should just send an empty with your sons legal name. Then say you "forgot" the thank you note. Whoops.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 01:33:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whenever a religious type ramps up the crazy its 100 percent projection on their part.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 02:48:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You tell her the truth NOW before you're pregnant. "MIL. You do not need a nursery. Use that money to save for the nursing *home* I will put ya ass in if you keep acting crazy."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 02:52:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>"MIL. I am not pregnant. When I CHOOSE to do so my child will be mine to raise, not for you to play doll baby with. The nursery will be at my house, so waste your money all you want. Get ya ass to the head doctor and MAYBE I will consider allowing you near my child. CHILL BITCH." If she throws a temper tantrum "Cry, bitch. I will drink ya tears. You ain't winning this one so go knit a tissue to cry into."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 02:55:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I will mail you when I see fit, Skids. CHILL ya ass!" You will feel like a million fucking dollars.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 02:56:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mail her back "It never came. Strange" Throw that fucker in the trash. The cake server....not Skids</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:08:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>You keep your chin up. You are worth every good thing in life. You hear me? Do NOT let this bitch play her games. You love yourself and keep loving yourself. And when you get settled into loving yourself you let this evil bitch have it. Verbal. Armageddon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:08:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guarantee it stops a tantrum mid "Nooboooddeee wuvs meeee because they won't let me be crazzzyyy with granndddbaaaayyybbbeeezzz"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:09:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>To the sex toy store I say!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:10:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Buy. Your Ass. A Furry Suit. Answer the door in it. (No shame to the furries...I don't fucking get it but y'all wouldn't get half the shit *I* do neither)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:15:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know what... I "get" that dementia involves a degree of these symptoms....but stories like these where they were already fucked up makes me wonder how much of it is dementia and how much of it is an act. I'm sorry but it seems so awful convenient.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:19:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. Sorry. I know there are actual cases out there....but Narc dementia to me is up there with Christmas Cancer. Fuck you, Hallmark Channel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:22:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know what I would do? I would let that shit go to voicemail and call her 24 hours later. "Phone was dead" "Batteries needed charged." "I was asleep." It conditions the loonies to be patient and gives you 24 hours to prevent yourself from tossing your device in the Vitamix.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:24:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too. I'm sick of other forms where its Either "Youureee soo meaaann" or "Remain Positive." You marry the cub of a psycho MILbear and then you tell my ass to be nice and positive. Damn, go shit a rainbow......</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:26:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why are you worried about her? No! None of your words will make her say "My DIL is right let me change now." No! Stop! Enjoy your family. Happiness is where our energy and revenge is best kept.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:33:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Skids sometimes I wish your family were immigrants. That way H could have been taken from you and I would never have to deal with your crazy."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:36:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Its more trouble dealing with the child the day after" Well there it is. They are doing this to hurt you, all the sugar and early mornings is to make YOU suffer. I so bad want to be petty and say let him stay 1 last time am leave him there aaaallllll morning and afternoon for them to deal with. OR let your HUSBAND deal with your kid while you go get your nails done. But that ain't fair to your kid. So what you do is say "Sleepovers are done because he comes home and acts crazy. I know youre doing it intentionally and I refuse to allow you to hurt my child anymore."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:37:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey! Welcome to the fucking club. I'm prone to go verbally nuclear!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:37:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well there ya go!! "MIL I wish they had taken YOUR kids from YOU so I don't have to deal with you. H could have been given to a BETTER MOM." Muahahahhaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:39:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please tell me you call her Shaun to her face now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:40:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I envision her mom like "Sizzup dude wanna chill, noob?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:41:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't pull that punch!!!! Nah what you said was too nice  #128521; you can DO IT!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:47:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally say bye 6 times then after you leave open the door run back in and say bye again. Repeat x3.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not. Enough. Get the marching band too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:49:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>YouTube the Lawrence Welk show ending theme. Shes old she'll know it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:54:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>My advice is don't take your anger for your MIL out on your spouce. Tell MIL, not him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:54:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>YES THIS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:56:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>RSVP: NO In MILs mind you are her handmaid to bear her a grandbaby. They want the incubator there because baby hasn't been born yet. Blessed be the Grandchild, OffDIL.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:56:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just the last sentence</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:58:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>You cant be angry until you tell her its bugging you. Walking in on you twice oh hell no there wouldn't have been a fucking twice at MY house.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:59:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well you want to see LO but we wanted dates....I guess we both loose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 04:09:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>"They don't WANT to see you they said you are mean."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 04:20:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>All this. Give 0 response. Literally get up and walk away from her/the situation. It works great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 04:21:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course buy fake positive pregnancy tests to "forget" on the bathroom sink now and then if she's snoopy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 04:21:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>For fucking real!!!! All this energy could be used for so much good!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 04:24:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Start browsing nursing homes. Every fucking time "baby" hints come out start responding about nursing homes care centers home hospice and the like. See how she likes THAT fantasy game!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 04:24:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd still say it if I had the chance. Scorched Earth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 04:30:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>There must be a subconscious thought your body is trying to shield you from is why your thoughts seem to be stopping.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 04:41:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hell yea! Fake car trouble. Or say "I am on my way let me get my errands done." And shop all day Meanwhile asshole grandparents get to deal with sugar crash sleepy angry little kid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 04:46:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your dad should have done a better job protecting you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 04:49:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see coon hound, jack russel, and Australian Shepherd</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 11:57:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like something similar at Wal-Mart or party outlet would work</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 11:59:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>"The stress of you nagging me caused a false positive, says so the doctor. He was its common when MILs build nurseries in their homes somehting about 'wanting something too much'."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 12:01:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine was one off the bat but hid her anger through passive aggressive comments then ramped up after the wedding.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 12:10:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Id photocopy that. Next time she brings it up say "Oh really?" And hand it to her with a "Quit your lies, MIL."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 12:14:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Son doesn't like the smell of booze on people is all." "Son doesnt like being around junkies."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 12:22:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>My vote is to let H deal with exMIL. Do NOT let on to your parents that you and your husband get along. Keep communicating and have husband screenshot all their lies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 12:30:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's a sexual predator</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 12:31:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should speak to the warden of the prison. You might be able to see if he recieved prison sanctions for inappropriate sexual contact with other inmates. And his parole/probation officer. Go to the courthouse and explain the situation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 12:35:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Fanny if you can see the future then you would have seen that you were not going on our trip and you would have stopped asking sooner."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 12:41:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need to stay as far the fuck away from that woman as you can. There is no magical string of words that will change her or make you feel better saying to her right now. Keep going to that therapist and see about removing her from your mind and your life. Also if you ever cross paths with her FUCK. NICE. You read her the truth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 12:49:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your sister needs to sit your husband down and tell him what its done to you. My mother way my husband down and described to him in detail how she treated me when he was not around and it was like a lightbulb moment for him. You need to show your husband the group chat and explain what his mother has done. That was deliberate. That was to hurt you. A CROWD of strangers in a delivery room?!?!? Who would do such a thing???</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 12:50:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would have reported that shit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 12:51:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>He bathes with her naked now too. UGh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 13:21:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Because nobody gives a fuck MIL thats why."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 13:29:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look....youre going to make mistakes. We are all human. How you avoid a JustNoMIL status is when your child or DiL brings something to your attention you apologize for your mistake and you do everything in your power not to repeat it. If they say "no candy for grandkids" feed them fruit and veggies. You explain to your DILs that you want to always strive for peace and harmony, that they are the women of the houses, the mothers, and the wives now and while you may accidently give stupid advice or say something out of turn that this is your first time as a MIL and you are learning too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 13:46:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who cares of your stairs squeak and she knows you are home? Good! She should know!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 17:41:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because I'm awful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 17:44:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>You step back and say "Dont touch me." If she does you walk away. Tell her "I can't see him. Its upsetting for him."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 17:47:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>"MIL. I do not want your underpants."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 22:30:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know...and like I said let H deal with exMIL. And then dont tell your parents that he and you communicate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 23:13:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would love to see her house because I like insanity when it isn't related to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 23:18:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course, I completely understand. Her style sounds like "flea market"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 23:24:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course he's not big! But she knows that's what she can get him on so she would poke at weight even if he were rail thin!! So what you do is if you go with it and act comfortable with "being big" (normal) she's out of ammo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 00:03:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>She claims you as her daughter as a control technique not as an affectionate thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 00:04:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you feel like playing games with her: "I would LOVE nothing more than Chil Fil Et" and tell her how much you HATE the restaurant you actually want to go to. I bet my ass you end up there instead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 00:05:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Harmony" "Melony" "Lyla"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 00:07:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Leave the gifts on the porch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 01:31:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Rain"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 01:33:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks part bishon (I know I spelled that wrong) and part terrier</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 01:34:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Puss In Boots (Shrek)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 01:34:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>That bow tie is life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 01:35:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>ME!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 01:36:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>How does one not cuddle this creature?!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 01:41:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Usually a foot firmly over the tailbone gives enough propulsion to thrust someone at least halfway across the yard. . . . .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 01:46:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd rip this bitch's throat out with my bare teeth</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 01:46:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a sucker for "matchy but not clashy" pet names.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 13:05:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let husband know he's out too if they come 'a stompin'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 13:19:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>OP it sounds like your MIL is exhausting and causes anxiety in you. Remember she is not an authority over you or your baby"NO" pick up the baby and walk away. She turns to husband to override you "I already told her "NO" " pick up your baby and leave the room. Your actions speak so much louder than any words. Women have been conditioned by our society to be abuse victims, what she is doing to you is abuse. She's invalidating you she is ignoring you and she is trying to hurt you through your child. No wonder you had PPD! When you speak up and it pisses her off GOOD! It takes these bittys a good temper tantrum or 2 to figure out they aint in charge. If she bawls like a baby "Keep crying MIL. Lets see where it gets you." And walk away. If people say you are mean/accuse you of being a bitch laugh and say "THANK YOU. That is the NICEST thing anyone has EVER said." Laugh and walk away. When the obligatory "But I raised kids before" line is dropped "Yes. 30 years ago you raised kids. But this is MY baby to raise, not yours. If you cant listen to me or treat me with respect you won't be welcome in my chidlrens lives."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 13:20:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Maybe when theyre a bit older" and walk away</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 13:20:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>*"Fuck your thanksgiving photo"*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 13:51:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ask her if your childs safety or her relationship with Junkie Mommy is more important.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 14:03:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your MIL isnt just doing pills if she's an addict she's doing whatever she can get her hands on. Get her the fuck away from your baby. This is a hill to die on. Your wife sayig "She would never hurt the baby" SURE! Sober, in her right mind she wouldn't but you mix those pills around enough with other things and before you know it bad shit happens. If its bad enough the cops and CYS will be called.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 14:10:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>If she actually means well and isn't a pain suggest she "recreate" her handmade outfits JUST for comparison photos. This will firstly keep her busy and keep her out of your hair and secondly it might actually be cool to have a matching photo if your baby looks identical to your husband at that age. If shes just a bitch who wants her do over baby "MIL I am NOT dressing my baby in old clothes for fear you will confuse my baby for yours. You are already showing signs youre going to try to take over my kid so back off if you ever want to see my baby in any outfit." Laugh at her CBF.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 19:02:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have my hillbilly father to thank</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 19:03:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That old man is my father.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 19:04:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell me what episode kitty and red are in.they were my favorite  #10084;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 19:38:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm telling you Hilbilly Dad has life figured out. Everyone marginalises him but he gives 0 fucks and is happy with what he has and has 0 tolerance for peoples shit. The friends he has are loyal as fuck and his enemies are scared. He would just crack you a cold one (beer) on the porch and say "set down."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 19:40:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Should you be eating that?" "Should you be out this late at your age?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 19:41:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Parole baby!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 19:43:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eh if she killed a man all her rage is out. She's probably chill as hell now...fantastic babysitter for the chidlren. I do hope you have her present in the delivery room to catch your baby and cut the cord. I'm.joking of course holee sheeet get the fuck out of there!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 19:43:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I must snuggle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 19:44:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Husky looks like me behind the glass of a doughnut display.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 20:38:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>From the sounds of it your MIL has been sick her whole life. Must have caught it from one of the disciples while bussing tables at the last supper.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Success</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 02:14:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Today was the fateful day of MIL and her FM party and through a combination of techniques taught here I won my way through a family reunion of MIL and her FM team. When MIL started trying to draw me into weight loss talk I grey rocked. Cousin in law went rouge and bragged about her weight loss and workouts...cue CBF and "We hate you" comments from MIL. Hahaha. Didn't even have to open my mouth! THEN MILs #1 FM GFIL tried to guilt me and made comments about "it would be nice to see us more often" Husband and I didn't respond and walked away. No MIL, we are done accepting hlep from GFIL/allowing him access to snoop in our home!!! Also was able to distribute my phone number to in-laws I dont hate so MIL no longer gets to play gate keeper between me and extended in-laws!!! So NOW I have direct communication vs going through MIL. Hehehe! It was a phenomenal success and I could not have done it without this sub. I do believe I can put all of her crap behind me and move on....meaning I never trust her again BUT I focus now on ME and MY joy vs stressing over "how to deal with crazy pants". I got her in the bag. I'm in charge now! Thank you everyone!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 02:46:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel light and glowing. I feel so tranquil. I have 0 vengeance thoughts just true peace.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 02:51:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tag her in Facebook photos of FHs birthday party. Please.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 11:57:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Neither do I...its the greatest thing to be without isnt it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 12:02:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>NOPE! And really its petty, but MIL likes to war over baked goods and food brought so she will tell us what extended want us to bring, and this year there was a tiny misunderstanding. It causes stupid drama so next get together I can directly text the host and ask what she would like me to bring with 0 issues!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 12:04:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Isnt it great? Mine was a small thing but this way I can side step SO much drama and unnecessary issues by just picking up my phone and asking what is needed for a get together, so I no longer have to go through MIL and have my words twisted!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 12:11:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read "Nice Girl Syndrom" "You Can Heal Your Life" "If You Had Controlling Parents" "Don't Let Anyone Dull Your Sparkle" and "Assertiveness For Earth Angels" and started doing free yoga videos online. We store emotions in our muscles and to loosen them up was like taking a huge breath of fresh air. I also researched nutrition and started making dietary decisions best for my bosy, implemented vitamins and supplements, and started meal prepping/making dinner from scratch and learned new recipes. I started delving into religion on my own, and I have found it is harder for people to hurt me when I am treating myself with respect and love every day and attending to my own needs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 12:24:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Many times a MIL will take her anger out on us, because prior to our arrival certain negative aspects of her realtionship with her son aren't visible. When we arrive we accidently bring attention to the fact that he and his mom were never close, he actually never liked his mom much, and his mother is controlling/manipulative. Or we highlight a MILs insecurities, we are younger prettier and have the ability to do in life what we want. A JustNoMIL has death and grandchildren to be excited for. You can't manipulate your way into a bedroom for your DIL to get pregnant, and you can't manipulate your way out of death/aging. You also loose your power as grandchildren want their mom not you and instinctively pull away from an overbearing controlling grandmother. Your son you once had power over doesn't listen and your DIL has a different way of doing everything so you can't control her either. A JustNo is the equivilant of a large lion who's teeth are falling out and has mange. And if we don't give them any good or bad response then that takes more of their power away. We are the new lions in town and MIL can't accept her new role in the herd.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 12:32:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's not dumb. She plays one so you and others in her life allow her to do tuese sorts of things because "She is too stupid to know better"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 22:21:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get that, true. You can make one have 1 single profile pic and just purge everything too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 22:22:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Be careful using an image of a tv Character though. Sometimes they ban you for copyright issues, like if you name yourself Homer Simpson and put a pic of Homer Simpson up. Happened to a friend of mine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 22:23:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>At first I missed out on stuff like this but eventually an invite became more meaningful because it meant a person had to actually look me up and text me to make it happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 22:27:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is NEVER "you" in any situation with anybody. When people find fault in someone that perceived fault always reflects their inner fears or struggles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 22:29:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope you thank God every night shes gone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 22:34:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>She tried to wear white to my wedding She told me, not asked, that she would be in my delivery room...I'm not even pregnant... She had me doing a weekly babysitting for HER elderly father. Every purchase we made she asked if it would delay her ability to have a grandchild....again...not even pregnant. The hell of it is we WANT kids one day, we do! But like a child asking for Slsomething x1000 times she thought by badgering us it would happen sooner. She's still waiting on that grandbaby...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 11:53:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can see why. For your sanity though if he knows your email that's how he keeps finding you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 11:55:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Post it, how so? Won't it be removed by mods?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 12:00:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>"My Stars" Because she seems the type to say this/was upset over earrings Sephora/ULTA whatever makeup store she bought that stuff at Mama June because she wanted you to loose weight/have DD be in a pagent Raven Haired Hag</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 12:02:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reason #102 I got rid of Facebook</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 12:05:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's trying to groom you to allow her to move in is what I think this poster is suggesting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 12:07:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would laugh at her and say something like "No, MIL. I already HAVE a mother. You're my mothet IN LAW."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 12:12:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>*"Mom, this baby won't love anybody but me and their dad for the first few years."*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 12:20:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea, no. Being 20 is no excuse. When I was 20 I wasn't breaking other peoples things or hitting people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 18:17:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Lets see this in action, MIL."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 18:21:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uninvite your mother. She doesn't get to show up to your wedding. Because she will make it misery comparing her ceremony to yours ECT.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 13:11:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>A boil, if he wears a collar it could be a reaction to the dye, or a mosquito/spider/tick bite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 13:15:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>"MIL I have all those vaccines and so do the grandchildren....I guess you can't come over...for your health of course."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 17:48:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Put Neosporin on it and see if it goes away in 2 days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 12:38:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is she your girlfriend or did she decide you were dating and you're just going along with it? To be honest this sounds like a recipe fo4 disaster. You need to be honest with her so she can focus her energy on someone who really loves her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 23:46:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Josiah isnt gay. Hes just not a country boy like his brothers so he sticks out. He also isn't as reserved as they are. To me he wants out of the spotlight and to retreat to his quarters to read or play violin. Hes afraid to be himself because these people are very aware of the public's opinions and comments. If half of America was shouting I was gay I would probably act like a deer in headlights on camera too. Oh and he's probably terrified of the Joy shotgun wedding snipe hunt as well. Oh and the whole purity sex is bad men are rape monsters my brother is Josh stuff too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 23:47:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree she seems bored with Ben. I bet when she feels low she looks at Derrick's Twitter...then feels better. Lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 23:48:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I cannot be the only person that loves cooked potatoes with the skin on them...I feel ashamed. Perhaps I should make a Jazz Twitter rant to cover my insecurities about this....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 23:51:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like to think Jeremy took her to the mall, they stood out on a balcony and he said to her "You see this Jinger? Everything the light touches, is your kingdom." Then he held her over the balcony and all the shoppers sang "The Circle Of Life" complete with attempted African chants.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 23:52:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jana and John David.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 23:53:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>And yet...somehow...despite the bare flesh...nothing about this turns me on to the degree I must gaze upon my Nikes.... I must be holier then you heathens!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 23:54:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think she also found a Sephora. I think she's low key jealous of her daughters. She gives me Narc mom gives.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 23:54:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I imagine Jeremy visualizes it daily</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 23:55:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>There wasnt a closet to put it in?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 23:56:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I the only one that would be pissed if my sister in law set up my new house? Maybe I wanted the joy of that as a new homeowner?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 23:56:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Josie Montana I'm a fundy but I'm also a pop star "Pull the Dugger Bus Out Front.... gett the beeeesssttt of both wooorrrlllddss."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 00:02:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have plenty for the cops. They might not be able to arrest her YET but by showing them the text you open up a case. The case stays open and you can continually report things to them. Eventually they will have enough evidence to press charges.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 00:03:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Take a karate class. It will make you feel better at the very least.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 00:08:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>You'll do something? Like what? Show up when I'm showering again? Stay home and iron your wrinkles. The sex is WAY too good for anything you have up your bingowings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 00:10:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm. "Well until you are de clawed you will never be around my child again."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 00:24:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly I wouldn't let her hold the baby at all. It eliminates a lot of this checklist. "I'm not comfortable with anyone holding the baby." Is a great answer. When they tell you you're nuts or whatever canned angry narc response turn your back and walk away. Also "Please, no pictures." If they want to freak out "Are you saying my child's privacy isn't valuable to you?" Walk into the nursery and shut the door until they leave. Keep snacks/Netflix in there. Just because they show up doesnt mean you need to engage. "Baby needs rest please come back when you can respect my parenting decisions."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 00:26:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Order a pair for yourself Mom and I'll keep them safe for you at my house."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 00:31:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>"MIL I refuse to allow you to continually hurt my daughter. No you cannot speak with her" and hang up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 00:35:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Id make it a point next time you see her to mention you now use a Diva Cup. Then ask if the reason she steals your pads is because she's ashamed she's now dry and barren.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 00:36:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would have thrown the purse to the ground and walked away</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 01:17:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>My money is on Josh being gay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 01:18:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>*shivers* Uncooked potatoes. Yuck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 01:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jill looks really cute in this picture. She looks appropriately styled and has a casual "stay at home mom of boys" vibe to her vs her typical Thrift Store Nightmare outfits. I want so bad to see a Duggar daughter fundie intervention for all. Pants and shorts for all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 01:26:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are downright nasty to some people on that site.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 01:26:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>He probably tests his sober limits when Jessa shows up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 01:27:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I doubt it. I bet Cathy or Derricks dad's police pension.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 02:03:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cancel the visit. She won't leave.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 02:12:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Croc s are foot cancer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 02:13:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Yep. Pretty much."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 02:14:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just died.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 02:14:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>YES!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 02:20:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kendra's parents seem to strongly dislike Jimbob and Michelle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 02:30:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck. Seriously, FUCK! Is never let her near MY children.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 02:37:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you know she isn't letting your kids "try" her wine? At the very least she is modeling to your kids that wine is okay and being drunk is okay. No no no.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 02:37:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I dont blame you one fucking bit. Holy SHIT that's awful!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 02:39:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stop giving a fuck what she thinks of you. I know its hard. But remember if she encouraged you or didn't you would still be where you are in life because YOU not HER got you there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 02:40:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love tiny tots with the skins on. Mhmm mmm! I don't peel carrots but I wash them vigorously (the vitamins are in the veggie skin)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 02:45:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>She wants you to call her for every little minute detail so she can control every single aspect. Her issue is she is not in control here and that scares her. So shes trying to control you by throwing tantrums. Ignore it. Ignore it. Ignore it. Not showing to your shower was the kindest thing she could have done for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 02:46:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Neither do I. I usually remedy the situation by pouring gas on the fire though and the silent treatment Anamorphs into a mutant creature screaming yelling cussing crying and me laughing at them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 02:50:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will forever visualize this when I am trying to sleep</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 02:54:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Quit letting this woman have power over you. She ONLY cares for her selfish wants...not your needs your feelings or your heart. She is the playground bully who grew up to be somebody's MIL.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 02:57:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its not normal...but sadly not uncommon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 02:59:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Funny...DH told me he broke several" Awkward silence "Ohmigosh...MIL! Are you NOT DHs mom? WAS HE ADOPTED!?!?! Is that what you mean by "your kids" ?!?!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:04:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think they see them as a pest. The way Kendras dad looks at Jimbob says a lot. Also Kendra's mom all but forced Michelle out of Kendra's birth. I think Ma and Pa Caldwell too are nervous Joe might be a Josh. I hate to say it because that sucks for Joe...but I'd be wary too if my daughter married into this circus.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:05:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I literally just said this in the other post: Cops get pensions in most states so that would be a helluva chunk of dough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:06:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe the people who donated to their Central America trip are paying for it hahaha jokes on those suckers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:07:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:08:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Delish. I'm going to stop talking about this now...this is Duggarssnark...not freejinger. Lets keep the topic on topic. Back to hating Derrick!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:09:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Quit drinking "DD isn't YOUR baby. She came out of ME not YOU"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:15:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>The baby rabies had begun with the "listen at the door" comment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:15:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>My parents...fuck...I don't even KNOW when their anniversary IS!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:18:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Because all Jews know a good lawyer" give her shit back to her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:20:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm straight. If MY MIL made references to my sex life in front of my children she'd be shown the door. Fuck that!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:20:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>What does the 19 year old say about her?? Egats....cannot imagine my grandma saying stuff like this. Ewewew!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:22:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>My patience is GONE for most people...for crabass old women it's lost for good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:27:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd buy her "Cultural Awareness" books every Christmas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:28:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Because I'm Old" is no excuse to be an asshole. Assholes come in all ages. Be grumpy 40. People suck now in my 20s give me hope I will mellow out in my 40s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:29:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spill your drink on her. Save your liver so you can outlive this dingbat!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:37:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder if Laura isn't a "fundy rebel" and the Duggars are doing her family a "favor" by allowing her to hang out with Jana so Jana can be a good example? Kind of how they forced Joy to hang out with "her best friend Sierra Jo"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:44:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know...same...I know who she is...but can't name 1 of her songs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:52:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Friendly Retirement Home Spiderman</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:53:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Old people are so wise</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:57:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I literally wear the same thing all the time. I lie and say its because I'm poor. I'm not poor I'm just lazy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:59:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bill Gates seems like the coolest guy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 04:14:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I miss emo pop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 04:15:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about mashed potatoes? Instant mashed potatoes? Can we trust them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 04:17:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm in LE and where I work my spouce could get it, or a person of my choosing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 04:19:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lets mix them! Imagine There's No Ocean. No surfers too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 04:20:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm willing to say conservative hate group may be behind this one for sure!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 11:49:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>When she said "We're going to have a other grandDAUGHTER" when joy annonced pregnancy. And then she was like "I dunno why I said that..."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 11:52:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I had to guess it would be the thousands. Was his dad in the military as well? That's some cash to be had too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 11:58:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would be pissed if my SILs ascended upon my home and took over like that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 12:25:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm willing to bet TLC needed footage of the siblings together to push the "we are all bffs" plotline so the producer said "Here is a Target gift card run wild."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 12:25:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>They failed Jessa then...by their own measure of course</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 12:26:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I give Kendra 2 more years. She's still on "honeymoon" phase. I let my in laws walk over me at first too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 12:27:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kendra seems scared to me. I imagine Jessa is a 2nd mother in law to nag you/make you uncomfortable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 12:28:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Money is on J-Anna being made a slave</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 12:31:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's awesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 12:32:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe they named him that to get attention over the Josh scandal. Jessa was mad she didn't get the fanfare Jill did so had to redirect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 12:47:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is cross ministries funding this? Hes obviously got some measure of academic....I said academic calm down...intelligence to get an accounting degree. They aren't a cakewalk either. I think he quit walmart because walmart doesn't let you flim there. I really think hes teetering on the edge of a breakaway. I think that he thought it would be smooth sailing then Josh gate happened then Isreals birth went unexpected then they were missionaries and got blow back from that then Sam's birth was a wreak. Then the Twitter rant and now presto no more show. He's now trying to be a college missionary. That didnt work so now he is trying to infiltrate Washington. Seriously nobody will hire him. The argument will always stand that "he hates transgenders"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 13:30:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bullshit. Shes just shown you her true colors. She WILL drug your baby when your back is turned.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 13:36:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you don't argue with her you give her no fodder. Or something like "You said it not me" will keep her from running to others pkahing victim</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 13:39:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stop leaving him with her unsupervised. You dont "owe" her visits.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 13:43:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't mean this as hate but 100 percent I could never be in a poly relationship because more partners equals more inlaws. I'm so sorry for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 13:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Derrick may have had a scholarship for the first degree or worked to put himself through ALSO some colleges offer students discounts if their parents attended. My alma matter does this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 13:51:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I never said I *wasn't* thankful Mom" The bible says answer a fool according to his own folly lest he be wise in his own eyes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 13:51:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>You move on by accepting that she sucks and treating her accordingly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 13:55:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stop rewarding her bad behavior and her bad behavior will stop. Mean girls don't get nice parties and presents.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 14:02:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You realize that no matter what you are still you and you are worthy of love. You realize that even though your friends moms seem awesome that they arent perfect either. If shes not supportive you don't go to her for support. If shes not sympathetic you don't go to her for sympathy. A GREAT book on this topic is clled You Can Heal Your Life by Lousie Hay. I highly recommend you read it!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 14:03:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd quit Facebook. You've seen the dark side of social media. People you want to share photos with you can text.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 14:05:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>The difference is you were PAID to be around the crankly old men. I would laugh too...all the way to the bank. But none of us get paid to be around our mothers in law. Many of us have been abused and treated poorly by them and its no joke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 14:16:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know but didn't Snowden all but prove none of us can?! Call people/text people memes and pictures for a few months then create a faux Facebook with a fake name and only give people access you trust.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 14:29:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Credit card fraud</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 14:37:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would starve myself too if it meant I never had to talk to "Ms Renee" again for another fitting....oh wait no you dont get to talk she interrupts you when she gets the chance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 14:39:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Joy just has massive boobs so she reports to baggy clothes which make her look heavy...because...you know...defrauding and all. If she were allowed to dress in tighter things that hit at mid torso and skinny jeans/boot cut jeans she would look amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 14:39:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Id be sick too if that gangly thing was my dad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 14:40:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least Ben and Jeremy don't require brown bags for sexy time. Somebody buy Jill a vibrator</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 14:41:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder if he wears the Pistol Pete head during baby making....its an improvement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 14:50:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>This one time my MIL called my husband to say "Tonight is your grandpa's birthday and I'm throwing a (last minute) party for him." We already had plans so husband said "No" MIL came back with "But its your grandpa's birthday" To which husband replied "Oh then we definitely aren't coming" See Bitchbot for how MIL and GFIL terrorized us in a little tag team formation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 14:51:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pepper spray peppery spray</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 14:52:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>BOTH my MIL and my mother and my father tried adding people to my list. In the end my wedding was a party for them and their buds and a photo OP for me...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 15:30:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>YUCK LOL.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 15:33:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would have said something about MIL mocking my eating disorder during my speech. That's tasteless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 15:37:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would text back "why are you sending me locations? We already picked one." "You domt have to like or approve my decisions. Come or don't come i dont care." Teach them now before the I dos that they have 0 say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 15:39:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Start recording conversations. When they lie press play.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 16:51:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know more gay men who act like John David then Josiah. Think about that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 16:56:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also I grew up like this and I'm willing to bet Joy Anna and I have common ground here based on how we are built. I was a tomboy and hated makeup/hair/clothes until I turned about 19-20. If she and I had a similar experience I bet her hesitancy to embrace femininity came from body esteem issues from her breast size and curves. So Joy probably felt she couldn't be "girly" without " tempting" men but was then unable to be masculine because "sin". Just a perspective based on my own experience. But I never got lesbian vibes from her ever. Matter of fact the only one I get the gay vibe from is Josh. The hyper fixation on busty women seems to be a denial of his "gayness" IMO.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 17:03:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I truly think she desires attention moreso then a new spouce. Derrick is notorious but its still attention she doesnt get. Josh is notorious and stole her thunder. Jeremy and Jinger are more interesting Joe and Kendra are cuter JOy and Austin make more sense Her and Ben are so "Meh"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 17:05:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its Jessa. Nobody cares about Jessa.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 17:07:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you ever feel like a fundy face Youre not original and can be replaced Do you ever feel feel so starving thin 1 scoop of tater tots to the wind...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 17:08:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry but she looks like Josh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 17:09:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It smells like the pit stains on derricks shirt. Not because its Indian because you cant cook</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 17:10:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blend your eyeliner Jill BLEND!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 17:16:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Worst would be Jessa and Derrick "Holocaust Abortion Trans Sexuals Twitter Rants" Ben and Jill "Duurrrr..." Austin and Jinger "I hate the woods/I love the woods" Jeremy and Joy would be strange and annoying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 17:18:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>DO YOU EVER FEEL already burried deep? 6 homework assignments scream all the sib-I-lings Dont you know that there's still a chsnce for you You just gotta believee in Godddd aaaannnddd Jimmm Booobbbb</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 20:12:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same here! Gotta get the girls flattering tops</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 20:16:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>They probably have brand deals...since people are afraid to air commercials with counting on maybe they are resorting to product placement</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 22:34:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its not a spark or a bang. Its a slow steady change like the leaves of an autumn tree turning red. Start being thankful for yourself. Start thanking yourself and loving yourself like you would a small child. A great book on this is called You Can Heal Your Life by Louise Hay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 22:46:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not Humping just observing: Honestly they seem VERY good with money. Their home is minimally decorated, cozy without extravagance. They repeat a lot of their outfits so I'm thinking they use capsule wardrobes. They eat healthy and Jinger cooks at home so that saves a lot of money. They host their friends at home vs dining out that's a lot of money saved. They probably do a lot with Jeremy's congregation vs seeking out frequent entertainment and they like to stay physically active and you can do that for cheap as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 00:09:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am guessing he had a scholarship for soccer. Also Jinger has lived in yard sale clothing so any brand to us is shocking</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 00:13:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think they are annoyed by the act. They probably see the true duggars behind the curtain. Also they're probably weirded out that their daughter courted 2 of them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 00:17:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was his head always this long</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 01:30:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate to do this....but all I see is a standing side hug</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 01:32:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like Gabriel a lot. Emmanuel is another name for Christ so they probably won't use that one...fundie in my area shy away from naming their children after God/Jesus</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 01:45:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Heeyyyy Zeeuuusss Dillard Yaay"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 02:29:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oooh a standing side hug with a lean</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 02:29:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>They dont play sports...or have sex</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 02:30:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Must Protect Penis"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 02:41:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>"teach them young"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New Daughters</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 02:47:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>With Lauren and Kendra replacing Jill what do you think the odds are Counting On will eventually phase out Jessa with a new in law? She has no concept of boundaries and minding her own business.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 02:52:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I cant lie I would wear that. . . I want to know why she looks so great in photos but on the show she looks so rough? I'm not being mean I'm wondering if they use poor lighting or something because the show doesn't do her justice. Jill also looks so good in some pics but so bad in others. I don't get the Duggar morphing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 02:53:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean more on the line of her talking head segments. I should have clarified.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 02:54:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I need to clarify I meant cut back on her talking head lemme edit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 02:55:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to smash my head against a wall because her talking heads are repetitive "When WE were courting" Yes yes we know already! We got this same speech last season....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 02:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only reason I mind her is she's pushy with everyone. Her decorating Jinger and Kendras houses gave me anxiety for them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:04:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because she repeats herself: Everytime someone is courting its a reash of hers. Every tkme somebody else has a baby its "When I had MY baby" everytime somebody gets married "On MY wedding day"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:05:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I felt she was very uncouth about Jana. I think she was trying to joke but it camw across very condescending "Its okay if you aren't as smart as her boys line up" Like who are you Jessa? The only thing keeping your husband from being the worst is Derrick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:06:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>What always puzzled me is WHY don't these girls wear their hair up ever?! You can hide so much with a proper up do and make an outfit look more complete with a cute bun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:25:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jessa and Jeremy would have exploded like John and Kate Gosselin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:26:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know but the 9th rehashing of the same stories is getting stale</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:28:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to be honest....I'm not sure where it started or why but as a kid I thought it was rude if I didn't clean my plate so I always thought I was paying the cook a compliment by licking my plate clean....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:30:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>And now all I can see is a tiny little Joe hungry.....and now I'm depressed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:31:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Defiance Or should I say J'Fiance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:33:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>That makes me feel prehistoric to admit I am so close to John David in age. He looks OLD and I 100 percent he can reverse that with proper nutrition.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Duggar Nutrition</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:37:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>So Joy looked rough during the pregnancy footage then magically aftet the doctor told her to start eating better she was flying around the construction with tools in hand hammering away like her old self. Jinger looks so much healthier (skin mostly) since leaving the compound. Jana and John David IMO look older than 28. I blame Duggar nutrition. I bet if Lauren can cook Josiah starts looking a little fresher too. Now that all the daughters are grown I bet the compound kitchen is cans of soup and processed junk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:37:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder if its not Jim Bob yelling in the background "No roll the bit about the parking lot wedding again"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:39:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wasn't it also true they refused to allow Jill to assist her birth?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:41:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could see her being a pseudo daughter to the Duggars from a rough home and wears skirts for a roof overhead/screen time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:43:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I grew up dirt poor but always always always ate. I can't fathom being a tiny child and being hungry. I also cant fathom being an older sibling of a hungry child trying to prepare food for them at 10-12 years of age while mom and dad were off babbling hypocritical shit about family values.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:46:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>J'Done with this woman's J'Shit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:49:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I kind of want to write fucked up fake letters for people to find when I die now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:49:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is good parenting in action</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:50:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Spants" isnt it? Why do I know this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:50:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its a 90s thing/dork white man father thing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:51:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Culture darling its our culture</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:59:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why do these people buy all this stuff for babies if they are soooo frugal? A changing table for example seems unnecessary if you really want to buy used ECT. You could lay a changing pad down on any surface to change a baby. A dresser...for a baby... seems really strange too. Wouldn't the baby just need a basket for onsieis/socks/shoes? Possibly a winter jumpsuit or coat? Matter of fact why a nursery at all? Crib in the master bedroom, basket of baby stuff in the master closet, and done? Id rather save the money for a bedroom set to grow with the kid when they are older vs baby furniture they dont need/outgrow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 04:01:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think cheap makeup ages the Duggar girls too. While some drugstore foundation is nice they probably buy cheap stuff not complimentary to oily vs dry skin. And the harsh eyeliner ages them as well. Josiah looks greasy and sickly like he lives on fast food.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:19:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Without makeup he and Lauren are equals IMO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:20:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Acne is 90 percent nutrition 1O percent what you put on your face. Try cutting out typical allergies/oil cleansing. Going diary free saved my skin!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:21:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did NOT know this. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:22:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Beat them young. Fixed it for ya</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:24:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I kind of feel like I care more about the daughter in laws to see how they either resist Michelle or are brought to heel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:24:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bet it becomes one. After all they value the babies more than anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:25:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was going to post on here no wonder she has a great figure because she isnt able to eat half the fundie garbage they makw.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:26:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh honey I'm a poor hillbilly I never left America. Travelling for me will sadly never happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:27:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's tragically hilarious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:27:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like the Crimson Chin the Jessa Chin J'Chin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:28:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was JUST thinking Jessa is a worst MIL then Michelle!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:29:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holiday dinners must be a fucking nightmare</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:30:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>In Colorado even deer get the munchies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:32:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jessa I could see cheating on Ben</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:41:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>If she weren't fundy I imagine she would say: "You git ur little ass up to that microphone and sing the effing song. Momma needs to milk this gravy train. I did NOT give birth to 19 of you to give up NOW."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:42:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>But who would sleep with Derrick?!?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:42:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really don't think Josh loves or loved Anna. I think it was forced on him by mom and dad from the beginging.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:45:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Welp time to hang one on MY wall</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:49:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ive always wondered why they frump it up when they could make dresses and skirts cute....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:52:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not to cause an argument but it acutally DOES fit because their goal is to "draw attention to their countenance" (face) hence the heavy makeup hair and big earrings. Older books mention using scarves and big collars to bring attention to your face.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:53:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because they are trying to attract people to the cult by always looking pretty and rich "See see you can be like us too!!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:54:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Them: "Gay people are child molesters" Us: Josh? Them: "Curious about girls. Sleeping girls."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 18:08:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hormones are affected by what we eat as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 18:09:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was trying to be nice and let you know what worked for me! Holy fuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 18:11:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Revlon? Too pricey try wet n wild</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 18:13:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honey I'm not saying all people in arranged marriages cheat we are talking about the Duggars</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 18:16:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm tired of this shit too. This is called DUGGAR snark. When we post something it's about DUGGARS.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 18:20:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good Luck Derrick. I mean this because literally nobody will hire you. You have said and done too much publicly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 22:28:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean if I have to post links I can....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 22:32:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking her mother in law is more her mom then her own mother! She even called her Mom in the talking head segment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 00:09:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I made the comment you're referring to because I thought people would be genuinely interested to know that this was actually part of their teaching. Not to be a Nazi or smartass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 00:12:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always find it amazing after they announce a courtship what some posters can uncover on this sub about the partner/the partners history with the Duggars. Well done! I always wonder if the fathers/mothers/siblings don't get together and set up betrothed behind the scenes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 00:14:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kendra and Joy look like sisters to me. So do Jessa and Lauren and Abbie and Jana. What I will say is I don't think any of the duggar chidlren resemble one another with the exception of Josh/Johanna and Jinger/Josiah. That's just my opinion though I think years of gaping at their antics have untrained my eyes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 23:23:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I cant wait until he has a transgender professor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 23:25:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its INSANE how tired and sad she looked after marriage...even pre pregnancy. Derrick must be exhausting to live with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 23:26:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jill as a nursewould make more money then Derrick as a fundy lawyer Now we know why she isnt a nurse</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 23:51:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nathan with the shade</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 23:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>WHAT? Why am I only hearing about this now!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 23:52:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's incredible. I creeped the IBLP Embassy Media site and Erin had a CD for sale...I wonder if they're still selling it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 23:53:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am too if hes honestly out of IBLP!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 23:54:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>That he doesn't love. Sorry. Hes a shit dad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 23:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>We forget too JD and Josh (not to defend Josh) were "dads" as soon as they could walk/talk. AND they worked for Jim Bob from a very young age. Combine the two no wonder they aged like shit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 23:58:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the girls rely on makeup. Not to say they arent attractive without it but you can hide and highlight with makeup. The Duggar men have nothing to hide behind. Have we ever seen them sans makeup? I'm not judging Jingers looks based on her maternity special...she had just given birth its not fair.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 00:01:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sex Suppressing Suppository</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 00:01:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't scroll up and look now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 00:03:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree. Shave that beard and it's a different man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 00:04:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thighs of a Greek Statue Thanks for that! I'm using it at work....HR here I commeee!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 00:05:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Raccoon Hat?!? Sweet Mercy LMAO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 00:08:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Josh looks like the opposite of a freak. Josh looks like a 2 jerk squirt a roll over and sleep. All sweaty. Poor Anna....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 00:10:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't miss Jill. Some thing about the way she spoke irked me. It wasn't breathy like Lauren or giggly like Kendra...it was just kind of childlike</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 00:11:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want a behind the scenes with green suits</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 00:13:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>They kept him off the air and put Jill and Jessa up because they were trying to save the show. Putting Josh up would have enraged the public thinking they were glorifying and profiting off of his actions. By staying the "we are victims we don't deserve to suffer for what he did" path they were able to rebrand and rebuild.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 00:15:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree. He was a public figure and he deserved to be on that camera and deserved public humiliation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 00:17:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh absolutely! People are curious and some people love watching trainwreaks. I admit I want more details, we only heard the porn stars side of the story lets hear his! Lets make him take the stand instead of his victims</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 00:18:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know Jeremy isn't the greatest but compared to Derrick and Ben...holy moly Jinger DID marry well!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 00:59:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will be very excited to see footage of the new daughters in law interacting with the daughters. I suspect rivalries within the next season! Stay tuned! Sadly I think Abbie will quit working...moreso because she will make more as a talking Duggar head on TLC then as a nurse then her headship telling her to quit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:00:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm willing to bet she had a crush on someone in their circle who chose someone else. Or maybe she is waiting for a "sweep me off my feet not make me sweep the floor" guy and they don't exist in her circle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:02:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I imagine too after witnessing Jill and Derrick's nightmare marriage, Ben not being able to support Jessa, and Jeremy clashing with Jim Bob Jana is probably nervous to court.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:02:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Double wedding. To two twins. Oh Jim Bob would keel over and die.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:06:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe the minority students and female students sat as far away from Derrick as they could Edited to add: Nevermind I went back and looked again. It looks whiter than me in February.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:16:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>My opinion: Their public social media accounts are fake and ran by publicists (except Jill). Their weddings are rehearsed several times for the camera. They have had other courtships that failed. Jill Jessa and Jinger were "Fundie Old" when they got married! Early 20s? Seriously? When they should have been wifed by the Godly age of 19? And spinster Jana... I bet all of them had prior courtship that did not turn into engagements. Derrick went on the twitter rant so their contract would be nulled and he and Jill could split as they were both "over the show"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 12:25:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>A "non reality" if you will...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 12:32:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are the odds she's trying to get you to lower your guard so she can control you. If you like her and think she loves you all her boundary stomps will be seen as "shes just trying to help". My MIL did this and it totally blindsided me. Good for you seeing this now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 12:33:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perfection.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 12:35:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Husband told me you would like to be maid of honor. Thanks for the offer but My sister has already been chosen."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 12:37:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well if it makes you feel better I'm the only one in my department without a tattoo and they all make more than me....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 12:40:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been thinking as well but what it comes down to is that I am obsessed with matching. So if I get a rose for example but buy a swimsuit with shapes vs flowers on it it would slowly torment me. I get that this makes me weird</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 12:41:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thats lovely</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 12:42:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL oh YES it was in the North eastern middle schools of America.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 13:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, you cant stop people from having prejudices but if you treat their daughter with kindness and respect and tattoos are their biggest issue then they have issues not you. Don't make it your issue  #128521;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 13:19:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope thats not how Josiah looked at Lauren on their wedding night</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 13:22:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haunted Mansion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 13:46:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi! Me! My mother was...tried to be...fundy. My father was passive and let her do what she wanted so she quit her job pulled us out of school and rammed every focus on the family book/tape down our throats. Dating was forbidden every friend we brought home was bad mouthed Pokemon were demons cartoon and television were evil sex was for chidlren and marriage. We were only allowed around the fundy or extreme Baptists. We were allowed to wear pants and makeup which alienated us from our fundy homeschooled "friends" but were not accepted by our evangelical church eithet for being too awkward. It was abusive oppressive and just down right imprisonment in that house. I spent my childhood and teen years alone in my room with no friends. I was suicidal and self harmed. I thought I was being influenced by demons but it was my mother. Ironically to escape I graduated college and became a corrections officer to escape the prison I was already in. Its very hard for me to relate to everyone else as movie/television references go right over my head. I spent college reading Wikipedia to figure out who Darth Vader was to relate to my peers. I fake my way through social situations. Dating was impossible. I finally married and my new husband dealt with constant panic attacks the first 2 years of our marriage from all the suppressed emotions. Part of me thought marriage was my only escape. My lack of ability to pick up on social cues played me into the hands of a few predatory men at college. I was stalked, sexually assaulted, it was somehow my fault when I told my mother who told me to keep quiet about it. Happy ending though I figured out everybody's family is fucked up in their own way and now my parents don't even attend church. My mother has been reduced to a miserable old lonely lady who is always the victim and pushes all her friends away. My sister and I have no relationship because of the competition in our house growing up she would verbally and physically abuse me. My brother is dependent on me for emotional support because of the damage done to him. Having lived in an abusive oppressive environment it makes working in a jail easy. Ive told 4 people about my childhood. Its still uncomfortable to talk about. There is a lot of judgement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 13:51:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Respectfully disagree. Parents can encourage competition and hatefulnes among their children in dysfunctional homes. I lived it. My mother 100 percent is the reason my sister hates me. I recently found out my mother had been whispering how much prettier and smarter I was then her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 13:52:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jimbob and Michelle are cold and mechanical. Gil and Kelly actually interact with their chidlren and appear to love them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 13:54:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shut your mouth</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>