<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject5375</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>the ultimate guide for entrance tests , b scool admissions and many more</TITLE>
    <DATE>2007-08-05 16:58:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Swaziland bans 'rape-provoking' miniskirts</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-25 03:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Autism! Don #8217;t fear it, embrace it!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-12 17:20:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>In the neurotypical world we tend to focus on the different as negative, rather than unique. We measure  #8220;goodness #8221; by how it compares to the norm, and if it matches our view of value. If the qualities are  #8220;out of the norm #8221;, than we immediately see the negative that blind us from the positive characteristics. We tend to interpret  #8220;different #8221; as a weakness, or deficit, both something to change. We tend to interpret behavior that we do not understand as  #8220;bad #8221;, not worthy, and needing to be suppressed. We do not look at differences as something that to value, understand, and marvel at. That differences may make our world better and enrich our lives. We are so conditioned to wanting to being  #8220;accepted #8221; that appearing different is something to avoid. Unfortunately we block ourselves off from the true wonders that these differences may bring. Why is this? Why do we fear differences? Partly, I assume, is that the  #8220;unknown #8221; scares us. We feel uncomfortable when things do not match what we are use to. How do you relate to it? How do understand it? Make it change, be like the norm, so I can feel comfortable with it! People have always been  #8220;uncomfortable #8221;, even scared of things that are different. They are not as predictable. It doesn #8217;t flow easily with how I regulate. It stands out as different, and will not be accepted! We become anxious; hyper-focused on the negative, and totally blind to the beauty that it may bring. It doesn #8217;t fit our  #8220;common mode! #8221; I have been in the field for over thirty years. I have seen many individuals who are radically different in how they communicate, how they process information, what they attend to, and how they experience the world. I was a  #8220;behavior change agent #8221; and employed to change these people; to make them  #8220;normal #8221;, or at least appear normal. Like everyone else, these differences also scared me, especially since it was my job to suppress and change them. I started out in the back wards of an institution, where people with severe differences were secluded from the rest of the world. People who came from lives of abuse, torment, and despair at the hands of neglect and rejection. It was through their eyes that I learned that each had beauty, value, and worth. Values that we could not see, because we could not get past their differences. Once I stopped fearing the unknown, and embraced their uniqueness, did their differences start to appear, not as weaknesses, but as different perspectives; different ways of experiencing the world. Accepting these perspectives, allowed me to redefine them not as weaknesses, something to fear, but as strengths and gifts, that if supported, not only benefited their lives, but also enriched mine. I look around and still see our  #8220;fear #8221; of that which is different, and our desire for it to  #8220;go away #8221;. Whether embarrassed, or scared, we are definitely uncomfortable with differences, so we immediately interpreted them as bad and needing to be suppressed, or changed. We do more damage by wanting to change our children, then wanting to support them.  #8220; If we make them  #8220;look #8221; normal, then they will be happier, and so will we #8221;. If it is not like us, then it is obvious unworthy. I beg you to resist this viewpoint, and try and redefine how you see things. Instead of immediately interpreting differences with a negative filter, try looking at them as potential positives; as different perspectives, that when supported, can be developed into strengths and gifts. Before suppressing the difference, observe and listen to it to understand it #8217;s value. Look for positive value first, to redefine how you interpret it. My experience is that many of these differences are actually gifts that will enhance our own perspective of the world. Try to resist the urge to smother or change the difference because we simply don #8217;t understand it. Try identifying the value in it, validating it, and fostering support for it. You will be surprised how the perceived  #8220;weed #8221; can turn into a beautiful flower! Your children come with a bundle of qualities. Many may look like ours, but many may not. Try to foster the children to develop all their qualities to see how they unfold. In my experience if we acknowledge, partner with, validate, and support the natural growth of these qualities, the children flourish, develop strong self esteems, and truly feel  #8220;safe, accepted, and competent. #8221; Take their interests, regardless of how strange they initially appear, and try to view them from a positive perspective. What are they attracted to? What do they seek out? What do they initiate? What do they find pleasure in? Take their interests, and turn them into strengths. Start by assuming that these qualities are gifts and what strengths can occur from them. The children will not only feel accepted, supported and loved, but will also develop into more competent, self actualized human beings. In turn they may change your experiences, and possibly enrich your own perspectives . You will see the world totally different and be happier and more fulfilled as a parent, and as a person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Great pic of the Apple store in Bangalore</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-12 18:17:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Great pic of the Apple store in Toronto</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-12 18:27:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Best Divorce letter ever</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-12 19:14:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hundreds of the famous and intelligent Calderon dolphins lay savagely slaughtered, soaked in their own pool of blood.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-12 20:22:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dolphin Killing Festival!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-12 20:24:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>What I am about to tell you gives you a WHOLE NEW MEANING of the  #8220;Red Sea #8221;. Every year, Danish people have a killing festival where they slaughter so many dolphins and whales that the sea LITERALLY TURNS RED!!! What is doing this? The young adults and teenagers! That makes it even worse. To top that off, children have a day off school to join the festival. Oh boy #8230; These teens kill the dolphins to prove their manhood. Although I think it just proves that your blood-thirsty psycho. The dolphins and whales don #8217;t even get a quick death. They are cut three times with a large hook. When will UN and EU stop this madness? To think that we were civilized men. Well we #8217;re wrong. Hundreds if not thousands of dolphins and whales are kill EACH year in the bloody festival. This is happening at faroe Island of Denmark. How can Denmark allow this to happen especially when they are on the brink of extinction? We need to start doing something!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hundreds of the famous and intelligent Calderon dolphins lay savagely slaughtered, soaked in their own pool of blood.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-12 20:38:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hundreds of the famous and intelligent Calderon dolphins lay savagely slaughtered, soaked in their own pool of blood.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-12 20:49:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is the Calderon dolphin's repayment for trusting men and coming near them to interact with fellow sentient beings.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-13 05:03:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Flying Saucers Spotted In Kerala,India</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-17 19:38:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Kitty Cat Diary #8230;A Day In The Life Of  #8220;Luna #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-18 18:30:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Autism! Don #8217;t fear it, embrace it! - Autism Awareness Page</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-10 20:22:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stop discrimination against autism</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-18 06:20:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do cats celebrate Valentine's day?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-14 15:49:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do cats celebrate Valentine's day?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-14 15:59:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do cats celebrate Valentine's day?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-14 16:28:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do cats celebrate Valentine's day?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-14 17:15:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do cats celebrate Valentine's day?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-14 17:38:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do cats celebrate Valentine's day?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-14 17:50:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do cats celebrate Valentine's day?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-14 18:19:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do cats celebrate Valentine's day?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-14 18:45:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Did Police shot a dead man in Danish capital Copenhagen?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-15 06:18:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do cats celebrate Valentine's day?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-15 07:43:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do cats celebrate Valentine's day?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-15 08:47:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do cats celebrate Valentine's day?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-15 12:39:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do cats celebrate Valentine's day?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-15 13:50:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do cats celebrate Valentine's day?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-15 15:12:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Prague zoo to set up Special unit to treat obese people Read more: http://www.digitaljournal.com/news/odd+news/prague-zoo-to-set-up-special-unit-to-treat-obese-people/article/426636#ixzz3SOyapUgK</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-21 18:32:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Prague zoo to set up Special unit to treat obese people Read more: http://www.digitaljournal.com/news/odd+news/prague-zoo-to-set-up-special-unit-to-treat-obese-people/article/426636#ixzz3SOyapUgK</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-21 18:42:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>All animals beware !!! Prague zoo to set up Special unit to treat obese people</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-21 19:24:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mattel's Wi-Fi Barbie can tell stories, jokes to kids</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-23 19:07:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mattel's Wi-Fi Barbie can tell stories, jokes to kids</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-24 03:57:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mattel's Wi-Fi Barbie can sing songs</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-24 04:07:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Swine flu outbreak: 774 deaths, 13,000 cases set alarm bells ringing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-24 17:50:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Afghanistan avalanches triggered by heavy snow kill at least 100</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-25 19:02:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Afghanistan avalanches triggered by heavy snow kill at least 100</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-25 19:13:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>More than 100 dead in Afghanistan avalanches: officials</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-25 19:22:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>3 Al-Jazeera journalists arrested in Paris for flying drone: judicial source</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-25 19:32:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Iranian army chief: Zionists, West created Islamic State - Middle East</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-26 03:38:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Apple Sends Out Invites For March 9 Event, Likely For Apple Watch</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-26 18:38:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What Happened When Three Women Watched Porn For The First Time</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-27 18:20:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Worst Ice Bucket Challenge: Caution: GRAPHIC DOG BITE.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-27 18:56:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-27 19:02:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Frghtening</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-27 19:14:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here are some statistics for you: there are 1.6 billion Muslims in the world. 62% of which aren't even middle eastern, they live in southeast asia. (When was the last time you heard of an Indonesian terrorist?) Let's pretend for a second that every single person in Iraq and Syria (the countries ISIS is trying to take over.) Is an extremist, their combined populations are about 50 million people. That's just over 3% of all Muslims in the world. Tell me the last time time you were around 100 people and at least 3 of them wasn't a complete asshat? You're more likely to be killed by heart disease than a terrorist. Where's the trillions of dollars being spent declaring war or cholesterol? More people die to gun violence in the U.S. every day than American civilians have died to Islamic terrorism in the entire 14 years since 9/11. http://www.washingtonsblog.com/2013/06/youre-more-likely-to-be-killed-by-a-toddler-than-a-terrorist.html</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Worst Ice Bucket Challenge: Caution: GRAPHIC DOG BITE.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-27 19:17:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Worst Ice Bucket Challenge: Caution: GRAPHIC DOG BITE!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-28 04:11:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-28 04:17:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That link has been taken down</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>#TheDress Official Color Is Blue and Black, Says Dress Company Roman Originals</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-28 15:52:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cool Cat rides dump truck like Vin Diesel</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-28 17:18:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cool Cat rides dump truck like Vin Diesel</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-28 17:24:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cool Cat rides dump truck like Vin Diesel</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-28 17:29:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cool Cat rides dump truck like Vin Diesel</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-28 17:40:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cool Cat rides dump truck like Vin Diesel</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-28 18:51:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL If you heated the head of a pin to the temperature of the center of the Sun, it will kill anyone within 1,000 miles of it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-01 05:54:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL One Tennessee man got arrested for attempting to have sex with an ATM.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-01 06:15:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Horrible acccident in China - Girl hit by firecracker explosion</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-01 13:59:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Chihuahua dog jumps on pitbull's back.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-01 15:55:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>34 more fall prey to swine flu; toll climbs to 1,075 in India</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-01 16:07:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL The Black Death, caused by the bacterium Yersinia pestis, wiped out 40 to 60 percent of Europe's population between 1347 and 1351.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-01 17:15:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Perhaps as a result of Valentine #8217;s Day romance, highest number of pregnancy and infertility test kits are sold during the first 3 weeks of March than at any other time of the year.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-01 17:51:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Uruguay's pot-friendly farmer president prepares to step down</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-01 18:22:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Perhaps as a result of Valentine #8217;s Day romance, highest number of pregnancy and infertility test kits are sold during the first 3 weeks of March than at any other time of the year.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-01 18:41:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You do not see dead birds on the roads or in the gardens unless they have died in accident. So where do they go to die when they die a natural death?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-01 18:49:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bangladesh #8217;s Charlie Hebdo? American atheist blogger murdered in Dhaka.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-02 16:01:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Man Falls Into Water While Throwing Dog: Guy Torturing Dog Gets Instant Karma</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-02 16:23:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nearly Beaten in Sierra Leone, Ebola Makes Comeback by Sea</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-02 17:12:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL During the Cold War, USSR thought the heavily trafficked building in the center courtyard of Pentagon was the entrance to a top secret bunker and the officers were getting their briefings there. Consequently, Soviets always had at least two missiles targeted at it. It was a hot dog stand.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-02 18:58:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>China dad tries to kill son's online gaming addiction with in-game assassins | SciTech</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-03 04:16:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL The force of the eruption of Krakatoa Volcano in 1883 created the loudest noise ever recorded: it was heard 4,653km away on Rodriguez Island in the Indian Ocean and some 4,800km away in Alice Springs; shock waves traveled around the world seven times.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-03 16:52:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL South Africa manufactured 6 nuclear weapons of the "gun-type" design in the 1980s. Before the anticipated changeover to an elected African National Congress government , the South African government dismantled all of its nuclear weapons, the first nation in the world to voluntarily do so.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-03 17:52:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>After 8 centuries, rats exonerated in spread of Black Death. Gerbils implicated.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-03 18:56:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mount Everest has a poop problem</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-04 03:59:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL In 1848, the British East India Company sent Botanist Robert Fortune on a trip to China's interior, an area forbidden to foreigners to steal tea seeds from China to India.He succeeded and within his lifetime, India surpassed China as the world's largest tea grower.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-04 15:43:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Dr. Kellogg firmly believed that red meat increased sexual desire and he advocated a diet rich in nuts and cereals. He began to develop a sort of anti-masturbation food and Kellogg #8217;s Corn Flakes are meant to help decrease your likelihood of masturbation.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-04 16:23:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Among the upper class in 19th-century Victorian Britain, pubic hair from one's lover was frequently collected as a souvenir. The curls were, for instance, worn like cockades in men's hats as potency talismans, or exchanged among lovers as tokens of affection.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-04 16:51:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Scandinavian and Icelandic Babies Have Napped In Sub-Zero Temperatures For Generations. They believe that napping outside in the freezing cold helps children stay healthier by exposing them to fresh air, rather than keeping them inside for hours in stuffy, overheated rooms.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-05 03:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL At the height of the Cold War, a broadcast prepared for Britain's Queen Elizabeth II to deliver in the event of a nuclear conflict urged her subjects to be brave and stand firm in the face of destruction, and for the survivors to pick up the pieces and rebuild.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-05 05:42:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The U.S. Ambassador to South Korea, Mark Lippert, was slashed on his right cheek and hand with a knife measuring about 10 inches long at 5:42 p.m. ET on Wednesday.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-05 05:49:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Before Nazi Germany decided to eliminate the Jews by gassing them, it had considered sending them to the island of Madagascar.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-05 06:07:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL The Roman emperor Claudius is said to have been so alarmed at the prospect of expiring while attempting to stifle one's natural impulses that he considered issuing an imperial decree making it permissible to fart at the dinner table.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-05 09:35:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Scientists took advantage of the three-day flight ban over the US after 9/11 to conduct experiments on the effect on the atmosphere of jet planes. They found the days were a little warmer and the nights cooler, suggesting that the exhaust trails planes leave in the sky act like clouds.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-05 10:56:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL During World War II, One Geologist from Colgate University,New York suggested bombing Japan #8217;s volcanoes to force an unconditional surrender .</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-05 11:22:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Hitler kept a framed photo of Henry Ford, founder of the Ford Motor Company, on his desk. Henry Ford also kept a framed photo of the Nazi leader on his desk in Dearborn, Michigan.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-05 12:05:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL In January 2009,One of Google's programmers was adding websites to the malware registry when he accidentally entered "/" instead of a full URL.Google's malware warning system took that to mean that every site on the internet was potentially harmful to its users and blocked for almost an hour.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-05 13:14:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL In Mohave County, Arizona, a decree declares that anyone caught stealing soap must wash himself with it until it is all used up.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-05 14:09:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL If you visit the Haskell Free Library and Opera House in Derby Line, Vermont you may want to have your passport in order. A line of the floor marks the border of the United States on one side and Canada on the other.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-05 15:19:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL During the Cold War the US considered airdropping enormous condoms labeled  #8220;Medium #8221; #157; onto the Soviets, to demoralize them against an anatomically superior American Army. The plan was never carried out.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-05 16:04:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>50 Cute Puppies Make Your Girlfriend Smile</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-05 16:50:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Original idea for YouTube was a video version of an online dating service, and had been influenced by the website Hot or Not</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-05 18:37:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL According to the Center for Disease Control, falling out of bed accounts for 1.8 million emergency room visits, over 400 thousand hospital admissions and 450 deaths each year which is more than the number of people killed by rifles.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-06 03:32:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL During the middle ages, English was a language used by commoners while the British elites spoke French.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-06 14:25:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL The tiny little island of Vulcan Point in the Philippines is the world's largest island within a lake (Crater Lake) that is situated on an island (Volcano Island, or Taal Island) located in a lake (Lake Taal) within an island (Luzon).</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-06 14:38:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL In 1987, a Canadian man named Kenneth Parks drove 14 miles to the home of his in-laws. Upon reaching their home, Parks brutally attacked them both, killing his mother-in-law. When the case went to trial, he was acquitted on unprecedented grounds: The attacker was asleep.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-06 16:02:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL According to a Wall Street Journal study in 2010 based on four broadcasts, a standard NFL game features just 10 minutes and 43 seconds of action. Commercials, replays or shots of players huddling account for the remaining time of the three hour affairs.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-06 16:34:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL The White House still Uses Floppy Disks in part for storing files.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-06 17:01:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Because of its prison system, the US is the only country in the world where more men are raped than women.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-06 17:57:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Warren Buffett has only sent one email in his life.It was sent to Jeff Raikes of Microsoft, and Buffett said it became his first and last email when it ended up in court.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-06 18:25:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Doctors' sloppy handwriting kills more than 7,000 people annually in the United States.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-06 19:00:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL In North Korea, it is the year 104. That #8217;s based off of the Juche Calendar, introduced in 1997. Juche 1 is based on the year Kim Il-sung was born, April 15, 1912.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-07 03:55:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-07 04:18:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>No its year 1 in 1912.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL In exchange for Pepsi products, Russia gave the company 17 submarines, a cruiser, a frigate, and a destroyer making Pepsi become, for a few days, the 6th largest military power in the world by number of diesel submarines.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-07 14:20:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL In June 1942, Japanese forces seized two islands in the Aleutians chain, part of Alaska. It was the first foreign occupation of American territory since the War of 1812.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-07 14:29:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL It used to be patriotic to grow cannabis in America. In 1619 farmers in the 13 colonies were required to grow 100 cannabis plants by law.Both George Washington and Thomas Jefferson owned Cannabis farms.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-07 14:48:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-07 16:44:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>The site appears to got reddit hugged. Check the Google cache version here: http://webcache.googleusercontent.com/search?q=cache:At8__q1gC3QJ:redkalinka.com/Russian-Blog/78/_The-day-Pepsi-became-a-great-military-power/+ amp;cd=1 amp;hl=ml amp;ct=clnk amp;gl=in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A man in Mexico has built his own floating island using 100,000 plastic bottles.it floats in a tropical bay near Cancun and contains a house,beaches,two ponds,a waterfall and a Jacuzzi.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-07 17:00:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL When Albert Einstein died on April 18, 1955 in Princeton Hospital, the nurse assigned to him did not speak German and his last words were not understood.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-07 18:24:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-07 18:46:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>The site appears to got reddit hugged. Check the Google cache version here: http://webcache.googleusercontent.com/search?q=cache:At8__q1gC3QJ:redkalinka.com/Russian-Blog/78/_The-day-Pepsi-became-a-great-military-power/+ amp;cd=1 amp;hl=ml amp;ct=clnk amp;gl=in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Women perform 66% of the world #8217;s work and produce 50% of the food. They earn just 10% of incomes and own 1% of the property globally.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-08 04:28:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Drug lord Pablo Escobar had so much cash, that rats ate almost $1 billion of his money each year.He had to spend $2,500 every month on rubber bands to "hold the money together."</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-08 06:10:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL The amendment to the Constitution granting women the vote was passed by only one vote. Tennessee was the 36th state to ratify the Amendment, and it passed the legislature when Harry Burn, a young legislator, changed his vote to "yes" after receiving a letter from his mother.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-08 07:08:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL At the Academy Awards, you can earn $125 by being a seat-filler for a celebrity while they go to the restroom.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-09 04:16:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL In 2007 Lehman Brothers was ranked the #1 "Most Admired Securities Firm " by Fortune Magazine. The company went Bankrupt in 2008.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-09 16:19:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Rich people in China often hire body doubles to serve their prison sentences.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-09 17:07:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Apple Just Canceled The Right Click</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-09 19:06:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL The CDC has an actual  #8220;Zombie Plan #8221; in place. It was started as a joke campaign, but actually evolved into real training and countermeasures because  #8220;if you #8217;re well equipped to deal with a zombie apocalypse you will be prepared for a hurricane, pandemic, earthquake, or terrorist attack</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-09 19:29:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Zug is a German speaking city in Swtzerland. It has a population of around 26'000 people. Known as a tax haven, the city is Headquarters to nearly 30,000 companies, of which 17,000 are stock exchange-listed companies.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-10 16:59:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL The official Twitter account of Sweden is given to a random Swedish citizen every week to manage.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-10 17:32:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL A Cockroach can live several weeks with its head cut off.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-11 18:09:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Atomic bomb tests were a major tourist attraction in Las Vegas during the 1950s.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-12 16:00:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What happens when you smack talk a cat</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-12 16:10:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL John F. Kennedy bought 1,200 hand rolled Cuban cigars just hours before he ordered his trade embargo against Cuba 1n 1962.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-15 15:09:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL As many as 250 men are estimated to lose their penises each year in a secret and brutal initiation ceremony conducted by the Xhosa tribe in South Africa. During the month of June, thousands of boys are sent naked into remote areas to survive with little more than a blanket and meagre rations.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-17 18:26:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>At least 19 people including 17 tourists are killed after gunmen target the Bardo museum in central Tunis: Tunisian Prime Minister</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-18 16:12:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Troy Leon Gregg, who was sentenced to death escaped from a Georgia prison the night before his execution,later that night,he was beaten to death in a bar fight.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-18 16:53:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mont Saint Michel - tide of the century</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-22 15:16:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL On August 14, 2003,a systems operator in Indiana noticed an annoying alarm with the power flow monitoring tool which the operator turned off. Five hours later, Fifty-five million people were without power. That one alarm was apparently the only alarm.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-27 17:32:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL A study has concluded that 90% of all bills in circulation carry traces of cocaine on them. This is largely due to the practices of drug traffickers who move large amounts of cash with cocaine all over their hands, and that the bills are often rolled up into straws and used to snort the drug.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-28 03:57:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL During WWII, the Japanese launched 9,000  #8220;wind ship weapons #8221; of paper and rubberized-silk balloons that carried bombs to the U.S. More than 1,000 balloons hit their targets and they reached as far east as Michigan and a total of 6 Americans lost their lives.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-01 20:10:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Siege over in Kenya. At Least 70 People Killed, 79 Injured</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-02 18:08:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ISIS fighters hit by deadly flesh-eating disease</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-04 17:30:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ISIS fighters hit by deadly flesh-eating disease</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-04 17:40:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Bangkok's official name is "Krung Thep Mahanakhon Amon Rattanakosin Mahinthara Ayuthaya Mahadilok Phop Noppharat Ratchathani Burirom Udomratchaniwet Mahasathan Amon Piman Awatan Sathit Sakkathattiya Witsanukam Prasit."</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-05 12:05:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Feds Give Disability Benefits to Many Puerto Ricans Because They Can #8217;t Speak English.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-10 19:58:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Quetzalcoatlus, thought to be the largest flying animal in Earth history had a wingspan of 35 feet. It could fly up to 80 miles an hour for 7 to 10 days at altitudes of 15,000 feet with a maximum range between 8,000 and 12,000 miles.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-15 10:19:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL John Malone, Largest Private Landowner in the U.S, owns 2.2 million acres - more than twice as much land as the state of Delaware.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-18 10:43:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL The Gingko Biloba species of tree is 270 million years old. It rarely suffers disease or insect attack and was one of the only living things to survive the Hiroshima nuclear bombing. The trees healed quickly and are still alive today.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-18 11:55:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Under Julius Caesar, February had 30 days, but when Caesar Augustus was emperor he was peeved that his month - August - had only 29 days, whereas the month named after his predecessor Julius - July - had 31. He pinched a couple of days for August from February to make it the same as July.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-21 17:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Viagra, or Sildenafil, as it's officially known, was originally conceived as a treatment for hypertension, angina, and other symptoms of heart disease. But Phase I clinical trials revealed that male test subjects were experiencing a rather unexpected side effect: erections.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-22 17:45:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Botto Bistro, an Italian restaurant in San Francisco, started a campaign " Hate us on Yelp " to become the worst rated restaurant in Yelp. It also offered a 25 percent discount to customers who gave it a 1 star review on Yelp.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-22 18:06:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL The first video on YouTube was uploaded exactly 10 years ago at 8:27 pm on Saturday, April 23, 2005. The 19 second video 'Me at the zoo' has since received more than 19 million views and more than 130,000 comments.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-23 14:46:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL "Buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo buffalo buffalo Buffalo buffalo" is a grammatically correct sentence in American English, used as an example of how homonyms and homophones can be used to create complicated linguistic constructs.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-23 16:51:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Lake Karachay, located in the southern Ural Mountains in eastern Russia, was a dumping ground for the Soviet Union's nuclear weapon facilities. Standing on the shore of the lake would give you 600 roentgen of radiation, enough to kill a human.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-23 19:26:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Cotard #8217;s Delusion is a mental disorder where people suffer the nihilistic delusion that they are dead or no longer exist.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-24 15:11:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Some of Russia #8217;s rich are hiring luxurious  #8216;ambulance-taxis #8217; to beat Moscow #8217;s traffic jams.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-24 15:21:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL The 2008 US Financial Bailout cost more than the Marshall Plan, Louisiana Purchase, Race to the Moon, S amp;L bailout, Korean War, New Deal, Iraq War, Vietnam War, and NASA #8217;s lifetime budget, combined when adjusted to inflation.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-24 16:49:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL U S Military distributes Non-lubricated condoms among its soldiers not just for safe sex, but as an emergency water canteen. A non-lubricated condom is part of the United States Military Standard Issue Parachute Pack Survival Kit (SRU-16) and can carry a liter of water.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-25 04:16:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>7.8 Nepal Earthquake moment | April 25, 2015</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-25 17:28:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Math visualization: (x + 1)2 -Funny</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-03 14:28:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Swiss probe thousands of unclaimed accounts opened before 1955, possibly with Nazi links</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-03 18:26:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>7.4 magnitude earthquake hits near Papua New Guinea, no reports of damage</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-05 04:29:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>'Isis' dropped from UN hurricane name list</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-05 17:22:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>France overtaking Britain as Gulf States #8217; main European ally</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-06 19:00:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>UN Official : ISIS Forces Girl to Undergo Virginity Surgery 20 times</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-10 20:03:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Vatican officially recognizes Palestine, while Israel fumes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-13 18:41:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Filipino Farmers Eat Rats, Trade Tails for Rice as El Nino Drought Begins</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-17 03:58:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Filipino Farmers Eat Rats, Trade Tails for Rice as El Nino Drought Begins</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-17 05:44:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-17 06:05:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its a government run program</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #8216;I have to work a lot harder #8217; in Russia than at NSA  #8211; Edward Snowden</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-17 09:03:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ireland days away from gay marriage equality according to latest polls</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-17 09:23:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ukraine's new law calls for demolishing monuments to erase its Soviet past</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-17 11:16:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Saudi Arabian woman angered by her husband #8217;s decision to take a second wife has exacted her revenge by raking up $100,000 in deliberate traffic fines on his wedding night.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-17 15:51:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-17 16:07:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Her brother was driving</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Saudi Arabian woman angered by her husband #8217;s decision to take a second wife has exacted her revenge by raking up $100,000 in deliberate traffic fines on his wedding night.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-17 17:08:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Google reportedly wants to put a 'Buy' button in your search results</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-17 18:20:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New Zealand flag designs: Kwi, piwi or kiwi?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-17 19:23:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A new island emerging off the coast of Japan offers scientists a rare opportunity to study how life begins to colonise barren land - helped by rotting bird poo and hatchling vomit.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-18 17:37:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rhino horn now more valuable than gold, diamonds and cocaine, at $60K a pound making poaching a ultra profitable business.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-18 17:55:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL In 1914, British WWI soldier Thomas Hughes tossed a beer bottle with a letter to his wife into the English Channel. He was killed two days later. In 1999, a fisherman dredged up the bottle in the River Thames. Although Hughes' wife had died in 1979, it was delivered to his 86-year old daughter.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-18 18:28:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It #8217;s Raining Spiders in Australia - They're descending by the millions</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-19 05:07:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-19 20:45:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>They should probably get nukes too. Just to be safe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>NYPD commissioner wants 450 more cops to fight ISIS in the city</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-20 04:42:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hundreds of Leg selfies are flooding social media in Algeria after a student was banned from her exam for wearing a skirt which came above her knees.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-20 19:31:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-20 20:11:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here comes the Facebook Page: https://www.facebook.com/pages/Ma-dignit%C3%A9-nest-pas-dans-la-longueur-de-ma-jupe/683432101802568?sk=timeline</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>University short skirt ban sparks leg selfie protest in Algeria</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-21 04:33:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hundreds of Leg selfies are flooding social media in Algeria after a student was banned from her exam for wearing a skirt which came above her knees.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-21 04:43:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hundreds of Leg selfies are flooding social media in Algeria after a student was banned from her exam for wearing a skirt which came above her knees.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-21 04:54:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Gaddafi's home town falls to Islamic State in anarchic Libya</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-21 17:17:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Isis 'now controls half of Syria' as ancient site of Palmyra falls into terror group's hands</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-21 17:35:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Chinese App That Steals Wifi Passwords Just Raised $50 Million</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-22 19:52:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Report: Israel offered Saudi Arabia use of its Iron Dome technology</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-23 15:21:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Google Fiber is reportedly sending out copyright infringement notices directly to subscribers offering settlements ranging from $20 to $300.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-23 19:13:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Heatwave sweeps across India, 335 people dead</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-24 05:06:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A computer algorithm that mines rap lyrics to create its own song</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-24 15:19:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Florida Cops Have Gotten Tons Of Military Gear From Washington</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-25 19:19:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Taliban-ISIS clashes leave 27 dead in Afghanistan</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-26 04:23:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Intense heatwave in many parts of India, toll 1242</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-27 17:53:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Chinese government takes its officials and members of their families on prison tours on a regular basis to give officials an introduction to what awaits them if they should engage in corruption. The tours include meet-and-greets with former government officials who were caught for corruption.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-27 18:39:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL A Woman in Oregon started a wildfire to give some work to her bored firefighter friends. Eventually, the fire, named as the Sunnyside Turnoff wildfire, spread to about 80 square miles  #8212; 51,000 acres  #8212; costing nearly $8 million to fight and took two months to bring under complete control.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-27 18:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Massive protests erupt in Mexico over Uber, company responds by offering free rides</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-28 17:43:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Finnish politician suggests sterilizing African immigrants 'to avoid total collapse' in Helsinki</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-28 20:14:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL After the death of Columbus, his heirs waged a lengthy legal battle with the Spanish crown, claiming that the monarchy short-changed them on money and profits due the explorer. The legal proceedings nearly dragged on until the 300th anniversary of Columbus #8217; famous voyage.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-29 18:31:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ISIS militants complain of Saudi favoritism in suicide missions: Saudi friends, family members favored on suicide  #8216;waiting lists #8217; letting others to get killed in battle - a less noble way to die.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-31 05:27:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Perhaps as a result of Valentine #8217;s Day romance, highest number of pregnancy and infertility test kits are sold during the first 3 weeks of March than at any other time of the year.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-31 15:40:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>279 migrant Indian workers died in Qatar last year, Amnesty International report says</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-31 19:39:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Buying sex made illegal in Northern Ireland under new law</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-01 18:49:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A 102-year-old German woman will become the oldest person to receive a PhD, which will be awarded to her by the Hamburg University on June 9, almost eight decades after the Nazis blocked it because her mother was Jewish.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-01 20:08:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-01 20:47:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>It will be awarded to her on June 9</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Uber faces crisis again in India after driver accused of trying to kiss passenger</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-02 05:10:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Iran: Ghezel Hesar prison executes dozens of inmates after they ask supreme leader forgiveness</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-02 17:18:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Alaska Governor Bill Walker issued layoff notes on Monday to more than 10,000 state employees, serving notice of a partial government shutdown that would begin on July 1 unless state lawmakers can agree on a budget for the forthcoming fiscal year.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-02 17:35:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Utah man gets prison for inventing his own church for tax avoidance</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-02 18:21:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bank Of America Fined $30M For Violating American Servicemen #8217;s Rights</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-02 19:17:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Morocco expels two French women after topless gay rights protest</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-03 05:29:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Montana police ticket driver transporting thousands of bees inside his car</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-03 18:12:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SAT cheating scandal broadens with indictment of 15 Chinese nationals</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-03 19:09:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Japan Officially Appoints Godzilla As Its Tourism Ambassador</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-03 20:21:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fish which can walk out of water and breathe on land for six days 'could spell major disaster' for wildlife in Australia</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-04 18:00:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>French schools have launched a crackdown on the African cultural practice of 'teeth-sucking' after teachers complained it was 'extremely vulgar' and offensive.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-04 19:10:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-05 18:21:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>In several other states, orphaned moose calves are often rehabilitated for release back into the wild with the help of private rehabs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Man saves baby moose, but then Montana wildlife officials kill it and blow it up with dynamite</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-05 19:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tajik IS Militants Told 'Return And Repent, And You'll Be Forgiven'</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-06 18:12:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>IS propaganda Video calls for jihad in Balkans on eve of pope's visit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-06 18:46:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nigerian Military's Atrocities Match Boko Haram, Says Amnesty</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-06 19:37:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>South Korea reports 14 more MERS cases, fifth death</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-07 06:20:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Florida legislators benefit from heavily subsidized health insurance</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-07 06:45:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A group of western tourists who stripped naked at the peak of Mount Kinabalu last month will be prohibited from leaving Malaysia, as their act of "disrespecting the mountain" could have caused the devastating earthquake that killed at least 13 people.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-07 10:29:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL In the late 1920s, Lysol disinfectant began being marketed as a feminine hygiene product. It was claimed vaginal douching with a diluted Lysol solution prevented infections and vaginal odor, and thereby preserved youth and marital bliss.This Lysol solution was also used as a birth control agent.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-14 05:34:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Canada outlawed baby walkers in 2004, saying they could be dangerous to babies, as well as delay motor and mental development. Anyone in possession of, or selling a baby walker, can face fines up to $100,000 or six months in jail.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-14 09:09:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Former Fed Chairman Alan Greenspan has a poorly veiled tic in his right eyebrow. Investors measured how high he raised it while talking, saying it was a better indicator of whether interest rates were going up.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-14 12:14:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Earthquake pushed 1 million Nepalese below poverty line</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-14 19:03:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Gun maker Colt files for Chapter 11 bankruptcy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-15 18:47:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Georgian Patriarch Blames Deadly Flooding On Communists' Sins</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-15 18:52:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Penguin Freed in Georgian Flood Crosses into Azerbaijan</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-17 19:00:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Uber Drivers Deemed Employees By California Labor Commission</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-17 19:04:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>International Whaling Commission asks Japan to justify its new "scientific research program" that plans to kill 3996 whales over 12 years.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-19 19:42:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A biotech startup has managed to 3-D print fake rhino horns that carry the same genetic fingerprint as the actual horn. The company plans to flood Chinese rhino horn market at one-eighth of the price of the original, undercutting the price poachers can get and forcing them out eventually.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-20 18:41:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>300+ Wildfires Rage in Alaska</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-28 18:36:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ISIS loyalists gain ground in Afghanistan</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 20:34:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Flash floods after a year's worth of rain in 3 days have killed 10 lions and 20 more remain missing in India's Gir National Park, the only natural habitat for lions outside of Africa.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-30 05:54:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Uber Bonds Term Sheet Reveals that the company generates $470 million in operating losses on $415 million in revenue.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-30 16:50:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Walmart apologizes after making ISIS cake, denying Confederate flag design</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-30 17:28:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Google Photos Mislabels 2 Black Americans as Gorillas</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-30 19:08:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #8216;Rent a Jew #8217;: German group launches program to stave off anti-Semitism</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-03 18:07:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Iran Repatriates 13 Tons of Gold Under Sanctions Relief</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 04:57:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mass Shootings Spread Like Wildfire. Contagion models suggest that 20-30% of school shootings occur within 13 days of a prior mass killing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 17:12:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Michigan lawmaker wants to call burning tires  #8220;renewable energy #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-06 17:57:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ISIS has cut off water supplies to the Mesopotamia Marshlands after capturing dams along the Euphrates River destroying wildlife and the livelihoods of the local people.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-07 17:33:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Kim Jong-un 'executes manager of terrapin farm for failing to supply food and water to the tanks'</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-08 13:22:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Earth heading for 'mini ice age' within 15 years</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 14:31:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Six Tropical Cyclones At Once in the Pacific Ocean on July 12</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-13 17:30:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Islamic State blows up baby while demonstrating members how to handle explosives</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-15 19:59:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An Australian TV Reality show smuggled a group of participants across the Syrian border to IS territory. They had a narrow escape as they came under heavy artillery fire from IS as filmmakers took them within half a mile of the front line.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-18 12:49:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A space rock worth $5.4 trillion is flying by Earth this weekend</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-18 17:23:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Uber Launches  #8220;De Blasio #8217;s Uber #8221; Feature In NYC With 25-Minute Wait Times</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-19 09:23:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>US consumers losing interest in new smartphone launches</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-19 12:20:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Snow falls on Mauna Kea as temperatures hit record levels</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-19 14:49:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>UK Wants 10 Year Prison Sentence For Online Pirates</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-19 15:58:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Over a Quarter-Million Vietnam War Veterans Still Have PTSD</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-22 19:44:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A New York City Airport is Building a Luxury Terminal Just for Animals</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-22 20:09:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL 50x was the highest surge pricing recorded by Uber Worldwide. At this price, recorded in Stockholm, a ride for a minute was costing $57.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-23 18:40:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>More than 1.2 million trees were planted across Australia on Sunday during National Tree Day. This year's tally brings the total number to over 22 million trees planted by more than 3.5 million participants since the annual event began in 1996.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-26 17:32:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Syria's Assad admits man power shortage, says army forced to cede territory</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-26 19:11:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL When Pyongyang's first golf course opened in 1994, Kim Jong-il was given the honour of playing the first round. He shot a 38-under-par round, which included 11 holes-in-one. His 17 bodyguards were put forward as witnesses to his remarkable feat.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-02 16:49:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Suicide blast hits Kabul police academy, heavy casualties feared</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-07 19:47:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rival lion kills one of Cecil #8217;s cubs, report says</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-09 16:22:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL On August 9th, 1945, a B-29 bomber left the island of Tinian intending to drop a plutonium bomb on the city of Kokura. On arriving at the target, the plane found it obscured by clouds. It turned south and went to its secondary target: Nagasaki.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-09 17:27:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Iran purchased several dolphins, some of which were former Soviet military dolphins in what some have alleged to be an attempt to develop kamikaze dolphins, intended to seek out and destroy submarines and enemy warships. However, the animals are today on display at the Kish Dolphin Park.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-09 19:27:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A firing squad of the Islamic State terrorist group on Saturday executed at least 300 civil servants who worked for the Iraqi Supreme Electoral Commission at a military camp in Iraqi city of Mosul.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-10 17:03:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Death Toll in Tianjin Blasts Rises to 85</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-15 05:58:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nearly 4,000 prisoners are currently battling wildfires across California making up about 40% of the nearly 10,000 firefighters deployed across the state. Participants make $2 per day in the program and $2 an hour when they #8217;re on a fire line.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-15 20:30:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Novak Djokovic complains to umpire about smell of cannabis during Rogers Cup tie, claiming it was making him feel 'dizzy'</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-16 15:02:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dog breastfeeds malnourished two-year-old child in Chile, saves life</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-06 19:07:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Over 1,050 Indian Islamic scholars and clerics have issued fatwa against the Islamic State terror group and described its acts and actions as against the basic tenets of Islam.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-08 18:40:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>82 people were killed and over 150 others injured after fireworks stored at a building caught fire and exploded in central Indian state Madhya Pradesh's Jhabua district Saturday morning.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-12 12:26:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Paper industry spends $170 million in a campaign to convince you to get back on paper</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-18 16:38:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>South Korea, host of the 2018 Winter Games, has been accused of bulldozing a 500-year-old virgin forest to make room for an Olympic ski slope.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-20 17:47:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Finland is Latest Nation to Establish Border Controls as Migrants Find Even Sweden Isn't Nice Enough</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-22 17:05:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cannabis 'forest' discovered in south-west London</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-25 15:08:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Decision Not to Close Schools During Muslim Holiday Sparks Uproar in New Jersey</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-25 15:41:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Military admits Syrian rebels exchanged US-equipment with al-Qaeda</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-26 13:51:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>30% migrants are fake Syrians, says Germany</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-26 18:40:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>EPA's fondness for high-end furniture costs taxpayers $92 million</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-26 18:56:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Suspects forced to stand on anthills, made to eat raw chili peppers and stripped naked and whipped in public - Mass Facebook vigilante movements are going viral in Peru, prompting civilians to punish alleged criminals for petty crimes.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-27 12:23:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Paris goes car-free for a day to fight pollution</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-27 20:15:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Russia's Orthodox Church supports Putin's decision to carry out air strikes in Syria against ISIS, calling it a "holy battle" for protecting the Christians in the region.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-04 17:46:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Facebook Dislike button arrives  #8212; in the form of reaction emoji</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-08 16:33:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>JetBlue Opens Urban Farm at JFK Airport to Feed Passengers and Local Food Banks</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-08 18:14:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>World's oceans facing biggest coral die-off in history, scientists warn</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-08 18:18:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bypassing the Risky Sea, Refugees Reach Europe Through the Arctic</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-09 16:18:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>News station replaces traditional TV cameras with iPhones and selfie sticks</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-10 10:01:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ninety of Mali #8217;s 300 remaining desert elephants have been killed during the past year as ivory poachers exploit a security vacuum created by an Islamic insurgency in the deserts near the city of Timbuktu.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-10 14:24:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Indonesia Haze: Singapore, Malaysia Gear Up To Fight Forest Fires</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-10 17:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Canadian start up has opened a pilot plant to take CO2 out of the atmosphere in the form of pellets. Company plans to scale it up on a Global scale enabling countries to suck more CO2 from the atmosphere than they dump in.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-11 15:00:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fire department saves iguana stuck in tree in Whitehall,Michigan</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-11 16:02:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mourners of Ankara victims chant anti-government slogans as death toll rises to 128</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-11 16:03:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Greenpeace is planning to buy four coal-fired power plants and their corresponding mines in Eastern Germany for $2.2 billion to shut them down.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-12 06:35:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>26 more elephants killed with cyanide in Zimbabwe</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-14 20:44:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>IMF Predicts Saudi Arabia Bankrupt by 2020</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-22 13:36:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-22 17:22:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Iceland's president explains how his country recovered so quickly from the recession:  #8220;The government bailed out the people and imprisoned the banksters  #8212; the opposite of what America and the rest of Europe did. #8221; http://www.businessinsider.com/olafur-ragnur-grimsson-iceland-2012-4?IR=T</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL 10% of the men who reside within the borders of the Mongol Empire as it was at the death of Genghis Khan are direct line descendants of Genghis Khan.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-25 08:18:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Greenpeace has been barred from bidding for the German coal operations of Swedish energy giant Vattenfall, which the environmental activists intended to shut down.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-02 19:19:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Indonesia is planning to build a prison island guarded by meat-hungry crocodiles for drug convicts. The reason for using the deadly reptiles as prison guards is that crocodiles cannot be bribed unlike human guards.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-10 10:27:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sweden calls on army to help manage refugee crisis</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-10 12:46:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Twin earthquakes with magnitudes 6.9 and 6.8, strike Chile</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-11 04:43:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Saudi Arabia #8217;s highest religious body has issued a strong condemnation of the attacks in Paris.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-14 14:27:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Suspected ISIS Terrorist Blows Himself Up in Turkey, 4 Cops Injured: Reports</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-15 09:41:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mumbai's Chhatrapati Shivaji Terminus Lit Up In Solidarity With France... With Dutch Flag Colours!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-16 15:58:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Paris attack mastermind may have committed suicide in raid, French ambassaador to India Fran #231;ois Richier says</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-18 16:09:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ISIS: "Hundreds Of Suicide Attackers" Are Waiting To Act</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 16:38:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thanks to Russian strikes, our troops advancing on  #8216;nearly every front #8217;, Syrian President Bashar al-Assad says</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-22 16:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Molenbeek mayor was given a list of jihadists a month before Paris attacks</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-26 03:31:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>France  #8216;could work with Assad's forces #8217; against ISIS</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-27 18:15:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Turkish president wishes plane downing had not happened</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-28 18:21:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>10,000 pairs Of shoes replaced Parisians In climate change march</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-30 16:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Eiffel Tower turns green as Paris Climate Summit kicks off</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-30 16:58:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL The Inner Court of ancient China #8217;s Forbidden City was the emperor #8217;s private realm, where no other men were allowed to stay at night. Male servants who stayed at night had both their penis and scrotum removed. A piece of bamboo was inserted in the urethra for urination.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-30 17:02:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Swedish pirate bay blocking decision will go to appeal</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-30 17:06:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL During the Cold War the US considered airdropping enormous condoms labeled  #8220;Medium #8221; #157; onto the Soviets, to demoralize them against an anatomically superior American Army. The plan was never carried out.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-03 16:19:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Norwegian newspaper has issued an apology to readers after publishing Santa Claus #8217; obituary.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-05 04:15:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The new global anti-Uber alliance: Ola, Lyft, Didi Kuaidi and GrabTaxi agree to ride together</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-05 19:28:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shipping is a big contributor to climate change. So why is it being left out of the Paris deal?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-06 18:20:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Poland could ask for nuclear weapons access under Nato program</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-06 18:26:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anonymous hacked the data of more than 1,000 climate change officials</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-06 18:34:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>France to sell land near Daesh-controlled Palmyra city in Syria</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-06 18:45:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Migrant crisis: Germany heads for 1m asylum-seekers in 2015</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-07 14:59:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Glaciers in Mt Everest shrink 28% in 40 years: Report</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-09 03:54:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sharp rise in wildfires in the Brazilian Amazon over the past 16 years</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-13 15:28:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Japan unveils net-wielding police drones for air patrol</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-13 15:41:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The new anti-refugee fences of Europe are killing wild animals</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-20 07:00:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Belize bans offshore oil drilling along barrier reef system</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-20 08:20:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Qatari royals rush to Switzerland in nine planes after emir breaks leg</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-29 18:32:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Major winter storm unleashes 60 cm of snow, travel delays in Turkey</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-02 03:59:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Another environmental activist is killed in Peru over his opposition to a major dam project</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-02 04:39:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Slowdown in Chinese manufacturing deepens fears for economy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-02 15:52:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>French academic defies Anne Frank Fund, publishes diaries online</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-02 16:07:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>'Israel is the only country Islamic State fears,' says first Western journalist to survive the terror group</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-03 10:25:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Trading on the mainland benchmark index, the Shanghai Composite, was suspended from trading on Thursday after shares plunged more than 7% for the second time this week.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-07 03:26:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Brent crude oil price drops to new low of $32 a barrel as US output rises</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-07 17:37:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Convictions unlikely in Cologne NYE incidents</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-08 03:57:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Seychelles, in a first-ever debt restructuring for climate adaptation, is swapping nearly $30 million of its debt in exchange for the protection of 30 percent of its ocean territory with an area larger than the size of Germany.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-09 06:28:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cologne sex assaults: Refugees attacked by mob, German police say</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-11 16:17:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Blast rocks square in central Istanbul, casualties reported</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-12 09:43:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Huge Explosion Hits Central Istanbul, Several deaths reported, Foreign tourists among the injured</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-12 10:09:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Number of people applying to carry airguns in public in Cologne shoots up in the wake of New Year's Eve sex attacks</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-15 16:21:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>South Korean president wants to hold North Korea talks #8212; without North Korea</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-22 15:10:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New poll shows Sanders chipping at Clinton #8217;s lead in S.C.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-23 04:36:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thousands of Brits have been left in pain after being fitted with hip implants in incorrect or "mismatch" sizes, a report has claimed.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-25 19:24:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>End Of An Era? Apple Warns iPhone Sales To Fall For First Time</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-27 04:09:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Google #8217;s DeepMind AI beats humans at the massively complex game Go</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-29 02:32:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Air our cars suck in Delhi dirtier than what they emit, claims automaker JLR</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-07 10:43:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>North Korea army chief Ri Yong-gil said to be executed</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-11 04:22:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>124 Crocodiles Suffocate In Mexico Truck Trip</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-11 04:30:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lightning in Bangladesh kills 42</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-14 04:27:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Brazilian judge orders Rio 2016 organisers to allow peaceful protests</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-09 16:04:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How Reuters "Tweaked" Its Latest Poll (Again) To Show A Clinton Lead</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-30 03:58:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New Zealand town builds a 25 meter long underpass to save blue penguins. The Oamaru tunnel allows the endangered penguin species, the smallest in the World, to avoid a deadly road during their nightly trek home from the sea.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-19 18:55:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Russia loses contact with a cargo ship headed to the International Space Station</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 17:32:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Philippines braces for severe typhoon on Christmas Day</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-24 13:47:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Costa Rica completes 2016 without having to burn a single fossil fuel for more than 250 days. 98.2% of Costa Rica's electricity came from renewable sources in 2016.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-01 13:37:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sterling slides to three-month low in Asia on Brexit concerns</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-16 04:37:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Canadian municipalities use beet juice to de-ice roads</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-16 18:12:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Brazil issues first license for sale of a cannabis-based drug</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 03:56:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Indian train network makes history by employing transgender workers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 13:15:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 16:17:09</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Environment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Dutch province of Flevoland is entirely man made. It's 1,419 square kilometers (548 sq mi) in size, almost a 30th of the country's total size.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-25 14:31:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>India has planted nearly 66 million trees in 12 hours</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 15:46:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tsunami warning issued after major quake of magnitude 7.8 strikes Honduras</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 04:09:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hazardous tsunami waves possible after 7.3 magnitude shallow quake hits Peru</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 11:00:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL 40 Million tonnes of mineral dust are blown from the Bod #233;l #233; depression in Chad, Africa to the Amazon basin each year. The dust helps keep the Brazilian rainforest soils fertile.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 14:50:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Boeing 737 Plane crashes on takeoff from Havana airport, Cuban TV reports</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 19:18:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>