<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject3644</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-09 18:33:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I prefer watching than playing Dota myself. I only watch competitive matches though, I don't see any difference between playing myself and watch ppl streaming it. I'm a really tryhard player, so I love winning much more than losing games (the only losses I found enjoyable are super close games without any douchebag). However my hero pool is fucking small, so I ended up playing the same things over and over. I'd want to master more heroes, but I was too lazy to practice, although some of them were too hard for me to even comprehend, I mean how can ppl play puck or invoker that smoothly! Anyway I got bored eventually, and after a few short breaks and comebacks I decided to quit indefinitely. That was a great improvement for me. Watching pro matches are far more enjoyable, especially when there are good casters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-10 10:06:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's such a shame to see Dota 2 become extinct in the Mecca of esports.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-11 14:44:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm all against freebooting on Facebook and other platforms, but I find it quite amusing when people keep listing Facebook views as their damages while Facebook view counting algorithm is clearly unreliable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-13 17:03:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't know if this is a thing but I also remember old Cloud 9 manager by his real name Conrad, don't even know what his nickname is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-14 17:51:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>[NoobfromUA delivered as usual.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pR9FAsFJqiw) Full dive and more highlights from the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-14 18:54:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>s4 possible thoughts during draft versus Mski: "Ugh I don't want to waste a ban on Huskar, so many OP shits to ban... Nah, fuck it, they won't run a pocket strat twice, just let it go" "Welp that game was a disaster, we were unprepared. I got it guys don't worry, we will counter it if they dare to run it again!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-14 20:57:50</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; SEA has to be the most inconsistent region overall. FTFY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-15 18:05:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did expect this but found out it was a joke when I realized it wasn't marked NSFW</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-16 22:39:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>He mean unknown can inspire pub player to build armlet instead of rad manta.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-18 19:34:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is Puppey tilting? Can he just sit the fucking in the fountain and land his ult instead of going around and get caught.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-18 20:47:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL production team should switch to VG booth cam when Burning ragequit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-18 20:53:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>The game is automatically paused when a player dc so it was definitely a ragequit. If it wasn't VG would let Burning reconnect so he can type gg and not make him look salty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-18 21:32:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems like a bug. No one has hats.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 12:40:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol classic Purge speaking without thinking. "She is 2k HP. She barely has any HP item at all" when she has bkb and sange.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 18:24:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think they should invent a score indicator for Bo2 matches. Tournaments still use this for their Bo2 matches and it's somewhat confusing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 20:23:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well in light of CDEC getting manhandled by OG please OP give us some updates on how Chinese think about it. A new thread would be even better!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-19 20:41:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not like Chinese teams can't/don't want to play meepo. It's just simply hard to execute, and it's basically a highly situational pick so it might not worth their time to practice it. Yeah it's their fault when they can't deal with meepo, but it's unfair to say that they should play it more. Beside secret and og, I don't see any other western teams using it, at least in this patch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-20 11:49:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>brb learning arabic and koran 101</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-21 14:27:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was a game for EG to win until rtz got solo picked up by Alch two times in a row. Even having items advantage OG didn't dare to push high ground because EG just simply split push much faster than their sieging speed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-21 17:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>omg someone please tell miracle just get a fucking bkb please!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-22 00:10:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kotlguy is still way too inexperience to be a decent host. If Redeye isn't available for the next major, Chobra would be a great substitute for him, proven by his performance at ESL One Frankfurt and TI5 group stage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-22 19:09:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>No they aren't. You can rearm Mek and Greaves, but they will be useless because you won't get another heal if the previous mek buff still exists</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-23 16:47:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It says "you fucker" in the subtitle I watched.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-23 16:59:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>This worked for me a year ago, but it doesn't anymore and I had to give up playing dota ;_; After few minutes of playing my laptop is hotter than satan's ballsack and it shuts itself down!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-25 19:05:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>So... no Puppey and EE couch?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-28 20:52:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn just 2 more seconds to end TSM journey! So intense! btw anyone know the song played right after map ending?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-30 19:57:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the first thing that poor guy should do is find a way to stop the bleeding before it's too late rather than trying to revenge. The dick is basically a balloon inflated by blood, so I think it's not a good thing to let it pop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-30 20:21:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry if it's late but I'm looking for a song played at the end of almost every map in this tournament. Tried google it but to no avail. Here it is http://www.twitch.tv/dreamhackcs/v/27878312?t=02h19m51s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-01 18:18:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>iirc mythbusters proved that acid disposal method doesnt work. This piggy one works though. source: my granpa has a pig farm.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-15 05:32:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>[What the fuck? What the fucking fuck?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8XqwO3FzP2Q)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 08:40:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Magnetic Field + Bloodlust + Assault Cuirass = Towers on steroids</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-17 06:01:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess the ability cooldown length is more reliable so they prioritized it over spell dmg. A 20 second cd skill will always be 20 seconds no matter what. A 300 dmg spell will have various results on different heroes using different items, could be 400 dmg, could be 200 dmg, so it's pretty relative and not that necessary to show additional 8% dmg. Just for example, a Necro with scepter and lv 3 ult will instagib an enemy having 47% HP, while with Lens the 1 hit KO threshold is only 2% increased which is 49%, so it's pretty irrelevant imo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-17 14:32:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Players are also paying Valve a lot of money, so they should be responsible for their services, and players have the right to demand it. How Valve is gonna figure it out is none of our concern, we just want the result. Dont you think that it's a little bit ridiculous for a service provider replying their customers "sorry please bear with it because our hands are tied?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-17 15:12:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every hero can be a viable jungler if they meet these two conditions: 1. They can farm or level up at least as fast as a normal safelane carry. 2. Their lineup can survive the early game without losing 2 out of 3 lanes. I see that you're trying to solve the first condition, but the second one is the main problem of this strat imo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-18 08:05:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>LPQ is meant to be a punishment, not a vacation. From your description it seems pretty okay to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-18 11:10:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>wow such a cool boss you are</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What should I get after Radiance on Spectre?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-19 06:56:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi /r/TrueDoTA2. Recently I've been spamming Spectre quite a lot and loved it because of his ability to join team fights frequently without losing much farming time. In my 2k9 enemies are still pretty tame so I can get radiance at 18-22 mins after tread aquila pms pretty much every game. However I'm confused on what the next ideal items would be after that. Usually I get Heart for the tankiness, but then my dmg output becomes really insufficient if my enemies ignore me, not to mention the item is pretty expensive and doesnt speed up my farm. When I tried to get diffusal, I'm too squishy and easily to be nuked down. I'd love to hear some input from you guys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-20 03:17:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm new to csgo, can you elaborate further why sometimes crouching is bad? I always crouch immediately when I encounter an enemy, thought it improved the accuracy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-22 05:08:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>In exchange of no free pathing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-23 04:49:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be fair this is some what better than OP's pic. Look at that giant rock monster punch, holyshit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-23 05:06:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Icefrog method of balancing is slowly switching toward heroes rotation i.e heavily meta based, patches favoring specific heroes. It's easier to add new heroes if you choose this way, just like LoL, instead of balance everything at once. For any games to live, they need fresh content. You can only have that many meta to switch around such as heavy pushing, lategame oriented... but new heroes are unlimited. It's also able to push the sales of comestics by deliberately buffing particular heroes having them, for example the recent Zeus arcana. So 14 new heroes is definitely not a wild guess, but at this rate of Valve adding new heroes, idk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-23 16:58:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Technically, yes. But you need to consider the reality. Heroes having "reasonable cooldown time" on their key spells are being forgotten. You dont see Enigma, Tidehunter, Warlock, Sandking... very often these days (edit: in pro matches), because they simply cant compete against those who have spammy spells.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-23 17:17:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>uhhh sorry im speaking about competitive scene. Sandking only has 1.9 and 4.6% pick/ban rate in 6.85 and 6.86, respectively.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-23 17:49:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im pretty sure that Icefrog is trying to make jungling viable again by introducing Iron Talon. If that's not the case idk what the heck that item is for.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-25 06:34:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember the dota 1 LC was a knight riding a horse, no?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-25 20:32:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unless it's a 5-man stack I'm pretty sure Gyro can outfarm naga in most pub games. By the time Naga got rad she might lose all outer towers already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-26 14:49:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why does this masterpiece only have 6k views? This deserves its own post on Reddit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-26 21:48:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Talking about cosmestics and shits, CS:GO even has Danny Trejo in [a fucking workshop promotion video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=krJvSi683zQ). Meanwhile Dota 2 is getting more and more lame sets like flying dutchman gyro or incoming assassin crEEd Ember! Not only players losing interest in items and trading, it seems to me artists also jumped the ship and went to a serious business over there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-26 23:10:05</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Any high rated players do good with him? I don't care about that Russian Zet player, he's essentially smurfing and if he was playing at 7k he'd be free food every game. What's your MMR? Take a look at [Meracle Arc Warden](http://www.dotabuff.com/players/91369376/matches?date= amp;hero=arc-warden amp;skill_bracket= amp;lobby_type= amp;game_mode= amp;region= amp;faction= amp;duration= amp;timezone=Asia%2FBangkok) records and see for yourself. He's 7k2 at the most toxic server in the world and still has 50% winrate with it, so I suppose Arc isn't free food at 7k (in case you don't remember this guy is the one made rat Naga become a big deal). And from his build I'm pretty sure his playstyle on Arc is similar to the Russian Zet player so you should take a look at [his vods](http://www.twitch.tv/vaxastyle/v/31881215), he might be a smurf but he's legitimately good. From my observation your micro has to be exceptionally good. It's all about efficiency when playing arc, without good micro you wont be able to split push and farm efficiently, you will feed a lot of necro minions while achieving nothing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-26 23:51:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's pretty easier said than done. Your points sound good but they dont seems practical for me. If you're playing Nyx as a support, your early rotation will just be as good as a lion/cm, maybe worse because you're melee, your mana burn wont do shit at early levels and he could always ghost walk away because your stun isnt RELIABLE. As a support you don't farm well, by the time you got blink which is essential against Invoker he could be too big of a problem to handle. You might have lv 4 mana burn, but could you survive that long to use it more than 2 times? Remember you're really squishy, and this is the meta of 5-man pub train. If you're playing Nyx as offlaner then you wont do shit against Invoker early. Nyx is also not a good offlaner. No escape mechanism, mediocre laning presence so you can't pressure the safelaner, or hard to compete farm. That's why it's better to play Nyx as a support. If you're playing Nyx as a support... **tl;dr:** what nyx can do lion can do much better. Mana burn sounds good in theory but isnt that practical.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-27 11:08:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's okay tapping is more efficient irl than spray and pray!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 10:02:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is a filter for patch 6.86 only statistics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 16:39:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>dafuq does the ":v" mean? Is this some kind of new meme I missed? Just left /r/dota2 for a day and I'm already /r/outoftheloop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 14:48:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not about the GOLD, it's about the efficiency of movement when you're playing cores. It takes times to ward, and if you have to do it as a cores, it will cost you a lot more than 75 gold when accounting for the time wasted. That's why supports are the most optimal role to do this shit, and it was intented when they buffed the passive gold income and reduced creep bounty. Not to mention item slots are valuable resource on carries in every stage of the game. I'm willing to buy two sets of wards as a core but no way I'm gonna travel across the map to put it myself. Sadly there are more supports find it okay to leave 2 sets of wards in the fountain than picking it up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 16:00:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>uhh they might also have a microwave to defrost I guess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 17:07:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>With teams like Steak or Winter's team, only their few last games were actually something. The rest of them were just like Secret vs Kappa Crusaders.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-05 09:45:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>As how Valve handling penalties in CSGO, the best plan for these players is that they should forget their Dota 2 careers and prepare for Dota 3 (in case it happens). It's likely to be indefinite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-06 20:59:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually I'm baffled by the fact that how the fuck this shit get upvoted to the front page? Is that many people find it reasonable?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-07 22:12:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically it's a strong niche pick, just like broodmother. If you don't specifically prepare for that and an enchant last pick catches you off guard then you're fucked. Game 3 of VEC (merlini's team) vs ex-Unknown last night was a prime example for this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-08 17:57:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you have a Youtube channel or anything showing the progress of creating these posters? I love your posts and it would be a great pleasure to watch and learn some design tips from you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-09 15:52:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Downvote me as hard as you can, but I'm pretty sure the CSGO one is better, or at least way more suitable to the game itself. Dota 2 uses ELO ranking system, and as you can see it's simply based on the outcome of matches i.e win/loss to calculate your rating. CSGO uses heavily modified Glicko-2, which is a CSGO-specific ranking system built by Valve. It considers multiple matchmaking parameters and rating variables to classify players accordingly to their skill groups i.e it doesn't matter if you win/lose, but more of how much you win by/lose by, how you perform in the match. That's why CSGO ranking sytem can't be represented by a single numeric value like Dota 2's MMR. So you guys might wonder why Dota 2 doesn't use that system? Because Dota 2 is way more complex game than CSGO. In CSGO you dont have clear roles, players' performance can be somewhat quantify by frags, kda ratio... and it's comparable between players in the same game. In Dota 2 you have specific roles with different kinds of impact in game, not to mention a massive hero pool. A player can be extremely good at some heroes but suck at many others, and it's impossible to build a ranking system being able to compensate for that. You might argue that CSGO also has many maps, but then everyone playing the same map in the same game, so it's comparable. In the end both ELO and Glicko-2 are initially built for 1v1 1-round games, so they both have massive flaws when implementing to team games like CSGO or Dota 2. But as I said, to some extend the CSGO one is a little more accurate than their counterpart in Dota 2. Recently Valve just made a big fix to their rank system in CSGO. What was the last time Valve did anything to Dota 2 ranking? Tbh Valve might think Dota 2 is too complicated to do anything so they just let it be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-09 16:55:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think party ranking shouldn't be a thing except for 5-man party. Valve might already consider that, but also doesn't want to discourage people from invite their friends to play so they made a compromise in CSGO, which is no party ranking, but allow parties to play in ranked match with their solo ranking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-09 17:02:09</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; [Eternal Envy is a glamorous and girly boutique...](http://www.eternalenvy.com/pages/about.php) Fair enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-09 21:38:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once you reach global if you're really good you wont play mm anymore. Most pros and high skill player play at community servers such as ESEA and Faceit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-10 12:35:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's how counter works.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-10 14:07:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dagger spam is no longer as effective as it used to be, when there was only 1 rune every 2 minutes, bottle crow got nerfed and you have to contest rune with a bitch having blink. Now either you're Invoker who has shit ton of regen and coldsnap the shit out of qop, or you have enough runes to refill your bottle and always being full HP.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-13 15:49:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Power creep of Dota 2 at its finest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-14 11:18:15</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; In a holistic view, we have traded a reliable cooldown reduction to an inefficient accuracy that benefits VERY few heroes AND also counters a SMALL POOL of heroes rather than a universal application. This isn't how item balancing in this game work. With more and more items are added to Dota 2, they're supposed to be unique and benefit only a handful of heroes, so every item has chance to be pick up and not being forgotten forever (looking at you Veil of Discord). And as a OD spammer I guarantee that 40% accuracy is no way an "inefficient accuracy". It's insanely good. Cast that shit on Windrunner and your team will have no problem shitting on her even under windrun buff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-14 11:24:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why didn't you sort heroes by their popularity so we might see the correlation between that and items? Looking at your graph I don't see anything but a bunch of dots lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-14 17:57:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>In scale of 1 to 420, how high were you when making this set?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-15 01:14:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey guys I found an abuser here, what should I do?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-15 01:20:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's just an ads from Google Adsense, not by D2L. You might also be able to see that on any Dota 2 related sites.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-15 18:17:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could anyone here provide the full context? From what I've seen it looks like Nahaz fired shots first out of the blue and the CSGO celebs just showing their disappointment toward that. If that was the case then both parties are dumb.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-16 17:21:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why don't OP link the oddshot vid directly, instead he made a self-post? It mildly annoyed me and I've seen it quite frequently recently, not only this sub but several others. Just curious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-16 18:34:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not if you have a decent amount of money to spare. [This agency](http://www.space-affairs.com/index.php?wohin=mig29nn_d) provides some flying tours on several Russian jetfighters such as Mig-29. They don't list their price there but iirc it's about $13k for a 30-min trip, and $18k if you want a 1-hour trip on Mig-29 to the absolute maximum altitude at 72.000 ft.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-17 13:03:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Feels like TI4. Most Alliance games were heavy pushing 20 mins deathball. Good for them but this is so shit to watch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-18 14:28:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell that to teams played Death Prophet at Starladder 13.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Advices on OD v. Invoker mid matchup?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-19 17:30:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi guys! I'm learning to play mid with OD. I'm 3k3 now so I'm pretty comfortable with most mid matchups because my enemies either have bad lasthit skill or tend to be overly aggressive and feed. However once in a while I meet some Invoker players, they just chill and contest last hitting with me. They go full exort so their dmg is so huge I can't properly compete, get all the cs and deny most of their creeps. When I try to bully them with orb, they immediately coldsnap and summon forge spirit to hit me. I would take a lot of dmg by the time I killed their spirit or imprisoned the Invoker, so I usually imprison myself to evade and walk away after that, but sometime they have sunstrike ready and I still take a huge chunk of dmg, and if they have supports waiting a round I'm pretty much dead. Although we can't kill each other, they always win the cs heavily and I'm really underfarmed. If I tp to help fight in other lanes, they get free mid tower because they push insanely fast. The game goes downhill from there as they keep snowball with midas. So guys, how do I deal with this kind of shit? Is there any particular skill build or itemization for this matchup? Currently I'm going with 4-1-4 skill build.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-19 18:12:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>As I said I choose to imprison myself because I feel it's the most effective way in that situation because he can only invoke only one more spell (usually sunstrike because he went QE build) if he already has coldsnap and forge spirit. If he walk up after imprisonment ended I just walk away because I no longer have coldsnap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-19 18:16:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Orchid is pretty much my go to build after forcestaff most of my games (I usually get it at about 20-22 mins) because of high killing potential. But the shitty thing is QE invokers tend to have euls and it renders the orchid useless!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-21 15:08:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>From [this Nahaz post](https://www.reddit.com/r/DotA2/comments/41zwf3/nahaz_wont_be_attending_the_shanghai_majors_as/cz6h6t2) and redeye's non attendance, I guess English coverage will just be casters only, no panel or analyst desk on site at all. Just like how it worked in DAC.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-21 23:26:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you have connection issues then you shouldn't play Dota ffs. Your fucking connection issues ruin the game for 4 other players, you deserve to go to LPQ. Valve doesn't put you into LPQ just after 1 abandon, they only do that when you repeated it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-23 16:16:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It won't happen unless it becomes a pain in the ass in pro matches.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-23 16:25:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Control runes. You have 90x3 HP heal per rune. His lightning arc only deals 63 dmg after magic reduction, and costs 65 mana. Each rune only provides 60x3 mana. That means if you get atleast 1 rune each cycle, you should be fine because it heals you more than his ability to harass. When you're better you can even play more agressive and try to bully him out of the lane, especially with OD and invoker.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-24 05:59:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! Idk why but both the oddshot link and youtube mirror seem choppy to me, even when fully buffered and replayed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-28 14:26:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>The SEA dota scene has been dead for several centuries and somehow they still managed to snatch 2 slots in every TI and major. They even get a fucking major instead of CIS region!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-28 14:39:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ayesee game knowledge is insufficient, but at least he has professional experience in broadcasting and a golden voice which can compensate for that to some extent. Lots of new casters just came out of nowhere without anything mentioned above, ofc they fell flat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-29 16:16:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just like how Na'Vi still keeps Dendi when he's just a mediocre mid now, instead of picking some random 8k pubstars and they would become new w33 and miracle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-07 15:32:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I watched a bulldog stream recently, he said he would never get necrobook on NP (idk why), if you can get an early midas then get it, if you're really far behind then get mek.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-08 11:55:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rubick's first skill.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-09 12:43:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's why when you report someone, make sure you put it in "communication abuse" category. It could make that player unable to chat or spam ping for 24 hours or more. Other than that it's pointless to report.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-10 03:44:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just tuned in, did I miss Trump's winning speech guys?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-12 05:00:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so proud to be the one inform you about this awesome series ["You Can't Stump the Trump"](https://youtu.be/s0Tn8WFMvQU?t=33s)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-12 05:14:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Their mind would be blown if they know he was supposed to share that Nobel prize with a communist!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-12 07:59:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im pretty sure the top deleted post was this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-12 11:08:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did what you said recently and I lost like 1k MMR right away. Immediately recover after spamming OP shits only. [Here is the progress.](http://i.imgur.com/ypv9d3E.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-14 14:31:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>People will always find a way to pass no matter what. Even a DMZ with mines every step cant prevent people coming to South Korea from the North. As long as crossing the border and coming to the US is far more rewarding than staying, there is no realistic way to stop it. With that problem I think the US should be tougher on dealing with undocumented labors. Make it impossible for them to earn money if they came here illegally. I'm not from US so I don't know if it's already the case, but maybe make it a felony to employ illegal immigrants?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-14 21:14:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always wish for the Trump-Sanders matchup. They might share some common ideas and both are strong anti-establishment but Trump is so good at debating and I think he would have an easy time against Sanders. However I feel his "rude and blunt" style might not work well against a female candidate. Hillary also seems scary for me because of her excellent experience in foreign policy, which isn't his strong suit. I'm really afraid she would crush him in that topic like how she has been doing so far against Sanders.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-15 18:46:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>It'd better happen soon, otherwise there will be no war at all because half of the army will pray "allahu ackbar" every morning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-16 07:43:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Half a second is a pretty big deal when you see it as 23% reduction, and usually that skill procs every time it's off cd when you're jungling, so you get heal a lot more. If you opt for 1 point E build, you can't kill big camps wtihout significant HP loss, especially the Hellbear camp.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-16 07:49:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's why I only get it when I play against furion and broodmother. Other than that its damage potential is fucking negligible. The ms bonus is not that useful when I have my blink. Tbh that skill need a rework so it has some sort of synergies with the rest of his skills.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-16 10:02:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell that to admiralbulldog. In my opinion this guy has the smallest hero pool among 7k+ streamers out there. Never see him play any "flashy" hero.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-18 04:34:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>So he doesn't have to waste money on TV ads and still gets shitload of exposure. That's what you get when you have to fund your campaign by your own money instead of donations form special interests. He's a genius businessman, so not only every vote counts, but every penny counts as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-18 13:33:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like how he's still able to instantly deliver such savage one-liners in a serious business as presidential debates to make his opponents look like a fool. Hearing something like "she should be running" makes me giggle like a little girl. Political or not, people always love a man with a good sense of humour.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-19 05:48:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've always wondered if it's true that being a state governor is better than VP since I watched House of Cards.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-19 14:31:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not coincidence that Bernie Sanders are super popular and loved on the internet and to be specific, reddit. The largest demographic of the internet is leftist, liberal shills so it's understandable that those who have rightwing viewpoints will be opressed heavily and become the silent minority.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-19 16:14:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wikipedia defines a shill is someone publicly helps or gives credibility to a person or organization without disclosing that they have a close relationship with the person or organization. It even has example of unintentional shill, as a satisfied customer giving biased opinions to further the interests of a company. edit. but i admit that word isnt the appropriate one, but i wont call them fan, it sounds too respectful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-19 16:26:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>iirc Trump said that socialism, single payer health care worked in those countries because their population is tiny, while America is an enormous one with more than 300 millions people and it makes sense to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-19 16:28:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>ok you're right</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-19 16:56:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very good one. I love the Trump tie! I just want to suggest we omit the eyebrow or rework it. The left one is too small to be visible and the right one look like a bandage on his forehead when viewing as thumbnail (would be even smaller when it becomes icon)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-19 18:16:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Talking about wait time I think one reason making Trump change his mind about universal healthcare (he supported it before) might be the veterans health scandal where 40 vets died while wating for care.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-19 19:44:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>So if I fill a very long bottle with 99 liter of water and 1 liter of a "heavier liquid", does the water still float on the other one? I can't imagine it happening because the bulk of water is so heavier than that liquid how could that happen?! (or mb I'm just dumb)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-20 06:15:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait a minute how about ashes? What are they?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-20 06:57:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why not heaven's halberd? Roughly same price as force staff, high range linken popping device and good on LC. Abyssal's active is too valuable to waste it on linken.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-21 04:13:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>According to [7 stages of grief](http://i.imgur.com/0Zhub4B.png), last time they were Anger. This time Huffpost sounds like they went to Depression already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-21 04:39:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>This thread looks like a parody for the donate call thread from sanders sub so I wouldn't mind it. However, he definitely needs help. Lots of his assets are real estate, meaning it's non-liquid. For campaigning you need liquid assets and mostly cash. I doubt he has more than half a billion in cash. And he already took a big hit on his business when he run for president. He lost a lot of business deals when he made those controversial statements about immigrants and muslims. If he win at the end then it's not a big deal, but if he lose it would be devastating. I could really see he went bankruptcy again if he won't make it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-21 05:00:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jump ship doesn't mean jump off the ship into the water. It means you leave the ship without permissions (as a sailor) when it's temporarily parking in a port during a trip). Maybe you smell blood in the water, so you decide it's dangerous to be onboard?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-21 06:07:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>About Univision he only said on his twitter that he "settled" the lawsuits. It's unclear that if he really did sue them or it's just a threat, and he still had to sell his stake in Miss Universe after that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-21 06:29:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imagine he plays Bristleback!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-21 15:41:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Although Bernie losing is inevitable, I still want him to keep running as long as possible. These stubborn Rubio and Cruz won't give up anytime soon, I don't want Hillary has a lot more time prepare for the general than our emperor Trump.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-21 16:06:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You mean [this circus](http://i.imgur.com/LfQOJI8.jpg)?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-21 17:31:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Surprise!](https://www.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/202wd3/i_participated_in_one_of_the_biggest_magic_the/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-21 20:17:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd rather mute all the players than have to wait 3 times longer for a game. Communication is overrated anyway, if you watch rtz stream you will see that he barely speak but still get 8k easily. I haven't seen a single toxic players since I started to mute everyone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-22 04:35:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>You split the player base, of course queue time increase, because there will be fewer player searching for games at any given time. Isn't that common sense?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-22 06:30:00</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I do not have exact numbers and statistics to back me up, but you would be surprised how popular Dota 2 is in this region that splitting the player base will not matter. I'm only quote this, because the rest of your comment is irrelevant with what I said. The player base might be huge, but at any given time most of them are playing. The only thing matters is the number of people actually queueing at that time, and it's surprisingly small because Dota 2 has a long average game time. The effect is really significant even when only a single queue options added, the player base get fragmented heavily because matchmaking system has to take into account individual ranks, game modes etc.Valve's first priority (and even Riot's) is always queue time when it comes to balancing matchmaking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-22 07:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just make a free blog at https://wordpress.com/, very easy to do for beginners. When you have traffic and recognition, money eventually come :p Remember share us your site when you're done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-22 11:22:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>These posts might sound retarded, but at least it shows some kinds of commitment. The hilarious thing is that a large amount of people in Bernie sub are just bandwagoners "only talk, no action" (kinda ironic how they support an ant-establishment candidate but act like a real established politican). I laughed my ass off when seeing a thread complaining about how a TX phonebank thread got 300 upvotes and 20 rsvps but only 1 person showed up at the event. Pathetic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-22 15:34:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Invoker is supposed to be a jack of all trades, master of none kinda hero, and I think he's in a right place now. Having lots of skills but nothing exceptionally good. People have to make the right choice of skill for each situation to be useful rather than sticking with only one combo all the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-22 15:56:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it would be the same as milk, once you open the bottle, you finish it in a certain amount of time or it will rot?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-23 13:26:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>This kind of opinion really bug the shit out of me. What exactly is "take next to no effort to produce"? If that's the case then everybody should be a YouTube millionaire right now. YouTube rewards those who can produce videos consistently, because that's what viewers want, they're a business, they have to pander their customers. You say that animation is hard to produce, but do you know how hard it is to produce enjoyable content on a weekly or even daily basis without running out of ideas or becoming dull? If you're good and unique, then you still get shitload of money even when you only have 1 video every 6 months. Look at Alan Becker! I understand you have a point, but shitting on other publishers like that to show it isn't a good thing to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-23 13:52:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's always easier said than done. There are literally thousands of youtube publishers doing what you said out there, if it's really as easy as you said, why only a few of them hit the jackpot? YouTube is a really fair environment for everyone. How exactly do you want YouTube pay animators more? How do you quantify the goodness of their works and compare them with others? If suddenly YouTuve favors those who release 1 video per month, then everybody else will do that, and as a viewers you will get less content everyday to watch. Lots of "good and unique" animators don't have recognition, but so do millions of let's play/reaction/reviews... people. It's a harsh environment for everyone, not a walk in the park. It's harder for some, as you said, but when you decided to play a game, you have to follow its rules.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-23 16:19:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blame the players, not the game. Seriously for anyone who doenst play dota that clip is shit to them, do you expect it has the same popularity for a video anyone can get it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-23 16:55:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>His point is that dota clip has lower recognition than that retarded clip. I just explain why. What are you talking about?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-24 05:20:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here is a little lifehack: browse Bernie sub in controversial tab to enjoy cucks' tears. Filter links from last 24 hours after every Dem primary to count people on suicide watch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-24 06:49:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Top 10 /r/all in 36 mins. TACTICAL NUKE INCOMING!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-24 07:39:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think a tank can fly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-24 11:41:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder what the next narrative will be when Trump pulls out a landslide victory in super tuesday. Waiting for Florida I guess?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-24 14:41:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm glad that US politics doesn't have the brawling tradition like [Ukraine](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=emKIIv2_cNI), otherwise they would shit bricks if they have to debate against Trump.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-24 15:41:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vietnamese reporting in! Most people here love the Clintons. Under Bill Clinton administration, diplomatic relations between two countries were fully restored, and people see him as a friendly and pacifist US president. Average Vietnamese people don't know much about Hillary and stuff like Benghazi etc., they only see Hillary as the former first lady of a nice potus, a strong woman, a competent secretary of states, so they love her. This is amplified by the fact that people here love Democrats because MSM tends to paint Republicans as hawkish and warmongers (especially Dubya). Usually the primary doenst get much coverage here because most people are uninformed about how US presidential election works, but it gets some articles here and there because of Trump and his comments about TPP and how VN is stealing jobs from US! In the comment section of those article most comments are just "I support Mrs. Hillary", "I wish Hillary get elected", "If Trump gets elected WW3 will happen". Pretty amusing I must say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-24 16:26:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you. However, I believe in "There ain't no such thing as a free lunch". We can make things cheap, so we might get the better end of the deals. But it always comes with a cost. We can make things cheap because we have cheap-ass labors, we have no regulations, our OSHA and EPA are basically a joke. Unless Trump want to bring environment pollution and slavery kinda jobs back to America, no way he can get a better deal, because that's just how things work. That's the thing always bug me with Trump's rhetoric.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-25 04:57:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Appreciate it man!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-25 06:13:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually I don't support either of them, I'm a fan of Trump, agree with a lot of his positions. I don't follow democrats race closely, but I prefer Hillary over Bernie. I don't like his minimum wage proposal and his body language during debates kinda turn me off, doesnt look presidential.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-26 10:37:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cmon dude, people get fired for their fuckups everyday. He dropped bunch of f-bomb in a family show, he got fired, what's the big deal? Enjoy the games jeez.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-26 11:03:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This gif](http://i.imgur.com/DRlMVuG.gifv) is also great to describe today's debate. Cap is conservative extremist Ted, Rubio is that cyborg and Trump is Ironman, who is a brilliant and charismatic billionaire.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-26 17:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>What exactly did you support the tournament by buying battle pass?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-27 11:56:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope OG fires this Doom ass after this tournament. Such a fucking burden, do more harm than good. Just doom the rubick ffs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-27 12:47:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone knows about PR 101 understand that this is just a tactical move by James, playing the victim card and turn this into a lose-lose situation for Valve, control the damage to his own reputation. Public opinion always side with the weak one against corporations no matter what. If the company is the right one, and they try their best to defend, they would look petty. If the company is the wrong one, obviously they're fucked. Valve actually doesn't have to do anything. Ignore this. Because from the business viewpoint they seem to be the right one here. And the other companies, which matter to James' career, already know about these PR shits, they don't care, damage has been done. The current party being upset is players, but honestly Valve don't give a fuck about that. People has the memory span of a gold fish and most are uninformed, they still gonna buy compendium/battlepass in the next shanghai majors. How about talents? Valve's events are too prestige to give up to publicly defend someone's fuckups and burn bridges.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-27 16:22:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>People who got their signs stolen should upgrade theirs to [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eKRryRyHZbg) (even electrify it!)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-28 15:53:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seriously, only 1 step? It's safe to say that Gabe is several orders of magnitude less significant than the names you mentioned. They're the final bosses of massive multi billions public conglomerates. Valve is a relatively small private company with less than 1,000 employees. However to the inner circle of gaming industry he still is a prominent figure, and James is totally fucked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-28 18:09:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shhhh... don't break the circlejerk..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-29 16:31:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The scary thing is that this post has been posted in /r/worldnews, and then quickly deleted by mods over there while having a lot of comments and upvotes. This censorship policy of reddit mods in many subreddits is fucking bullshit. It's not a hoax, it has image and video evidence, and somehow they still try to hide it! I guess these mods won't wake the fuck up until a jihadist decapitates their own children in front of them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-29 21:06:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope that you're joking. You do know that temporary foreign labors do exist, right? Most blue-collar workers in wealthy Middle East countries are foreigners. They're the ones stayed outside 10 hrs everyday to build Burj Khalifa. Japan also imports a lot of foreign workers from south east asia countries every year. They're all legal and temporary, usually 3-5 years per contract. Isn't that much easier to control? Since many developed countries still do well without illegal immigrants, this "deporting illegals is not good for the economy" argument sounds really weak.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-01 09:56:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>That Donald Trump portrait will be the one on the US$200 bill issued in 2024 after Ivanka becomes the first female potus. Source: I have a Ph.D in Divination.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-01 17:51:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>[MSM get BTFO! Based Ron Paul!](http://i.imgur.com/vwMin.gifv)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 01:39:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow thank you! High energy post right there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 02:10:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.nytimes.com/elections/results Fast and easy to follow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 02:20:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>free cnn stream here, livechat available http://2ndrun.tv/news_directory/national/cnn/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 03:21:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's okay guys our most dangerous enemy is Rubio and he's not winning shits, not even meeting the 20% threshold for delegates. Expect drop out anytime soon. Cruz isnt even a threat the establishment even hate him more than Trump. Nomination is coming!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 03:49:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only Donald Trump has balls to hold a press conference and answering questions instead of making boring stump speech like everybody else. Respect!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 05:07:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>here you go https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3OGJa37SOXY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 05:15:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least this will ends Ted Cruz's silly rhetoric "I'm the only one who beat Donald Trump"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 05:39:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>CNN projected MA for clinton</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 07:17:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>What 1960? Do you know what event they're talking about? Hint: Scott Kelly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 08:42:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not only he has a plan, but it's also an in-depth plan. He spent [over 1 million](http://www.slate.com/blogs/the_slatest/2013/05/27/donald_trump_spend_1_million_to_research_potential_presidential_candidacy.html) just to research for presidential run. How do you outperform every other candidate while only spending 25 million so far without a plan? (Clinton, Sanders and Cruz spend 97, 81 and 41 million, respectively). An opportunist is someone like Chris Christie, Trump is a strategist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 08:48:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Admiral Bulldog's low hero pool is starting to bite Alliance in the ass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 09:25:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look at it this way: Alliance has played 7 games so far in this tournament, and 4 of them was AdmiralBulldog playing Beastmaster. That's not the ideal diversity, consider the fact that BM is a somewhat situational pick and definitely not a OP hero this patch (kinda discounted Void). s4 draft is fine tho.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 09:51:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uh.. yes? You can't draft much when your teammate can only play that many heroes, and most of them got banned or picked by opponents. Are you the one stupid here?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 10:02:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn't Liquid pick the same cores as well? Both games were NP/Invoker vs BM/Naga.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 10:49:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well said. That's why Trump positions and policies are highly vague (merely 30s video for each issue in his official campaign website), unlike other candidates putting lots of effort describing them. He targeted that specific demographic and he knows they don't care much about details. And surprisingly they're the most loyal and hard to sway, so he's immune to attacks (bigot, racist, xenophobic...). The more political informed people are, the higher chance they can change their minds. I guess 1 million researching for presidential run of Trump paid off very well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 11:56:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not kidding if this is a League of Legends major tournament MVP definitely gonna get fined.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 14:43:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well at least there will be no caster advantages for Chinese teams.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 15:56:24</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; his Beastmaster is insane I give up you win rofl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 18:06:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you guys don't get refund then this is basically a fucking scam. I'm not a lawyer but this sounds like a fucking class action lawsuit right there. Go sue them!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 06:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>What? Disrespect? [Welcome to real sport dude.](http://giant.gfycat.com/UncommonNauticalKillerwhale.gif) edit: lol at these retard downvoting the truth</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 08:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not a surprise, he deliberately do it. [This article explained it well](https://www.bostonglobe.com/news/politics/2015/10/20/donald-trump-and-ben-carson-speak-grade-school-level-that-today-voters-can-quickly-grasp/LUCBY6uwQAxiLvvXbVTSUN/story.html). For comparision, this is [a Ivy League version of Donald Trump speaking.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Rksd80-FCAw)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 09:17:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not a big deal with someone like Puppey or EE. edit: fuck you Puppey and EE haters</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 09:33:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>His build this game is basically still the normal Void build, which is blink and agh. Vlad is not a must have item every game since its main purpose is just for farming sustain before getting blink. This game MoM is better since you have to counter phoenix attack debuff and burst down slark in chrono. Diffusal is a situational picks to counter obvious incoming ghost scepters (clinkz duh!) and it also works against silence debuff from ES.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 09:36:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>He uses it because why not. It doenst mean he desperately needs it. That dude is a genius in drafting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 09:52:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally I also think climate change is a hoax. I know about scientists saying this or that, but I haven't witnessed anything "changed" yet, so I don't think that claim is that bad. There's a lot more things way higher up in my priority list than these environmental nonsense. Just my personal opinion tho.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 10:09:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>LET'S GO EHOME LET'S GO!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 10:37:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Players should realize blink enigma is no longer a viable build anymore, wasting 2k gold for an item having no use but enhancing an unrealiable skill. Just go for utility items like Puppey and become a walking threat. Lackluster performance from lanm and cty costs them the game despite of having somewhat better early game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 11:07:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Build it like Puppey has been doing all the time. Mek, arcane boot, greaves, crimson guard, bkb... Much more useful for overall teamfight than just all in on a single blackhole. 2k gold is 2/3 amount of money for a crimson guard already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If Ted Cruz wasn't a nasty liar, his rally backdrop would look like this</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 16:08:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 16:37:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the actual fuck? You asked why Trump denying climate change isn't bad, I give you my opinion why I think that's not bad. Get your downvotes and fuck off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 18:07:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, and it's called Blitz chess. Do you think an average master can win a game against Magnus Carlsen even when he has more time to think? [This](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yqxnZoaTUDI) would be how Puppey draft against most captains, maybe except PPD.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 18:19:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where do you think young people get education from? The government, the older ones! The hatred against Japan and Korea will never go away in China, just like how religion never ceases to exist. To back up my statements, please google "2012 China anti Japan protests" and count the number of young people in those images.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 18:22:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's why I said "except PPD". Are you dim or smth?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 18:29:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's would be a horrible scenario. Because even when Chinese teams are in a slump right now, they're still miles ahead SEA Dota (except Fnatic/MVP ofc). If the next major only has 3 Chinese team (1 invite, 2 qualifier), it will only push the China scene into the point of no return faster.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 21:23:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Friendly reminder that MVP has ping disadvantage when playing against SEA teams. I highly doubt SEA teams can win a bo1 against MVP in LAN, let alone bo3. And I don't underestimate anything, I just form my statement based on the fact that SEA teams haven't had any meaningful achievement in recent major LANs (MDL, WCA, Starladder, The Summit, Frankfurt Major...)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 22:04:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don't have to be captain when you're in a team having a NA version of Puppey.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-03 22:55:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you take your second paragraph out of context, it can be used as an argument to talk about real sports as well, so I'm a little confused about what's the message you want to share here. It seems like you're trying to devalue the additional productions. Good production is good production. A lackluster production value in a certain event doesn't represent its importance and effect on esports, and Dota in particular. Where were you when the Frankfurt Major and TIs happened? Did you see how good production value and professionalism made the even much more enjoyable? Luckily, there's an option for people like you. Just use Dota 2 client and tune in to watch games whenever they're available. Pure Dota, no bullshit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-04 10:41:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any huge play in pro dota is just one team punishing mistakes of their opponents.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-04 11:09:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some criminal magnates in the same caliber of Pablo Escobar?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-04 13:16:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Except Universe immense hero pool is universally acknowledged by everyone lol. Don't compare that one trick pony from Alliance with Universe. Btw come tune in alliance v. col to see that residentsleeper NP get shit on the face.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-04 13:30:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's just his habit from public ranked, he always has like 40-50 mins queue time so he has to disconnect as soon as the game ends to find new game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-04 14:01:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have long queues because your MMR are too high so you usually only match with high MMR players, which is scarce. Therefore by disconnect early and find queue immediately, you have the chance to meet other high MMR players who are on the queue already and join game with them, or meet the high MMR players in your previous game finding again. If you somehow find game late a little bit, the players in your previous game might found game already and you miss that batch, so you have to wait another hour to have high MMR players again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-04 14:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL eat shit Alliance. Icefrog buffed Bulldog's heroes so he can be relevant again, Gabe fucked over Liquid so they can have direct invite. Too bad NA dota doesn't tolerate these bullshits. CoL delivered the justice hammer! Exterminated the disgusting rats! Chinese teams get rekt? Alliance gets rekt? Secret winning? Best Major ever! edit: one downvote = one liter of Alliance fangays tear</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-04 14:53:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>ITT: people who doesn't realize this is a sarcasm post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-04 14:57:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most players in any Premier League club aren't British, why do people consider them English clubs? Because they play in English league. Just like how CoL coming from NA qualifier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-04 15:08:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Desperate people do desperate things.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-04 15:13:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I only heard people called Liquid NA during the ixmike/TC version. Never heard anyone called current Liquid and OG NA.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-04 19:03:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>CoL isn't a NA team? Then why do they come from NA qualifier? Do you call soccer clubs playing in Premier League international teams because most of their players aren't British? There are only 6 teams left, 2 SEA, 2 NA, 2 EU. Still asking why people go nuts about NA and SEA. So do you want people praising Alliance instead? Yeah I know your favorite team get rekt, it sucks, but don't deny other team achievement like a sore loser.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-04 19:08:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Too bad after next patch they will likely become shit again, just like OG right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-04 19:14:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Woah the best artwork I've ever seen in this sub. Very good facial expression of the minions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-05 11:00:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why does a buffalo represent scalpers (in the second day comic)?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-05 16:29:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Too bad MVP is like [Lonesome George](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lonesome_George) of Korean Dota. Once they disband, Korean Dota is officially over.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-06 05:57:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your first argument is the reason of having law. Punishing someone based on morality alone is ridiculously flawed. [This video explained that extremely well.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kBdfcR-8hEY). Your second argument is the reason of having trials and judges. A case has never happened before will be decided by a judge during a trial, and it'll set the legal precident for similar cases in the future. You can't simply decide to put some form of punishment to Empire based on public opinion without having any trial, or at least some kind of hearing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-06 07:02:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>So what's your point? No one here argue if kicking players is a moral decision. The moral decision here is in the thread title "we should punish Empire for that". Even with that, your post is simply wrong. Moral decision is a choice based on a person's ethics, manners, character and what they believe is a proper thing to do. People bases their moral decision on a variety of references, including religious beliefs, personal values and logical reasoning. Fiscal decision is just a moral decision based on logical reasoning. OP's decision is a moral decision based on personal values.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-06 07:15:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a moral decision according to the academic definition of moral decision, which I've mentioned above. And seriously I don't get your point here, since my original post is about defending the idea of not punishing people based on morality alone, and your replies seem completely irrelevant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-06 07:59:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>sanders for president</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-06 17:22:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't worry you guys are the luckiest people in medical profession. Somehow all the doctors survived after disasters/apocalypses in movies are vets!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-06 18:01:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Invoker has always been a beast in lategame since its debut. It didn't get picked much in previous patches just because of its mediocre laning phase, which has been improved recently. However I feel its current state is balanced enough. 4 games in the grand final isn't a sufficient sample size but the 50% winrate of Invoker might tell something, as both teams are highly skilled.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-06 18:15:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It makes the situation seem direr. As the dude above me said, people usually doesn't hold vets in high regard, comparing to others like a neurosurgeon, so the characters don't have the best medical treatment in that case.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-06 21:43:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>The problem is that Cruz or even Rubio and Kasich don't need to catchup to have a chance. This is Trump's game to lose. If Trump doesn't meet the 50%+1 delegates threshold to get the straight up nomination, everyone will be back to the start line at a brokered convention. That's what Rubio and Kasich are banking on. That's why the GOP brought back Romney to tell Kasich's supporters vote for Rubio in Florida, and Rubio's ones vote for Kasich in Ohio. Because if Trump lose 2 out of Florida, Ohio and Cali, he will likely not have enough delegates to win it right away despite winning everywhere else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-06 22:23:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's not PR, that's purely retarded from whoever responsible for preparing the questions. It reminds me of what many people tend to ask foreign tourists "How do you think about my country?". It's fucking dumb! What if I think your country is shit, but I don't want to sound like an asshole so I have to lie? Clearly Puppey didn't want to visit that shithole again so he had to dodge that question by a political correct answer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-06 22:30:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let me ELI5 for you. Your assumption is like calculating the number of seeds in an apple based on number of seeds in an orange (which you already knew) because they are similar in size. But it's dead wrong because they're totally different species!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-07 08:52:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>This. iirc there is a [twitchchatreporter](https://www.instagram.com/p/-UO16lRWJ7/) from James or Slacks about a guy dedicated to watching twitchchat during a major/TI. Not a mod, just literally sitting there watching twitchchat. edit: added link so I won't encounter another retarded reply like the one below.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-07 10:04:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Riiiiiiight! Then what the fuck is this? [Twitch chat observer.](https://www.instagram.com/p/-UO16lRWJ7/) [Another post about this guy.](https://www.instagram.com/p/-V4qwmRWKk/?hl=en) [Reddit thread about this.](https://www.reddit.com/r/DotA2/comments/3tmjon/frankfurt_major_social_media_staffs_job/?ref=readnext_4) Next time check your facts before condescendingly lecturing anyone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-07 13:38:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because what's the point of doing that? This might sound harsh, but nobody will give a shit about them anymore as soon as they're retired or stop being relevant in term of achievements. Even television personalities lose popularity really fast once they're out of spotlight, and then they only get a last small influx of people google search their name when their obituaries are announced.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-07 20:51:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>What? This post is creepy af. I can totally imagine OP has like a full folder of her hosting footage and images already. You don't usually put that much effort to compile a bunch of pictures and add caption to make a shoutout post like this. A kind self post is way too enough to show your compliment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-11 00:47:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't worry I got your back. Your comment just got 1 point higher!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-11 01:47:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always respect soldiers and veterans no matter who they are. They're brave and patriotic individuals fighting for what they think the best for their countries and families. Even when somehow they end up fighting in a allegedly injustice war, it's the officials' fault to blame, not them. Just like how GWB should be the one get criticized for lying about WMD and pushing the Iraq war, not the US marines. I'm still in Vietnam. Although I'd love to move somewhere else as soon as I have the chance, I wouldn't use the word "escape". There isn't much democracy here as Vietnam is still a big remnant of communism, but it's kinda bearable to some extent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-13 16:51:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>they stay but might be relocated elsewhere in the room.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-13 21:08:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes you're right. Valve are just trying to seduce you into buying it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-14 20:34:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>The funny thing is that they don't actually have to pay more. Bringing back manufacturing to the US doesn't significantly increase the price of final products,. It's estimated that iPhone price would only increase $2-3 if it's "made in USA". Apple mainly outsources their works because China can make it insanely fast.  gt;  gt; In 2007, Steve Jobs decided that he wanted a glass screen for the iPhone only a few weeks before it launched.  gt;  gt; American suppliers said the deadline was impossible. In China, a factory constructed a dormitory even before signing a contract so its employees could work 12-hour shifts.  gt;  gt; When the deal was sealed, 8,000 workers were roused from sleep, given a biscuit and tea and they started fitting glass screens into the iPhone to produce 10,000 iPhones a day. edit: [source](http://www.entrepreneur.com/article/228315)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-14 20:42:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any Trump-related opinion in this sub should be taken with a huge bowl of salt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-14 22:13:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't find the original source on Alliance for American Manufacturing, but [this one](http://www.globalwireonline.org/2012/06/18/why-your-iphone-is-political/) mentioned it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-15 01:02:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>The idea of letting non-US citizens phonebanking is just ridiculous. The American president is elected to represent interests of American citizens, not the ones from other countries. I know that phonebanking is usually just gathering voters' information, but every single help from foreign sources should be consider outsider influence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-16 00:50:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>They don't show off because they don't want to make themselves and their properties become targets of harassing and vandalizing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-16 01:33:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Umm... because there are more people want her than Bernie?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-16 01:35:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>If that's the case, even when he wins every remaining state with about 50-60% and Cali with 90-10, he will still lose. Just do the math it's not that hard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-16 13:05:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>TL;DR: We the artists don't get enough $$$ when collaborating with pros. Please change we want more!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-16 15:52:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Copyright strikes have a 6-month duration and will expire after that as long as you don't gain another one during that time, so I think you could take that risk. It all depends on you though, don't take risk you can't afford to lose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-16 19:41:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>This feature in CSGO is kinda cool and OP did a poor job describing it. When a player dies, they can watch other alive players' POV. If they're pro players having some major achievements, it shows as a small pin next to their name right in the middle of the screen like "DHW semi finalist", "ESL Katowice champion" so other know they're the real deal. The good thing is that it isn't exclusive to pros, everyone has it. But instead of tournament medals, average people show their event achivements. This can definitely be implemented well in Dota 2. We already have the kill screen randomly showing some cosmetics, would be great if we can choose to put a trophy we want there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-17 04:06:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why do you need locks when burglars can still break into your house with crowbars and pincers? Because it discourages people from actually committing crime, it increases the risk they have to take to achieve the same reward.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-17 18:01:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's victim blaming. People make their own choices to join ponzi schemes, no one forces them, but why it's still a crime to conduct a ponzi scheme? Because it takes advantage of a lack of investor knowledge, makes false promises to influence their choices. That's pretty similar to this situation where the campaign implying Sanders still has a good chance in the race, but in reality he doesn't, while many followers aren't well-informed about the delegate math.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-18 19:19:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>A video isn't automatically qualified as fair use even when it matches all the criterias. Copyright owners always have the right to claim copyright infringement, and your video is only seen as fair use once you successfully defended it. The burden of proof is on you. If you're confident that your video is indeed fair use and you can prove it then go ahead. imo this sounds fair enough to use.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-19 01:06:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfortunately nope. During cell division, enzymes duplicating DNA tend to fuck up and can't duplicate all the way to the end of a chromosome, resulting in a shorter version of that chromosome after each replication. To deal with that, we have something called [Telomere](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Telomere) at the end of our DNA strands. It's a buffer zone containing no genetic information, protecting the DNA but wearing down over time after each cell division. Once we run out of Telomere, it's DNA's turn to get hit. Damaged DNA initiates cell death or prevents cell from growing, leading to organ failures. It's an inevitable ending as long as we don't know how to replenish Telomere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-20 04:16:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Take my comment with a grain of salt because I'm not familiar with your networks and how it recognizes revenue, but your influx of views has incredibly low view duration, which might really affect the income. Look at the video having 166k views, average session is just merely 12 seconds. Ads in my videos doesn't even appear until 10s mark. That means the amount of monetized views won't be as big as you imagined, and the click-though rate would be abysmal. No offense but this seems kinda plausible to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-20 04:26:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you should make a seperate channel for these videos. You still be able to link them in your videos and video description without messing up the mainstream content of your channel. Make a playlist and you can put it into your channel page so users can see them while browsing your main channel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-22 07:29:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even Canada and United States are not safe against this threat. [This 6-year old video](https://youtu.be/pKcMM_uyFHM?t=5m24s) demonstrated and predicted it perfectly. That's why Donald J. Trump is the best choice for you guys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-22 07:53:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Although most of his accusations are ridiculous, he has some decent points. edit: nvm most of his points are spot on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-22 08:07:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>[mfw reading this comment](http://i.imgur.com/TDqa1nV.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-22 12:11:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep, I feel like her accent is just as bad as Jimmy's.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-22 12:38:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>You sound like a person having an Islam-fever. "Christian criminals are the bulk of the people in our jails". Seriously? Isn't that just because Christian citizens are the bulk of America population? With this rate the most popular religion in the world will be Islam in the next few years. A third of Europe population is gonna be Muslims soon. Your wish of having more people exposed to Muslim will be granted. At least Trump shows that he has intent to prevent it from happening in your country.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-22 14:43:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Terrorism seems to become a trend in Europe. I guess only Poland will be the only place in Europe where this kind of thing will be unlikely to happen in the near future.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-22 14:50:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Highest dota population doesn't mean shits. Encourage your fellow Filipinos to buy more hats. More $$$ for Valve = more bargaining power.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-23 03:37:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure about that, but if your sole purpose is just wanting to avoid auto content ID match, just flip the image horizontally, crop a little bit, put the image in motion and add vignette effect. However if it's a copyright infringement indeed people are still able to manually file a claim. I wouldn't risk it, better safe than sorry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-23 04:09:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>It doesn't solve any problem. 1 day before the kicking deadline, teams see that other teams didn't kick any player, so they stick with their roster. Suddenly the next day team A announces that they kick their mid Eric and pick a free agent player. Despite really wanting Eric, other teams can't pick him because they're full, and they can't kick anyone because the deadline is up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-23 04:31:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>CNN shows HRC has a huge lead: OMG stay in line they're liars only 1% reporting in. CNN projected HRC wins: OMG it doesn't matter who's winning, it's proportional. CNN announces that HRC crushed Bernie in term of delegates: ???</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-23 04:34:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just quote my own comment in another thread here  gt; It doesn't solve any problem. 1 day before the kicking deadline, teams see that other teams didn't kick any player, so they stick with their roster. Suddenly the next day team A announces that they kick their mid Eric and pick a free agent player. Despite really wanting Eric, other teams can't pick him because they're full, and they can't kick anyone because the deadline is up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-23 04:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I heard a lady on CNN just commented that AZ demographic is kinda similar to CA and this might reflect the future result of Trump in CA? Can you confirm this claim? I would be absolutely happy if it's true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-23 05:37:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since no one knows for sure how the algorithm of content ID works, I just listed as many methods as possible to bypass it for images without altering the original ones too much (visually). Proceed with your own judgement. In term of video editing, I suggest you stick with adding vignette and putting them in motion. It's a video, not a powerpoint slideshow, never leave any still image in your video. The vignette both changes the original image color histogram (to deal with image matching) and make it have a cinematic vibe. See them in action in [this video](https://youtu.be/T8-85cZRI9o?t=3m18s) (it's around 3:18). Much better, eh?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-23 13:12:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well to be fair it's a double edged sword. This systematic progress of dumbing down Dota 2 makes it more appealing to new players but it also turns off many hardcore players who love a sophisticated game with various complex and trivial mechanics a.k.a "the elitists". I'm not an elitist by any mean, I'm cool with all these changes but deep down I feel kinda sad. It's like they stripped away parts of something I've accumulated for awhile. I wonder how many new players this game actually gained from all these changes, as well as how many old players left because of that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-23 13:32:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well your question is mostly covered so I just want to add this bit: clearly you've never seen [Sprint the Anti-ballistic Missile](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=msXtgTVMcuA). This monster goes 0 to Mach 10 (7,673 mph = 12,348 kph) in just 5 seconds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-23 13:48:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>It used to have a lot more open discussions in the beginning, until most of them were just trolls posting fake concerns to promote and plant negative ideas about Donald Trump. Clearly this didn't amuse the mods, so they decided to ban all kind of negative posts there, and divert all the questions and discussions to /r/AskTrumpSupporters. It was necessary and reasonable when you consider the fact it had to survive in a platform dominated by Trump enemies supporters. Obviously when all things left are postive, it gains the "cult" atmosphere. So nothing strange there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-23 21:02:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>The amount of federal employees working at wizardry ministry depicted in the movies seems a little bit too much for a 3,000 citizen population</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-25 00:50:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>This solution does exactly nothing against the scummy moves. What will you do when a team kicks their player (A) right before the roster drop deadline when most top teams have finalized their lineup. The buffer period won't do anything because teams can't dump their players to pick A up. Even when a team able to react in time and immediately fire one of them (B) to create space and pick A up right after the announcement and before the deadline, then the I-am-fucked status just transfers from A to B. It doesn't change anything. It just makes sure that those poor players have a time window to scramble a shitty team from 5 other teamless/fucked players.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-25 00:56:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>The thing you want is actually how Riot manages the competitive scene of LoL (LCS). It's so hilarious to see that /r/dota2 used to bash this model of management, now people start asking for it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-25 08:37:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>No? Where did I say that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-26 00:54:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm kinda late to the party, and there's already a long post about Vietnam up there, but I just want to add another perspective because I feel that post didn't really answer the OP questions and it sounds like a political correct propaganda more than anything to me. I was born in the early 90s so I luckily didn't have to experience the real communism age, but my parents did and they have always reminded me about how horrible it was. The most fucked up thing was the government control of provisions of food and essential goods. You have a ration stamp cards, each month you bring it to the government appointed grocery stores to exchange for foods, gasoline, clothes, tires, soap... pretty much everything you uses everyday. It made the store clerks one of the most prestige jobs in the society (imagine it's like working in Google nowadays), because that means your acquaintances will always be guaranteed to have the best foods possible, and for those who aren't, sorry, here is your rotten piece of meat! And God forbids you lose that ration stamp cards, because if you do, your family will have nothing to eat that entire month. You might wonder why we didn't grow ourselves something or breed livestocks? Because it was a crime! You couldn't do it privately. No trading whatsoever without the regulation of government. Since there was no TVs, our perception of the West was only what they told us in the radio, which was 100% bs propaganda. But we knew it's a totally different lives out there, especially when a huge paper factory funded by Sweden was being built in that area. That's where our parents meet each other the very first time, where they both working at after it finished. My parents told us how the local residents used to rush to the road to watch the Swedish engineers riding motorcycles back home after their shifts, because they looked so different from everything else they've seen in their lives. They also told me how people used to scavenge expired canned foods from trashbins in Swedish residence area, and wonder why western people throw away such good foods! Nowadays the economy is somewhat better, but the democracy is still the same. tl;dr: communism is a period of poverty and misery because of fucked up regulations.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-26 04:13:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>So what's the difference? Regulations are just the government's tools to enforce their ideas. When the ideas are fucked up then obviously the tools they used would be fucked up as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-26 09:04:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>My little brother is learning English as a second language and he used to watch CNN and listen to NPR everyday to practice. Since I followed Trump presidential campaign I have recommended him listen to a bunch of Trump's speech in meetings and hearings. Better listen to high energy and intellectual materials instead of some msm crap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-28 07:15:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, here is [farmer Trump with pitchfork](https://criticl.me/sites/default/files/public/images/post/3816/internal/trump-greebacres.jpg) for ya!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-29 17:00:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you really play dota wc3, because Dota 2 is the one with built-in delay. The easiest thing to see is dota 2 creep aggro has a noticable delay, while in wc3 it's almost instant. Micro in wc3 is far more superior than dota 2 because it was built on a RTS game, the hitbox and unit control were perfect. Dota 2 unit hitbox was a nightmare in its early days, and even until now it still is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-29 17:29:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>First thing do you have any idea how huge 250ms latency is? I would call that number bs. Second thing if everyone played in private servers so they didn't experience the delay, then why you bring it in as an disadvantage of wc3 in the first place?!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-30 02:15:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL based Anderson just BTFO lying Cruz!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-30 10:20:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be fair you chose one of the most difficult niches in YouTube. Thanks to its low entry requirements, Letsplay genre has became overly saturated, highly competitive and people completely figured the shit out if it, so the chance of you being either unique or best-of-the-best is pretty much non-existent. Without that your only choice is slowly and painfully grind your way to a decent audience base and start to snowball from that. That said, I hope you don't give up, just think of it as a hobby and things will be much more enjoyable. I took a look at your channel and there's still lots of room for improvements (I just guess based on your username, ignore the part below if it isn't the case). First thing, establish your brand so new viewers see that you're serious and want to subscribe because they expect you will produce more good contents in the future. That means make a channel profile image, channel art/banner, a consistent video thumbnails in term of style. This is mandatory and I suggest you do it asap. Maybe you already missed some potential subscribers because they visited your channel and thought you're a random channel just uploaded a random video for lulz. Second things, intro and outro. Intro might be optional, but it helps enhance your brand, it prints your brand image into viewers' brain. If you do, make it less than 4 secs. Outro is highly recommended for your type of videos. Directly ask them to subscribe, like and watch other videos. It sounds silly but call-to-arms actually works very well. People tend to forget to do those things until someone reminds them. Last thing, your keywords are still not optimized.  gt;  gt; tom, clancy's, the, division, ubisoft, massive, dark, zone, dz, rank, 30, 50, solo, poobs, plays, let's, lets, guide, play, billtog, funny, hardaway, library... There are too many short tail keywords and too generic terms. I suggest you take a look at[ this post](https://www.reddit.com/r/PartneredYoutube/comments/4bbiwe/cant_get_views/d180taa) for a gist of how to properly tag your video. And if you have time, make caption/subtitle for your video. Youtube can't watch your video but it can read the caption to know what your video is about and rank it properly in search results.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-30 10:52:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know about other networks, but if you monetize with Google Adsense it does have a detailed breakdown of estimated earning, which is pretty close to the finalized earning i.e the exact amount you receive each month.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-30 17:59:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every system has a certain percentage of false positives. You have to look at the greater good, not individual cases. If the benefit of torture outweighs the drawback from false positives, then I would say it's fair enough to accept torture. That also means I have to accept the risk of having my relatives being tortured. Of course I would be mad af when that happens to me, but it doesn't mean the system doesn't work. And to be fair how often do you see someone wrongly accused for terrorism? Because from your words it seems to be highly likely to happen, which is ridiculous. This is a serious crime and it usually receives a lot of public attention, it's not easy to convict innocent people of terrorism.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-31 21:22:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Although I'm okay with this comment, because this can also be used to say about Trump and I support him, I would never use this kind of argument to defend if the OP question was about Trump. Those who love both candidates and prefer Hillary a little bit more will always vote for her. Those who hate both of them and depise Hillary a little bit more will not always vote for the lesser of two evils i.e Bernie. They might vote for another party or not vote at all. You can't use the differential between their votes to illustrate her favorability rating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-31 21:54:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then you're still wrong. The vote count doesn't prove anything. It doesn't prove that there is a majority of people loving Hillary. Firstly, not all the people who hate her vote for Bernie. Secondly, there are people called Republicans out there as well, and I bet most of them hate Hillary. Your vote count doesn't account for these people. OP question didn't exclusively talk about Dems, so I think it's fair to consider it. Based on national favorability polls I think it's safe to say public opinion is aligned quite well with Reddit's.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-02 06:43:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don't need karma to post. However, in order to avoid spammers, some popular subreddits require you to have a certain amount of karma for your posts to be visible. Self-promotion is frowned upon on Reddit, so there are a bunch of rules about that. The most important one is that less than 10% of your posts and conversation should link to your own contents. You can read more about it [here](https://www.reddit.com/wiki/selfpromotion). These rules are usually loosely enforced, but if you get caught by mods/admins, you will likely to be banned from their subreddits, or worse, reddit-wide. Make your advertisements as organic as possible, people hate blatant spammers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-02 06:54:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would love to see monthly updates from you. Just post it right here on this sub, it's not like we have too many good posts anyway. It's okay if you don't want to reveal your channel, performance stats and video category are enough imo. Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-02 14:44:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or maybe lots of AdmiralBulldog fanboys get triggered.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-02 14:50:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd love to visit a sub with full of Artour-related posts instead of these things: * Shits from leafeater * Low effort dadjokes and puns * Any kind of shoutouts * Retarded gameplay suggestions from 3k players * "Hey guys I made a new set for ____/a new artwork for my set, check it out!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nitrogen Triiodide Detonation</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-06 10:55:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-06 10:59:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a repost which I made from [this video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y39152VWCPk). Hope it helps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-07 03:13:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because it's an old game so your main source of traffic would likely come from searches. You can make an educated guess by using the Display Planner's Google Adword video keywords suggestion. It looks like [this](http://i.imgur.com/nLwQSUK.png) for the 3 keywords "dragon warrior 3", dragon warrior 3 gameplay", "dragon warrior 3 walkthrough". Remember, your videos need to be on top of seach results for all of that search volume to become views.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-07 16:21:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a non-German it took me 10 mins to finally realize what you said lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-07 18:36:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah don't worry I get it. Google dictionary is a wonderful thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-08 15:16:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mostly good. RIP headphone users tho.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-09 06:21:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Short explanation about the game of Go](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I90Ntco66iA) mentioned in this video I've just uploaded today, in case someone is curious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-09 06:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Short explanation about the game of Go](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I90Ntco66iA) mentioned in this video I've just uploaded today, in case someone is curious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-11 05:18:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you seriously think that everyone has patience of a saint to sit and watch 40 seconds of intro and pointless rambling before watching the actual content? Even when your content is super well-presented and interesting, and in this case it's not, most people would've not seen it because they left already. Make it quick and concise, ideally less than 5 minutes. Speak as fast as possible if your video has to be long.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-11 19:41:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats! It has also been exactly a week since I uploaded the first video of my own channel. It was about one of the last week big trends so it caught some traffic and got more than 600 views. I've only had 10 subs so far tho, including 4 from my housemates! Expecting next week won't be as good as this one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-12 07:32:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your genre is pretty hard to grow so don't expect too much. Not everybody will succeed with youtube that's the truth, especially in a highly competitive market like what you chose. The only way I can think of to skyrocket your channel right now is try to make a super interesting video just for the sake of promotion and exposure. It doesn't have to be what you're usually making, it just need to be related enough to the games you play. If you can ride the right trends, catch the right waves, you would gain a lot of traffic to your channel. Lots of big game specific channel became big this way. For example, [this video](http://np.reddit.com/r/GlobalOffensive/comments/3w5p1y/when_im_valve_031/?ref=search_posts) and [this video](http://np.reddit.com/r/GlobalOffensive/comments/4csegq/when_im_team_liquid_mlg_columbus_2016/) on /r/globaloffensive. The former one was made right after a big controversial balance patch of CSGO, the latter one was made right after an underdog team pulled a big upset. Both are super easy to make, share the same format but instantly went straight to the frontpage after posted. Look at the stats. That first video gained 60 subscribers and 500k views, while the second video only have 135k views but it alone drove 265 subscribers, because the second channel is active and the first one is just one time poster. I don't even play LoL since I'm a Dota 2 person but I also know that Ekko is currently broken as fuck in LoL, a trend right there. If you can make some kind of satire/comedy video similar to the ones I've mentioned I don't think you wouldn't be able to get some traffic to your channel. No matter what it is people always love humorous content. I mean comedy not the one you've already made on your channel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How Do Chess Computers Think? [6:48]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-13 21:51:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How Do Chess Computers Think?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-13 22:05:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How Do Chess Computers Think?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-13 22:16:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-14 12:47:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just a personal opinion and little bit nit-picking, but I think you should improve your video thumbnails, they looks kinda clunky and obsolete. I know design is a highly subjective matter and everybody has their own tastes, but I'm not a fan of using gradient for texts, it makes them a typical wordart from Microsoft Word 97! Use some modern fonts instead of oldschool Impact, use shadow or strokes if you want to make it stand out from the background. People nowadays love flat design and minimalism. Just go to the trending tab on YouTube and you can clearly see good examples there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How Do Chess Computers Think?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-14 15:13:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-14 18:47:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>uhh that's the point of the vid, they don't win against humans by thinking, they're just better at calculating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-15 13:19:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol that's weird, looks like he's pointing to something but I only see him standing in front of a blue backdrop. Nothing happened.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is what happens when you ride a bike too close to a tanker</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-15 17:45:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Truck conducted a little brake test. Apparently the dashcam owner passed, the biker didn't.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-16 09:41:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-17 06:47:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually I don't know how to call this kind of bike. It's highly popular in south east asia, manual gears but automatic clutch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-17 09:27:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>nope, still no luck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-17 16:21:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you setting your expectation a little bit too high? Because I also run a 2 weeks old channel and you guys actually did better than me and lots of other channels in term of subscribers, and subs is the only thing that matter after all. You can't expect your works to have the traffic it deserves, that's not how this works. My video is only 6 mins long and I didn't even go for animation yet, just static presentation and it took me almost a week to make, but I'm still happy with 700 views so far. An established channel might disappoint with 100k views for a video, but a new channel might see 1k views a huge success with that same video. It's not about efforts and quality only, brand and exposure also matter. I'm not saying you can't have a high expectation, just don't let it lower your morale when expectation doesn't meet reality. YouTube is a long game, most people will quit during their early phase, you need to survive past this to see the snowball effect kicks in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Where is Octomask from?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-20 18:08:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Octomask is a company making GoPro-ready dive masks. I've been looking for a while but unable to figure out where the hell this company is in! Their official website doesn't even show that. Where is its headquarter? Where are their manufacturers?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-21 15:04:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-22 19:05:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could you give an example of people legitimately without phones but still being able to afford a PC/laptop + pay the internet bill to play Dota/CSGO?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-22 20:08:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>CS:GO is rated "Mature" i.e not for children under 17 years old, technically they're not supposed to play that game. Cyber cafes aren't that cheap if you're a regular player, in fact it would cost much more than playing at home given the same amount of time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-23 07:41:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>weird. Be a normal person so you can play with normal people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-02 06:32:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's a long vehicle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-02 12:01:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>700 views is too small of a sample size to make any meaningful conclusion. Normally with that amount of views, you would have 10-14 ads clicks. That's where the money mostly comes from. But you might have a really bad luck and right now only a few people clicked the ads, and they're from low CPC countries so you got practically no money. Maybe your next hundreds of views will have a much higher click-through rate and they're from high CPC countries like Germany, and the result will be heavily skewed. That's why the head/tail ratio comes closer to 50/50 when you keep flipping a coin. If I was you revenue would be my last concern right now. Come back later if this doesn't change even when you have 10,000 views per month consistently.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-03 17:22:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pandatv isn't an exclusive platform for gaming streams. All the dancing girl streams are under Entertainment category.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Specific] Please swap this dude's flip-flops to a pair of appropriate shoes and please don't reduce the image resolution. Thanks in advance!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-24 15:14:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-25 03:10:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is awesome, thank you so much! @to the other guy posted in this thread: please check your account because you might be shadowbanned, before this comment it showed 3 comments but I only saw this guy and automoderator's posts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-03 18:55:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cmon guys, Secret hasn't been eliminated yet, technically they still have a chance to become the champion. I have to admit that I'm being extremely optimistic here but there has been a lot of /r/Prematurecelebration materials lately in this sub.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bus gives scooter waiting red light a little nudge</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-09 19:18:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 03:38:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was a cab. Actually there were also 2 traffic cops hanging around at that intersection, one was walking toward the scene near the end (the man in yellow-ish uniform)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>On her way to work one morning...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-11 15:37:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-12 14:36:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought there would be no one can top Epicenter's production value. Man I've never been so wrong...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Small hatchback has a sudden brake failure, plows through several scooters (minor injuries only)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-12 17:50:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-13 09:29:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Panic and inexperience might be a few reasons I could think of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-16 18:00:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>[The official site of Department of Transportation only has the data of 2012 and 2013](http://www.mt.gov.vn/vn/tin-tuc/13956/so-lieu-phuong-tien-co-gioi-duong-bo-dang-ky-moi.aspx). I can't find credible sources of other years. Here is some quick vocabulary for you to understand that table: Vietnamese | English ---|--- Ph #432; #417;ng ti #7879;n c #417; gi #7899;i  #273; #432; #7901;ng b #7897;| Road vehicles  #272; #259;ng k #253; m #7899;i | New vehicles T #7893;ng s #7889; | Total  #212; t #244;| Cars M #244; t #244;| Motorcycles C #7897;ng|Sum</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-18 18:47:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your accent is fine, but locals might still recognize you easily from the way you talk, especially your choice of words and common expressions. It's not the hard part tho, you will be able to get used to it in no time I think. Being able to speak Vietnamese is a big advantage, so you won't have any trouble blending in with locals. Just try to understand and aware of the most significant cultural etiquette, avoid doing things people would frown upon. Most Vietnamese men love drinking, so if you have a good alcohol tolerance it's another big ass plus. Even locals will have a hard time buying stuff without getting rip-off if they aren't veteran consumers, so don't do that alone. Ask someone to go with you if you want to buy anything that isn't in supermarkets or shopping malls. Theft is more common in the southern, so you should keep that in mind, especially if your upcoming destination is Saigon (HCM city). source: i'm a local.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-18 19:06:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well you could try L #224;ng c #7893;  #272; #432; #7901;ng L #226;m ( #272; #432; #7901;ng L #226;m old village) in Son Tay district, 44 km (27 miles) from Hanoi. [Google Maps link.](https://www.google.com/maps/place/%C4%90%C6%B0%E1%BB%9Dng+L%C3%A2m,+Hanoi,+Vietnam/@21.1447505,105.4756044,15z/data=!4m5!3m4!1s0x3134f5941df088b7:0x4a1cbbccdcb1f462!8m2!3d21.1533196!4d105.471249) You can have a quick look at it [here.](http://vivuhanoi.com/lang-co-duong-lam-kinh-nghiem-du-lich-trong-mot-ngay.html).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 19:42:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then where are African teams?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 20:10:14</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; TEAMS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-19 03:42:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi /r/malaysia. I'm coming to KL tomorrow for work and will stay there at least 1 year. Which mobile carrier is the best for me who don't actually need to call much but use quite a lot of data for social media/reddit?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-26 01:49:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does this kind of accident happen frequently in Malaysia? I've just been here like 1 month and this happened right next to my office. I don't think my daily commute bus line going near any construction site (blue gokl) but I guess I'm going to use monorail from now on, just to be sure :'(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-05 06:30:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd love to have that but game dev doesn't want that because it shortens the lifespan of the game, and that's harder for new players to catch up with the old ones. That's one of the reason RTS games like starcraft aren't popular anymore these days, because people have too much information from the internet and the metagame becomes obsolete so quickly after every patch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-09 16:15:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>yay! more free rides later!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I think she used all of her luck that day</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-17 17:34:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dad reflex of a bike mechanic saved not only 1 but 2 children!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 17:47:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>1 dad reflex 2 children</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 17:57:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 15:47:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the backstory! I was always looking for that as well, you made my day sir!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 23:54:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idk but whenever there is someone next to me I can't pee at all, even when my bladder is going to explode. It's not that I'm afraid of someone accidentally see my dick, my brain just seems to shut the piss flow when there is people around. Going to a private booth and it immediately gets back normal just fine. Weird eh?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 12:32:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi guys! Is there any reasonably cheap and reliable way to go to bukit jurga for those who don't have a personal vehicle? Me and my friend are both expat staying in KL so our only way to go around are public transport and taxis. We're planing to have a paragliding session there. The best I can think of is grab hitch, but I don't think I can book the return trip, and traditional taxis are kinda expensive :c</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 13:22:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why haven't you visited Vietnam already? It's cheap, and since you're in Malaysia it's just a 3-hour flight away! If you're into riding, you should try a motorcyle trip around Northern area with tons of passes and beautiful mountainous view. I just write a blog post about [how to participate in Vietnamese traffic safely!](https://vietnamesefacts.com/how-to-survive-vietnamese-traffic-like-a-local/), if you ever plan to visit Vietnam, just check it out, I think it might be useful for you :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 13:27:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>If any of you guys here want to have a good look at what you should and shouldn't do when joining the chaotic traffic of Vietnam, I just wrote a blog post that might help you out https://vietnamesefacts.com/how-to-survive-vietnamese-traffic-like-a-local Feel free to ask me anything about Vietnam here, I'm a native and will try my best to help you guys :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 15:54:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Riding a motorcycle is easy, but riding safely in Vietnam... hmm maybe a little bit tricky, our traffic condition isn't for rookie riders :p Going around northern routes on a scooter/vespa is doable, but again it's not for a novice rider, since a scooter is an urban vehicle, not quite suitable for touring/long trips, especially in mountainous area where the road condition sometimes can be off-roadish and a lot of passes which require engine braking for maximum safety (scooters only have normal brake)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The company name is "Sure Reach"... but that isnt the first thing crossed my mind when looking at this ads</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 22:45:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 23:18:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need to take btc circulation into your calculation. If you have 1 btc, you sell that, and immediately buy it again, you got 2 btc worth of volume. Do that another time and you got 4 btc worth of volume despite there's only 1 btc circulating in the market. The amount of mtgox btc injected to the market is equal to 1/3 daily vol, but it might be a few times higher than the actual number of btc circulating in the market, that's why it can cause a massive drop in price if there isn't a sufficient amount of capital coming in the market like osowp95 mentioned.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 00:50:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Implants should only be considered as a last resort. Dental implant can be infected without proper maintenance and trust me, it's awful and unable to fix anymore. You also lose the ability to sense/control your bite force so you can damage them if you bite something too hard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 00:32:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not a web developer so please take my words with a bowl of salt but as a Vietnamese working in outsourcing in Malaysia I'd say you might get better chance in a more developed country, especially Singapore since it's a hub for SEA startups, English is more popular over there than other countries such as China or Vietnam, which can be a slight drawback in finding jobs and daily life. Although the cost of living is much higher there but so is your salary, leading to a better overall purchasing power, which is great if you want to spend time travel around other countries in the region. Not sure if this would relate to other countries, but in Vietnam the supply for developers/designers is pretty abundant so the market is highly competitive and people somewhat shoot their own feet by keeping driving down the price to get more clients, accepting lower pay for job offers. And to me it's mildly interesting that you're wanting to move to Asia meanwhile I'm thinking about how feasible it is for me to get an IT/engineer degree in Canada and live there :p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 10:47:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think some kind of rack would be better than human spotter for this case.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 19:26:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>From what I've learned in high school (and still remember), heart doesn't actually pump/rest at once. A human heart has 4 separated chambers and they take turns to pump and rest, making a continuous sequence to pump blood around the body. Scientists realized that it takes more time for a chamber to rest than pumping, so basically heart muscles don't work all the time, have proper rest time so they don't get tired.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 22:50:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>i think they don't have property tax because people over there only have the rights to use the property/land, not actually own them, which means it sucks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 23:58:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Usually ISO has higher priority when it comes to auto exposure balancing in most cameras, especially in smartphones, unless you choose specific modes like Tv on Canon DSLR. Cranking up ISO is more foolproof than increasing exposure time because a camera can't detect if there are lots of motion or not, and a noisy photo is always better than a blurry one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 23:25:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>As someone from a 3rd world country, I concur. Pascal's principle just gets mentioned briefly in 8th grade physics class and its mathematical formula only appears later in the first year of high school \(10th grade, usually 15 years old for normal kids\). This kid is way too young for a 8th grader.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 07:55:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Quick questions: 1. Can I travel around West Malaysia by bus without a passport. I'm a foreigner and my passport was submitted to immigration for employment pass renewal thus I only have my national ID/driver's license (unfortunately they aren't in English). Some friends said they have ID checking at TBS. 2. There is a female voiced announcer at the escalators in MRT stations. What does it say?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 08:12:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol seriously what is this... i'm not malaysian so i'm always out of the loop with this kind of meme xD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 18:51:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well if there aren't teammates to blame the ladder anxiety is much more serious in ranked play. That was a big reason leading to the decline in popularity of RTS titles like Starcraft.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>