<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject5062</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I Am Astronaut Chris Hadfield, Commander of Expedition 35.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 16:06:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello Reddit! [Here](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VYM8xTQt3Bg) is an introductory video to what I hope will be a great AMA. My name is [Chris Hadfield](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chris_Hadfield), and I am an astronaut for the Canadian Space Agency and Commander of the upcoming mission to the International Space Station. We will be launching at 6:12 p.m. Kazakh time on December 19th. You can watch it online [here](http://www.nasa.gov/multimedia/nasatv/index.html) if you're so inclined. I'm looking forward to all the questions. I will be in class doing launch prep. for the next hour, but thought I would start the thread early so people can get their questions in before the official 11:00 EST launch. Here are links to [more information about Expedition 35](http://www.nasa-usa.de/mission_pages/station/expeditions/expedition35/index.html), my [twitter](https://twitter.com/Cmdr_Hadfield) and my [facebook](http://www.facebook.com/AstronautChrisHadfield?fref=ts). I try to keep up to date with all comments and questions that go through the social media sites, so if I can't get to your question here, please don't hesitate to post it there. Ask away! Edit: Thanks for all the questions everyone! It is getting late here, so I am going to answer a few more and wrap it up. I greatly appreciate all the interest reddit has shown, and hope that you'll all log on and watch the launch on the 19th. Please be sure to follow my twitter or facebook if you have any more questions or comments you'd like to pass along in the future. Good night!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 16:14:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>To facilitate getting less repeat questions from the last AMA, what I've done is answered a number of the "standard" interview questions up front, including those sent to my son in PMs the other day. I will provide them below in individual posts. **What are you bringing with you?** The Soyuz is very small and the weight balance affects how it flies, so we are very restricted in what we can bring. I thus chose small items for my family and close friends: a new wedding ring for my wife, commemorative jewellery, a watch for my daughter (I flew a watch each for my sons on previous flights), a full family photo for my Mom and Dad, and some mission emblem guitar picks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 16:14:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Aliens** No astronaut has ever seen an alien, despite what popular media would like you to believe, though we are, of course actively looking; it's one of the basic purposes of exploration. As we speak, the Mars rovers are hunting for signs of life on our nearest neighbour. I'd love to help discover life somewhere besides Earth, but it's important to keep perspective and reason: while everyone often sees things they don't understand, to immediately label them 'UFOs' and conclude that they have to be alien life is just wishful thinking and a bit silly. Don't confuse entertainment and lack of understanding with fact.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 16:15:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Sex in space** People have sex on Earth all the time. It is a normal, basic human function and fundamental desire, necessary for the propagation of our species. It is also steeped in cultural and personal significance, and thus gets extra attention. There will, of course, be sex in space, just like everywhere else, but for a small crew, the subdividing emotional attachment that goes along with it could be very harmful. We also have had very limited hygiene and privacy to this point. With bigger and bigger crews and spaceships, however, it will become a natural part of human existence in space, just like on Earth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 16:15:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Pooping** Our Space Station toilet looks like a camping toilet, and uses airflow in place of gravity. When waste comes out of the body, either solid or liquid, it is pulled into the toilet by airflow. The urine is mixed with other waste water (humidity, water samples, etc) and purified back into drinking water. The solid waste is collected in a small sewage tank and put into an unmanned resupply ship, that is then jettisoned and burns up in the upper atmosphere. For a good summary, watch http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Jj-WgWLdiG8</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 16:16:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>**What do you have to do to become an astronaut?** Astronaut selection requires 3 fundamental tenets: health, brains, and experience. You have to be able to pass the toughest medical in the world to be a Space Station astronaut, so stay in shape and eat right. You have to demonstrate the ability to learn complex things, so an advanced technical university degree is needed. And you have to demonstrate good decision-making when the consequences really matter, so important to have work experience such as a medical doctor, or test pilot, or saturation diver. That will whittle the selection group down to several hundred - after that other skills matter: languages, flying experience, diving experience, personality, attitude, how you present yourself. And above all, a driving, fundamental desire to be an astronaut is required, to successfully endure the life demands of the job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 16:16:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Did spaceflight change religious view?** No one gets to be an astronaut without a strong personal conviction that gives them strength and confidence. No matter what religion or creed they believe in, all astronauts have something fundamental within themselves that they can draw upon. The actual experience of space travel in fact deepens this, reinforces it, and accentuates the awe and wonder that are at the base of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 16:16:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>**What do you miss the most?** I miss a hot shower, fresh food, the smells and variety of Earth, and direct human contact.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 16:17:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Are you scared?** Fear comes from being unprepared when facing the unknown. Being thrust into an unexpected situation and not knowing what to do makes everyone uncomfortable, and thus we fear it, especially if it can embarrass or kill us. As astronauts, we avoid this by working for years to understand the unknown, and decide in advance what we will do. That's why we study so much, and why we live and work in simulators. Often the 1st time you try something hard you are nervous, but the 50th time it feels normal. We try and make everything that might happen during a spaceflight feel just like that. So it's not that we're extra-brave - we're just extra-prepared.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 16:17:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Won't you be lonely?** In the centre of every big city in the world, surrounded by noise and teeming millions of people, are lonely people. Loneliness is not so much where you are, but instead is your state of mind. On Station with the world in our window, people on the radio, family just a phone call away, and other crew members to chat with, plus a full plate of experiments and work to do, loneliness is no more of a problem than it is everywhere else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 16:17:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>**How's the food?** Space food is fine, tasty, and of good variety. It's limited to food that has a long shelf life, with no refrigeration and no microwave, so it's a lot like camping food or Army rations. The majority of it is dehydrated, so we add cold or hot water to it, like Ramen noodles or instant soup or powdered drinks. But we have a mixture of Russian and American foods, plus specialty items from Canada, Europe and Japan, so we eat well, and also use dinner as a good time to get together and talk, relax, and be human.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 16:18:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Why spend money in space when people are hungry on Earth?** In all societies, we need to balance how we spend our money. The vast majority needs to be on human health and services. A portion also needs to go to education. In addition, some needs to be for research and exploration. It is vital that we take care of our people, educate our young, and develop opportunities for the future. If we don't challenge our citizens with demanding ideas and possibilities, they will either go elsewhere which is a loss, or not realize their potential, which is a tragedy. The key is to decide what is the right balance of budget, and when you look at the actual figures, I think the Space Agencies of the world get it about right. I know in Canada we work very hard with the money we are given to do as well for our country as we can - developing useful products, better understanding the world and human health, and inspiring our next generation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 16:18:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>**What does launch feel like?** Launch is immensely powerful, and you can truly feel yourself in the centre of it, like riding an enormous wave, or being pushed and lifted by a huge hand, or shaken in the jaws of a gigantic dog. The vehicle shakes and vibrates, and you are pinned hard down into your seat by the acceleration. As one set of engines finishes and the next starts, you are thrown forward and then shoved back. The weight of over 4 Gs for many minutes is oppressive, like an enormous fat person lying on you, until suddenly, after 9 minutes, the engine shut off and you are instantly weightless. Magic. Like a gorilla was squishing you and then threw you off a cliff. Quite a ride :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 16:19:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>**What language do you speak?** I grew up speaking English, learned some German in high school which I unfortunately mostly forgotten, and since studied and learned French and Russian. On station English and Russian are the standard languages, and all astronauts are trained in both.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:01:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. The reason is that the blood doesn't drain to your feet. You're lying on your back so you don't black out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:03:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty well. The advantages are full-size, tools and equipment being just right. The disadvantages are that there is drag in the water, and your blood rushes to your head when you're upside down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:06:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't hate anything about it. The worst part at first is motion sickness, then later that you can never have a good shower. You can't properly clean your body like you can on earth. You can only just have a sponge bath.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:07:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, it looks like stars from the surface of the earth, but not nearly as bright as the moon. The brightest things are lightning storms. You can see lightning storms at night for thousands of kilometers. Regular lights just look like stars from the earth. Big cities stand out as one big local glow. This is an excellent question. Nobody ever asks this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:08:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shrimp cocktail. Because the horseradish sauce has a really strong, sharp flavour that survives rehydration.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:09:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>The best part is being weightless forever. It is like magic. It is like having a superpower where you can fly. You can fly forever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:11:00</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;On a high level, how does what you experience with the Canadian Space program differ from what most astronauts experience with the US one? The big difference is that the US has launched vehicles. Americans fly in their own space ships. Canada has never had human launch vehicles, and we have always flown in other countries' vehicles. It is sort of a space between ownership and being a guest.  gt;What should Canada be doing with its space program going forward? Doing what it is doing. I think we're doing the right thing right now. We are looking at Canada's needs and cooperation internationally, making sure that Canada is involved in everything from the Hubble telescope to studying pollution in the atmosphere to being on Mars to commanding the space station.  gt;Being from Sarnia do you cheer for the Leafs, the Red Wings, or someone else? The Leafs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:15:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I try and manage my stress at work, not at home. I think that's an important thing to note. Stress normally occurs when you can't solve a perpetual problem or you can't get comfortable with a certain idea. When you can't control your own destiny. I try not to let myself be that way. I try to truly accept the things I cannot change. I like to show up at home not stressed. But to answer more directly, I run, I play guitar, I go for walks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:16:15</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Is there any point hoping for a Canadian shuttle or moon landing in my lifetime Building your own human launch vehicle is extremely expensive. It makes more economic sense to cooperate internationally with people who've already developed that capacity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:18:12</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Do you think NASA will ever be able to accomplish a long term space plan when the Presidency changes hands every 4/8 years Yes. It is easy to despair, but it is better to look at history. It has never been easy to organize a major project. But we've done it anyway, and there are lots of examples. The Space Station *is* a long term space project, the Mars rovers, Voyager, Messenger orbiting Mercury. All of those, plus the hundreds of satellites orbiting Earth -- those are all part of the long-term space plan. It's not perfect, but we're making it work anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:20:16</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; How is preparing for a Soyuz flight different to the preparations you had to go through for Space Shuttle missions? A shuttle mission is an end in itself. It is limited by the amount of time a shuttle can stay up (about 2 1/2 weeks). A Soyuz flight is going somewhere, and staying there for half a year. A Soyuz flight is part of a long mission. A shuttle flight is a mission to itself. To further that, the Shuttle is far more complicated than the Soyuz. As well, as a Canadian I can be a Soyuz pilot, but could not be a Shuttle pilot. Soyuz parallel parks better, too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:21:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>The shuttle program was only one of many NASA programs. It was a way to get to space and back, and the purpose of spaceflight is not to launch and land. It is what you do when you get there. With all of the unmanned vehicles, and with the space station that we've built, the relevance for the populace is huge and permeable. As well, the US is working on building follow on vehicles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:24:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Assuming I already had a competent crew, so that I wasn't counting on this person to operate the vehicle and keep us alive, I would bring an extremely talented artist. One who could capture the experience in a way it had never been captured before. That may be a songwriter (such as Stan Rogers, if he were still alive) who could put a profession -- a way of life -- into perspective.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:27:15</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Was it all done in a simulator? did you ever get a chance to try it in a real jet? Yes, I did. Simulators all have serious limitations. Our test program was initially approved in a simulator, but all the real testing was done in flight in f-18's. We rewrote the procedures for out of control flight recovery. In the test program, we put the jet out of control around 120 times. However, I have only accidentally had an F-18 in an out of control spin once, and the recovery procedures worked (during a practice dog fight).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:27:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>A huge meteorite burn up between me and Australia.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:28:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha! No. We're not beginners, and we're not unprepared. We train for years so that we're ready to do our job properly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:28:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>It takes about 15 seconds from being in the sun to being in complete dark. It is like sunset happening completely in 15 seconds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:30:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I like Russian space food the best. It has the most natural flavour and it is more like the comfort food that I grew up with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:33:05</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;How does your body feel after being in space for 6 months? Adapted. You feel like a spaceling. You feel completely normal, and don't even remember that you're flying. There is no up or down. You are really no longer an earthling, but a spaceling.  gt;Are you excited to meet the ISS robot: Humanoid Kino Bot in 2013? I know of Robonaut on board, but I'm more excited to see Canadarm 2 again. It is a much more capable robot.  gt;How did it feel when your saw earth from space for the first time? It feels like someone's revealing a secret to you. Like you're getting to see something magic for the first time. It feels like an honour. Like a huge privilege.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:34:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I am a science fiction fan. I grew up as a science fiction fan. I like Arthur C. Clarke, Issac Asimov, Robert Heinlein. I like Edgar Rice Burroughs, Star Trek. That said, nowadays I prefer science fact.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:44:07</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;What does it feel like to look down on earth during a space walk? It is wildly beautiful, the colours and textures, the global view, the chance to have the Northern Lights ripple under your feet. Stupefying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;What is your biggest fear associated with embarking on a mission? That someone I know and love on Earth will get hurt or die, and I won't be able to help or be there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:46:30</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Do you land in Kazakhstan on the return flight? Yes, after 5 months in orbit, we'll land on the open Kazakh prairie, normally near Arkylyk, a few hundred km from where we launched</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:48:54</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Are you mentally at work all the time during the mission, or will you feel like you can 'get away' for a break now and then? I will deliberately mentally get away. Play guitar by the big cupola windows and steal some time to truly appreciate what is actually happening - to me, and in history</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:57:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Part of the job of being an astronaut is trust in others - I have no choice, and it has worked for me so far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:58:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I served Canada for 25 years in the Air Force, and was eventually promoted to the rank of Colonel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 17:59:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have an BEng, an Masters in Aviation Systems, and graduated from Test Pilot School.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:00:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>The great people I work with, pushing themselves and me to the limits of what we can do with our lives.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:00:39</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Favorite guitar player Mark Knopfler</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:01:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like magic, like a genie touched your head and said "Fly!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:01:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Luckily, astronauts get to do both. I prefer it that way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:02:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Space X is an excellent company, working hard to make spaceflight as safe and inexpensive as possible. It's the right direction to be heading.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:03:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure, our connection is intermittent and slow, but if I can do an in-space AMA, I will!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:04:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Station only has so much space inside, pun intended, like a sailboat at sea, and with new equipment arriving all the time. We have to put the trash out, just like everyone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:05:11</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Poutine I wish we could! I love poutine, especially on a cold day. But it doesn't keep nor travel well, and definitely isn't suitable for freeze-drying :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:06:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Space Station has 130 experiments running simo, from studying the human heart to collecting dark matter from the universe to measuring the health of Earth's atmosphere. We run the experiments, and the building, and fix everything that breaks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:07:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Study what you love, and learn it as well as you possibly can - pursue your passions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:07:26</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;How big a threat are micrometeorites to the ISS and how do you deal with them? We get peppered by micrometeorites all the time, but the Station has armour. It won't stop a big one, but we have emergency response prodecedures if we get a puncture.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:08:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Station has no distinctive smell - it is clean and well-maintained, like being inside an airliner, maybe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:08:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll trim my moustache with scissors and a vacuum cleaner.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:09:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maple syrup, maple cookies, buffalo cranberry jerky, blueberry bars, chocolate, Holy Crap cereal, specialty honey ... lots!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:10:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>When we come in from a spacewalk the airlock has a distinct smell, like gunpowder or ozone - that is the smell of space.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:11:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sleeping with no gravity is wonderful - you can relax EVERY muscle, you don't need to roll over, you don't need a pillow - VERY comfortable!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:12:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>They should look at the photos of the tracks and Lunar Landers sitting on the Moon :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:13:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have the ARED - Advanced Resistive Exercise Device - like a big squat machine, and work out 2 hours per day. With that, we have largely beaten osteoporosis.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:14:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been in Russia and Kazakhstan for months - I dodged nothing :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:15:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shaving is similar, though you can't rinse your razor, so we use them up faster. We use disposables.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:15:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bought an Omega Speedmaster, very useful for spaceflight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:16:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have a squishy thing inside we jam our nose into while we clear our ears - we scratch our nose on that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:17:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It feels so ... unfair! Even your ARM is heavy. It takes about 1 day on Earth for every day in space to readapt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:17:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:18:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not at all - you are in a perfectly smooth, frictionless vacuum, moving near-effortlessly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:19:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>When things don't stay on the table or fall to the floor, you lose them ALL the time! So we use Velcro a lot, on almost everything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:21:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I invented a form of darts - with a heavy metal knob that had a velcro sticker on it, a long zip-tie as the haft, and a handkerchief parachute to slow it down, all duct-taped together. I aimed at Vecro on the walls, threw it slow and straight - worked great!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:23:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Worthwhile things often involve risk. The secret is to balance risk vs reward. I am NOT a thrill-seeker. I take calculated risks to do things that I deem worthwhile. Like being strapped into a Soyuz rocket in 6 days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:24:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>The coolest gadget on ISS the the AMS - collecting dark matter and high-energy particles to try and figure out what the universe is made of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:25:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Being underwater, especially when I lived on the ocean's floor for a few weeks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:26:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes - I flew the world's largest centrifuge in Star City, Russia, to practice manually flying the Soyuz home through the atmosphere. It can get to  gt;20G, but we only go up to 8.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:29:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>My day has been fine. We did a media tour of Quarantine here in Baikonur (they were all wearing masks so we wouldn't catch their colds), I exercised, I studied, I did emails, and now I'm doing an AMA. I also ate well - the food in Quarantine is good!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:31:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>International cooperation is difficult, especially with finance and risk, but the ISS is a shining example of success in that area. I think we are doing what you suggest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:32:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I spent the 1st 8 years of my life in Sarnia, and the next 8 in Milton, so they are both my hometowns. That's where I grew up, and became the adult that I am.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:35:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Robonaut works in a fixed location inside ISS. We put it in place. There are plans to bring up legs for it, and eventually it will be able to move on it own, but it's still in early testing and certification.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:36:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Space is absolutely silent. With no air to transmit sound waves, there can be no noise. So when you're out on a spacewalk, all you hear are radio transmissions and your own breathing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:39:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Interesting question, one of perspective. I find every day fulfilling. I work hard at what I'm doing, I do it as well as I can, and I find satisfaction in every small thing. It is not like my life is compromised so that I can fly in space. I love each part of each day, AND I fly in space. I think it's largely how you look at it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:42:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>This question was sent to me yesterday when my son was announcing the AMA from /u/Tuesday_D:  gt;I want to know about the differences in experience between NASA launches and Russian Space Agency launches and how that might change his perspective of the mission. They are very similar - years of training, focus towards launch, dress rehearsals, a week or 2 of quarantine, a rocketship nearby getting fueled, suiting up, ride out to the pad, pressure checks, and ... launch! The differences are language, size and design of the ship, and Baikonur isn't Cocoa Beach.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:44:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Space Station is noisy, as the fans and pumps have to move the air to keep us alive. So it sounds like playing in the back of a bus. The best part is that the guitar floats in front of you. You don't need a strap! You have to relearn how to bar chord, as without weight, your arm goes too far, and you overshoot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:45:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, we get alone time during the 5 months in orbit. My sleep station is like a 1-person closet, and when I pull the door closed, it is private. Also, the Station is BIG. You can work for hours and see no one else, especially when there are just 3 of us onboard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:48:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I find theoretical math hard, but also useful. It's like using a complex machine to do something you couldn't do any other way, like a backhoe or a fly rod. Once you see the purpose of it and learn how it works, though, it gets easier. It just takes dogged work and repetition to figure it out. Also true for spaceships.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:49:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since we are an international crew, we chose which annual holidays to celebrate. We agreed on 25 Dec Christmas, January Orthodox Christmas, and New Years, so we'll celebrate all three!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:51:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>What excites me most in space technology is ... propulsion. We are very limited in what we have now, and to go to Mars or further we will likely need something better. The VASIMIR engine, the ion drive engines, much more efficient solar power, these all help point the way to the future.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:54:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am bringing books, mostly as gifts for my crewmates. Ebooks are nice, but it's also nice to hold a book in your hands. I brought humour books (Dave Barry) and classics (Conan Doyle), and my wife has packed books for me as a surprise. I hope :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:54:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apollo 13 was a great film. I thought it was well told and was quite accurate. Armageddon on the other hand...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>People disbelieve a lot of facts, and it is rarely wise to try to rationalize with them. We have taken pictures of the equipment left on the moon. There is no question if we've been there, except to those who would rather believe than learn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:57:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>When in space, if you look away from the Sun, it is total darkness. It's because there is no air to reflect and refract the light around you. You can even take a picture looking at the Sun. The bright Sun will be blown out in the image, but space around it will be black. The only light becomes the glow of the Earth and starlight. Very cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:58:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>[NEEMO 14](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/NEEMO), in an underwater lab.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 18:58:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Having a conversation in weightlessness is like chatting in a swimming pool. Your sort of drift around, and don't always look at each other. But when you want to say something important, or be clearly understood, you need to get your heads lined up and make eye contact. Maybe also like a conversation in bed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 19:00:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a funny question. I'm not instructed to say anything. My answers are honest and factual.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 19:02:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been working towards being an astronaut since I was a nine year old boy watching man land on the moon. I love my job, and get a tremendous satisfaction from doing it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 19:03:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perhaps there is scientific merit in choosing different test subjects for spaceflight, but the key is we are not just there to be experimented upon. We also have to do everything - fly the spaceship, speak Russian, operate the Canadarm2, perform spacewalks, know all the systems, and stay healthy. Scott has 15 years of hard-won experience that will allow him to command the ISS and safely stay there for a year. We stand to learn a lot from his service, as well as Michael's.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 19:07:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am a true Canadian, yes, born, raised, Leafs fan, Tim Horton's maple dip lover, have lived in 6 provinces and visited them all, Rick Mercer advocate, speak 3 languages including French and English, know all the Stan Rogers tunes by heart and feel great pride in our home and native land. Thanks for asking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 19:07:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go WOSS! I am a proud graduate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 19:08:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmmm ... my last corndog was ... never. Not good astronaut food, sorry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 19:10:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sure hope we go to Mars in my lifetime. We have satellites orbiting it, rovers driving around and sampling it, and are learning on the Space Station how to build spaceships that we could trust to go that far. One small step at a time, it's amazing how far you can go. 30 years ago, who'd have thought I'd been commanding a spaceship?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 19:13:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favorite subject in school was English. I love the exquisite power of language, especially when well-used. It can sometimes turn our random thoughts and mental images into poetry and lyrics and speeches that truly communicate and inspire.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 19:17:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I decided to become an astronaut when I was 9, the day Buzz and Neil walked on the Moon. I have been working towards being one ever since. My education, my experience, the skills I gained from 9 until 32 all were key in getting me selected. And in the 20 years I have been an astronaut, I have studied and prepared pretty much every day. Being an astronaut is not really my job. It is more a definition of who I have turned myself into.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 19:20:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Precisely. Regardless of what they believe beforehand, I find spaceflight enhances a person's views, as opposed to greatly changing them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 19:23:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>During my first spacewalk I was riding on Canadarm2 as the Space Station was coming across the Indian Ocean in the dark, at 8 km/sec. I shut off my spacesuit lights to let my eyes adjust, so I could see the lights of Australia. But instead, I saw ... the Southern Lights. Thousands of miles of greens and reds, yellow and orange curtains billowing and flowing with light, pouring up out of the Earth under my feet. I couldn't believe it. Could this really be the Earth I knew? How could this always be happening and I had never known it? It gave be a new-found wonder at our ignorance, and really showed me our planet as a ball going around a star, just another planet, but an immensely beautiful one. Made me love our Earth even more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 19:27:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dear Redditors - it is late, and my flight surgeon just came in and told me to get to bed. We have lights-out here in Quarantine in 30 minutes, and I have to get back to my building and get to sleep. Tomorrow we go get into our Soyuz spaceship. It's our final look inside before our launch on the 19th. We'll check where everything is in its final configuration, and make sure we're happy that it's ready for us to go to space. A pretty exciting time in anybody's life, and hugely so for me. Thanks for the great questions and dialogue, and for giving me a chance to try and share this incredible new human experience. Goodnight from the Baikonur Cosmodrome Chris Hadfield CSA Astronaut</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 19:30:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. But being in space makes me feel like I need to take batter care of the Earth. To be a good steward and advocate. To pick up trash when I see it, to notice the beauty that surrounds me, to recognize what's precious. I try not to hate anything - it's rarely a motivator to do something good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 19:32:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>One last thing - huge thanks to my son, Evan, who encouraged me to do this AMA, taught me how to use Reddit, and set it up for all of us. Thanks, son! Love, Dad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-13 19:41:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe that in the vastness of space there is a likelihood of alien life. However, there is no evidence whatsoever to suggest that any creatures more advanced than man have ever been to earth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I will be living in space from December until May. What types of photos or video do you think I should take?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-15 06:30:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello again Reddit! Since seeing the interest expressed by redditors at [my AMA the other day](http://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/14schr/i_am_astronaut_chris_hadfield_commander_of/), I've been thinking about how to keep everyone here involved in the mission. Therefore, what I would like to do is get a feel for what types of photos (and to a lesser extent video) you'd like to see and try to oblige. The best suggestions, (and those that I am capable of) I'll be looking to upload to my [twitter](https://twitter.com/Cmdr_Hadfield) and [facebook](http://www.facebook.com/AstronautChrisHadfield) and hopefully my son can then post them here. So, if you were me -- what would *you* capture on film?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This morning our rocket rolled out to the launch pad. Two days to liftoff!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-17 10:41:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>One last kiss for my wife, and it's time to go to space.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-19 05:09:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-19 16:38:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just to make it clear, this has been posted from his account by his son. He is not yet capable of posting, as the Soyuz does not connect to the ISS for a few days. I just thought people would want to see the launch video.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-19 17:57:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fear, pride, and awe. Like a storybook, a single tear rolled down my cheek. I have never been more proud of anything than I was watching him this afternoon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-19 18:21:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for posting this! I (his son) got beat to the punch! What an amazing experience. I wish everyone could be there to see what man is capable of, and how awe inspiring our world truly can be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-19 22:11:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>They do, but it is very similar to 90's dial up. Not exactly conducive to most sites these days (especially reddit).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-20 03:17:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>As close as close can be, yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not sure if it's up to reddit standards, but here is a song I recorded yesterday on the International Space Station.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-24 17:14:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-24 20:17:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Technically, his son took care of it. But he asked for it to be posted on reddit, and I was pretty devastated to see it tank. He gives me the titles because at the moment he only gets packet email while they fix internet. (edit: His internet is now fixed, and he is posting links on reddit.) I assumed it was due to the fact that the youtube version had my shitty video/photo compilation attached to it. Glad that it worked out on Soundcloud. It is a pretty nice song and I'm happy people enjoy it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-25 07:21:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll pass the message along, sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It may not fit here directly, but on my last post I was asked to record the ambient noise from the space station for use in recordings. Here it is.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-26 16:14:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-26 16:22:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here is the reddit link I've made: http://www.reddit.com/r/Music/comments/15gx3p/it_may_not_fit_here_directly_but_on_my_last_post/ Here is the direct soundcloud: https://soundcloud.com/colchrishadfield/space-station-noise</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-26 21:02:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jewel in the Night was recorded in the sleeping quarters, whereas this was recorded in the US lab. Sounds in the sleeping quarters are dampened. (Son's note)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-27 06:48:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is a song by my father and his brother for my Grandmother, Eleanor. (Son's note)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-27 17:29:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow! There was a lot more interest than I expected. I had upgraded the soundcloud account to fulfill what I expected would be more than enough demand, but we've already hit the download limit. Sorry to people who have been unable to download. I will see about upgrading further to allow more downloads. Edit: Upgraded! Download away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-27 18:58:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here you go: http://www.freesound.org/people/subject5062/sounds/172547/ (Son's note)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Earth, Moon and Soyuz: Kevin Ford took this picture as we approached Station last week. Amazing work of extraplanetary art.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-31 16:32:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yesterday, I took this picture of the Rocky Mountains from Space. Flying over Canada in nine minutes, it can be tough to get a clear shot.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-31 17:30:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>From Space, this cloud looked a bit like a hand slowly sliding across the water. It was downright surreal.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-01-06 13:50:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-01-06 15:41:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just read your comment, from here in my sleep pod on the Space Station. Thank you for the nice words, I really appreciate them. Aspirations are the necessary seeds of fulfillment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hi Reddit, from the International Space Station. Tonight I was playing the guitar here and thought of a question for you. If you could have me play one song here in space, what would it be?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-08 22:49:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm thinking of appropriate songs to play and I'd love to hear all your answers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-08 22:51:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're also more than welcome to answer on [twitter](https://twitter.com/Cmdr_Hadfield/status/299996159487918080).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hi /r/technology, from the International Space Station. My 'AMA from space' will take place this Sunday at 4 p.m. EST. Really looking forward to your questions!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-15 16:48:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hi /r/Canada! I'm writing to formally announce my 'AMA from Space', starting this Sunday at 4 p.m. EST. Looking forward to the questions!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-15 16:56:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I Am Astronaut Chris Hadfield, currently orbiting planet Earth.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 21:49:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello Reddit! My name is Chris Hadfield. I am an astronaut with the Canadian Space Agency who has been living aboard the International Space Station since December, orbiting the Earth 16 times per day. You can view a pre-flight AMA I did [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/14schr/i_am_astronaut_chris_hadfield_commander_of/). If I don't get to your question now, please check to make sure it wasn't answered there already. The purpose of all of this is to connect with you and allow you to experience a bit more directly what life is like living aboard an orbiting research vessel. You can continue to support manned space exploration by following daily updates on [Twitter](https://twitter.com/Cmdr_Hadfield), [Facebook](http://www.facebook.com/AstronautChrisHadfield) or [Google+](https://plus.google.com/u/0/+ChrisHadfield/posts). It is your support that makes it possible to further our understanding of the universe, one small step at a time. To provide proof of where I am, [here's a picture of the first confirmed alien sighting in space](https://twitter.com/Cmdr_Hadfield/status/303244780006150145). Ask away! --- Thanks everyone for the great questions! I have to be up at 06:00 tomorrow, with a heavy week of space science planned, so past time to drift off to sleep. Goodnight, Reddit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:11:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>My laptop here onboard communicates to a server in Houston via satellite relay, and that server on the ground is hooked through a computer to the internet. The data rate is very slow, not fast enough to watch video, but perfect for things like Reddit and Twitter. We have the data link about half the time. No Skype, but when we have the right communications links I can directly access the internet in Mission Control, Houston, and Tweet and do this AMA real-time. We have that link many times, every day. It's a great capability to have, really lets the crew keep in touch. Currently just off the Western coast of Australia in the Indian Ocean.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:16:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>We didn't see the meteorite that did all the damage in Russia, as we were on the other side of the Earth. But I see small ones burn up between ISS and the earth every day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:19:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Privatization is the right and natural way to go, and we are on the cusp of it now. We have a Space X Dragon coming to ISS in 2 weeks, we'll grab it with Canadarm2. My favorite experiment is [BCAT](http://www.asc-csa.gc.ca/eng/sciences/bcatc1.asp) - looking at the behaviour of nanoparticles and structures and how they form without the weight of gravity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:22:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks like a carpet of countless tiny perfect unblinking lights in endless velvet, with the Milky Way as a glowing area of paler texture.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:24:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Air Cadets in Canada is a superb program for people between 13 and 18. It taught me self disipline, leadership and how to fly, and directly laid the groundwork for where I am floating today. Per Ardua Ad Astra.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:26:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>During my 2nd spaceflight, while doing a live National TV News broadcast, I forgot the name of the Space Shuttle Commander. He always went by his nickname of Rommel, and to come up with Kent Rominger somehow escaped me. Instead, I said Ken Cameron, the CDR of my 1st flight. Oops.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:27:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I watched a large meteorite burn up between me and Australia, and to think of that hypersonic dumb lump of rock randomly hurtling into us instead sent a shiver up my back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:29:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be an astronaut you have to be healthy (eat your greens and exercise), smart (do your homework), and trustworthy (do your jobs well). Then you get the suit and rocket.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:31:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those are several bad ideas :) We're here for a pretty pure purpose, on behalf of everyone else. Keeps mutinies to a minimum.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:36:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>All the pictures I take are for everyone, and available here: http://eol.jsc.nasa.gov/ If seeing the world with our own eyes as one place, vivdly, daily, doesn't educate people on global issues, what will?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:38:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never get lost in the Space Station, but I often have to look around to decide which way I want to use as 'up' right now. Maybe this is how fish and spiders feel. I did a Japanese art experiment to view the world in floating drops of water, and make HD video of it. It was fun and beautiful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:39:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>The vacuum of space has no smell, but when we come in from a spacewalk the airlock smells like ozone, or gunpowder. It likely comes from the gentle offgassing of the outer metal and fabric of our suits.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:40:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm still learning! But sometimes now, I am graceful. I feel like an adapted ape swinging through the jungle canopy ... until I miss a handrail and crash into the wall.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:44:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have robot ships at the Moon, on Mars, and by every planet in the Solar System. We'll go to the Moon in person again as soon as we've learned all we can on ISS, and have solid, reliable engines to take us there and back. Can you invent those engines? You have an entire life to do it in. Then you could ride them, and stand on another world.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:44:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Simply fly - to push off and glide magically to the other end of the Station. It makes me smile to myself, every time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:46:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Australia looks coolest - the colours and textures of the Outback are severly artistic. The most beautiful to me are the Bahamas, the vast glowing reefs of every shade of blue that exists.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:46:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try to look out the window as often and as long as possible. Truly see our world.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:47:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have special computers that run the spaceship, yes, but they are based on normal Earth computers. To AMA I am just using a regular laptop. It's the connection that is like magic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:49:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love sleeping weightless. No mattress, no pillow, no sore shoulder, no hot spots. Just relax every muscle in your body and drift off to sleep. I'm trained as an EMT, and Tom is a doctor, plus we have a basic pharmacy onboard. If it were really bad, we'd get in our Soyuz and return to Earth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:54:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>The ones that the taxpayers want. My job is to perform them as efficiently and creatively as I can, like what I'm doing today, and during these 5 months.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:57:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>We conduct science every day, but are lighter-loaded on Sat/Sun. The biggest danger is launch - all that power and acceleration. Once we survive that, it's just a steady threat of radiation, meteorite impacts, and vehicle system failure like fire or ammonia breakthrough. We need better engines for spaceflight to be safer and simpler, and thus cheaper. Like the difference to cross the Atlantic in a prop vs a jet airplane.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 22:58:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>we use Nikon D2 and D3 SLR cameras with lenses from 400mm to fish-eye.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 23:06:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>We can adjust the temp, but we keep it comfortable room temp, good for working out and living, sleeping. No coffee table book planned, but you never know :) I shave with cream and a standard multi-blade, just wipe it on a cloth every time, works fine My family is fine - in fact my son Evan is helping support my social media, and taught me how to use Reddit. My other son is in China and turns 30 tomorrow (Happy Birthday Kyle!) and my daughter is in Ireland. I talked with my wife today, she's fine too - all were at launch in Kazakhstan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 23:09:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wrote the 1st version of the song, Ed used a bunch of my ideas for the main lyric and came up with that awesome melody, I wrote the 2nd verse, Ed chose the bridge. We worked together, and Ed is just a wonderful Canadian guy. I really like what we did, and the Coalition for Music Education is doing a lot of good for young Canadians with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 23:11:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dreams are the same, I think - the idle ramble of my recharging brain, organizing my perceptions into fancy and drama. It's when I'm awake that things are very different :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 23:12:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please contact the Cdn Space Agency to set it up, at their website. They will try and fit it into the existing plans if they can. It would be good if we could!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 23:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm typing now in my 'Sleep Station', a small padded room with a door, completely private, like a bedroom without the bed, and phone booth sized.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 23:15:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometimes we hear pings as tiny rocks hit our spaceship, and also the creaks and snaps of expanding metal as we go in and out of sunlight. The solar panels are full of tiny holes from the micro-meteorites.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 23:16:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>At first, yes, but after a few days, you start to see the whole world as one place. An awesome perspective to be given.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 23:17:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Privacy here is about the same as how I grew up - one of five kids in a farmhouse. It's never a problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 23:23:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I love Bowie, and I've been singing and playing that song. Changed the words a bit, though, so Major Tom has a happier ending.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 23:30:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's always positive and negative. We lost a crew early in Apollo, and the last 2 Moon landings were cancelled even though the rockets were built. Skylab decayed and fell from the sky before the Shuttle could be made ready to fly. We've endured accidents, budget cycles, and many naysayers. But meanwhile we have accomplished countless acts of magnificence, from walking on the Moon to Hubble teaching us about the universe, to international cooperation, to Curiosity drilling on Mars, to permanently leaving Earth on ISS. I'm working as hard as I can to help that all happen, and have been for 20 years. It's hard to leave home, but we're managing to do it as a species, regardless. Pretty amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 23:31:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a new one - lemon curd cake. A sin to eat, but we're short on sin up here, so I think it's OK.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 23:33:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was Canada's first spacewalker, doing 2 to help build the mighty Canadarm2 robot onto ISS. It was the most magnificent experience of my life. Alone in a 1-person spaceship (my suit), just holding on with my 1 hand, with the bottomless black universe on my left and the World pouring by in technicolor on my right. I highly recommend it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 23:36:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't seen the video yet, but I will, and I look forward to it - thanks! Yes, I attended Royal Roads Military College near Victoria for the 1st 2 years of my undergraduate degree. My Mother-In-Law lives in Victoria! I've never been to that Institute, yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 23:37:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>We live on Greenwich time, UTC, same as London England. We shut of most lights at bedtime - it feels right to do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 23:38:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone with a good moustache.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 23:52:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Earth is hit by 100 tons of debris a day, most of it natural, a small fraction man-made. We maneuver the Space Station out of the way when NORAD tells us debris may come too close to us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 23:54:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favourite picture is of noctilucent cloud - to me it is both beautiful and scientific. I never thought I'd even see those rare phenomena, let alone get a top-notch photo of them. You can see the photo [here](https://twitter.com/Cmdr_Hadfield/status/287978095405838336).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-17 23:58:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Decide in your heart of hearts what really excites and challenges you, and start moving your life in that direction. Every decision you make, from what you eat to what you do with your time tonight, turns you into who you are tomorrow, and the day after that. Look at who you want to be, and start sculpting yourself into that person. You may not get exactly where you thought you'd be, but you will be doing things that suit you in a profession you believe in. Don't let life randomly kick you into the adult you don't want to become.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-18 00:01:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Space Station is solar powered, with lots of reserve in the batteries while we're behind the Earth in the shade, so no real need to conserve it. We work out 2 hours per day, every day, just to stay at a constant level of fitness to be ready to do a spacewalk, and to have strong bones and muscles when we come home. We have ~130 experiments running on ISS. I help fix them, recharge them, conduct them, and keep the Station healthy to support them. The ultimate lab tech. If you would like to research more into what is being done on station, you can check any number of the websites provided by the [Canadian Space Agency](http://www.asc-csa.gc.ca/eng/iss/default.asp) or [NASA]( http://www.nasa.gov/mission_pages/station/research/index.html) for [Expedition 34/35]( http://www.asc-csa.gc.ca/eng/missions/expedition34-35/).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-18 00:04:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bought my first guitar with my big brother when I was about 11, and we taught ourselves how to play. I learned formal music and played trombone at school, right through university. I play and sing in 2 bands in Houston, and played with the Chieftains at the Houston Symphony this past Friday night by video. Today I recorded a song my brother and I wrote, like an aural snapshot of life up here. I've always loved playing music.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-18 00:05:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello UBC! Hello UBC Astronomy Club!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-18 00:08:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are trained to be able to do everything onboard - we have to be. It takes many years. Station has many levels of current protection, circuit breakers inside and out, most that can be reset remotely. Our solar panels are big and powerful, and we have enough taht we can lose some and still power everything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-18 00:08:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hit my head about once per day :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-18 00:12:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>A long list of questions, I choose ... plants: we have grown plants as experiments for many years on space stations, but have none right now. This close to Earth it is simpler to bring food here than to count on growing and processing it. But to leave Earth and go to Mars, we may have to have a relaible small farm onboard. We think we have learned how, through previous testing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-18 00:16:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be an astronaut who orbits earth and stays for a while, it needs to become your main life's work. It takes: physical fitness to the highest standard, an advanced technical degree, and a proven ability to make good decisions when consequences matter. Then apply to the Space Agency of your country, and compete with the thousands who also want to fly in space. [Jeremy Hansen](http://www.asc-csa.gc.ca/eng/astronauts/biohansen.asp) and [David Saint-Jacques](http://www.asc-csa.gc.ca/eng/astronauts/biosaintjacques.asp) were the 2 most recent Canadians to get hired - check them out online.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-18 00:19:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Each astronaut has personal goals as part of their career. One of mine has been education and public awareness of what we are doing in space exploration. This current 5-month mission combined with the advent of social media has made this possible like never before. I think it is important that people see the world from this new perspective that technology has given us, and I do my utmost to make that happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-18 00:20:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>The aurora - Northern and Southern lights. A fantastic continuous light show as we swing north and south, just shimmering and dancing there, demanding to be stared at.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-18 00:27:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a species, we have always taken the very best of our technology and used it to take us to the furthest reaches of our knowledge - the horse, the wheel, the sailing ship, steamship, propellor, jet, rocket, Space Station. Yes, we will establish a permanent base on the Moon and beyond, but when depends on inventions not yet made. My guess is that power generation is the primary obstacle, and fossil fuels and even solar power won't be enough. Meanwhile, the Space Station is the crucible where space exploration technology is designed and tested. When we go further out, it will be heavily indebted to the pedigree of space hardware proven on ISS.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-18 00:28:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>About 1 day back on Earth for every day weightless. Some things come back quicker, but bones and muscles take time to truly recover.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-13 19:00:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi all. My son alerted me to the thread, and although I'm racing around (the world) today, I wanted to pop in to give my sincerest thanks and gratitude for all the support I've received from this eclectic online community. The AMAs, general discussions and feedback have all been tremendous. I am genuinely humbled by the response we've had so far. To those who asked questions, provided answers where I couldn't, helped create visibility for the space program or even upvoted a photo - you are actively making a difference. Every little step forward, and every new eye opened is proactive movement towards a sustained and well-supported space program, and thus better understanding of the universe and our Earth's place in it. Thank you reddit. Sincerely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've recorded a version of Danny Boy for today in orbit. Hope you like it!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-17 19:36:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hi from orbit, Reddit! I helped Canada unveil its new high-tech $5 bill yesterday. What do you think of the new design?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-01 19:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-02 14:18:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is Chris' son, Evan. I am using his account just so that people notice this. No bitcoin has been (or will be) accepted from orbit at this time. It is illegal for Dad to take any tips outside of his pay, as he is a government employee. I don't know much about bitcoin, but from what I've read the Canadian government counts it as taxable income. Sorry to be the bearer of bad news, but this can't be a first.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A few months ago, you requested I record Space Oddity. From my last full day on board the International Space Station - I hope you enjoy it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-12 23:04:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>For my final post on Reddit from the International Space Station, here is my (slightly-adjusted) cover of David Bowie's classic, Space Oddity.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-12 23:05:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>44 years ago today Mike, Buzz and Neil took us to the Moon. They inspired me like no other. Eternal thanks.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-20 16:15:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-29 23:57:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Many thanks for all of the birthday wishes, reddit! It is a heart-warming welcome for a spaceman back on Earth. A lovely thing was done for my birthday this year: http://my.charitywater.org/chris-hadfields-birthday. The best gifts live on long past the act of giving - I really appreciate the shared goodness. Thanks again to all!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hi /r/nyc. I'll be at the Union Square B amp;N on the 1st signing my new book.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-27 02:19:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was told it was hard to get a New York crowd out to a bookstore on a Friday night, so I thought I'd check with reddit to gauge the level of interest. I'll be signing books from 7:00 - 9:00 p.m. on Nov. 1st at the Barnes and Noble at Union Square, 33 E 17th Street - I hope to see you there. You can see more from the book tour schedule here: http://chrishadfield.ca/booktour/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Earth smiles broadly as the Sun rises. One of my favourite shots from orbit.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-27 03:04:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hi /r/toronto! I'll be hosting the first stop on my book tour at the Manulife Indigo on the 29th.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-27 22:26:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone! I'll be launching my book tour with a signing from 7:00 - 8:30 p.m. on Oct. 29th at the Manulife Indigo. I'm really looking forward to seeing everyone. You can see my returns to Toronto, as well as the whole book tour schedule here: http://chrishadfield.ca/booktour/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'll be signing books at the National Air and Space Museum this Saturday, Nov. 2nd.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-27 23:17:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello redditors of /r/washingtondc! I will be in town briefly this coming week to launch my book tour in the US. Signings of the book will be taking place at the NASM from 2-5pm on Saturday, Nov. 2nd. It would be a real pleasure to meet all of you in person - I hope to see you there. You can see the entire book tour schedule here: http://chrishadfield.ca/booktour/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A little over a month ago I challenged my son to make a video for my book launch that wasn't just some over-the-top ad. Here's what he came up with.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-29 22:43:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hi Houston! I'll be at the Gilruth center from 5p.m. tomorrow, signing copies of my new book (for the general public). I'd love it if you took the time to come out and say hi.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-04 20:15:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi /r/houston! I'll be signing books from 5:00p.m. onwards tomorrow, Nov. 5th at the Gilruth center. I'm excited to return to my home of over twenty years, do some medical tests, and meet all of you. You can see the whole book tour schedule here: http://chrishadfield.ca/booktour/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-05 00:14:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you. I really appreciate that you took the time to help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hi /r/Chicago! I'll be signing my new book at the B amp;N in Skokie tomorrow (the 6th). I'd love to see you all there.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-05 20:43:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone, I'll be signing books from 7:00 - 9:00 p.m. tomorrow (Nov. 6th) at the Barnes and Noble at [55 Old Orchard Center in Skokie](https://www.google.com/maps/preview#!q=55+Old+Orchard+Center+Skokie+IL+60077+United+States amp;data=!1m4!1m3!1d4058!2d-87.7473719!3d42.0614716!4m15!2m14!1m13!1s0x880fc58f48c75529%3A0xdfc74f2ebabce735!3m8!1m3!1d26081603!2d-95.677068!3d37.0625!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!4m2!3d42.061472!4d-87.7473811). It would be nice to be able to meet with all of you - I hope you take the time to come join us. You can see more from the book tour schedule here: http://chrishadfield.ca/booktour/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hello /r/bayarea! I'll be doing a book signing in Corte Madera tomorrow (9th) starting at 4p.m.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-08 18:56:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone, I'll be doing a public interview and book signing from 4:00 - 6:00 p.m. tomorrow (Nov. 9th) at the [Book Passage in Corte Madera](https://www.google.com/maps/preview#!q=51+Tamal+Vista+Blvd.+Corte+Madera+94925 amp;data=!1m4!1m3!1d138028!2d-122.4816766!3d37.8854318!4m15!2m14!1m13!1s0x80859a61adc41a77%3A0xc57476c4f5c70937!3m8!1m3!1d26081603!2d-95.677068!3d37.0625!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!4m2!3d37.9339776!4d-122.517763). I hope to see you there. You can view the entire tour schedule here: http://chrishadfield.ca/booktour/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hi /r/LosAngeles! I have two book tour stops in the LA area today (Huntington Beach) and tomorrow (The Grove).</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-10 17:30:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone, I'll be doing a book signing from 3:00 - 5:00 p.m. today (Nov. 10th) at the Barnes and Noble in Huntington Beach, as well as tomorrow starting a 7p.m. at the Grove. I hope to see you all there! You can view the entire tour schedule here: http://chrishadfield.ca/booktour/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-13 16:28:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hear, hear.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-14 00:40:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>No.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hello /r/Michigan! I'll be giving a talk and book signing in Lansing (Schuler Books) this Sunday (24th) from 2-5 p.m. I'm looking forward to seeing you all there.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-22 16:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-22 18:33:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfortunately, yes. It was a last minute addition so we could have any at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I am Col. Chris Hadfield, retired astronaut.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 02:57:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am Commander Chris Hadfield, recently back from 5 months on the Space Station. Since landing in Kazakhstan I've been in Russia, across the US and Canada doing medical tests, debriefing, meeting people, talking about spaceflight, and signing books (I'm the author of a new book called ["An Astronaut's Guide to Life on Earth"](http://www.chrishadfield.ca)). Life after 3 spaceflights and 21 years in the Astronaut Corps is turning out to be busy and interesting. I hope to share it with you as best I can. So, reddit. Ask me anything! (If I'm unable to get to your question, please check my previous AMAs to see if it was answered there. Here are the links to my [from-orbit](http://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/18pik4/i_am_astronaut_chris_hadfield_currently_orbiting/) and [preflight](http://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/14schr/i_am_astronaut_chris_hadfield_commander_of/) AMAs.) Thanks everyone for the questions! I have an early morning tomorrow, so need to sign off. I'll come back and answer questions the next time a get a few minutes quiet on-line. Goodnight from Toronto!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:01:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're welcome. I retired form the Cdn Space Agency, so my chances of another ISS voyage are virtually nil, bit I would gladly go back. One-way to Mars - maybe, depending who was with me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:02:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>First key step is success in your studies. That will open doors more than anything else at this phase. Here's 5, way up high.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:04:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Favourite thing - the people. Choose a career that surrounds you with people who have skills you do not. You'll get better just by being there, learning by osmosis. Most difficult thing - remembering ALL the details taught over many years, to have them at front of brain on ISS when needed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:05:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the invitation! Never hurts to ask. If I have time and hunger at Montreal dinnertime, I'll send you a note :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:07:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>3 things: 1 - keep your body in shape. You get strong at the gym and thin in the kitchen 2 - get an advanced technical education, one that challenges you, at least a Master's degree 3 - make decisions, and stick to them. It's a skill that gets better with practice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:13:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right at landing I felt dizzy, heavy, and then nauseous. After working out 2 hrs/day on ISS I was plenty strong, just disoriented. The inner ear takes time to recalibrate, as does blood pressure. Within 12 hours I could walk fine, though with a bit of staggering. I see human spaceflight moving ever-outward from Earth. The logical sequence is Earth orbit, the Moon, asteroids, Mars. We have so much to learn/invent at each step, and there's no rush. It needs to be both driven and paced by technology, and drawn by science, discovery and then business.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:16:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, it is - you can get stuck floating in the center of Node 1, where open space is biggest due to hatches on all sides. But ISS has fans and forced air to mix and refresh the internal atmosphere, so there's always a small crosswind. Wait long enough, you'll get pulled to an air inlet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:16:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>We all tried it - too muffled, not the right type of propulsive nozzle :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:21:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was blinded by contamination in my spacesuit during my 1st spacewalk. It was the anti-fog used on my visor, took about 30 minutes for my eyes to tear enough to dilute it so that I could see again. Without gravity, tears don't fall, so they had to evaporate. No way to rub your eyes inside the helmet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:25:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>What we are doing here is important and worthwhile - discussing exploration, its purposes, its benefits, the useful results and insights we gain that make it of net worth to a nation. The best thing each of us can do is become informed on the subject, perhaps choose to work in aerospace, and directly tell your gov't rep what you support and why. It has to be based on cost vs benefit to be chosen over all other demands for tax dollars.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:28:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Picking one book is hard - I liked Before the Dawn, Carrying the Fire, and I read Darwin's Ghost while on orbit. I also read Sh*t My Dad Says up there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:28:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>My wife would object, sorry. And she's strong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:32:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Galaxy Quest 2. Both, always both. They serve different purposes - we need robots and sensors for certain tasks and risk levels, but we need people to understand, solve and appreciate the complexities of being in a new place.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:35:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool question. As I think about it I'm mentally playing back all the imagery and feeling of seeing cities from ISS. My favorites are the big, old cities, as they are well-lit testaments to history and culture - London, Paris, Cairo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:36:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're welcome. Why do you think that version of Space Oddity was so popular? I've been thinking about it some.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:41:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a strange environment, weightlessness. I wouldn't want to bring an animal that would be scared or unable to adapt. Also food and pooping are problematic. So perhaps something calm and simple, a reliable pet, like a snail. Nah, who am I kidding - I'd like Albert, my pug. He'd be hilarious and cheerful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:42:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>More - because it's impossible to burp when weightless (the gas, liquid and solid in your stomach all mix together). As an experiment, try standing on your head and burping.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:43:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes - I emailed with several of them today. Good people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:46:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, there is merit in the argument, but it's the facts that are important. How much does India spend on health, welfare and infrastructure vs research, development and exploration? What are the real numbers? All nations need both, in proportion. If we don't challenge and inspire our young, then we are losing out in the long run.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:47:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, we did. NASA kept our passports and visas, and brought them to us at landing, so we had them at the Karaganda airport to leave Kazakhstan. A funny but necessary detail of returning to Earth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:50:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I felt a special thrill when I could see the plume of Niagara Falls from orbit. It's a wonder of the world up close, and very cool to see from ISS. I also liked seeing the Manicouagan Crater in Quebec, a 215-million-year-old scar 100 km across, evidence of a huge asteroid impact, still easily visible to passing spacecraft.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:52:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your nose can't run without gravity ... you lose the 'drip' in post-nasal drip. But your sinuses don't drain either, so lots of full sinus feeling. I blew my nose regularly, and occasionally took a decongestant. It affected my singing voice a bit, I think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:55:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Formation flying is a learned skill, with high danger. Start with the theory, truly understand the aerodynamic effects and safety plans, as well as all signals. Brief with all pilots together, in extreme detail. Start flying formation far away, very gradually work your way in. Have an exit plan, always. Watch cross-controlling. Consciously relax, every 30 seconds. Build-up complexity of maneuvers. And have fun!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:58:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>When we have to sneeze in our spacesuit, we lean our heads forward and sneeze into our chest, to keep it from splattering on the visor. Still messy, but the best compromise - clean it up when you de-suit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 03:58:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes - we ask for a little help all the time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 04:00:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't play any computer games, sorry. In orbit life is just too grand and rare, and I've been too busy since I returned to Earth. Maybe at Christmas with my kids. I'll go with what they recommend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 04:03:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Space is profound, endless, a textured black, a bottomless eternal bucket of untouchable velvet and untwinkling stars. My goals for 2014 are the same as always - learn things, be useful, feel satisfied, play music, laugh and have fun, every day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 04:10:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've always thought that was an odd way to ask. 'Believing' and 'believing in' are 2 different things. Our best telescopes have shown us that there is basically an unlimited number of planets in the universe. To think that Earth is the only one where life could have developed is just self-importance. But to think that intelligent life has traveled all the way here and is sneaking around observing us is also just self-importance. The universe is basically endless. We have not yet found life anywhere but on Earth, but we're looking for it, to the best of our technical ability. All else is wishful thinking and science fiction.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 04:13:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, we even pose for Superman-like pictures, normally with a big goofy grin on our faces. But the inside of ISS is small enough that super-hero leaps often end in a tumbling crash into the other wall. An interesting experiment on ISS is to close your eyes and imagine that, instead of flying, you are falling. You can suddenly make the mental transition and it can be startling, like that panic rush you get in a dream. Then you open your eyes :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 04:14:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>My wife has a bit of a thing for Tom Selleck, but she likes mine best.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 04:17:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not that I know of, and with a small crew, the interpersonal psychological effects would be complex and perhaps destructive. Astronauts are just people in space, but we are professionals and crewmembers, and mutual respect and team success is key.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 04:23:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Balancing work with family is hard. I think most people try, mess it up, apologize, change something, and try again. The key is to get the whole family, self included, to see the big picture on both sides - work is necessary for income/standard of living/self-worth, and family is necessary for love/commitment/joy/humanity. Talk about the balance, often. Be patient. Remind each other when you are messing up. Make exceptions. Give insight - take each other to work, spend time swapping roles. Make no job beneath you. Accept that it won't always be good. And work at it, together.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 04:26:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I floated maple leaves on Space Station Mir and handed out maple sugar candies while playing Gordon Lightfoot, Stan Rogers and MacLean  amp; MacLean on guitar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 04:27:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, but that was a funny satire article.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 04:35:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gravity is visually the most realistic spacewalking movie ever made. I've done 2 spacewalks. They got the immensity and tumult of it just right, the feeling of tininess in a vast universe, with an ever-omnipresent Earth. The story line is very Hollywood, with lots of technical errors and oversights, but it's not intended to be a documentary or training film. It's just entertainment, and Sandra Bullock does a great job with her role, triumphing over adversity. As an engineer and astronaut I can easily criticize it, but why would I? Just sit back, relax, and enjoy the spectacle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 04:38:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for saying that, I am glad to hear it. Remember 2 things: - the small daily decisions of life are the ones that will actually turn you into who you become - celebrate all the victories and joys along the way. Don't measure your success nor self-worth on a distant outcome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 04:42:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>We very seldom get sick on ISS. There's no one to catch a cold from. The worst that can happen to is get a headache (they feel the same, take a headache pill, no biggie), or to get injured (I scraped my knee on a sharp corner). Throwing up is problematic, as without gravity, your vomit bounces back off the other side of the barf bag into your face. Plan ahead, bring a cloth to clean up. And tightly seal the bag - you live in the same air as the trash.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 04:45:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, I'm glad you told me that. I try and notice things, especially people who are quietly counting on me. Please tell your daughter 'Hello'!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 04:45:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>A fine question. I agree.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 04:50:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you everyone for the questions! I have an early morning tomorrow, so need to sign off. I'll come back and answer questions when I next get a few quiet minutes on-line. Night from Toronto!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-16 02:17:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure what you photoshopped. This is what I remember having happened.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-19 22:22:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love this Lego spaceman! Brilliantly done - right down to the guitar frets and wrap-around moustache. Thanks to the artist!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>On Monday I was given the opportunity to talk at TED about fear. It was an incredible experience, and I hope you like the result.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-19 20:15:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-19 23:25:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Surprising - the diversity and depth of people and thought. It seems like every speaker and passing conversation sparks a new idea or perspective in me. Like a chef with a whole new rack of spices, a painter with new colours. And an expectation and acceptance of new ideas and points of view.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-19 23:30:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Canadian version of the same - called the Beaverton.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bowie's last day - we had permission for a year, so Space Oddity comes down today.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-13 17:02:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-13 17:02:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello again reddit! It has been a year since my son and I created and released the [Space Oddity video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KaOC9danxNo). We have been amazed and delighted that so many people enjoyed it - and maybe saw what spaceflight can really be like. It helped show that humans have left Earth, and that the Space Station is a new stage, for not just science and exploration, but for our art and music too. With exploration comes insight  #8211; with perspective comes self-realization. We had permission from David Bowie #8217;s people to post the video on YouTube for a year, and that year is up. We are working on renewing the license for it, but as there are no guarantees when it comes to videos shot in space, we thought you might want to have one last look before we take it down. Thanks for everything. You've all been incredible throughout. Chris and Evan Hadfield Edit: Here's an [article](http://www.economist.com/blogs/economist-explains/2013/05/economist-explains-12) that details some of the copyright complications.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-13 19:23:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're mistaken.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-27 17:28:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>With me on Time and Don Pettit on your wall, we #8217;re all in good company together. The suits chafes a bit, doesn #8217;t it? Great creativity!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-12 22:43:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>The key question: what are our goals? I see them as threefold: - are we alone? - what is normal planetary behavior? - ...and curiosity, our 50,000+ year pattern of natural human exploration. With that, in your next 50 years I expect to see increasing probability of ET life, and maybe hard evidence of life itself. I think we will learn about the neighborhood we truly live in, and thus have an ever-increased understanding of Earth and it's ability to sustain life. And I think we will continue to learn on ISS for 15 years or so and then establish a habitat on the Moon, following the ISS model, but including India and China. Once we have solved the problems there of power generation, water/air recycling, food production, radiation protection, communication, navigation, psychology, in-situ resource usage and propulsion, then we will be ready to not just send probes to Mars, but to move there. That ought to keep us busy until you're 85 or so :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"In Canada", a tongue-in-cheek tribute for Canada Day from the Hadfield family.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-01 17:02:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-08 22:59:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not that I'm aware of, I'm not. That's the avatar for #personalrocketscientist, the online Q amp;A I'm doing with UK and Irish students during my current book tour. Sorry to disappoint.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-13 19:17:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're talking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-23 20:56:27</DATE>
    <TEXT> #1053; #1077;  #1087; #1083; #1086; #1093; #1086;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Every now and then, you get the sort of feedback that forces you to stop and smile.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-30 03:57:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I am Chris Hadfield. AMA.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 20:31:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello reddit! It has been almost two years since my last AMA, and I think with all I've had happen in the past little while it would be nice to take some time to come back and chat. The previous AMAs can be found [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/1s4l7v/i_am_col_chris_hadfield_retired_astronaut/) and [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/1dhovl/hi_from_orbit_reddit_i_helped_canada_unveil_its/). If I'm unable to get to your question today, there's a chance that you'll be able to find my responses there. Before our conversation, I #8217;d like to highlight three things that I've been up to recently, as they might be of interest to you. The first is [Generator](http://www.generatorevent.com/) ([fb event](https://www.facebook.com/events/712627588883618/)). Happening on the 28th (in 5 days) at Toronto's historic Massey Hall, it is a blend of comedy, science and music in the style of Brian Cox and Robin Ince's yearly event at the Hammersmith Apollo in London. The intent is to create a space for incredible, esoteric ideas and performers to reach a mainstream audience. For example, Marshall Jones' slam poem [Touchscreen](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kFX2LrNE3VI) is undeniably fascinating, but through an uncommon medium that makes seeing it inaccessible. I want Toronto to have a platform where performers can meet a large audience more interested in their message than their medium. It isn #8217;t a show that is easy to describe, but I think it will be one that is memorable. While I wouldn't call it a charity event in the way that term is often used, the proceeds from the show will be going to local non-profits that are making definitive, positive change. If you're in the area, we'd love to have you there. The more people come out, the stronger we can make it in the future. I'm really looking forward to it. The second is my recent album, [Space Sessions: Songs From a Tin Can](http://chrishadfield.ca/music/), of which I am immensely proud. The vocals and guitar were recorded in my sleeping pod on station, and then later mixed with a complement of talented artists here on Earth. The final music video of the album, from the song Beyond the Terra, will be released in the coming days. My proceeds from the album will be going to support youth music education in Canada. The third is my upcoming animated science-comedy series, "It's Not Rocket Science", which will be a released on YouTube and is aimed at changing the talking points on a number of contentious public views of scientific concepts. For example, encouraging vaccination by explaining smallpox, not vaccines, or explaining climate change via the Aral Sea, rather than CO2. While it is still in production, we have set up a [Patreon account](https://www.patreon.com/notrocketscience?ty=h) to provide background updates to how things are progressing with the talented group making it a reality, as well as helping to cover the costs of keeping it free to view. With that said - ask me anything!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 20:39:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>When the rocket stops, it feels like you are being pulled upwards. We're so used to the subtle inevitability of gravity, its absence makes you feel like you're floating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 20:40:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>He sure has. He said it was the most poignant version of the song ever done. High praise!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 20:41:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's more natural than you may think. Perhaps it's a throwback to the womb. I slept very well from the 1st night.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 20:43:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I liked the Martian very much. I liked it better the 2nd time, in fact, without the 3D glasses on. Matt Damon is convincing as an astronaut, and Andy Weir wrote an excellent book.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 20:50:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually, test pilots and astronauts try and NEVER have adrenaline in our veins while we're working. If we do, it means we have made a mistake or weren't ready for what was happening - and that will kill us. The real joy of the job is in becoming capable of doing something extremely difficult, and doing it well. There is no real desire to 'top' anything. The world is chock-full of things I am not yet good at, so I am never bored.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 20:53:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the more widespread we are, the greater our chance of survival. Local disasters all depend on your definition of 'local'. A volcano or a hurricane can have devastating effect, but so can an asteroid. We need to do both - expand to the edges of where our inventiveness can take us, and use that same restless intellect to make the most of where we already are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 20:57:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think we will send people to Mars with the engines that currently exist. The transit time with chemical rockets is so long that the complexity and thus the risk becomes prohibitive. Before anyone is truly ready to fund that human voyage, we will need engines that can thrust the whole way (accel/decel), and thus cut the transit time down to something reasonable. When will that happen? Maybe soon, it is just up to all of us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 20:57:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go Jays!!!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 21:00:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I expected the Space Station to smell bad, like a closed-in place with unwashed people, but in fact, it doesn't. In 6 months there I never smelled body odour. We sponge bath every day, and the air purification and circulation system is very good. It was a pleasant surprise. The Space Shuttle and the Soyuz, on the other hand, both got a little ripe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 21:05:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Orbiting Earth 2593 times, what I really came to appreciate was the commonality of the human experience. From orbit you see the repeated patterns of human settlement and civilisation, and inevitably start to sense that each of us inherently wants the same things out of life - joy, grace, time and stability to think, better opportunities for our children, laughter, someone to love. The precept of 'Us' and 'Them' is one that is taught; it's not the fundamental reality. Seeing the whole world as 1 place every 92 minutes drove that home within me, forever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 21:08:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Using the space toilet is slower than on Earth, and you want to do it right or pee goes everywhere. It's a nice moment, with the loud whirring hum of the fans, pumps and separators, to take a break and think a bit in an otherwise very demanding place. We kept a copy of  amp;$#@ My Dad Says in the toilet stall, wedged under a handrail. Perfect space bathroom reading.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 21:12:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think movies like The Martian remind us of what is fascinating. The movies don't cause interest, they reflect it. The science fiction and fantasy help push back the edges of what we allow ourselves to imagine. Then when they are then underpinned by real images of Pluto, water geysers on Enceladus, the surface of a comet, water flowing down the slopes of Mars, and 6 humans living off the planet, that imagination becomes reality. It's a powerful combination, like the stories that excited me as a child, the explorers who showed the way, and the life I deliberately chose as a result.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 21:16:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>The link between excited fantasy and reality is the key. Go to a planetarium or science centre, and go with a purpose, with specific things to see. Look at Saturn through a telescope, or the craggy surface of the Moon. Visit a spaceport, and see where humans leave and return to Earth. Study some fact or topic and then use all the tools at hand to go prove it. Make it mentally interactive, a process of curiosity answered, of personal discovery.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 21:19:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>The age of the universe astounds me. As humans we are really bad at large numbers. When I hear someone say 13 billion, what I hear most is '13'. I just don't have an intuitive feel for a billion. But to think that universe was here for 9 BILLION years already before our Sun began shining and the Earth coalesced into its rockiness amazes me. With my 10 fingers and toes and perhaps 80 years of life, the enormity of time threatens the gaskets of my mind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 21:23:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>No astronaut I have ever met has seen an alien. And I was president of the astronaut professional society (The Association of Space Explorers) for several years, so I've met almost every space flyer. The odds are that there must be life somewhere else in the universe with the enormity of chances, but there is no actual evidence yet. We're hunting though - on Mars, on Saturn's moons, and beyond.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 21:26:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>To become an astronaut, I recommend 3 things: keep your body healthy, get an advanced technical education, and learn to make tough decisions and stick with them. After that, learn other languages, learn to fly, learn to scuba dive, always be pursuing new skills. And at the core of it, forever be in pursuit of your passion. It's amazing where life can lead if you constantly improve yourself in the direction of your secret dreams.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 21:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was the NASA psychologists who put the guitar on the Space Station. They recognized that music and art are fundamental and necessary for mental health, and for the soul. That Larrivee Parlour guitar was taken to the Station on the Shuttle in August 2001, and has been there ever since. It gets played almost every day - lots of astronauts and cosmonauts are also musicians. I was VERY happy to have it there - a wonderful link with home in an otherwise extremely remote existence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 21:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>We would love to host a Generator show outside Toronto. This upcoming one is nearly here (5 days away!) and is shaping up to be exactly what I had hoped for: art, science, thought, humour and music, all highlighting individual and collective creativity and unexpected insight. Once we finish in Massey Hall on the 28th and debrief, we'll decide where and when to host the next one. Looking forward to it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 21:39:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Flying a spaceship is an enormously complex task, especially with the level of danger and consequence involved. The only way we can make it work is to start simple; learn one thing completely, and then move on to the next, then the next. Once you understand a few things, put them together and understand how that system works. Then practice it, especially as it breaks and goes wrong. Never be content with how much you know, or how good you are - be relentless in self-improvement. Eventually you will be capable of operating the whole ship in a practice setting, and then for real. The key is in personal competence, and visualizing your response to all possible failures. It takes the stress away when you then do it for real.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 21:42:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are many people working on making spaceflight simpler and safer, and thus cheaper. The folks at Virgin Galactic, Blue Origin and Space X are all trying out different technologies, and are getting close. I eagerly watch each of their launches to see what they're trying next, seeing what goes wrong, and what they change for the next try. It's still early days in space travel, but we figured it out for rail, sea and air travel. I'm optimistic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 21:46:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>My teeth were crooked when I was young. I had a weird underbite, and my baby teeth hung on too long so my adult teeth started coming in over top. It was a mess, but a good dentist pulled the reluctant baby teeth and made me a retainer that I wore for a couple of years as everything slowly settled into what I have now. Not flawless movie-star, but pretty even and good for chewing :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 21:50:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>We contacted Ahmed Mohamed immediately and made sure he knew that he was welcome at Generator. It wasn't so much expecting that he would be able to come, but more to reinforce to him how much we support creativity, original thinking and the confidence to be different. In a world where some adults and institutions behave so fearfully, we wanted Ahmed to clearly see that it's not like that everywhere. An important thing to know and understand, especially at his age.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 21:53:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Today for lunch I had cheese, sliced meat, a seed cracker and a bunch of grapes, plus some berries. Finger food while Redditing! I'm in Jasper Alberta, getting ready for the Dark Skies Festival. So beautiful outside, and sparse clouds, so should be a fine, memorable night.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 22:03:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>To orbit the Earth is an awesome privilege. The work to get there is lifelong and beyond hard, but to then actually be there is on the edge of miraculous. My favourite moment on ISS was once in the Cupola, the huge bulging window facing Earth. We had just crossed Australia at sunset, and were arcing up over Indonesia, when we began to cross a thousand mile storm. The lightning was almost continuous below, lighting up a thunderhead like a flashbulb and then catching across the storm as if it were contagious, a rippling wave of searing white light. Tom Marshburn floated quietly into the Cupola beside me, and we hovered in wonder, too amazed to grab a camera, pointing to the magnificence and speaking in hushed delight. We wanted to go get the rest of the crew to come see, but the spectacle was too mesmerizing to leave. We kept gasping and laughing in wonder, until finally we drove up and past China and the storm fell behind us. We felt like the luckiest 2 guys in the universe. And still do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 22:07:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love every chance I get to work with Adam Savage. He is creative, talented, highly-trained, hugely curious and good, fun company. We spent a hilarious afternoon at ComiCon in San Diego, just did a screening and review of The Martian together, and are looking at what to do next. Maybe I can help put the new turbo in his Land Rover :) We're patient, though, as fortunately the world is wide, life is long, and human foibles are endless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 22:11:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Without gravity, hard things become easier, like moving a Buick with one finger. But some simple things become harder, like putting on your shoes. Pay attention the next time you lace up your Nikes - I bet you use gravity to hold you still while 2 hands and 1 foot are busy. In space, you helplessly float around and bump into things until you finally get the laces tied, and then start looking to see where the other shoe has floated off to. I tried for 5 months to do it gracefully, but never achieved shoe-tying elegance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 22:16:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I saw the results of our election, I sent a congratulatory note to my friend (and 1992 astronaut classmate) Marc Garneau. He's an honourable, hard-working, smart and good Canadian, who has given his entire life to public service. I look forward to seeing what he, Mr. Trudeau and their party choose to do going forward, especially in space exploration and research. As a member of Canada's Space Advisory Board, I look forward to meeting with them once they get settled in, and to do my best to give good advice and options.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 22:17:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>no, but better there than on Earth</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 22:28:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Learn other languages, learn to fly, learn to scuba dive, learn medical training, always be pursuing new skills. There is no one specific path to becoming an astronaut. The best thing you can do is train yourself to enjoy building up the skills that end up defining who you are. Becoming the thing you dream of is a long shot, no matter what. The key is to HAVE a dream, a destination, a personal definition of perfection in life, and then to use that end goal to help decide what to do next. It is not the end goal that changes you, but the summed total of each of the small, daily decisions. Actively pursue your dreams by deliberate small choices - what to eat, to read, how to exercise, what to study, where to go, when to change direction. It's amazing where all the little decisions can lead you. Never hate what you are doing. Make the most of it, find pleasure in the nuance and the art of it, become better at it, laugh at it, make it one of the things that you can do. If it's truly insufferable, then you must change and do something else. But get the most out of each step of life as you go. There's always more there than you think. And celebrate success now! Don't wait to walk on the Moon to notice the thousand small victories that got you there. Rejoice in each new skill, every discovered idea, each small improvement you make in yourself. All the choices and ideas you list make sense. Do what is closest to your heart, the ones that make you the most excited. That way you are inevitably turning yourself into who you want to be. Edit: Sorry for the confusion on my reply. I had answered a similar question elsewhere, and addressed the more philosophical side. To be specific: Get an advanced technical degree, at least a Masters, in a field that interests you. Your work in Physics is fine. It's no so much what you've learned, but a proven ability to learn complex things. Maintain your health - eat and exercise to keep a strong, fit body. Likely worth getting a physical, to know what peculiarities you may have - heart, vision, height, weight, etc. You can then compare that to the required standards of the various space agencies. Once school is complete, work in a field where your decisions matter, have consequence, to prove your ability to make good decisions. It's why the CSA hires pilots, doctors, people who have managed programs, etc. Then gain other skills - scuba, flying, languages, climbing, engine/computer repair, etc. What might make you stand out in selection, and useful on a spaceship? But I strongly stand by the first section I wrote. There is no direct path, so be sure that you are doing what is important to you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 22:29:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes - I am the only Canadian astronaut who is a military test pilot. What matters is competence and proven capability. Pursue those.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 22:33:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Being a role model is a responsibility, and I treat it that way. Most public figures do. I have been very lucky, have had great privilege and public trust, and I see that as a fine obligation. To be in a position now to influence young people to perhaps make more of themselves is a great delight. It helps motivate me to be a better person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 22:35:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>My time is gone - sorry! Thanks to ALL for the questions, observations and discussion. I hope to see some of you at Generator on the 28th, and if not, somewhere else soon after - it's a small planet we share. Thanks again!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 23:18:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have no personal interest in becoming a politician, no.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-26 15:01:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know you're in safe hands when you're launching in a rocket with Captain Space.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-26 16:04:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I remember. He was a very good companion for diving. Mike, right? He'd just finished working as a boathand, if I'm not mistaken.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hi /r/canada. In two days, I'm hosting a comedy-science event at Massey Hall in Toronto. I wanted to take a moment to explain the reason why.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-26 17:35:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello /r/Canada, I wanted to take a minute to discuss [Generator](https://www.facebook.com/events/712627588883618/), an event I'm putting on at Toronto's Massey Hall on Wednesday. Specifically, I'd like to discuss why we're putting it on at all. A few weeks ago, one of our major news organizations called me to comment on a scientific achievement. It wasn't in my field, and I had no relation to it, but that's not all that uncommon. What struck me was that when I checked the show that evening, I noticed that as I was unable to participate the entire section had been removed. That bit of science didn't make it to your ears, because they didn't have someone they trusted to explain it to their audience. As this sort of request has continued to increase over the last few years, my son Evan and I realized we aren't doing enough to make ourselves aware of our own local talent. The fact is that there are many people in this country who could not only have taken my place in that interview - they should be the initial point of contact. We have outstanding biologists, chemists, physicists and educators. We have what is likely [the most educated population in human history](http://newsfeed.time.com/2012/09/27/and-the-worlds-most-educated-country-is/), with some of the best scientific output per capita, but most of us can't name five science-friendly Canadian icons. We deserve better, but the question I keep returning to is: how should it be done? What can we be doing to make Canadians more in tune with the eloquent, talented minds around them? Evan and I brainstormed a number of ideas late this Spring, and came to the conclusion that the problem is one of platforms. How can we expect to find and highlight our own talent, when the system we have in place for discovering talent requires promotion or distribution from the United States? How can we keep our minds from flowing south if we don't give them an audience who works to keep them here? Over the following months, we spoke with dozens of Canadians and international science communicators, to professors and poets, to musicians and comedians - planning to find a way to create a platform that not only benefited them, but the country, as well. I want Generator to become that platform. After three months of dogged, hectic work, we're landing in Massey Hall on Wednesday, with proceeds going to local educational non-profits. It isn't a night of science. It is a night of amazingly talented people that I think everyone should know. [TWRP](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PVXDD_dZpUQ), [Mark Little](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T_BQzKij-74), [Marshall Jones](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kFX2LrNE3VI), [Marianne Mader](http://steamlabs.ca/), etc. I don't expect it to change the world, or create an environment overnight that promotes science and Canadian achievement. I understand what a lofty goal we've set out to achieve, and that perfection is forever out of reach. But I also understand that without trying, we won't ever achieve anything. In short, [Generator is coming](http://tickets.masseyhallroythomsonhall.com/single/SYOS.aspx?p=2144), and I really hope to see you there. None of these goals would be possible without your continued support. Thanks to everyone who upvotes, mentions, or attends. Sometimes, one small step is something much more. Let's take it together. Thanks for reading!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've recently released the first full album of original music recorded in space. It may not be Space Oddity, but here's Beyond the Terra, my whole life in a song.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-12 17:52:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It may be a bit complicated to get to my workstation, but the commute is worth every ounce of effort.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-29 22:43:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I was told you might like my battlestation. The line to use it is usually pretty full, but you should see how the monitor renders space scenes.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-29 23:01:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-29 23:03:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure. Thanks for the heads up!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-29 23:04:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't worry. If you flip the wrong one you die. No pressure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-29 23:12:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha! https://vimeo.com/138802207</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-29 23:18:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>128k Memory, 37 million horsepower.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-29 23:21:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>[It looks like this.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=94-puZit3DA)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-29 23:34:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, but we spend a great deal of effort to make sure it doesn't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-29 23:39:29</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Im just amazed at your wifi connection up there Canada? Oh, its not *that* bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 04:19:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was recently discussing with my family if we should do another speaking tour of Australia (in part due to unfortunately missing Brisbane last time around). As it is a very long way to fly from Toronto, I was thinking it might be good to pair it with something that was already happening I was looking to take part in. However, I don't feel I have enough knowledge to judge what that is. What would you suggest?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-09 04:06:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is very nice to read. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-24 01:25:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you see the exploration and settlement of Antarctica as an analog for how we will get to Mars? Alternatively, do you feel a sense of urgency to get humanity to Mars?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In August I brought ten artists to the high Arctic to capture a unique experience. Two of them released videos today. This is the first, a visual vibe from Ben Brown.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-24 01:54:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In August I brought ten artists to the high Arctic. Two of them released videos today. This is the second, Tim Kellner's 'Arctic'. Incredible.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-24 01:59:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I recently took ten artists on an icebreaker through the high Canadian Arctic. Their only mission was to capture the experience. Today two of those videos were released. This is the first, by Ben Brown.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-24 02:17:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I recently took ten artists on an icebreaker through the high Canadian Arctic. This is the second work released today, by Tim Kellner. I am in awe.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-24 02:19:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-24 03:04:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very, very few of us have any experienced the true magnitude of our country, and in turn have a skewed image of what it is that defines us, and what we are. In order to effect real change, we need to see, learn, and then act. These videos, as well as all the works made by those who joined us, are simply an inviting way to see a unique place that few will get to experience first-hand, but all could do with a bit more understanding. We didn't go to the Arctic to proselytize. We went to witness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-24 18:09:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Writing, music, videography, photography, and to a certain extent public speaking. It was intended to cross mediums. You can find links to the artists [here](http://www.generatorevent.com/arctic/). A few are yet to release their content (Tested, Elmo).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-24 22:24:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I, too love science, and have always had to balance the pragmatism of passion vs income vs family. You never get it quite right, but the continued re-balancing is important - in fact, it's your life. My wife and I would both be quick to point out that giving up on your dreams does not come for free. Recognize that. We've also always held that extra and continuing education is key. You mention 'the current political climate'. If you wait for the political climate to be just right, Hell may freeze over. Here's what I recommend: Have a plan that takes care of the fundamental needs of you and your loved ones. Keep that going as the centre of your life as much as you possibly can. But always be looking for ways to pursue the things that you are passionate about. There are always options and other ways to do things. A PhD is daunting at the outset, but 10 years afterwards it will just be what you chose to do during that period of your life. They key is passion - you'll need it to sustain you during all the extra work and trade-offs and time crunches and things that go wrong. Finally, make a decision, stick with it, and own it. Your decisions define who you turn into. They occasionally need adjusting, and often they take more time than you'd like. Expect that, and, most importantly, be deliberately joyful with each new skill, each new insight. There's more than one finish line in life, and only you can judge your own success. Have fun at Generator - I know the cast will!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-20 15:52:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>"The best part was when Chris played Canadian folk tunes." \- My crew, I like to imagine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 10:38:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you're moving at 5 miles a second, unblurred high resolution night shots can be a bit difficult. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 05:41:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Luca_Parmitano#Career</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>