<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject3357</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>19 and getting an abortion soon. Looking for comfort/advice</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 17:50:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m a 19 year old girl and I #8217;ve been dating my boyfriend (18) since March and we have a great relationship. I never thought I would get pregnant this soon, I always hoped to get pregnant after I got married. We didn #8217;t use birth control but he did always pull out. My periods are irregular so when my period was a few days late I wasn #8217;t too worried but still took a test when I was 4 days late (I took the test on November 7th). When I saw that the test was positive, I was in complete shock, I couldn #8217;t believe it. My boyfriend and I have always talked about what would happen if I accidentally got pregnant and we would most likely go through with an abortion, but there was still a possibly that I would keep it. But as soon as I saw the positive test, I immediately knew that I was going to have an abortion. My boyfriend is extremely supportive and let me choose what I wanted to do. Him and I are both in school and living with our parents and both our parents are very religious and we don #8217;t know what would happen if they knew I was pregnant at 19 or if I had an abortion. We are not in any way ready for a baby right now. Anyways, my boyfriend called a hospital near us that serviced abortions and I talked to a lady that scheduled an appointment on November 22nd (that was the soonest opening). She said I would have an ultrasound, get my blood drawn and other tests. I have been researching whether a medical abortion or surgical abortion would be best but I #8217;m still not sure which would be better. My LPM is October 8th, but I conceived around October 17th-23rd, so I #8217;m technically around 3 weeks. For a little backstory, I #8217;m an extremely emotional and sensitive person, so this is hitting me very hard. I don #8217;t want to have a baby right now but I also don #8217;t want to have an abortion. In class yesterday, I couldn #8217;t stop tearing up and wiping tears away. I know this is going to cause me a lot of pain and grief. I will probably feel guilt for the rest of my life. In conclusion, this is very difficult for me to handle but I know I have to do what #8217;s best for my boyfriend and I #8217;s lives and careers, I also would want my baby to be raised in the best environment possible. If anyone could offer some comfort and assurance to me, I would really appreciate it. Edit: YES I knew that pulling out wasn #8217;t a sufficient form of birth control, I had plans to get an iud very soon. Also, anyone who is not planning on getting pregnant would be shocked as well to see a positive pregnancy test. Please do not comment negativity, I know what I did and I don #8217;t need negativity at this time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 17:53:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you I hope so too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 18:01:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 18:14:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I planned on getting an iud but the clinic never called me back for an appointment, I was going to go this past week. Literally anyone who isn #8217;t planning to get pregnant would be shocked to find out that they were pregnant. Fuck out of here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 18:51:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am thankful that I have an abortion service near me, I #8217;m also glad that I #8217;m in Canada so I don #8217;t have to pay for it. I #8217;m definitely going to try and go to a councillor after this is done with. Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 18:53:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the recommendation but that is not an option for me, If I carry a baby to full term, I #8217;ll 100% want to keep it and not give it away. It would be too complicated to deal with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 19:07:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 19:13:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was going to get an iud a few months ago but the clinic never called me back and I was going to go the clinic this past week to find out what happened but then I found out I was pregnant lol. I #8217;m definitely going to get one asap once this is all over. Thank you for this reply though, it touched me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 19:13:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s the thing I struggle with the most, I keep thinking about what the baby would be like, look like, be named, etc. I hope it fades away for me too over time. Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 19:33:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you I hope so too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 20:07:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much for your support, I appreciate it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 20:09:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I have, I #8217;m going to try and see which free counselling services are available nearby. I #8217;m sure it #8217;ll help me a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 20:20:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for your advice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 21:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awe thank you for this reply, I appreciate it a lot. It did help me! And thanks I may message you before/after it happens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 22:06:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the advice, I #8217;m going to definitely look into counselling options.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 23:10:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the advice. Thankfully I #8217;m very expressive with my emotions so I think that should help the healing process. I am sensitive so the negative comments do get to me but I #8217;m trying to focus on the positive comments and not have second thoughts about this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 05:04:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know that #8217;s how it #8217;s supposed to be counted but it doesn #8217;t make sense</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 06:53:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>The procedure doesn #8217;t scare me at all, the only things that #8217;s difficult about this is the emotional side. This may be bad but I #8217;ve been drinking a lot lately purposefully just so I can #8217;t turn back on my decision. But thank you for the advice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Positive surgical abortion experience at 8 weeks</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 20:07:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just thought to write about my experience (19) to give others a sense of what might happen to them. Everything went very well and I feel no regret about it. I feel so much stress relief and peace of mind. I live in Ontario, Canada, the surgery happened in a hospital. Yesterday morning I put two misoprostol pills in me at 3:20am, got to the hospital at 7:20am and waited for a bit with my bf and then got weighed, blood pressure and temperature taken, took 2 more misoprostol pills but orally and changed into the hospital clothes and sat with my bf, then I left him and waited in a different area and while waiting I peed and was bleeding a lot from the 2 additional pills I took and then the surgeon and anesthesiologist introduced themselves to me, I waited more and then someone called me to the room and I layed on the table and that #8217;s when I started to get pretty nervous, a lady was talking to me to distract me from the the person putting the iv in my hand and then she put the gas on my face and told me to take deep breaths and I was trying to relax and the last thing I remember saying was that my hand hurt from the drugs going in me and then I woke up in a recovery area and was looking around at everything and I kept asking sooo many questions lmao and the lady said to relax cause my heart beat was a little high and I told her I was hurting and she gave me morphine in my iv and then after a few minutes I was wheeled to some other recovery area and they gave me ginger ale, apple juice and water and offered me cookies and crackers but I didn #8217;t want any food at that time. I took 2 more of the misoprostol pills and some antibiotics to take and a nurse gave me a Rhogam shot in my side cause I have rh negative blood and I had to wait there for around 20 more mins and they kept checking to see if I was bleeding and I wasn #8217;t bleeding until I sat up to drink the drinks and then the nurse took out the iv and told me I could get dressed and pee and she said she would get my bf and as soon as I sat on the toilet it was like I peed out blood, so much came out and when I came out of the bathroom, my bf was coming towards me and I was so happy to see him, then we took an Uber to a hotel and I had diarrhea and was really hot for a few hours but since then I #8217;ve been feeling like my normal self and haven #8217;t had any pain. I also had a copper iud inserted during the procedure. I expected to feel more pain afterwards but I haven #8217;t felt pain since yesterday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 23:58:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Activated charcoal is good for removing toxins and colloidal silver is an anti-bacterial and anti-inflammatory</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 18:20:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please send me the video!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 02:47:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you I #8217;ll check them out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 19:47:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I constantly have this thought :) it #8217;s not bad at all, we need to have a majority of progressive people in the world</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I just want to feel better</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 18:11:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I (19) had a surgical abortion on December 8th at 8 weeks, afterwards I felt absolutely no regret and felt great that that situation was finally over with. A few days later, it started to really affect me, I cried a lot and wanted to self harm. Since then it has just gotten worse and I think about what happened all the time. I don #8217;t know how I feel about it anymore, I don #8217;t know if I regret it or don #8217;t regret it. I want forgiveness and I feel so sorry to my baby but I don #8217;t know if I #8217;m truly sorry since I went through with the abortion. I miss being pregnant and feeling my belly and knowing my baby was in me. I feel like I betrayed my child. I feel like they #8217;re questioning me about why I did it in the afterlife but I don #8217;t have a good enough reason. I #8217;ve definitely sunken into a postpartum abortion depression. Every pregnant belly I see, baby I see, and baby-related thing I see makes me so sad. I ordered a book called  #8220;Peace After Abortion #8221; by Ava Torre-Bueno a few days before the abortion and it should be getting to me soon. I hope that book will help me. I #8217;ve also been listening to some abortion story podcasts on Spotify. I don #8217;t really want to see a counsellor as I #8217;ve seen a few before and they didn #8217;t work out for me. The only person I have to talk about this is my boyfriend but he doesn #8217;t know how to help me deal will this (One of my friends doesn #8217;t want kids and my other friend just had a baby a month ago so it #8217;s hard to seek comfort from either of them). My bf says it #8217;s been hard for him emotionally too so I #8217;m not the only one hurting but it #8217;s been harder on me. I haven #8217;t felt hate towards myself in a long time, I hate myself for this so much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 23:59:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you I #8217;ll look into this book</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 20:22:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe in a higher power as well but I #8217;m not affiliated with any religion and I #8217;m kind of scared that I #8217;ll be punished for what I did in this life or in the after life. But if there is an afterlife, I hope so so so much that I #8217;ll be able to meet my baby. Someone else recommended that I read  #8220;The Healing Choice: Your Guide to Emotional Recovery After an Abortion #8220; and I #8217;ve started to read it and I like it so far. I wish you the best with dealing with this. We #8217;ll heal eventually.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 16:26:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I suggest you don #8217;t do it because my bf and I used the pull out method for 8 months until I got pregnant and now I have an iud to insure an accidental pregnancy doesn #8217;t happen again. Even if you do it 100% perfectly, there #8217;s no guarantee that it #8217;ll work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 16:36:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had a copper iud inserted on December 8th and had some pretty bad pain for the first week but since then it hasn #8217;t felt like there #8217;s an iud in me. I #8217;m still waiting for my period to come, I hope the bleeding isn #8217;t heavier/longer and more painful. In my opinion, a copper iud is worth the pain and heavier/longer periods as long as it #8217;s not too debilitating. Good luck in whatever you choose!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 05:02:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Animal agriculture</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 12:57:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had a surgical abortion too. Thank you, sending comfort your way as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 01:19:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cibc has bad hours too, it #8217;s so annoying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 01:47:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bank with both TD and cibc. I started with TD but switched to cibc a few months ago because td charges me when I have more than 25 interactions per month. I spend with my cibc cards mostly. I #8217;m still with TD because my phone carrier is attached to that account and so is my work and I #8217;m waiting until I leave that job to leave TD completely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 02:03:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree, I also like how envelopes aren #8217;t needed for cash/cheque deposits.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pain during sex and cramps and bleeding every day with copper iud</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 04:46:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I (19F) had a copper iud inserted on December 8th and had some discomfort that day but afterwards I was fine pain-wise, and I had sex 3 weeks later and didn #8217;t have any pain. I had sex a week later and it hurt during and afterwards for about 30 mins. Pain during sex has been reoccurring since then. About a week ago, I began to experience cramps accompanied with light bleeding while I wasn #8217;t having sex or doing any strenuous activity. This has been happening everyday for around a week now. What #8217;s strange is that the pain always occurs between 2pm-6pm but for the past few days it #8217;s been lasting longer until past 10pm. Even with taking multiple pain pills and having hot compresses on my lower back and uterus area, the pain is still pretty bad (5/10). The blood that I get with the cramps isn #8217;t period-like blood, it #8217;s like a very slimy pink or red discharge. Once the cramps are done with, the discharge will become brown until I have cramps the following day. The cramps feel like period cramps but stronger. But the pain I feel during and after sex is different, it #8217;s more like an uncomfortable pain. I #8217;ve stopped having sex for about 5 days now because sex isn #8217;t pleasurable for me at all anymore. I will mention that I think I had a period from December 23rd-26th which was light and fairly short for me, I usually bleed heavy and for 5-6 days. I used a menstrual cup but I don #8217;t think that messed with the iud because the pain during sex began way after my period. I #8217;ve done so much research online about what could be wrong with me but nothing seems to match my symptoms. The possibilities that I #8217;ve found are either perforation of uterus, displacement of iud, pelvic inflammatory disease, normal pregnancy or ectopic pregnancy. My boyfriend and I have been having unprotected sex and he cums in me every time so pregnancy is possible. I did take a pregnancy test 2 days ago and it came out negative but it could be too soon to tell. All throughout my time of having this iud, I #8217;ve continued to check that I could feel the strings and I haven #8217;t noticed them become shorter or longer. That could erase the possibility of perforation of my uterus and displacement of the iud but I don #8217;t know for sure. I saw a doctor today but they didn #8217;t tell me what they think could be wrong but I have an ultrasound scheduled for Thursday morning (the 18th) but my fear is that the iud may appear normal since my cramps don #8217;t usually start until the afternoon. If anyone could have any idea of what could be happening to my body and the iud I #8217;d really appreciate the feedback.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 19:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is possible that the iud I have now is too big for me, there is a smaller size but they didn #8217;t have that at the pharmacy I went to to purchase the iud. I have been pregnant before but I had an abortion at 9 weeks. Thanks for the advice though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 00:20:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m very introverted and before I found my current boyfriend of 10 months now, I didn #8217;t know how I could be in a relationship because of how quiet and reserved I am. My boyfriend is pretty extroverted and at first I was concerned that we were too much of opposites. But we mesh well together, I think extroverts go well with introverts most of the time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 18:48:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dairy, meat and egg.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 19:32:18</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Normal milk #8221; yeah drinking the breast milk from another species is completely normal!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 19:50:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>No none of that is normal, animals don #8217;t belong to humans. They produce that milk as a result of being pregnant and their babies are usually taken away from them after being born and the mom #8217;s milk is taken for human consumption. Nothing normal about that. It #8217;s barbaric and is unhealthy to humans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 19:58:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmao you really think the breast milk from a cow is beneficial to humans? In what universe does it make sense that full grown humans drink the milk from another species that #8217;s meant for their babies???</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 20:06:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>There #8217;s plenty of research that I #8217;ve read online. Milk does contain calcium but there are many better sources that someone can get calcium from. The countries that consume the most amount of dairy have the highest rates of osteoporosis. The negatives heavily outweighs the positives when it comes to dairy and humans. There #8217;s absolutely no reason that humans would need dairy milk, all the push towards it from the government is for money, they don #8217;t care about the health of people. There #8217;s literally so much evidence against dairy milk online, make sure the  #8220;scientific articles #8221; you read aren #8217;t sponsored from dairy companies ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 20:29:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alrighty, continue to believe the propaganda and live in ignorance!! Here #8217;s some articles since you #8217;re so set in your beliefs: [link](https://academic.oup.com/jnci/article/105/9/616/986948/High-and-Low-Fat-Dairy-Intake-Recurrence-and) [link](http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/download?doi=10.1.1.573.4684 amp;rep=rep1 amp;type=pdf) [link](http://www.bmj.com/content/349/bmj.g6015) [link](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4524299/) [link](http://www.breastcancer.org/research-news/20130327) [link](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3533146/) [link](http://drjaygordon.com/health-concerns/dairy-2.html) [link](http://www.aulamedica.es/nh/pdf/9247.pdf) [link ](http://www.msard-journal.com/article/S2211-0348(16)30100-6/pdf) [link](http://europepmc.org/articles/PMC3582227) And other peer reviewed articles against dairy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 20:30:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t like dairy milk because it #8217;s harmful to cows and to humans</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 17:37:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll rephrase. It #8217;s common, but it #8217;s not normal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 13:13:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wasn't allowed to rent anything from blockbuster that had a rating other than "G"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Am I the only one who tracks their  #8220;pregnancy #8221; with apps and online?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 19:44:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ever since I had my abortion in December I #8217;ve kept track of how my pregnancy could #8217;ve been. I use two apps to track how far along I would #8217;ve been and as every week passes I search online to see how big my belly would #8217;ve been. I love to watch vlogs of women talking about their pregnancy. I know this isn #8217;t helping my emotional state but I can #8217;t help but wonder what my body could #8217;ve looked like right now and how my baby #8217;s development could #8217;ve been.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 19:54:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I (19) had an abortion in December and decided to have a surgery because I did a lot of research before hand and taking the abortion pill seemed really painful and that it caused a lot of bleeding for many days. I was nervous for the surgery but everything went well, the whole process took around 4 hours but the surgery itself took around 10 minutes. Prepping and waiting for the surgery and recovery took a long time. I did have a lot of bleeding for the rest of the day but after that I had minimal bleeding for the next two weeks around. I was in pain right after I came out of surgery but they gave me more morphine in my iv. I don #8217;t remember having any more pain after that. Where I live, both the surgery and pills were free thankfully. I also didn #8217;t choose to take the pill because I didn #8217;t want to be home around my family while I was having an abortion and I didn #8217;t want them suspecting anything. Emotionally, the abortion really fucked me up for a while. As soon as I found out I was pregnant I was so sad that I was going to have an abortion, I never thought I would have to do something like that. Around 3 days after the surgery happened, I decided to look at videos of d amp;c abortions which wasn #8217;t smart. I cried so hard that night and felt so much guilt. The first month after the abortion was really rough and it still affects me (it #8217;s been almost 4 months now). I think about my baby everyday and hope that we #8217;ll reconnect one day. Everyone handles abortion differently, I #8217;m very emotional so it took a big toll on me. I honestly still don #8217;t know if I made the right decision but I have to live with what happened, I can #8217;t change the past. It #8217;s a healing process that takes lots of time. I hope this helps! Good luck to you, everything will work out fine whichever route you choose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 20:03:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah sorry I just edited it to include the emotional part of it but you #8217;re welcome!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 21:00:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t think I #8217;m going to stop until the due date passes. Yes I want to get a counsellor and the hospital provided me with information with who to go to but I just haven #8217;t reached out. I don #8217;t want to deal with the waiting and trying to find ways to get there (I don #8217;t have a car). I know I #8217;m being stubborn with this. Thanks for the comment though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 17:16:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven #8217;t cut since Valentine #8217;s Day due to not wanting obvious marks on my wrist/arm during the hot weather and I #8217;m hoping I won #8217;t do it again when the weather gets colder</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>