<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject2577</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-27 15:01:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thought I was crazy for doing this.. wow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-29 09:02:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>A movie I watched 5 minutes of as a kid and was too scared to watch anymore.. It must of had the title of a children's movie but it was actually a horror movie or something, hence why my mum put it on for me unknowingly. This would have been around 2001-2002 maybe but the movie may have been a fair bit older. All I remember is some giant, human-eating pigs on two legs running through a town and chasing people. I thought it may have been Spirited Away because of the scene where the parents turn into pigs but I swear they were trying to eat people. Don't know if my child brain made it worse than it actually was or if it was something else. I just remember crying in terror.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-29 09:38:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>The movie "The Misadventures of Amy Everhart" has a lot of talk about a pickle, I can't remember any lines though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 15:21:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Duck testicles.. tasted like chalky, salty lumps for anyone wondering.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 14:29:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That starsigns were basically teams of the universe and were competing for something (no idea what my 7yo brain thought that was). I wrote "Go gemini go" on my dresser.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 15:06:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Researching and considering all sides and opinions about a topic before forming an opinion. So basically thinking logically.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 15:13:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>When the movie follows multiple unrelated stories and then they all end up being related in the end.. so cheesy but I love it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 14:24:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/z6t55/what_is_the_funniest_dream_youve_ever_had/ This one always gets me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 14:33:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Savings? More like spendings haha"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 14:44:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I scared the shit out of my little brother and then ran out into the kitchen, slipped on the floor and almost broke my knee.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 14:53:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a C shaped scar on my shin. Around 5 years ago my family was renovating the house and the front veranda was missing. Long story short Mum called me from outside and I ran out the front door completely forgetting there was no veranda.. I fell into the hole where it should have been and scun my shin on a sharp metal beam on the way down. Hurt so much but I guess I deserved it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 15:06:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Minority Report.. Probably just because I had no idea what was going on the first time I seen it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 15:13:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Catchya round like a rissole</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 15:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>The first time my grandpa went through a McDonald's drive-thru in the 70's he recited his whole order to a bin. My family and I used to pretend to do the same every time we went through one. Also, my best friend and I were looking up pet names for her boyfriend at the time, and one of them was "chocolate mystery" which we found hilarious and began using for each other. Every now and then it still resurfaces.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 15:41:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Think about how I would feel if I had achieved something and nobody was happy for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 15:51:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>with cheese and gravy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 16:08:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Longest Journey/Dreamfall</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 09:01:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>A red patch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 09:25:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chokers. Ugh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 09:36:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pronounciation instead of proNUNciation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 09:41:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That stupid skittles measles one. Gets to me so much. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s6_cj35ZMnk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 09:45:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everything happens for a reason. Not sure if I still agree but it is an interesting way of looking at things.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 09:54:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Long Live, Taylor Swift.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 14:50:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I invited my now boyfriend and his friend to stay at my family's place for a whole weekend.. We had never met in person (or even spoken on the phone) before and it was a 7 hour drive for him. We've now been together for almost 4 years, have our own place and are happier than ever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 15:08:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bugdom</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 04:47:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3GRSbr0EYYU</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 15:07:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>A hairdresser cut my fringe wayyyy to short once. Like one inch long.. it stuck out horizontally</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 15:19:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Madagascar.. seen it an unholy amount of times</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 15:22:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was watching a rap battle between two men from the 1940's.. true story. Everything was black and white and they were sitting in fancy chairs all proper and one of them ended their rap with "bippity boppity boo".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 15:29:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>This.. I swear I have like 5-10 on repeat every time this happens</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 15:35:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was in a sack race once when I was like 8 and my pants fell down under the sack.. so I started crying and wouldn't take the sack off until I got back to the car. No one even knew why I was crying but for some reason it scarred me for life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 15:41:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not bad, but at this stage I don't think I'm really the best person to say  #128514; never get bored of King Julian though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 15:43:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apparently Russian is good because the alphabet is so similar.. could be wrong though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 15:50:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mum ended up tying my pants with a piece of rope ha. Not my proudest moment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 15:52:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yepp and it took forever. Ruined that school year haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 16:18:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>You never know</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 16:20:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah okay, wow I didn't know that. Thought English had a crazy amount of slang haha guess not  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 16:21:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha I probably would have if I was a guy, but I think that would've been social suicide in my situation  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 16:34:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pelvic muscle cramps/spasms when I was around 15. I couldn't move all night and couldn't walk the entire next day.. I was crying in pain but had to stop because it hurt too much. Looking back the pain was so severe my parents probably should have called an ambulance but apparently that's not how living in the country works  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 13:28:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blood is thicker than water.. the actual meaning is the blood of the covenant is thicker than the water of the womb.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 15:51:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pilates.. I think you can guess how I pronounced it. Also wifi and destined. Twelve year old me thought it was "wee-fee" (I'm not proud of this) and I still sometimes mispronounce destined as des-tYned. All due to years of reading it wrong in my head and never hearing it aloud.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 16:00:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Public transport.. I find it so unnecessarily complicated. Every time I have to use it I spend an abnormal amount of time planning and going over what I have to do so I don't get stuck somewhere.. And writing very precise directions in my notes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 16:16:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your mother sucks dwarf cock. -The Witcher</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 16:30:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I rinsed a lettuce and left it in the dish rack with the drying dishes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 16:32:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>My boyfriend saw a kangaroo check both ways before crossing a highway. He saw it in his mirror after noticing it stand there and watch him drive past.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 16:36:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Possums. They make this seriously terrifying raspy growling noise. They used to sit in the tree outside my bedroom window and I would hear them during the night.. Scared the shit out of me until I found out what it was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 14:27:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>He pulls the hair out of my hair brush and leaves it in the sink. Also, he shaves his beard over the washing basket so bits of facial hair get stuck on the clothes. Why?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 15:52:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not necessarily a celebrity but Christina Grimme. I used to be a huge fan of her videos and I still can't believe how she died.. She had such a big future :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 16:00:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Came here to say this, deaf culture is a thing. Some deaf people even hesitate to give their deaf children cochlear implants because they're scared they could feel disconnected with them in a sense. It's no different to any other cultural/social group within a community.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 16:32:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was a kid, probably around 4-5, Mum and I were on a walk in the bush near our house. She doesn't remember much of this for some reason but we saw a brown snake in the grass in front of us (for non-Australians brown snakes are extremely deadly and very common snakes). The next part is a bit foggy but I vaguely remember dropping my bag right next to the snake and walking away, while Mum ran to hide behind a rock a couple of metres away. While Mum's hiding behind this rock she picks up a stick and tries to grab my bag with it, all the while loudly whispering to me to get away from the snake. Instead of listening though I decided I would just go right up and grab my bag. So I picked up my Teletubbies bag and this is where it gets weird.. I have a perfectly clear memory of leaning down and petting the brown snake on the head a couple of times while seeing Mum staring at me in shock and then screaming at me to get away from it. I then calmly walked back to her, handed her the bag and we kept walking. The more I think about it the more bizarre it is simply because I was the biggest scaredy-cat as a kid. I wouldn't even touch the harmless snakes they would bring in to pre-school for us to pet, and I knew brown snakes were dangerous. I can only explain it as something just came over me. The fact that Mum doesn't remember makes me think it's a fake memory but I have such a vivid image of petting the snake, and Mum's face when she saw me. Really creeps me out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 01:33:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I know it couldn't have been a dream because Mum remembers going for the walk and seeing a snake, but that's where it ends haha. Yes brains are very weird.. and that sounds horrifying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 01:34:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah the rumours are true, everything is trying to kill us</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 01:38:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ouch!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 03:37:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, sounds almost like a glitch in the matrix story haha. Memories are very strange things and annoyingly enough making fake memories can be as easy as remembering real ones, but that's pretty freaky.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 04:12:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love how your first instinct upon seeing a hose was to pet it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 08:29:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love this theory. Maybe the reason I pet the snake was because in that reality I loved snakes but now I hate them because I got killed by one.. Haha makes too much sense. Going off that theory though, if I died when I was around 5 in the other universe, does that mean I've only lived in one other universe (this one) since then? What happens when you die from old age.. Do you keep living in a different universe after that? Maybe there's a universe full of super old people haha. Yeah honestly who knows.. I definitely believe there's so much more to life than we know of though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 13:39:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's really interesting, I'm like 80% sure it was from first person perspective. After thinking about it so much though I don't know what's real and what's not anymore haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 04:18:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes.. in the middle of the bush though in a tiny town I would have been as good as dead if it bit me anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 05:52:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah okay haha. Oh no was he okay? :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 07:13:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's so sad, sorry to hear that. :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 07:39:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Old dogs are great, hope you find one that suits you! My partner and I have a 6 year old jack Russell cross who we adopted a couple of years ago and surprisingly she's fine with hardly no exercise haha. We walk her when we get round to it but she'd rather sleep anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-07 07:53:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>This has happened to me too. It used to happen a lot with small things but once in relation to My family and I used to go and visit my great grandmother every Monday in the nursing home. Not long before I moved out, we went and saw her. When we were saying goodbye I had an overwhelming feeling that it would be the last time I saw her (and not just because I was moving away). About a week later, Mum called me to tell me she had passed away. On top of this, she said her and my grandma decided to go and visit her on the day she passed.. It wasn't a Monday and no one knew she was dying but they felt like they needed to visit her. So they made the hours drive and sat with her for her last few hours. Very strange how it worked out but I'm definitely not convinced both scenarios were a coincidence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 14:20:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pokemon cereal. It was like Lucky Charms but we can't get Lucky Charms in Australia unless you want to pay over $20 a box :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 14:39:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>In high school I was sitting with a group of my friends and we were talking about how we used to argue a lot in primary school, and how we were all just trying to fit in. A kid who used to follow us around a lot (and who wasn't even born when we were in primary school) happened to be there and came out with "Oh yeah.. I remember when Clare used to try and fit in!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 14:41:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>My brother is signed to ABC music. At one of his gigs, an old hippie man wanted a photo with me when he found out I was his sister. I guess you can say I'm famous.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 14:43:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>A bath.. and a backyard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 16:18:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you talked about JumpYard with anyone on the facebook or messenger app? I'm pretty sure it's been confirmed that your messages are scanned for key words that can be used for ads. This happens to me almost on a weekly basis. For example, I was talking to my friend about a mutual friend who got engaged, and I had engagement rings ads on my facebook wall for days afterwards.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 08:38:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scribblenauts. I think everyone should play it at least once.. The concept is awesome but does get boring after a while.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 08:49:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha I was thinking about downloading it again after writing that comment. Such a great game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 02:24:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't meet up with them but wish I did. I was grocery shopping with my boyfriend and we were stopped at a pedestrian crossing. Next thing a woman who looked like my twin but with better fashion sense walked across.. this happened literally 5 minutes away from where I live but I've never seen her since</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 14:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once my friends were talking about how somebody hit a golf ball on the moon. My reply was "how did they hit it that far?".. I deserved everything i got</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 14:59:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I re-downloaded an old chat app out of boredom and 10 minutes later found the guy I'm with now. My life would be completely different in every possible way if I didn't download that app that night.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 15:03:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>How old my relatives baby was when 5 minutes ago they were literally talking about her 1st birthday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 15:14:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>A woman from a smallish town near where I grew up was murdered a couple of years ago. She was working late at a school there and the cleaner on duty kidnapped her, raped her and burnt her body. Around a year later, her father was crushed and killed by a tree on his property. I can't even begin to imagine how the family (especially her mother/his wife) handled all that, was heartbreaking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 15:21:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cologne</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 06:30:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>hahaha reminds me of this... http://imgur.com/a/kd2T6</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Who is your favourite Youtuber?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 11:24:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 11:30:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine is Kendall Rae- she does really well researched, genuinely good conspiracy videos and other similar videos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 11:31:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god I can't stand him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 12:02:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great list. :) I love BuzzFeed unsolved, I'm not a huge fan of buzzfeed videos now that all my favourites have left but I do love Shane and Ryan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 14:56:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still a student at this point but in school I loved English and also health but get grossed out easily. This meant I couldn't do most health professions but speech pathology was a perfect mix of everything I enjoyed.. so here I am</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 11:20:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just got this too :D boyfriend is jealous to say the least</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 15:32:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>My boyfriend thought Ed Sheeran's "I don't wanna know about your new man" was "I don't want to know about your wing man" for a ridiculous amount of time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 15:46:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm super allergic to horses but I still spent most of my childhood riding them and/or being obsessed with them. Resulted in a lot of sneezing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 15:47:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>People would sleep in more probably</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 15:49:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cupboard space</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 13:06:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dog is called Poppy but she usually gets called "Pooper", "Poppo", "Floofer" or sometimes "floof". She farts/poops a lot and is very fluffy if that explains anything. Edit: I also forgot Poptart and Popsicle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What happened to the user with the CIA username who was going to have lifesaving surgery?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 03:33:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Struggling to learn most diacritics. Anybody know of any useful resources/tips?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 15:16:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>So basically I was wondering if anybody had any useful tips or resources for learning diacritics? I have found interactive charts really useful for vowels and consonants but can't find any which have been helpful (or even sometimes include) diacritics. I've tried listening to my uni recordings (although they're pretty average) a thousand times but I just can't get it. Thanks in advance :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 06:53:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 06:53:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>English sorry!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 06:53:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you anyway though :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 08:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand them and what they all are, I just can't hear them in speech recordings. The main ones I have trouble with are lowering, raised, advanced and retraced tongue root, entire tongue advanced and retracted, and no audible release.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 08:24:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I meant IPA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 14:13:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I think you're right, because I'm finding it pretty much impossible to be able to hear the differences in crappy, online recordings with no comparisons at all. Plus, they're super subtle which makes it even harder. Maybe some people can do it, my facilitator being one of them but I think it's pretty unfair to expect students to be able to. I'm being assessed on this soon too (in class listening test) to make matters worse. Thanks for your help though, I'm going to try just memorising as many of the recordings as I can and hope for the best haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 14:14:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Accents of English and disordered speech. So basically everything, were just expected to be able to identify all of the IPA diacritics in any form of speech</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 16:03:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cotton grows on a plant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 16:04:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Big job= taking a poo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 16:07:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Raw celery. It's so cheap and obviously healthy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 16:12:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Roses are red Bacon is red Poems are hard Bacon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 16:18:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Toad in the hole</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 07:47:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I #8217;m pretty sure my dog has the same dream over and over.. She starts by making this low growling sound like she does when she hears something (dog barking, train etc) and then it turns into excited yapping. This happens almost daily. No idea what she #8217;s dreaming of though so I guess this answer was pointless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 12:21:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Snakes. They should have definitely been called angry ropes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 08:49:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eating leftovers instead of buying takeaway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 08:52:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know how to play minesweeper.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 09:01:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pooping</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 09:07:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Find a job as a new graduate in the new area I would have just moved to with my partner.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 09:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Speech pathology, so the finding a job part is extremely wishful thinking haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 09:42:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha, I like that. Thank you :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 09:24:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought play it by ear was play it by year for a reaaally long time. Also, I had always pronounced "destined" as dest-eye-nd until I was corrected about 6 months ago. Oh and throughout reading the entire Harry Potter series I had pronounced Hermione as her-moyne. Not proud.. And also possibly dyslexic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 14:40:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was about 13 at the time, and was really curious about psychics so I downloaded an app where you get one free psychic reading. Mine consisted of the woman telling me that she couldn't believe how young I was and that I would "meet lots of people" in the years to come. Pretty broad, but I did meet lots of people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What #8217;s the most interesting piece of information you can recall?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 13:20:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 13:27:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well shit that #8217;s unfortunate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the funniest memory you have?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 13:32:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 13:38:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure go ahead</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 13:55:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well thanks for those interesting Roman facts, my history is terrible so anything helps haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 13:58:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha oh no. How did you ever recover from that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 14:00:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pfft hahaha, never trust young children</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 14:21:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha aw that #8217;s nice. I also have memories of telling jokes with my siblings that really weren #8217;t funny at all but somehow were to us.. no one crashed any cars listening to them though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What gives you that  #8220;nails on a chalkboard #8221; feeling?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 16:28:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is your creepiest/scariest experience?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 13:39:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is something you should probably regret but don't and why?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 13:50:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 13:53:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, what are the chances you would have stayed friends after uni anyway?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 13:56:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I cut my hand open by putting it inside an opened can.. Out of curiosity. I was a dumb kid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 14:03:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>My boyfriend's brother... I think he's just completely oblivious to the fact that he stinks or he doesn't care.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 14:06:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>"You have crippling anxiety but you get a cute dog"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 14:07:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>A tampon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 14:08:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was writing a list of dates into a table, and accidentally wrote "32th". I then fixed it by changing it to "32st".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 14:19:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Longest Journey</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 14:22:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rottnest Island. It's the tiny island off the coast of Perth that's full of quokkas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 14:32:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>This desperate pup https://imgur.com/a/Yf1iK</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What video never fails to make you laugh?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 14:33:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 14:35:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha yes this is one of my favourites too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 14:38:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hadn't seen this but that scream got me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 14:43:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I forgot all about the demonic ducks.. thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 15:14:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This is mine](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3GRSbr0EYYU)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 13:12:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I ask my boyfriend to open jars for me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 13:17:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've found that when I feel like this, I just let myself have time off from studying for a day or two and just do whatever it is I'd rather be doing. Then after that, I usually feel guilty enough and motivated enough to study again. It sounds dumb but it's the only thing that works for me and I end up studying so much more effectively. Also, I like to plan everything into tables so I can see what I have to do and cross things off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 13:23:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just think about how un-important whatever I'm mad about is. And then I think how my entire existence is completely pointless and then I have an existential crisis.. But it's better than being angry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 09:19:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>What you #8217;re describing is vocal play, and basically the child is just messing around with their voice and figuring out what they can do with it. This usually starts a lot earlier than 10 months though, and at this age they #8217;re most likely doing whatever they can to communicate- which includes squealing and non-babbling noises :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 09:40:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Red dead redemption.. I wanna be a cowgirl.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the best "try not to laugh" challenge you've come across?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 13:42:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 13:43:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just experienced my first 3 day long migraine but y'know can't complain</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 13:48:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes but I guess I'm relieved now it's over. And how are you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 13:52:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will do :) any in particular that I should watch or just all of them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is that one awkward thing you did that you think about when you can't sleep?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 14:04:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 14:05:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is my SO.. unless my dog counts and in that case 100% yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 14:07:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dogs= dorky borkies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 14:14:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/a/2V989 This is her in her new jacket which definitely did not burst open as soon as she stood up. She says hi back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 14:18:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well at least no one else.. knew.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 14:24:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gran Torino</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 14:25:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I worry about everything but I always get shit done</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 14:40:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perfume, board game, video games, books, make-up (pretty sure 99% of girls want the naked heat palette- me included), baking stuff, bedding, skin care pack; depends what she's into.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 14:43:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always put the wrong lids on things.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's your favourite TV series of all time?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 14:46:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 14:55:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've actually never seen it.. Aside from bits here and there as a kid. Definitely on my watch list though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 15:00:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it still worth watching after seeing the funny parts in compilation videos?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 15:07:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha that was awesome. Their laughs make it 1000x better too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 15:08:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>That looks really good. Is it scary?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 15:10:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll have to give it a try. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 15:21:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve thought about watching this. Sometimes I can #8217;t get into medical themed shows though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 15:27:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Funny or just really good?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 14:42:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good choice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the creepiest thing that has ever happened to you?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 12:01:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What keeps you up at night?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 17:09:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 08:47:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Football. Ugh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 10:44:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, I'm Australian so not American football. AFL. It's like a religion here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 10:55:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>To another friend: "He doesn't even exist in me."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 11:53:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like dogs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 11:55:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I Boost Immunity- Donate vaccinations when you complete quizzes. https://iboostimmunity.com/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 12:08:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>We talked online as friends for a whole year before finally getting to meet, and then we started dating. Then we had to endure the long distance for the next year while I finished school, and then we both moved in together to go to uni. Still together after almost another two years. We got to see each other every 3-4 months through the long distance part but it felt like it went forever.. Would do it all again in a heartbeat though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is your weird phobia?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 12:25:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 12:27:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya I'm a little scared of this too. Quite common but still weird that its so common imo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 12:29:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had to google this one.. what sounds don't you like?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 12:32:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm guessing just teeth that have fallen out? Cus this would be super weird otherwise</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 12:33:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well you would hate half of my family then lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 12:34:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ughh me too. I can't stomach that either.. or visibly broken bones</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 12:35:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>This weirdly makes sense to me.. even though I've always said what's the point in making it if you're only going to go back to sleep.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 12:41:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>But why</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Have you ever won anything in a competition? What was it?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 12:43:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 12:46:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that's a fair enough reason to hate ants. Far out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 12:49:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's so strange.. I guess it could be the nightmare. Phobias are weird though like why are we even scared of random things that can't hurt us? It's just as valid as disliking holes or clowns imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 12:50:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>What kind of phone was it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 12:55:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>For when you're done throwing up the first lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:03:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly, and to make it even worse as an Australian I'm not even scared of the spiders that can hurt me, just the hunstmans (literally not even brave enough to google how to spell it properly) which are completely harmless and just eat small insects.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:04:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well it's possible I guess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:05:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about q-tips? and cotton pads? or is it literally just the balls</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:06:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:06:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not bad, I used to enter online competitions as well. I've never won anything on there but maybe because I didn't enter anywhere near 1000 a month</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:07:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that's depressing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:08:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow good job. Reminds me of when I won a stuffed horse at a sideshow. I had to pick a duck out of a container and the number on the bottom corresponded with the prize. I wish I won a TV</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:08:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not bad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:09:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do they only blow your legs off because they're not patient enough to wait for the door to go all the way up?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:10:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>It must remind you of school sports. That's terrifying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:11:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha, I didn't even notice that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:12:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're lying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:14:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ouch, push her down the stairs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:15:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jk don't do that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:15:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>But why? Is it because of how tinny it sounds? That's so weird haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:15:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aren't we all</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:16:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit, good job. What's the secret?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:17:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha aw. But he was the 39455849th visitor so it had to mean something</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:20:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>How small do the bumps have to be?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:38:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll have more trust/faith in them and not make them feel like they can't do anything for themselves. I also won't get drunk every night and scream at them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:39:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no. If it makes you feel any better I got given concert tickets when I was around that age but dad wouldn't let me go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:42:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Food.. I would probably die without it. sorry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 13:49:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a great idea. :) Yeah I totally agree, they're awful. Makes it even worse when there's literally no evidence whatsoever to support their claims, yet that doesn't change a thing to them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 14:01:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because you find it gross or because you're frugal?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 13:52:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had the worst stomach pain I'd ever experienced in my life (to this day) for about 5-6 hours when I was a teenager. I couldn't move during the pain or walk standing upright for the next day after the pain subsided. Turns out I had an ovarian cyst burst and it was pelvic cramps which aren't serious but just hurt a shit tonne. Could have easily been something more serious though.. Still not quite sure what kind of pain I have to go through before my parents decide to call an ambulance for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-30 10:39:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>To always lie about your children's ages when at any restaurant/theme park/zoo etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 04:39:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>The longest journey</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>People who have experienced an unexplainable jump in time or know someone who has, what's your story?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 08:13:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Serious] What is something that has happened to you (or someone you know) that you still cannot explain to this day?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 08:18:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 08:21:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>It depends what their reason is. If it's stupid, then find a new friend. If it's reasonable, then consider how serious it is and weigh up options/talk to your partner.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 08:31:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>What did it look like?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 08:32:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that's terrifying. Creepy because you could make out actual details from the reflection and it wasn't just a trick of light</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 08:34:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, do you think he'll ever tell you? It must have really scarred him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 08:38:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit, that's freaky. I had dream similar to that once. Did you tell him?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 08:40:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, not many explanations for that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 08:53:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Welp, time to burn the car. Stuff that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 08:56:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well let's hope she was joking. Would she normally trick you like that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is your favourite ask reddit thread?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 10:10:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 10:16:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is pretty good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 10:44:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahahaha that's gold.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 10:38:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was born to be a good friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 06:07:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks guys, I #8217;ll try my best to live up my destiny</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 12:35:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my best friends from high school had a new stepdad. Her dad had died about a year earlier and her Mum had married someone else. I remember meeting him and thinking he was strange, he just seemed off.. Even though everyone else loved him. Well they ended up getting a divorce because he had been spying on my (underage) friend in the shower and when she was getting dressed. And who knows where else. Creep.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 02:53:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I paid $9 for a normal sized bottle of water at a concert once.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 12:55:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>So wholesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 13:07:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi I #8217;m just going home now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 13:13:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably not the strangest I #8217;ve had, but one time I dreamt it was my birthday and my grandma bought me 2 dogs and my dad bought me a used couch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do you believe in the parallel universe theory? Why?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 05:44:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 05:49:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup me too haha. Although it freaks me out when I start thinking of every possible thing that could happen to me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 05:56:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mind reading but only if the person is within 30cm.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 06:00:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have to organise all my immunisations for placement and I haven #8217;t even started. Ughh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 06:02:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometimes when I type my phone password in, I mess it up (accidentally) and it still works. Like sometimes it #8217;s so obvious that it #8217;s wrong but if I do it fast enough it works.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 06:04:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now that I think about it, probably nothing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 12:06:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>It always reminded me of animals who had been abandoned which makes it 1000x even more sad  #128546;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 12:15:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mum does this too.. and it #8217;s always the best gossip</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 12:17:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nose spray. Not addicted in the regular way but my nose couldn #8217;t function without it. My friends still tease me about my weird nose spray addiction.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 12:34:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I found out a trick to stop using it if you #8217;re interested.. although 6 years is a lot longer than I needed it for. I started using it in only my left nostril so I could still breathe, but my right nostril was healing at the time. Then when it was completely healed and I could breathe I stopped using it in the left nostril.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 13:39:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah it #8217;s a struggle. I could only find one cheap one that worked as well. I think that #8217;s right because my dad is like that as well, he #8217;s been on it for decades now. Good luck with it, hopefully you sort it out :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 13:41:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>The famous town gold mine. I #8217;m scared of small spaces and the dark so no thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 13:52:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like your choices</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 13:58:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I created an entire Pinterest board for my future home decor</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 14:02:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>My grandpa on my dads side, he died before I was born. Also Taylor Swift (no shame).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 14:06:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>New. Although she hasn #8217;t really changed aside from the whole standing up to the media thing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What does "ba ba ba" translate to?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 05:49:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>There was a Russian song I liked when I was younger and I'm trying to find it. All I remember is it saying what sounded like "ba ba ba ooh" and I was wondering what that meant in English? Thinking that might make it easier to find. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 11:26:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 11:26:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh. Well thanks anyway! Lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 01:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks but no, I probably should have mentioned it #8217;s a female singer and I think she #8217;s quite famous (my auntie loves her- has all her albums) I could probably just ask my aunt but I don #8217;t really see her much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 13:10:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Arvada Kedavra- gotta stay on top of ol #8217; Voldy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 12:37:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mum said the only way she could stop was cold turkey. She always had a pack in the house though in case she needed it and freaked out, but every time she felt like one she just waited a little bit longer until she was fine. She told me she forgot all about the packet she hid and accidentally found them one day, and they #8217;d all turned to dust.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 12:50:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least there #8217;s finally an end to the completely irrelevant reasons why it #8217;s  #8220;okay to vote no #8221;. Don #8217;t know how many times I #8217;ve said the phrase  #8220;this is about gay marriage not safe schools #8221;. Ugh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 13:04:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once when I was about 15 there was a huge storm at our house. Usually when it rained someone had to go and clean the gutters, so Dad went out to do it. Anyway, Dad had been on the roof for about 10 minutes, when we all heard this massive bang. I #8217;m pretty sure I literally fell onto the floor it was so loud. My first thought was that Dad had been struck by lightening on the roof, so I ran outside to check (literally the scariest moment of my life). Turns out it had actually hit a giant pine tree in our backyard about 10 meters from the house. Dad said he saw it happen and it looked like half of the tree lifted up into the air, and then landed on the ground. Weird story but it had a happy ending because we were actually planning on getting the tree cut down because of termites. but weren #8217;t sure how to due to the size of our yard. I guess nature done us a favour.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 13:16:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m too controlling. Not in the toxic relationship way ( #8220;you can #8217;t go out #8221; etc.) but I like being in control of situations. It #8217;s weird because I don #8217;t even realise I #8217;m doing it and I never do it to be manipulative. I just feel most comfortable when things are done my way and honestly it stresses me out otherwise. I think it #8217;s my anxiety taking over.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I think I dreamt up an episode of Black Mirror last night..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 04:02:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>So last night I had a dream which I #8217;m pretty sure could pass as a Black Mirror episode. It started with a man relaxing at home, drinking a beer on the couch. His girlfriend was visiting and I think she was walking around the house organising a meal. She was talking and making jokes as she was cooking and spoke with a really thick southern accent. She seemed to be in her mid 30 #8217;s. The man hands his girlfriend a USB stick, and tells her to plug it into his desktop computer to download a virus he is  #8220;experimenting with #8221;. This goes on for a while, it is given knowledge that he has asked her to do this on many occasions over a number of years. Each time giving her the same request. Cut scene to my perspective. I am with a young girl around my age (20-22) who speaks with a thick southern accent. We are best friends, and go on adventures together. I watched us go to the beach, a wedding and shopping at the mall along with many other things. Over time, she starts to act strange. She begins to say mean things to me and this leads to her mentally and physically abusing me. This goes on for months and months, and I #8217;m unable to get away from her no matter how hard I try. Suddenly, I am on a train with this girl. She starts acting really strange, walking around the train and giving me really creepy looks. Eventually, I realise that the train has no driver and we #8217;re the only ones on it. Somehow she is operating the train, and she speeds up until we #8217;re going insanely fast.. All the while staring at me smiling. I start screaming at her to stop, I ask her why she #8217;s doing this and what she wants from me, and why she #8217;s been so horrible to me. She laughs in my face, and tells me that I #8217;m not real and none of this is real. Turns out, the man in the living room was my dad, and he had downloaded my consciousness into his computer. He had created this false reality for me, and had been torturing me for years by telling his girlfriend to download the viruses onto his computer. The girl who I was friends with was my dads girlfriend when she was younger (not really any relevance here, except for where he got the idea of her from). After she tells me all of this, I #8217;m in shock, and begging her to free me. I watch a cut scene of her laughing as she restarts the computer (each time refreshing my memory), and downloads another virus to put me through another lifetime of torture. It ends with her doing this over and over again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 04:09:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Waldo moment. Just didn #8217;t grab me like the others, and the ending was poorly done in my opinion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 05:18:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>No but thanks for your help :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 06:00:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>She is around 5 years old, and from Australia. Not sure of her weight but about the same size as a Maltese or jack Russell. Her temperament doesn #8217;t always remind me of a jack Russell, she #8217;s more of a lap dog. She does love walks though and can be quite active and excitable. She loves burrowing under blankets and digging holes, and tends to chase flies but usually will just sleep. She is also wary of other dogs and has lead aggression towards dogs, but great with all people even strangers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 07:23:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was definitely a weird feeling haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 12:54:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chicken wings.. would be interesting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 23:46:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks  #128514; maybe I should send it to Brooker</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 14:10:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Princess Diana was murdered.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 14:21:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Earrings.. I don #8217;t have my ears pierced. That was awkward</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 02:19:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>My uncle, he #8217;s hilarious and tells really good stories. He #8217;s a firefighter. I #8217;m not American though so I won #8217;t be seeing him on Thanksgiving but at Christmas  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why is it a norm on reddit to instantly assume everybody is male?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 02:40:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 02:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks anyway dude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 02:44:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought I was too but I #8217;m on reddit so it must be a lie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 02:47:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks man, but 53% are male</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 02:50:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>So did I at first, so I googled it and then asked this question haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 02:51:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I guess you #8217;re not wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 02:57:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m exactly the same, haha. I always wonder if they would have slightly different replies if they knew I was female. Also, this happens when my dog is wearing a pink harness and lead.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 03:03:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it #8217;s pretty hard to know for sure. I do think there #8217;s definitely more males on reddit though, just that the female population isn #8217;t as small as everyone assumes it to be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 03:29:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha, oh wow. How old was this family member? I #8217;m sorry the school system failed them so badly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 03:31:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was also thinking it would definitely have a lot to do with the subreddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 03:33:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about my username makes you think I #8217;m male? Genuinely curious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 03:37:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really cute, love it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 03:45:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your female privilege explanation was pretty condescending.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 03:56:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice assumption, I #8217;m not even a feminist. You #8217;re just unnecessarily rude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 04:01:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, I thought you said women didn #8217;t have privilege on the internet? I never actually disagreed with anything you said, I just said you were rude. Which is true. Unless you disagree, bitch?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 04:06:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha. Wow, you #8217;re fucking sad. It #8217;s my female privilege that makes me think I should be treated with respect? Not the fact that I #8217;m a human being? I never said it had anything to do with the fact that I was female. I don #8217;t really feel like talking to you. Reddit is a place for honesty, sure. But I can think of a thousand ways you could have written your original comment without sounding like a pretentious prick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 04:31:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t know why this has to be a gender issue. I didn #8217;t feel condescended to because I am female. It #8217;s people like you that create barriers between the sexes. Why can #8217;t I feel disrespected simply because you were rude? I can #8217;t speak for everyone (which is entirely my point) but I completely disagree that no one cares about you and your feelings because you #8217;re male. That assumption is just as bad as your apparent belief  #8220;all females are privileged #8221;. I never done or said anything that didn #8217;t deserve your respect. It #8217;s not hard to have manners.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 04:32:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well you were being condescending. So my point is valid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 04:35:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>You really are a judgemental sad sap, aren #8217;t you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 04:36:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha probably a good decision.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 09:03:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once I saw my doppelg #228;nger when I was stopped at a crossing. She was walking across it and my partner and I just looked at each other.. it was freaky. She dressed nicer than me though so she seemed like the 2.0 version of myself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 09:06:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally my favourite performance on the planet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 09:23:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah I see. Thanks for the tip! I will try that and let you know how I go</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 13:08:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha thanks! If only my brain was as creative awake as it is asleep  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 13:15:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think a lot of the time it #8217;s mums or dads who have their kids in the car and can #8217;t really take it back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 21:09:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure  #128522; what #8217;s your project on?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 11:37:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>The longest journey home.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Currently staying the night in a haunted house.. So, what #8217;s your ghost experience?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 11:39:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 11:45:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, that #8217;s amazing. I wasn #8217;t expecting such a sweet story : #8217;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 11:46:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 11:47:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has there been anything that #8217;s scared you shitless?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 11:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nopeeeee nope nope. I would #8217;ve died</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 11:53:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rude</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 11:53:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>No thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 01:02:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I was thinking it sounded like White Christmas too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 12:32:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>One job done properly is worth 100 half done jobs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 13:04:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>In my first year of uni I had a class on sourcing evidence. It was already an extremely dry subject, but the teacher I had for my tutorials was on another level. She didn #8217;t leave her chair to teach the class, was only a nurse (pretty sure she had zero teaching qualifications) and literally sat in silence for 60% of the class. Needless to say I changed classes second week. I also had an anatomy teacher who I #8217;m pretty sure bullshitted his way through his entire career. Literally couldn #8217;t answer the simplest of questions, and when he didn #8217;t know something he #8217;d make it up. This was obvious because he #8217;d contradict himself 10 minutes later. Ugh.. glad first year is over.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 13:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure what it was, but in an underground car park in Darwin, Australia. It honestly could have been used as a sauna.. nothing else I #8217;ve ever experienced comes close to that level of humidity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Olivia Rogers, Miss Australia 2017 is a speech pathologist  #128522; it #8217;s nice to see some light being shed on our community.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 13:38:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 07:19:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone #8217;s horse got loose and ran around the school grounds once. Also, for year 12 muck up day some students let sheep loose in the quad. I didn #8217;t realise how centred my schooling was on farm animals.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 07:30:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>You HAVE to ask her out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 07:35:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wanted to be Hannah Montana sooooo bad. After many painful childhood years, I discovered you can not be a different person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 07:36:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Christmas lunch is literally all I want</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 07:37:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pass the parcel. I don #8217;t know why this isn #8217;t an adult party game yet it was my fav</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 07:40:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would give small dog syndrome a whole new meaning</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is your favourite dessert?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 12:11:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 12:43:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha, what were you going to say?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 12:52:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s a long time to eat a peach</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 13:30:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>She waits for us to come inside before she will drink water after going for a walk. It #8217;s really sweet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 13:40:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Big 70 #8217;s curls. Or 40 #8217;s dresses. I would look like such a hipster if I tried either of those things</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 13:42:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, I wouldn #8217;t say it #8217;s my passion but it does sound pretty interesting. #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Who is the hardest person to buy Christmas presents for in your family and why?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 13:48:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 13:54:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 13:58:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Neither does mine. Although, I was lucky enough to find a set of an old tv show he used to watch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 14:03:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahahaha. Yeahh I don #8217;t think I #8217;m brave enough for that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 14:08:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds infuriating. She may as well just go and buy them herself hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 14:11:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate giving people money because it #8217;s just so boring haha. But I totally get where you #8217;re coming from</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 14:35:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember having mango weis bars as a kid, loved those.. almost forgot they existed. Great list!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 15:04:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>You get a present, and wrap it up in layer after layer of newspaper. Then, everybody who #8217;s playing sits in a circle while someone is operating music. The parcel is passed around the circle until the music is stopped, and then whoever is holding the parcel gets to take a layer of paper off. This goes on until someone gets the present. You can also add smaller gifts (like lollies) under each layer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 08:47:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Intern. Made me love Robert De Niro even more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 08:49:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>The word "decoration" contains the word "decor". Mind blown.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the juiciest gossip in your family at the moment?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 08:52:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 08:58:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha, sounds like an emotional roller coaster for everyone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 09:07:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>No worries, it #8217;s a really sweet movie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 09:09:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit, that #8217;s a lot of money for presents. Hahaha so much pettiness.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the best psychological thriller in your opinion?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 10:25:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 13:43:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>A board game, books, DVD series, jewellery, kitchen stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 06:33:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Teleport me to the beach when I #8217;m sick of studying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If you had to make a salad with the last two things you ate, what would your salad be made of?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 14:01:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 09:36:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would wear stockings, a skirt (probably just above the knee) and a nice blouse. Also some nice flats or small heels, and a jacket if it #8217;s cold.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 12:13:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Years ago in primary school one of my best friends told me and my other friend a story about how she was roller blading around her house, and fell onto her parents door. The door opened to reveal her parents doing what no kid wants to witness. So naturally we decided that  #8220;door #8221; was the perfect code word when we wanted to talk about sex (remember we were 12). We still joke about it.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 06:34:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>The crunchy nut cereal game?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 06:43:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn haha I loved that game. Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anybody else remember buying 24 can mixed boxes of kirks/possibly Schweppes soft drink? I can #8217;t find evidence of it anywhere.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 09:52:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I going crazy or was this a thing? they were big boxes and had like 4 cans of each flavour</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 10:02:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha no my partner was talking about how they would be a great idea, and I remembered them already being a thing.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 10:03:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 10:04:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish they stocked them in typical supermarkets again, I don #8217;t have a Costco :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 10:05:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope so</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 10:07:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>IT WAS GOLDEN CIRCLE I found it. Thanks everyone haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 10:31:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha, I wouldn #8217;t have even been thought of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the best non-fiction book you #8217;ve ever read?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 10:35:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 10:37:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha yeahhh not buying my super religious mother the bible that #8217;s for sure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 10:44:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve been wanting to read this for a while</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 10:48:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it a good idea to buy my very anti-Islamic mother (who loves war related things and non fiction books) a really good non fiction Islamic themed book for Xmas? Or would it be insulting?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 12:58:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>She #8217;s not a bad person, just misinformed. My dads the one with the hate problem</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 13:05:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well the book seems really educational, it #8217;s about a Muslim woman who escaped from Isis. If she were to read it I believe it would give her a better angle on the whole thing I #8217;m just a bit worried it could stir the pot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 13:19:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I guess you #8217;re right. She is a lot more open minded than it sounds, but I agree Christmas probably isn #8217;t the time. Thanks for the help :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 14:31:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it #8217;s nice and not too small for a one year anniversary. I guess it depends how close you are but if I was given this I would be happy  #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 09:52:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>The blonde hair in your last photo looks the best on you in my opinion. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 11:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I put 1x1x1x1x1x1 into a calculator once. I was reading off a list of numbers to multiply if that makes it any better? :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 11:51:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>No there were more numbers after all the ones haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 11:55:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/gallery/vuo9k4w</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 12:07:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do this with my online university lectures.. I'm almost always completely wrong for some reason.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 12:10:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do this but instead I end up convincing myself somebody has already thought of it and couldn't use it for some unknown reason. Don't do this though it's completely pointless and not accurate at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 10:32:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read that as  #8220;shits on my chest every night #8221; and I was thinking wow you cat owners really are easily pleased</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 10:33:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Olives</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 10:38:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do something similar but I imagine I #8217;m in an abandoned cabin in the middle of the snow. Not sure why that thought comforts me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is your favourite true story somebody had told you?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 10:52:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 11:10:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, I #8217;m not sure this classifies as true  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 11:13:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha awh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 12:03:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unpacking</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 12:09:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I ate my boogers as a kid and now the thought makes me want to vomit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 12:16:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nando. There #8217;s only one Nando. Everyone must fight for the Nando in true hunger games style.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 12:18:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was awkward. I was in a long distance relationship and we had no option but to kiss out the front of my house, probably in clear view of my family. That was roughly 3 years ago and we #8217;re now living together.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When/where are you the most happy?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 14:04:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is your biggest pet peeve?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 09:49:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 09:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I put a reminder in my phone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 09:51:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Minesweeper. Even when I get a chance to mention it people think I #8217;m lying :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 09:54:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, I can beat hard mode after a few tries. I #8217;ve done it 3 times I think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 09:55:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ewww the nail part grosses me out  #128541;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 10:00:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha the only reason I even know how to play it is having hours of free time during high school. Couldn #8217;t play much else on school laptops</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 10:03:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those ugly ass 90 #8217;s [sunnies](https://pbs.twimg.com/profile_images/823322605100945408/9JwNun_r.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 10:04:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, you need tries because sometimes it #8217;s completely up to chance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 10:08:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, on the hardest level you can get cornered and have a 50/50 chance between 2 squares if that makes sense. It #8217;s usually when you have very little squares left.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 10:14:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha yes trust me. You can google it if you don #8217;t believe me. It #8217;s not only based on chance, it doesn #8217;t happen every game but when it does you have to guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 10:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate this so much. Like what is so important in their life that they can #8217;t be a tiny bit more patient</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 10:20:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>To make it harder I guess, there #8217;s literally no way around it. Sometimes I would only have a couple of squares left in the opposite corner to the 2 that I need to choose between, so completing them first wouldn #8217;t do anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 10:24:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha it used to piss me off sooo much when it happened. I #8217;d spend ages on a game and lose because of one tiny wrong guess  #128557;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 10:57:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yess I hate the whole fashionably late thing. You #8217;re not fashionable you #8217;re just a pain in the ass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 11:18:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>My boyfriends brother is like this. He mumbles soo bad and then when you ask him to repeat himself he doesn #8217;t say it any louder. Ugh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 12:04:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can #8217;t trust anyone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 02:46:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>My sister in law #8217;s sister gave birth to her daughter on her birthday. That day is also my birthday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 02:51:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is really clever. Love it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[TOMT] [MUSIC] A Russian song by a woman only lyrics I remember are  #8220;Ba ba ba oooh #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 00:13:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve been trying to find this song for a while now. It #8217;s a Russian song by a woman who is pretty famous in Russia I assume, she #8217;s my aunties favourite singer. I could just ask my Aunty but I won #8217;t be seeing her for a while. It #8217;s an upbeat song, and I remember the other songs she sang were more serious if that makes sense? This song seemed to be more of a  #8220;fun #8221; song she sang. The lyrics I remember are: Ba ba ba ooooh Ba ba ba oh. Ba ba ba ooooh Ba ba ba oh! Sorry this is so vague haha I can #8217;t remember any other words (because it was in Russian). Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 01:32:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will do, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 03:02:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha no  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 03:30:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>The phonetic alphabet.. Is that even impressive?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 03:42:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>The one where the prime minister fucks a pig</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 03:48:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bragging about how much you can drink, the wild night you had last weekend or how you almost passed out in the gutter. Nobody cares. (Goes for men too).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 04:58:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vikings</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 08:56:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm good at handling myself in (somewhat) stressful situations.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 08:58:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mum used to follow the school bus when we had school excursions and stay the whole time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 08:59:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Drank the last caramel latte that my boyfriend was saving</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 09:00:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only way they will go the way I like is if I stay positive and motivated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 09:02:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably eat my boogers. I was a gross kid</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 09:03:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not really that weird but my boyfriend delivers food and told me one guy had a pond in his living room.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If you could only eat one very specific food for the rest of your life what would it be?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 09:09:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 09:17:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's hard :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 09:40:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you have one too?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 09:41:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>No I swear on my life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 09:41:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lovely</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[TOMT] [music] Russian(?) song with linked recordings!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 10:02:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been trying to find this song for years and could only remember some words in the chorus and the tune. I have linked the chorus and verse (all I can remember) played on an online keyboard so sorry it's not the best. I think it's clear enough though for someone who knows the song. Chorus - https://instaud.io/private/aabd8eff6ba51deed74fcd3b5e2775af80f8c84d The only lyrics I remember in the chorus are: Ba ba ba oooh Ba ba ba oh. Ba ba ba ooh Ba ba ba oh! Verse - https://instaud.io/private/38b1d76f500b611dc32e6e3a1d04d3efdf7058db The verse was all in what I think was Russian and I could not make it out. I'm like 80% sure the song is Russian but may not be. The singer is female, I think middle aged and quite popular. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 10:06:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha I didn #8217;t know it was common. Is there any purpose to them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 10:20:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m making this for Christmas because I love it so much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 10:21:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha that #8217;s so funny that someone thought of that. They sound cool, I want one now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 11:35:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it was a combination of me being her first child and her worrying about the teachers leaving me somewhere haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 12:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Before- really tired, acne scarred zombie After- slightly less tired, less acne scarred zombie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 12:46:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The stranger things intro mixed with Ariana grande  #8220;into you #8221;. https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=IcftmFsVMRY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 12:48:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dom (or maybe Irving) from Mr Robot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 13:20:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>That song with the old men in Black and white pushing around a piano ugh I hate that song Edit: we no speak americano</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 15:33:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha yup I would probably eat the whole thing if left alone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 01:25:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>This has happened to me too, many times. Sometimes when I randomly think of someone I #8217;m actually expecting to hear from them/see something about them soon after. Like for example the other day I randomly thought of my boyfriends brother and how he hasn #8217;t contacted us for months. Literally less than an hour later he called. Happens way too often to be a coincidence</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 14:50:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>No sadly :( thanks though! Can #8217;t really say for sure but the year would probably be around 2007 ish? Maybe earlier but no later than 2009 as that #8217;s when I heard it. She was probably around 30, quite pretty but I can #8217;t remember what she actually looked like (only saw a glimpse of the album cover). Sorry it #8217;s so vague haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 03:48:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Finish uni, move into a bigger place in a different city with my boyfriend (hopefully on the beach), get a good job preferably in private practice (speech pathology), buy a house, get married, have 2 kids. That's how I want it to work out anyway, life does have a way of changing things up though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 03:54:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have to travel for hours to get anywhere, it's hot 90% of the time in 90% of places, people are generally nicer in country areas than in the cities (definitely a LOT of exceptions though).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 04:26:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally if I want to go to the nearest TOWN its an hour away. And i'm in a city... how is that not true? Haha. But yeah the heat one was a bit of an exaggeration.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 04:30:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Obviously there's places near each other within an hours drive but nothing of significance. If you're a tourist and want to see the Australian sights you'd be doing a bloody lot of travelling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 04:39:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love watching other people play horror games (e.g. Outlast) but I couldn't play them myself haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 07:57:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Laidback. What does that even mean? No one #8217;s that laidback that they can use it as a personality trait, surely</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Which anonymous  #8220;leaking of information #8221; internet post has stuck with you the most?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 08:00:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 08:10:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not exactly what I had in mind but I guess that answers the question #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Which case of an insider leaking information on the internet stuck with you the most?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 08:28:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 08:36:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now you can keep your Fappening answers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 09:57:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. Not putting my location on reddit but I #8217;m in a pretty populated area for outside of a major city.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 11:21:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too. I think we're pretty done for</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 11:22:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scrambled eggs, toasted sandwich, starve until I go shopping next.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 13:45:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha far out, what does get to you then?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 14:22:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I think they #8217;re all pretty valid reasons to be pissed haha. Wow no offence but your friend seems like a total dick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 15:01:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh I see. Well it definitely sounds like it #8217;s for the best.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 07:53:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I cry every time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 07:54:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Littering in general drives me insane</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 07:55:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cold KFC (especially popcorn chicken)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 07:56:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Feebee</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 07:58:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will Ferrell. Still haven #8217;t disliked one of his movies and I find him genuinely funny</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 08:03:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had an imaginary friend for a few years when I was younger. Her name was Mary and I was pretty full on with it.. looking back I weirdly have an image of  #8220;her #8221; in my head but it #8217;s most likely just imbedded in my brain from imagining her for so long.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 08:05:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Focus on yourself and only think about the bad parts of the relationship/person to make yourself feel better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 08:08:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would have pillow fluff all over my bed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 09:37:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I loved Daddy #8217;s Home :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 11:12:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to sing in talent quests and do some charity performing, and one little girl who also sang told her Mum that she wanted to be just like me when she was older. It was so sweet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 11:14:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any kind of scary amusement park ride. Not for me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 11:14:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>When my camera flips my photos</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 11:15:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ewww it #8217;s gross and really lazy imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 11:29:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 11:30:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup I #8217;ve seen it happen too many times.. they usually don #8217;t maintain rides like they #8217;re meant to and have teenagers running them. No thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 11:34:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to try this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 11:38:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually I think it #8217;s the opposite.. like when you take a photo with the iPhone front camera and it looks completely different after you take it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 11:46:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Student placements</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 14:38:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Floofer. Her name is Poppy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 14:39:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good luck with this, I #8217;ve been trying to fix mine for years.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 14:46:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it means a lot to you- a day to remember Has a lot of bad memories but it #8217;s a great song so I feel conflicted when I listen to it, lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 14:47:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Lion King maybe?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 14:48:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mango</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 15:30:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sid and his creepy ass toys from the first Toy Story</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 01:40:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>We both downloaded the same terrible dating app because we were bored, I messaged him, we talked for a bit and now we #8217;re living together. (There was quite a gap between talking and living together though, btw).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 01:46:53</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Buddy the elf what #8217;s your favourite colour?! #8221; Gets me every time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 01:52:40</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;I have nipples Greg, could you milk me? #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 14:42:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>This messed me up big time.. it #8217;s been fruit for so long but now it #8217;s Froot again I can #8217;t deal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 01:22:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I second this, it #8217;s the only movie that keeps popping into my head when I hear it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 13:50:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was talking with my two best friends in high school, and a kid who was about 5 was listening to us intently. We were talking about how we used to fight when we were younger and how I used to try and  #8220;fit in #8221;. Kid stands up, looks at us and comes out with:  #8220;Ah, I remember when Clare used to try and fit in #8221;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 15:27:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t give it to her and ignore her until she gets over it would be my strategy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 15:31:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Finished half of my bachelor/masters degree</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 15:37:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wishing you were somehow here again from the phantom of the opera. Makes me cry every time but I still love it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 21:56:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Applied science and speech pathology  #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 23:38:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>It definitely is! I think I want to work with kids in private practice or with people with voice problems.  #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 23:55:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like they would steer clear of religion, not really fucked up but very controversial</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 00:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ohhhh my godddd... TRAMBAMPALINE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 02:55:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good point haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 10:21:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>It touches on the after life though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Has anyone else felt scared of something in a dream which you normally wouldn #8217;t be scared of in real life?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 10:25:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>The other night I had a dream that I was laying on the ground, and to my left was a giant jet moving really slowly through the sky. When I say giant I mean giant, it was like 100x the size of a normal jet and seemed to be quite close. Like obviously if that happened to me in real life it would be scary but something about it irked me in my dream.. The fact that it was so big and was moving so slowly gave me a really weird feeling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 13:50:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my gosh, this is exactly it. Thank you!! I will google it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 05:46:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can #8217;t imagine how it would be in real life and not in a dream.. that would really freak me out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 14:02:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometimes I get a really weird feeling of dehydration mixed with a strong feeling of dread, or a feeling that I shouldn #8217;t be where I am in that moment. I #8217;ve had it ever since I could remember. It only happens if I #8217;m somewhere that feels wrong.. Like for example if it was a really nice day outside and I was sitting in my dark bedroom I would get it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 14:20:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I literally just posted a comment on this because I thought there was no way it happened to other people as well. For me it #8217;s the really strong thirst but mixed with a feeling of being somewhere I shouldn #8217;t be. Like if it #8217;s a really nice day outside and I am inside a dark room I would get it. Definitely happened more as a kid though, I only get it very rarely now. Such an odd feeling</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My boyfriend experienced something super glitchy..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 23:51:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I was driving with my boyfriend yesterday when he told me something that had happened to him the day earlier. He didn #8217;t tell me at the time (we were also driving when it happened) because he didn #8217;t want to scare me. He said that he was looking at the road, when it seemed like a diagonal cut in the centre of his vision moved everything slightly to the left, and then back to normal. Literally like the most generic  #8220;glitch #8221; ever. He said he has never experienced anything like it before and we have no idea what could have caused it. I said sometimes my vision trips out when I get a rush of adrenaline but he said that #8217;s not what happened to him, because the diagonal cut was perfectly straight and he saw it happen clear as anything. Besides nothing had happened to cause it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 00:34:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>He could have been dehydrated, and it had been a very long day of driving.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My boyfriend #8217;s dad keeps  #8220;forgetting #8221; to buy my boyfriend Christmas/birthday presents</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 06:37:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I #8217;m a little upset about my boyfriends family (specifically his dad and step-Mum) this Christmas. My boyfriend has always had a good relationship with his dad, and last Christmas everyone exchanged gifts and everything was fine. This year, my boyfriend turned 21 and didn #8217;t receive anything at all from his dad because he kept forgetting to get him anything. Now Christmas has rolled around and we had bought gifts for all of his family members who we saw, and got none in return. I don #8217;t care about not receiving anything but it makes me feel really helpless and sad when my boyfriend doesn #8217;t get anything from his own family. His dad told us that he couldn #8217;t afford to buy the  #8220;adults #8221; gifts for now, but him and his wife definitely could afford to buy for his two stepsons (one of which who is in their late teens) as well as other family members on her side. Besides, we #8217;re both students and managed to buy for two families. I think his dad could definitely afford to buy him SOMETHING, especially when I have family members who aren #8217;t that well off for money either but could afford to buy me and my boyfriend gifts. And the fact that they bought for people on my boyfriends step-mums side of the family. I #8217;m not sure what to do about this, I #8217;m hoping his dad and step-Mum actually pull through this time and get him something but I #8217;m not too hopeful. Any suggestions? Hate seeing my boyfriend feel neglected.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 06:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you #8217;re right. I #8217;ll try and plan something he #8217;ll like for his next birthday, he had a pretty quiet one this year so I think he #8217;ll appreciate it. Thanks for your help :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 14:49:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dog loves everyone but would growl at our neighbour. This happened on multiple occasions. Not long after he beat another dog to death.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What moment in your life seemed like it was straight out of a movie?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 14:55:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 15:00:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s my favourite movie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 15:01:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did this and it was a black horse but it would jump over the shadows made by trees on the road.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What future technology scares or excites you the most?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 09:07:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 09:09:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Geralt of Rivia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 09:10:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scares or excites you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 09:11:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>That robot chick freaks me out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 09:12:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely not.. I can #8217;t help but think of the worst possible scenario for every new technology now thanks to BM</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 09:14:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exciting technologies for me are things that will help the planet but robots are literally the opposite of that  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 09:16:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would throw a spanner in the works. Hopefully not!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 09:19:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to try VR so bad, will be interesting to see where it goes..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 09:19:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed.. although the idea of consciousness copies scares me more I think</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 09:19:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 09:23:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Totally agree although I think some things should be avoided for sure. Not just because of moral reasons but because there #8217;s other technologies more worth while</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 09:37:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely making copies of someone #8217;s consciousness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 09:46:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I notice the older ones do it too but definitely more subtly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 09:50:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah I wouldn #8217;t actually. Theres definitely a lot that don #8217;t, I love Pewdiepie. I feel like modesty goes such a long way when trying to keep a fan base. And I don #8217;t mean just buying things, I mean specifically making videos clearly just for the purpose of flaunting their money. Eg. lavish holiday montages.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 09:53:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking of mainly the British Youtubers I used to love but now clearly only care about one thing, zoella, pointlessblog etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 09:59:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most of them have in some way or another. I think one of the reasons Pewdiepie is so popular is because his modesty is a rarity on YouTube. If they #8217;re not flaunting their wealth they #8217;re begging for merch sales. Most of the Youtubers I used to watch had a holiday montage. They #8217;re so common I don #8217;t know how you haven #8217;t seen one. Jake Paul is on a different level of showing off to most Youtubers lol Edit- sorry that lol sounded rude but it wasn #8217;t meant to be haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 10:22:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think way too many of them do that. I don #8217;t know if it #8217;s  #8220;most #8221; or not, I haven #8217;t done any studies, but it #8217;s a lot. A video with clips from a fancy holiday and music, usually.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 14:17:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, I don #8217;t think it #8217;s bad, it #8217;s just very refreshing when they can make videos related to their actual content and not just to show off. I suppose you #8217;re not talking about vlogs or travel accounts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My dog would rather sit in a shoebox than on the car seat.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 02:48:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 03:53:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah she can jump up and down</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 03:54:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m pretty sure she was raised by cats  #128514; had the personality of one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 10:13:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can also relate. My dad was so poor growing up he #8217;d have to lie on his fists to stop the hunger pains, and had about 3 toys his entire childhood. One which was an upside down wheelbarrow. Ever since I can remember he has worked tirelessly to prevent his family from going through the same. Might have to thank him properly one day soon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Need advice relating to past trauma due to a relatives alcohol use</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 13:37:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry if this isn #8217;t allowed, mods please delete if it isn #8217;t. So long story short, my mum is an alcoholic and it has caused me a lot of trauma in the past. I #8217;ve had my own issues with alcohol, not abuse but it #8217;s taken me a long time to be able to enjoy it in a healthy way without the negative connotations. I want to have a small get together for my birthday this year (which would actually be joined with my grandpas birthday as well) and invite some friends and have a few drinks. The problem is, it would be at my parents home, and all of my family would be there. I don #8217;t know how to explain it but something about drinking around my Mum (when she #8217;s also drinking) and my family members who her drinking has affected so much just irks me. I don #8217;t think I could enjoy it. I don #8217;t have any other choice of location as I can only come home for a couple of days due to being flat out at uni. It really sucks because I want to enjoy myself and have a nice birthday, but don #8217;t know if I can do that when drinking. Of course being around my Mum drinking would make it hard anyway, but I #8217;m not sure what to do. Would it be smart to just forget about alcohol all together or is there some other alternative?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 15:40:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, I didn #8217;t know that was a thing. Will do some research :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Super creepy book from my childhood has disappeared..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 01:22:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>So back in primary school we had a thing called home readers. You had to choose some books from a bookcase and take them home to read. One time, I brought home a book called  #8220;*girls name* #8217;s party #8221;. (Can #8217;t remember her name but I #8217;m leaning towards Lucy/Lacy). Now this book definitely appeared to be a children #8217;s book. It had the same style of all of the other books in the home readers collection, and didn #8217;t strike me as odd from its appearance. Once I started reading it though, it was pretty clear that it was not a book children should be reading. The book was about a young girl who invites a bunch of her friends over for a party. Except it #8217;s not a party, it #8217;s a S #201;ANCE. She invites her friends over to play with ouija boards and make their own out of pieces of paper. Needless to say it was a very disturbing experience for 7 year old me, and I don #8217;t even think my parents let me finish it once they realised what it was about. I #8217;ve tried to find this book online but haven #8217;t had any luck whatsoever. So yeah that #8217;s my story about a creepy ass home reader book that has since disappeared from existence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 04:12:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you mean? My parents were disturbed by it too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 04:12:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah it had pictures, and it was clearly aimed at children by the wording and stuff. Could have been one of those adult picture books though but it was very much like the other books</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[TOMT] (book) A children #8217;s picture book about children who have a s #232;ance party</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 04:39:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I remember reading this (clearly disturbing) picture book as a kid about a girl who throws a party for her friends, but it turns out to be a seance party where they use homemade ouija boards to contact spirits and do other spooky stuff. The title of the book was  #8220;*girls name* #8217;s party #8221; although could be a variation of that. I keep leaning towards names like Lucy, Lacy, Jenny or Jackie but I can #8217;t find anything. It was definitely a picture book and was aimed at children, hence why it was in my school library. Does anyone know what book I #8217;m talking about or am I crazy? I remember it clear as day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 06:34:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can #8217;t find a record of it. It was a school book so I have no chance of going back to find it sadly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 06:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll try that, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 07:23:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did just earlier. I can #8217;t seem to find anything either it #8217;s a bit of a mystery!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 07:28:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember the front cover was a cartoon picture of the girl, with some stuff in the background (bits of paper I think) and I remember one other picture in the book. One was all of the friends sitting around a table/on the floor where they had paper squares and glasses of water in a circle. Most of the pictures were pretty similar. I remember thinking that the front cover wasn #8217;t a very good depiction of the story because it seemed really misleading, like as if the book was about an actual birthday party (I think there may have even been balloons but I #8217;m really not sure). It also wasn #8217;t the kind of book you would expect for a spooky kids book, it was really disturbing the way the s #232;ance was depicted.. like a normal thing for children to do. I can #8217;t remember anything else really</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 07:36:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am also pretty sure that the story was mainly made up of the girl teaching her friends how to set up and conduct the s #232;ance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 08:04:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>It definitely could be, hard to know without any more information though. I don #8217;t think it was a teen book though more aimed at young children. Thanks for your help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 09:30:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was definitely more of a modern style, probably published around the early 2000 #8217;s. I #8217;m sorry I can #8217;t remember the exact style of the illustrations, definitely had colour though and were quite cartoonish looking I think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 09:36:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s the most frustrating thing ever haha. I was actually thinking of asking my little sister to keep an eye out for the book at school, but I think I #8217;d have the same results as you. Hope you find your book, I can #8217;t say I #8217;ve heard of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[TOMT] [book] A young adult fiction book about a school where the students are ghosts</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 09:40:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is going to be a stretch because I can #8217;t remember much about this book at all, but I would love to find it again. It was a young adult novel about a child/teenager who moves to a new school in a new neighbourhood (narrows it down I know) and I think all of the students are really old fashioned. It #8217;s revealed later on in the book that they #8217;re all actually ghosts and the school has been deserted for years. That #8217;s what I think it was about anyway if you know of any variations of what I #8217;ve said that could be right also. Was probably written in the 90 #8217;s. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 09:48:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn #8217;t think it was because I #8217;ve read all of those as well, but it definitely could have been. Thinking it may have been  #8220;the haunted school #8221; but I #8217;m not 100% sure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 09:54:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks but I just had a look and I don #8217;t recognise any of the covers, I don #8217;t think I #8217;ve ever read her books</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 11:13:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah I see. It #8217;s possible, I do feel like I remember it clear enough to not feel that way though, at least I think I do haha my memory could be wrong of course.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 00:06:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>It wasn #8217;t intense, it was a childish book. It was just the topics in there that were disturbing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 00:07:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>No :( thanks though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 00:08:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I may have been around 10-11. I remember it so clearly so I wasn #8217;t too young</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 00:10:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow that #8217;s crazy.. interesting to see if your new copy disappears also haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 05:58:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>It could definitely be the haunted school from the goosebumps series. It has a very similar concept!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A children #8217;s picture book about a girl who invites her friends over for a s #232;ance..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 07:24:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>So Ive been trying to find this book I read when I was about 10-11. It was a picture book aimed at children, and it was about a young girl who invites a bunch of her friends over to have a s #232;ance and talk to spirits. I am pretty sure the name of the book was  #8220;*insert girl #8217;s name* #8217;s party #8221; (could also be sleepover/slumber party etc.). I thought the name of the girl was similar to Jenny/Lucy but I can #8217;t find anything so it could be any name. On the cover was the girl with balloons in the background (I think). There were also squares of paper (the ones they used for the s #232;ance). I remember a picture in the book was the kids sitting in a circle, with the squares of paper forming a homemade ouija board. I think there were also glasses of water. I am pretty sure that the story line was the girl teaching her friends how to set up and conduct a s #232;ance. It was a pretty weird book for children to be reading. So yeah that #8217;s about all I can remember but I #8217;ve tried literally everything to find it. It was probably written in the 90 #8217;s/early 2000 #8217;s but definitely no later than 2007 ish. Thanks in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 07:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just posted, thanks! You could be right, it would make a lot of sense if it was like that. Haha I #8217;ve never actually read those.. might have to give them a google  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 10:39:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>This has happened to me on more than one occasion... why</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 10:49:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely only when you get a pimple</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 10:50:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>No :( was definitely a picture book. Thanks for your help though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 10:55:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably not the creepiest but the creepiest I can think of off the top of my head.. My dad once stayed overnight at a motel in a pretty small country town. He said that during the night, he felt someone tickle him but no one did. He also said it looked like there were blood stains on the sheets. The same night, in the same hotel, his brother said he could hear someone breathing beside him, and no one was there. He said it also felt like someone was laying in bed with him or like there was pressure on the mattress. Freaked me out as a kid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 10:56:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pls don #8217;t kill any more loved famous people :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 10:57:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>How everything we see is just a reflection of light. We don #8217;t even know if we #8217;re seeing things the way they really are.. or everyone could be seeing things differently. Or maybe there #8217;s other dimensions alongside us but we just can #8217;t see them..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 10:58:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shitter #8217;s clogged</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 11:02:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. I think it #8217;s crazy how humans are so sure of things in general. We #8217;re only going off our own senses</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why do you think we are/aren #8217;t living in a simulation?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 11:05:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 11:07:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Popping pimples.. but yeah I hope nobody actually does this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 11:08:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You got me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 11:09:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well it #8217;s definitely glitched..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 11:10:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely. So often I feel like I know exactly what people are going to do/say next</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 11:11:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s crazy. Also, ask anyone and I bet they #8217;ve had a similar experience/know someone who has</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 11:53:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is the biggest flaw in your opinion?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 13:22:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would mean there would be multiple? Edit: sorry I think my lack of punctuation was misleading.  #8220;What is the biggest flaw, in your opinion? #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 13:31:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something small in white ink.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 23:39:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>A picture book aimed at young children</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 00:26:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>[FENTOOON!](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=3GRSbr0EYYU)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 12:31:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I found this too, Black Museum however is now probably my all time favourite. I did also love USS Callister though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 13:09:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Full sugar soft drink. It has an insane amount of sugar in there (yes I know this isn't technically eating).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 13:19:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my gosh your story reminded me of something really similar that happened to me. I was laying in bed one night, when I heard this horrifying moaning/breathing sound outside my window. It was like a really low rattly sound kind of like what I imagine a demon would sound like. I was so scared I pretty much shit myself and ran into my parents room and told them, visibly shaken. Turns out possums make that noise when they're asleep and I was terrified of a snoring possum.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 13:24:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Joop Go. I bought it for my boyfriend not long after we met and he still wears it all the time. It smells amazing but I may have classically conditioned myself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 13:30:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>There were many.. But I lived next door to a lady who was a bit strange. She was really nice but had a stealing problem.. She once stole 7 electric frying pans from the school once when she was volunteering. She also stole my parents ladder and hid it under her house. It was not subtle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 13:35:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's different every time, usually just the typical feeling of being paralysed with the last images I was dreaming of stuck in my vision. One time in particular stuck out though.. It's kind of funny and terrifying at the same time (and super weird). I dreamt that there were these people going around looking for the funniest person in every family. When they found them, they would stick grapes up their butt. No joke. So lucky for me I was the funniest in my family and I woke up to sleep paralysis with people simultaneously sticking grapes up my butt. I couldn't make this up if I tried.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 13:36:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Possibly, I think she definitely had some form of mental illness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 13:58:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mum calls wifi "wire fire" and oh my gosh it grinds my gears</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 14:03:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember reading something about what your body goes through when you ingest that much sugar, it was crazy. One of the worst things you can have in my opinion. Congrats by the way :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 14:05:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>James and the giant dick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 14:12:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe all "addictions" that aren't caused by an actual introduced addictive substance (e.g. nicotine, ethanol) are bullshit. Simply increasing dopamine in your brain does not equal addiction</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 14:16:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can confirm monopoly brings out sides of me I didn #8217;t know existed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 14:18:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>The longest journey/dreamfall. It feels like everyone #8217;s forgotten about it but it #8217;ll always be my favourite story</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 14:23:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to play fireboy and watergirl, minesweeper, run, and unfair Mario (this one causes rage quits though) during high school. Still play them when I #8217;m bored.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 00:36:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>What?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 09:19:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>He #8217;s gorgeous! Is he a labradoodle?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is Poppy. She loves my parents #8217; new pool.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 09:21:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anybody know where I can buy wax blocks/discs for a warmer online in bulk?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 10:32:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>My boyfriend bought me an at home waxing kit with a warmer for Christmas, and I was wondering if there is anywhere I can buy melting wax in bulk? I can only find the tubs for microwaves. The normal refills of the same brand also aren #8217;t too cheap, and I need to ship to Australia. Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 10:46:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sadly not :( Somehow I don #8217;t think I #8217;ll ever find it haha it must be very unpopular. Thank you so much for your help though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 13:44:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my primary teachers was going away for a couple of days, and we had a substitute teacher for the time she was away. Before she had left, the class (or more specifically most of the boys in the class) had been really badly behaved. She gave us all a talk before she left saying how she expects everyone to behave for the substitute teacher. That didn #8217;t happen. When she came back and heard about what had happened she was really upset and cried. I don #8217;t know why everyone remembers this but I think it was a bit of a wake up call for some of the kids cus they were better after that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 13:45:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>They can pee wherever. Going camping? No problem. Hiking somewhere without a toilet? Also no problem/peeing on shoes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 13:49:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t take it for granted</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 14:07:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah.. or possibly pregnant</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 01:25:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>No :/ was definitely a picture book. Thanks though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 10:14:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whelp I want one now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 10:15:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t be, appreciate your help :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 13:50:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is beautiful! Old post I know haha but where is it from if you don #8217;t mind me asking?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 12:36:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Having any form of interest in a kangaroo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 13:50:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why don #8217;t you test it and let us know</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 13:51:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Walking in public</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 14:14:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I grew up in the bush so it doesn #8217;t really apply to me but I totally understand, people from the bigger cities here would react like that. I know a girl from Melbourne who had never even driven on a road that wasn #8217;t a freeway.. that was eye opening haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 12:38:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get scared when anyone is yelling at me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 13:18:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone said they wouldn #8217;t touch me with a 10 foot pole in high school. Same guy also said some horrible things about my family. Still remember to this day (jokes on him though- he #8217;s still trash).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 13:37:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well technically the statement is true already in your case  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 13:51:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>No one knows my grandmas real birthday, apparently there was a mistake with the birth certificate but no one knows for sure. Apparently she hates talking about it so I #8217;ve never brought it up. Also, someone stole an important photograph that belonged to my uncle and replaced it with a cheap replica. No one knows who did it. It was the source of a shitload of family drama for a long time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 13:56:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Littering. It #8217;s so lazy and unnecessary. Also obnoxious people</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 13:58:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Life #8217;s not fair One job done properly is worth 100 half done jobs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 13:59:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s kind of weird, but I remember laying in bed with my Mum before I could talk and being frustrated that I couldn #8217;t tell her I was still hungry. Could be a false memory but it #8217;s very realistic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 14:13:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not me, but my little sister had a teacher in primary school who she thought hated her. One time, she made her go up in front of the whole class (even after other kids actually wanted to) and demonstrate  #8220;the penguin dance #8221; to the tune of give it up. I think she #8217;s still a little scarred by it  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 14:15:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let him dab on them haters</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 14:17:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It made me super self conscious and always question whether I #8217;m good enough/people actually like me. Even when I #8217;m in a situation where I clearly don #8217;t have to worry about those things they creep up on me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 14:19:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ewwww nope</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 14:29:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I went to see Avatar in 3D when it first came out. The 3D was out of sync and no one done anything until like 30 mins into the movie, so they rewinded it and brought everyone free lollies. The weirdest part was getting something for free in a cinema</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 08:06:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Oh shit wrong needle"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 08:11:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>My hopeful little self wanted to be a jockey. No one had the heart to tell me I would literally never be small enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 08:12:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dad actually trusts the news.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What do you want to achieve before you die?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:40:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What #8217;s the weirdest thing that #8217;s happened to you?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:42:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:44:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be awesome. Are you a builder?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>What would you do with it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Liar</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:45:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly nothing sounds worse to me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:46:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds productive  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:46:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome. What about?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:47:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nothing at all?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:48:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got scammed as a teenager for $500 :( I was so naive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:49:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spaghetti bolognese is better as leftovers in the microwave IMO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:50:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can #8217;t figure it out. Maybe another bird dropped it?! It #8217;s a mystery</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:52:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should definitely go for it. Would you live in it or sell it? Would be so cool to design and build it yourself- would make it really special</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:53:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would read that. Goodluck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:54:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that #8217;s fair enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:55:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>What type of game?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re an idiot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:56:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg me too. I #8217;m aiming for 1000 miles though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:57:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Future bitches aren #8217;t gonna want your old ass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:59:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha I could tell. That would be cool, I can #8217;t say I #8217;ve played a murder mystery before</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:01:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d love to do that too but I don #8217;t think it will ever happen haha. What do you like to write about?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:02:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe someone threw it at you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:04:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I used to love Cluedo if that means anything haha  #128514; Thanks for the tip, I might give it a go!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:05:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>A murder mystery board game haha. I think it #8217;s called Clue in the us?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:07:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:08:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s actually really fun! I used to play it with my cousins. Haven #8217;t played it for years though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:09:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>That nice :) I imagine saving a life would be an incredible feeling</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:13:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spontaneous sex</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:14:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>That fucking cow cheese that doesn #8217;t have a ring in its nose. Or Shaggy from Scooby doo not having an adams apple</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:15:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aw I #8217;m happy for you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:17:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re trashy and I hate you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:22:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can only try!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:25:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds interesting. Good luck! Yeah all that stuff can be hard. Don #8217;t let it slip away though it would be an awesome achievement :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:25:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>No worries :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:29:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chokers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chocolate, Chinese, ice cream, pizza and cake. Probably not all at (depends on how sad I am though)  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:41:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha well at least you know I #8217;m telling the truth  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:47:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good luck with all of that! I #8217;d like to own some land too, or live on the beach. One or the other. What would you call your cafe? :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:50:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be so cool. How do you do that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 12:01:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mum always said this. I hope you never have to experience that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 12:05:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s really interesting.. As someone who is on the opposite end of the scale all I can say is try and find a good balance between the two. It can be a really good trait to have but you can #8217;t get too invested in other people #8217;s feelings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 12:07:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope you find it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 12:24:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s a good goal to have</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 14:05:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Criminal. I #8217;ll take my chances that they weren #8217;t just arrested for petty theft</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 03:57:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>The toilet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 05:53:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The mask.. I just can #8217;t stand it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 06:00:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I watched the whole thing and the second one (son of the mask) with my boyfriend because he likes them. It was pretty awful  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DAE hate Facebook page admins?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 10:02:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I swear they #8217;re all middle aged parents who never achieved any form of authority throughout their life so they make up for it by enforcing their crappy saving tip Facebook page rules. No offence if you happen to be one.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 01:03:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be fair, Facebook has turned into a giant ad with very little social interaction. Most of my family barely even communicate there anymore (disregarding messenger).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 01:03:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s a shame they can #8217;t see how pathetic they look</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 03:22:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have too many to choose but probably USS Callister or White Christmas</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 08:19:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some serious droughts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 11:35:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ever since I watched Hang the DJ (Black Mirror) I #8217;ve wanted [Amy #8217;s camel coat](https://m.imgur.com/ZBBJDhK) soo bad. I #8217;ll never find one I love though  #128514; #128557;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 05:39:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I think one of these possibilities is accurate. From memory though it definitely felt like the author thought this was a normal thing for kids to do, it wasn #8217;t portrayed as a bad or weird thing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 23:25:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was my first thought too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 01:24:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Turkish kitchen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DAE hate it when the term internet troll is misused?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 02:17:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The weirdest experience of my life.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 06:01:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have been meaning to post this story here since I joined this subreddit, but only just got round to it after thinking about it a lot recently. So basically I experienced something when I was about 4 years old that has really stuck with me. Bit of back story- I grew up in rural Australia, with lots of dry scrub and snakes. As an only child at the time, my Mum spent a lot of time taking me for walks in the bush around our hometown. One day I was on a bush walk with Mum, and we come across a brown snake (very deadly snakes). I think we must have been stopped for a water break, because I had a Teletubbies backpack which I took everywhere and it was on the ground next to me. So after seeing this snake, I had this really strong urge to reach down and pet it, so I did. Meanwhile, Mum had jumped behind a big rock nearby, and was trying to grab my backpack (which was on the ground right next to the snake) with a long stick. While doing this she was yelling at me to get behind the rock, and to stop petting the damn snake. This memory is crystal clear to me and had been a fact in my head for as long as I can remember. It #8217;s really strange because I was never a brave kid, at kindergarten when we had  #8220;reptile day #8221; I was too scared to even touch the harmless lizards. I was however extremely curious, and would touch things I wasn #8217;t meant to (putting my fingers in bird cages, open tins and on hot irons are a few examples). So the next thing I remember is finally listening to Mum and hiding behind the rock with her until the snake disappeared. Turns out, after talking to Mum about this her recollection is completely different to mine. She remembers everything I remember, except I got behind the rock with her from the beginning and didn #8217;t even pet or go near the snake. This has made me think that I have created a false memory of the event, but it #8217;s just so clear (and not in 3rd person which is a tip I heard about to detect false memories). I #8217;ve believed my whole life that I petted that snake in the bush. Recently I #8217;ve been researching the parallel universe/multiple dimension theory and the idea that my memory did happen, but in a different universe where I got bitten by the snake and died. Anyway that #8217;s my super weird glitch in the matrix story, let me know your thoughts!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 07:44:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that #8217;s definitely the most logical explanation, such a weird feeling though when you #8217;re certain about something</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 09:29:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Teen porn features girls aged 18+, not 14. That #8217;s child porn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 14:47:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you don #8217;t condone it, then you should be able to see that just because something is common or popular doesn #8217;t mean it #8217;s acceptable. Therefore making OP #8217;s issue (even if it was JUST the weird  #8220;innocent #8221; comment alone) a valid one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 23:30:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree to an extent. I think harm reduction is always the best method but this isn #8217;t something that should be lumped together with other mental illnesses. It #8217;s shunned and unaccepted by society for a reason and that should never change. Especially if they #8217;ve committed. The day we start empathising with pedophiles as if they have depression is a day I hope we never see.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 01:01:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too, not necessarily just my own experience but I #8217;ve heard soo many stories that can be explained by the parallel universe theory. I mean, maybe  #128514; I don #8217;t know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 12:29:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>My Pop used to lift heavy boxes working in a factory as a teenager, and as a result he now has stuffed up eyes (apparently lifting in your youth can cause detached retina).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 12:32:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>It wasn #8217;t  #8220;bacon is good for me #8221; boy was it? #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 12:33:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry.. all the best!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 12:41:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anonymity</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What #8217;s the first fact that pops into your head?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 12:57:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:00:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>There #8217;s this new technology that monitors your thoughts to determine if you #8217;re capable of committing a crime. Eventually, just having criminal thoughts is enough to get you arrested. People go insane trying to find ways to stop themselves thinking of bad things.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:01:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I #8217;d like to see a source for this too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:01:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rebel honey bees breaking all the rules</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:10:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Black mirror</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:12:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>This one freaked me out the first time I heard it. They #8217;re so heartless  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:13:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>How did you go?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:13:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:14:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a teenager I fell for someone selling an iPhone on some sales site. Lost $500 but learnt a shit lot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:15:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Paradox</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:17:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>No worries, glad it went well! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:17:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>They look so innocent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:20:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Luckily they don #8217;t need to</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:26:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait what</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:28:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:29:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, I dunno</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:29:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>No way.. decoy vaginas are you making this shit up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:29:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometimes they #8217;re green</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:32:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That probably goes for anything. Asshole humans</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:34:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I regret googling the corkscrew penis</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:37:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that #8217;s even cooler</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:37:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>No pun intended</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:38:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha that #8217;s actually really interesting, thanks for sharing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:40:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m pretty sure mine ways like 10 because my brain is so big</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:43:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks I guess  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:44:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:52:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually really like this fact</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:55:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never knew that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:56:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:57:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my gosh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 13:59:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s a lot of rashes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 14:02:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit. That #8217;s insane</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 14:06:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean I wouldn #8217;t really call that a fact</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 14:10:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, I thought of it randomly one time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 14:13:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no. Haha at least he tried it I guess, my family don #8217;t believe me when I say how good it is. I think it #8217;s because it #8217;s technically  #8220;sci fi #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 14:14:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love how associating those sayings with horse racing instantly made them make sense to me. I #8217;ve been saying them my whole life literally having no idea what they meant</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 14:20:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, I never really thought of that but it makes a lot of sense. Reminds me of how deaf toddlers sign to themselves at night just like a typical child would talk themselves to sleep : #8217;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 14:23:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ewwww</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 14:24:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate to be the one to inform you but that is not in fact true</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 14:24:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine are ok</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 14:45:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 23:40:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is, it #8217;s part of their speech development. Called  #8220;practicing #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 23:49:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>that was the joke :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 01:57:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah yes. Also why ADHD drugs are literally just stimulants</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 03:08:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah the most widely used ones are stimulants :) haha I love that story about the guy who didn #8217;t know he had ADHD, went to a party and took some Adderall and ended up feeling super calm for the rest of the night</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[20/F] loss of breath if I lay down too quickly?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 10:16:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Title pretty much explains it but basically, I #8217;ve noticed that lately if I lay down too quickly, I lose my breath. The feeling is hard to explain but it makes me cough, and is really uncomfortable. I #8217;m not too fit at the moment (I don #8217;t exercise much at all aside from walking a fair bit) but I eat pretty healthy and am a healthy weight (140 pounds- I #8217;m about 5 #8217;4 #8221;). Anyone have any idea what this could be caused by? I have anxiety but have only noticed this in the last month or so. I also had multiple ECG #8217;s and a chest X-ray about a year ago which was all clear.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:21:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not me, but my dad drank a litre of Borax cleaning solution stuff that was made up in the fridge. He thought it was cordial.. and sculled it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 06:25:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am from rural Australia and attended a pretty small high school, so we occasionally joined up with other schools in the area for educational days of different sorts. All up there was only about a couple hundred of us at these things. One time we had a driving education day at a school about an hour from my hometown. There was a lady there from another nearby town who spoke to us about a car accident she was in a few years ago, and as a result had minor brain damage and motor impairments. Fast forward about a year, and we hear news that this woman was murdered by her husband, along with her three kids (all very young). Her husband had been suffering depression (very prominent in farming districts) and had come home from work one day, and shot her and his kids with a shot gun before killing him self. Really affected me because of what she had already went through, and the fact that young children were involved. Was very significant because nothing like that really happens where I live. Here #8217;s a news article for anyone interested: http://mobile.abc.net.au/news/2015-10-06/inquest-into-hunt-family-murder-suicide-begins-in-nsw/6823866</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Serious] Have you ever had an experience where you remember dying but didn #8217;t? What was it?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 03:56:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 04:21:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s really cool, weird how it #8217;s so rare to dream of being a ghost</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is your favourite conspiracy related documentary?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 04:39:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What #8217;s the best 25 words or less answer you #8217;ve heard/come up with?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 07:45:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the dumbest thing you #8217;ve done while drunk?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 10:35:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 12:04:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is 100% me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 12:04:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha, what better selection?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 12:04:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aw thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 12:07:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m glad you stopped</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 12:07:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 12:08:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>One time my grandpa tried ordering drive thru by talking to a bin. He was sober though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 04:03:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just not getting sick of the other persons presence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What #8217;s your scariest paranormal experience?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 06:03:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 06:08:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please explain</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anyone ever experience really sharp hearing for a few seconds?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 11:08:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>So a couple of times now I #8217;ve been doing something, and suddenly my hearing just feels super sharp and everything is louder, and then it goes back to normal. Both times included my boyfriend, the first time he was in the lounge room (like 5 metres away from me) and he said something, and it sounded like he was standing right behind me. It just happened again earlier when he was in the bedroom gaming and said something (he did raise his voice a little) but it felt like he was literally standing right next to me talking in my ear. It definitely feels different to just listening to loud noises normally, it #8217;s just a really weird sensation and I #8217;m wondering if anyone else experiences the same thing or if my brain is just weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 12:09:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s actually really weird you said that because lately caffeine has suddenly stopped having an effect on me (I normally got anxious and a bit shaky after just one cup of coffee). So maybe it #8217;s affecting me in other ways like this now.. I did just have a can of Pepsi before it happened- weird. Love the account btw, it sounds totally accurate in my opinion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What was your best online purchase?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 12:21:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 12:59:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 01:39:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope :( I think it #8217;s vanished off the planet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Should I buy a Samsung A5 or is there better value for money smartphones out there?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 07:19:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 09:10:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was looking at those, but they #8217;re pretty hard to find in Australia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 14:25:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah well it #8217;s for my Mum and she actually doesn #8217;t really care about the camera quality (she takes her DSLR everywhere) so I was thinking it would be hopefully worth the money. Is there anything else you don #8217;t like about it? Ah okay, I actually wasn #8217;t too sure of the price of the OnePlus, her price range was up to $500 so it would be pushing it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 14:29:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes a couple, it seems like the price is a bit too much though (it #8217;s for my Mum and her price limit was around $500)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 14:30:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also do you mind me asking where you bought the A5 for that price? Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 21:33:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s okay, thanks for your help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 21:43:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for your help :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 06:11:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I even sifted through every single book on Goodreads with the words party, sleepover and multiple female names in its title. No luck :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 04:55:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn I would #8217;ve loved this as a kid. I had to use sticks as wands</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 11:48:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Forcing my computer to shut down until it stops whirring is strangely satisfying to me. Does that make me a psychopath?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 11:48:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Parallel universes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 12:53:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love stories about how people have memories of being killed/dying in the past, but nothing really happened. I have my own similar story which also makes it that much more interesting for me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 13:09:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure :) Once when I was about 4, my mum and I were on a bush walk just outside of town and we come across a brown snake (very deadly). I had a backpack on at the time, and had placed it on the ground for some reason just before we spotted the snake. Next I remember clear as anything walking up to the snake, and petting it on the head. At the same time I remember Mum jumping behind a nearby rock, yelling at me to get away from the snake whilst trying to reach my backpack with a stick. After I pet the snake a few times, I turned around calmly and went back to Mum behind the rock. I #8217;d believed this my whole life until recently when I mentioned it to Mum. She said that she remembers everything exactly the same as me, except I never touched the snake. I just went straight behind the rock with her. So basically I have a vivid memory of petting a deadly snake in the wild (literally so out of character for me as well- I hated reptiles although I was a bit disobedient) when I actually didn #8217;t. Could be a false memory, but I dunno. The fact that it #8217;s so close to mums story besides that detail is what weirded me out the most</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 13:15:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>It really is! No problem :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Location of the kidneys has changed</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 01:23:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I remember the kidneys being lower in the back. This is such a clear memory for me because I remember going to the doctors, and having her check my kidneys by tapping my lower back, in the love handles area (lower outer sides). Now the kidneys are in the middle/upper back area, closer to the midline. This is so weird for my because I remember it so clearly. I remember people saying how dangerous it was to get hit in that exact love handles area because it could damage your kidneys. Anyone else remember or am I crazy?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 02:09:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually just done a search on this sub and it seems a lot of other people remember this too. Crazy... I was already a believer for the most part but this has secured it for me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 03:00:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg yes the small intensities were never like that! Sadly I don #8217;t remember much about the liver, never really knew much about it til I started uni (was big then).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 03:55:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you serious?! That #8217;s insane</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 03:56:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah this changed over a year ago for me too, I can #8217;t remember exactly when. Definitely a while ago though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 07:55:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow! Do you remember when you studied this? Literally the only explanation for this aside from an ME is that everybody who remembers it the way I do has somehow been taught wrong/learnt wrong. And I find this WAY harder to believe when people who have actually studied it remember it this way too. It #8217;s just crazy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 07:56:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, what do you mean? Would it not be extremely fast evolution?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 08:56:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my all time favourites! Awesome job</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 23:53:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>This makes the most sense to me. Some diagrams I #8217;ve seen are more like where I remember the kidneys, and some are just completely different. Thanks for your reply! I wonder why so many diagrams are inaccurate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 03:34:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, that #8217;s really strange. Thanks for sharing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 05:05:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>She always runs off with other families at the dog park :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 05:07:07</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;He doesn #8217;t even exist in me #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the funniest photo on the internet?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 08:32:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 08:41:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You guys suck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What exactly is residue?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 13:13:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can somebody please explain what exactly residue is and the theories for why/how it occurs? I don #8217;t really understand why its a thing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 09:28:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>About a year ago, there was a Donut King app that gave you free donuts from playing some platform game. How it worked was you built up points from playing, and could redeem these every 24 hours. After a couple of practices (it was super easy to get points), I found the exact hour that the vouchers were refreshed, and managed to get the best possible voucher every day (it was first in best dressed). Ate wayyy too many donuts through those months.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When was a time your gut feeling was correct, but not in the way you expected?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 09:35:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 09:50:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, well that definitely explains the weird vibes. Is your friend okay?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 10:34:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Far out, sounds like a very unfortunate situation</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 12:42:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that was a rollercoaster</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 00:01:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg this reminds me of when I was a kid. We would play  #8220;the Lion game #8221; where my sister and I would pretend to be lions in a zoo and Mum would feed us while narrating everything like she was a zookeeper. It was as weird and funny as it sounds</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 13:08:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell Bruce I love him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 04:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Quokka #8217;s are only found on a tiny island off the coast of Perth, Australia and in some zoos in Aus. There was a trend a few years ago where people would take selfies with them, you may have seen a couple and not realised they were quokkas. E.g. [some of these](https://news.nationalgeographic.com/news/2015/03/150306-quokkas-selfies-animals-science-photography-australia/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dat feeling.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 14:03:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>She had a feather stuck in her nose (and a mini tongue blep for good measure)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 14:08:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 08:55:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gorgeous!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Took a picture of my dog with the flash on... Got Cyclops instead.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 13:09:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 13:18:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I COULDNT THINK OF ANYTHING ELSE WITH LASER EYES</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It was only a matter of time..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 05:00:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My first personal ME</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 06:30:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>So recently I experienced my first personal ME.. or  #8220;false memory #8221;, I really don #8217;t know. I was talking to my boyfriend about how we were disciplined as children. I said that I was smacked a few times as a kid, but he said he was never smacked because all his dad had to do was yell at him and he would start balling his eyes out (lol). However, I have a superrr clear memory of him telling me a story about how his Pop smacked him once. I remember him saying he was staying with his Pop, and he was being naughty so he smacked him, but once he realised he had made him cry he felt horrible and apologised profusely. Except this never happened, at all. We ended up getting into an argument over this because I was basically in shock that it never happened and he was annoyed that I kept telling him something he had said, when it never even happened to him. So yeah, that was my first (potential) ME. I have had some false memories before (or maybe other ME #8217;s- who knows) so it could be rubbish. Anyone experienced anything similar?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Serious] What's something that has happened to you that you can't explain with logic?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 07:15:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 07:19:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, were they wearing the same thing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 07:20:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which ones affected you the most?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 07:23:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could it have been a hoax or is there no trace of it/everyone is denying it now?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 07:24:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's crazy. Were you close with the friend who had the accident?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 07:26:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like this is a lie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 07:28:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>That guy who was obsessed with quantum immortality and drove himself insane over it.. More sad than weird though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 07:29:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please elaborate!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 07:31:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good point. I've always found it strange how we base everything off of our own little world.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 07:44:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow. That #8217;s an incredible story but very sad nonetheless. Thank you for sharing :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 07:44:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you nope right out of there?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 07:50:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 03:50:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Weird.. I only discovered the original thread this morning and now this pops up. So I guess I must ask a question now! What is the best thing about being 4?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 04:49:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is very true. Haha thanks for the reply :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 14:11:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s always been with  #8220;people #8221; for me. I used to sing this song all the time a few years ago when I learnt piano/singing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 06:12:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally me these last few weeks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 06:07:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like you could be experiencing depersonalisation. It used to happen to me a lot, but hasn #8217;t for a few years now. It #8217;s a sign of anxiety/depression and probably other mental illnesses if you suffer from any. Always freaked me out when it happened it #8217;s such a weird feeling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Has anyone else experienced strange/glitchy behaviours in others?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 07:43:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something happened today in class which freaked me out. It could be nothing but it just felt weird, like kind of  #8220;off #8221; in a sense. I was sitting at a table listening to my coordinator speak, and she said a sentence which I can #8217;t remember but it was along the lines of something you would say at the end of a statement (e.g  #8220;and that #8217;s how you would do it #8221; etc.). When she finished that sentence, she repeated it EXACTLY the same way. And I mean the exact same tone, intonation everything. This probably sounds like no big deal at all but it felt reaaaally weird. I actually thought my brain may have glitched out for a second because of how unnatural it sounded. An important note to add is that my teacher is a speech pathologist, and an excellent communicator. She always speaks fluently and even though this would be weird if it happened in any circumstance, it #8217;s super weird that it happened with her. Also, she didn #8217;t acknowledge it, stumble on her words or anything else that would signify she  #8220;messed up #8221; her speaking if that makes sense. It #8217;s hard to explain but it just sounded wrong. Anyone else have a similar experience or know why this would have happened?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 05:56:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>It honestly felt like this, which is even scarier than my teacher being a robot haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 15:16:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, a speech pathologist can help with this. There are a lot of reasons your son could be talking so loud, an SP would be able to do some assessments and figure out the cause and go from there. It could be something as simple as an attention thing, or he could have a sensory processing issue (again- nothing you can determine without a formal assessment). There are a lot more causes aside from just poor hearing. So I would personally recommend it, even if it #8217;s just to get a better idea of what #8217;s going on. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 00:01:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes voice therapy would be suitable but any clinic that works with children would also be able to help. Most paediatric SP #8217;s have a very wide practice area (unless stated otherwise) and this would be something they come across often. Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 13:23:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s getting a bit ridiculous  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 13:41:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mum came into my room to get me to help her turn off her iPod. Apparently I sat up, turned it off and then rolled over. I was asleep the whole time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[TOMT] [boardgame/craft] Winnie the Pooh cardboard cutout from the early 2000 #8217;s</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 16:13:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is definitely going to be a long shot, but I remember a Winnie the Pooh cardboard cutout scene that my grandpa put together for me when I was about 4. I remember it was a scene from Winnie the Pooh, with 3D layers if that makes sense.. like the cardboard was layered to look 3D. There were also mini cutouts of the characters which makes me think it was some kind of board game (it is not the friends of the forest game). I remember the big iconic tree and a bridge really clearly. I really want to find it online but it #8217;s proving very difficult when I can #8217;t even remember what it was, lol. Anyone else remember something similar? (I am also from Australia so it may not have been a thing overseas) Edit: Solved! It was a book titled  #8220;Winnie the Pooh and the hundred acre wood press out book #8221;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 13:44:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>[The Lion King: Opening in Antarctica in 2019](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=M6TDQq5eywg) It was very convincing- had me for the first 30 seconds ha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 13:46:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would probably go to the hospital.. that #8217;s not normal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 13:47:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>That blinker fluid was a thing :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 13:48:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha this sounds familiar, my mum, grandparents and younger siblings followed me to every damn school excursion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 13:54:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Use it to better yourself. No one is perfect, but you have an advantage now because you know where to improve.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is your go-to awkward moment to think of when you can #8217;t sleep?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 14:00:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 14:03:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well do you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 14:03:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What food did you think you would love, but once you tried it you actually hated it?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 14:19:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 14:21:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m with you on the fudge</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 14:22:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds atrocious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 14:28:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>$25 worth of fuel, when they don #8217;t have a car</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 14:31:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Overly attached girlfriend</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 14:32:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hated sushi at first but now I love it, turns out it was just really shitty sushi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 14:35:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you like mango smoothies?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 14:39:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg thank you. I #8217;ve never tried them but my dad (who also loves all seafood- aside from the ones he #8217;s allergic to) told me they taste like snot and I #8217;ve never understood the hype since.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 15:34:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>You haven #8217;t tried my mums lemon cheesecake- it #8217;s known for being the perfect level of sweetness so it doesn #8217;t turn sickly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 09:54:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do I see sheets of plastic in your future?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 11:48:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You probably hear this a lot, but it's important to study smarter, not harder. In my first years of uni I would spend hours writing pages and pages of copied notes just to try and retain the information long enough to pass an exam, but now I find it so much easier and more effective studying other ways. For example, I try to figure out exactly what I need to know, and then work out how much of this I already know and how much I don't. Once I figure out what I don't know, I mentally create questions to find answers to in my own way so I'll actually fully learn and understand the answer. It's a good idea to use a lot of resources (e.g. textbooks by professionals in your field alongside your uni lectures/notes and trustworthy websites/articles) to get a deeper understanding of the content and see different perspectives. Basically the thing that's made the biggest difference for me is just not writing down literally everything (including things I already know and things I don't fully understand) and just focusing on what I don't know. If there's things you can't figure out, make a note of it and ask someone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 15:07:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I guess it does, I never really thought of it that way. Personally I don #8217;t seperate things into categories on paper but it would definitely line up with how I work mentally. I #8217;m just not really that organised ha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 15:15:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>For some reason I #8217;ve always remembered a dream I had as a kid that scared the shit out of me. I was lost in an Egyptian temple of some kind, and I couldn #8217;t find my parents or siblings. After looking for what felt like hours I finally found them, but they were all standing in a line wearing these creepy ass Egyptian masks. I was trying to talk to them but they just kept staring at me and not moving. Not sure what triggered that dream but it really stuck with me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 15:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>He was pretty much just the worst kind of person. Super judgemental, belittling and entitled, I don #8217;t think he ever said a nice thing to anybody. He still lives in our hometown and has never left.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 15:28:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>This. How is it still going?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 15:35:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>When people spell  #8220;definitely #8221; as defiantly, definately or any of the other 10000 ways they do</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 15:37:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I still love safe and sound.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 15:50:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>The original  #8220;IT #8221;. I would probably scream and pass out but also be very confused</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 15:54:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>You might appreciate this list: https://www.reddit.com/r/Retconned/comments/6spczm/what_seemingly_crazy_wormholes_has_retconned/?st=JFMKXZQJ amp;sh=cf428383 A lot of interesting things I hadn #8217;t thought of learning about before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 09:29:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>A burrito. Literally any burrito. If it's somewhat burrito shaped I will eat it. I love burritos</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 09:40:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have two older half brothers and a younger full brother and sister. I get along great with all of them, but hardly get to see my older brothers so I'm not close with them at all. I guess I'm pretty lucky that I have good siblings but I do wish I could see my brothers (and nieces and nephew) more often.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 10:50:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure if anyone #8217;s posted it yet but I couldn #8217;t leave it out.. [How to destroy the celebration with a trumpet ](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=QxnY2SWZTvk)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 10:57:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>When the guy gets all beaten up from doing something heroic, and friend who happens to be female patches them up. Cue sex scene</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 11:00:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a kid I loved The Misadventures of Amy Everhart. I #8217;ve never met a single person who #8217;s seen this movie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 06:31:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eh, not sure if I could stomach dogs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 06:37:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Australians all eat ostriches For we are young and free</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 06:39:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was eating dinner with my family and Mum had cooked a duck. I got a thigh piece and had just finished it, when I saw a bit of meat I missed. If anyone wants to know what a duck testicle tastes like I #8217;m your gal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:58:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brings back memories of riding on the back of Dad #8217;s ute and driving around the farm pulling these out of the ground.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 14:41:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Woooouldnt it be nice if the world was paper You could wipe your ass on the next door neighbour</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 01:46:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>The lion and the bear from Telletubbies. That shit still scares me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 15:42:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>May have been some kind of seizure? Scary nonetheless</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Weird glitch or trick of the eye/mind</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 05:40:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>So earlier today I was getting changed, and when I was changing pants I looked down at my feet. For a second I could #8217;ve sworn my sock had a hole in it, and I could see two of my toes poking out. I was just about to change my sock when I looked again and there was no hole.. literally just a normal sock. So either I experienced a glitch or my brain expected to see a hole for some reason and tricked myself into seeing it. Was creepy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I think my Dad is considering divorcing my alcoholic mother</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 09:35:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had this bomb dropped on me today. If my mother doesn #8217;t sort out her drinking, my dad told me he might leave her. He #8217;s literally the only thing stopping her from drinking herself to death as well.. I guess I just need to vent but I also think some advice would help at the moment. I don #8217;t know what to do. I feel like because of how close I am with my mum and my knowledge of therapy I need to be the one to help her stop but I don #8217;t know if I can handle that level of responsibility. My dad #8217;s keeping secrets from her (mainly financial stuff) so basically their marriage is already in turmoil. He said he keeps secrets from her so she doesn #8217;t find out what he has and run away with his money to feed her addiction. What do I do?! I can #8217;t just sit here and watch it all turn to shit but I can #8217;t force things to change either. My family is one of the only stable things in my life so having this tear it apart would destroy me, not to mention my younger siblings. Ugh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 13:39:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t feel like it but thank you :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 14:00:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think so, and yeah I do. Such a trippy thought that your brain can do that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 14:52:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, this made a lot of sense. Thank you for this I honestly don #8217;t know if I can help her, at least not at this point in my life. I can barely handle my own problems and I can #8217;t think of a way I could help her without it taking over my life. She #8217;s tried getting help, and has definitely improved but she said herself that she can #8217;t find enough motivation to quit. Even destroying our family isn #8217;t enough for her, I really don #8217;t know what I could even do. What you said about being hyper-responsible resonated so deeply with me.. that is literally me to a T. Thanks again, you helped me feel a bit less hopeless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 14:55:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you. Yes, it #8217;s extremely hard to stop feeling like I need to take control of everything. I also think seeing my dad so helpless adds to that feeling. I truly just don #8217;t know what I could do</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 14:57:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Catching up on uni work.. student lyf</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 15:15:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes that is very true. Thanks for your reply. I haven #8217;t had any therapy, I don #8217;t know if I could to be honest.. it would be a huge step for me but feels impossible with my anxiety the way it is. I #8217;ll put some more thought into it. Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 05:11:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>As someone with an alcoholic parent, either take some serious action around her drinking ASAP or consider ending the relationship. The sex toy is just the beginning of many more issues, eventually it #8217;ll take a huge toll on you and your children (who are always first priority). Alcoholism really isn #8217;t something to take lightly, it ruins relationships and families.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If birthmarks are a sign of how we died in a past life, how did you die?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 07:09:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 07:12:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think either option is totally plausible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 07:17:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe you were impaled by a post</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 10:27:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I also got stabbed in my groin area</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 15:35:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>She is literally the queen of bridges</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 15:59:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>This reminds me of what happened to me about a year ago. I threw out an empty margarine container and found it in the fridge again the next day. I #8217;m certain it was the same one as well. It didn #8217;t end up being any use though, I just threw it out again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to develop a healthy relationship with alcohol?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 12:01:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>After all the crap that I #8217;ve been through as a result of alcohol I #8217;m finding it hard to enjoy drinking at all. Basically the biggest problems for me (which I #8217;m sure many of you can relate to) are worrying about becoming dependent myself and how much just being around alcohol reminds me of everything. I would love to go and have a few drinks without the shitty feelings that go along with it. Does it ever go away? Are there any tips to get over it or am I better off just staying away from alcohol all together? I would love to hear your experiences/opinions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 14:35:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Being the smartest person in the room</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 14:40:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's so sad, but if it makes you feel any better a lot of people just get their pets put down behind their kids' backs. Not saying what your mum done was right at all but at least your kitty still had a life :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 06:43:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I didn #8217;t necessarily mean me, I thought it was a clever response :( Everyone #8217;s been the smartest person in the room at one point in their life, it feels good but isn #8217;t good for you because you can #8217;t learn anything new.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 09:10:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m literally just going off the saying  #8220;if you #8217;re the smartest person in the room, you #8217;re in the wrong room #8221;. You would learn a lot more around people smarter than you. So yes, of course they can teach you things, but you #8217;d learn more if they were smarter than you. Still, I didn #8217;t mean to offend literally everybody I just thought it was a clever response.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 07:51:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, it honestly was like my brain just had to take a minute to figure out what sock I was wearing.. because I do have socks with holes in them exactly like what I saw.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 07:54:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is no longer mildly infuriating, this is maximum level need to go and take a 20 minute breather infuriating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 08:13:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m really good at telling how much time has passed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 09:46:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Zootopia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 14:17:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>[My pup](https://m.imgur.com/gallery/4wmc34I) after suffering the exact same fate..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 16:07:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well now I will</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 11:17:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scoobies :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 07:29:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sportacus from Lazy Town. I think it was the accent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 02:21:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you my Mum..? She done this once while jokingly showing off to my dad jumping over the piles... they hadn #8217;t known each other long and she had to get back into his truck and drive home</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 02:29:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was about 10, my family went to this field day thing at a school where you could enter mini competitions and play games. I decided to go in the sack race with a heap of other kids. Half way through the race, I felt my pants fall down under the sack. Flash forward about 30 seconds and the race is over, and everyone is giving their sacks back but I can #8217;t so I hop back to my family, tears streaming down my face, repeatedly sobbing  #8220;I #8217;M NOT TAKING IT OFF #8221; (I was a sensitive kid). Mum ended up tying my pants up with bailing twine which was almost as embarrassing as them falling down in the first place.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Arnott #8217;s Tim tam are running a promotion with a genie where you have to download the app  #8220;Shazam #8221;. Weird coincidence?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 09:33:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 15:07:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought so too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 14:26:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Came here to say this. Definitely the most beautiful game I #8217;ve come across!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 14:36:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>My name is Clare and every budgie I #8217;ve met hates me :( maybe it #8217;s in the name</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 12:08:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vaccines. Do. Not. Cause. Autism.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 09:51:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 15:56:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>By putting effort into finding and making healthy food I actually really wanted to eat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 14:43:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Learn how to compromise and see things from the other persons' perspective. It can be hard sometimes but a little empathy goes a long way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 14:49:07</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Oh no the plague has got me #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why did you go to the ER?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 14:58:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 15:04:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>How did you manage that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 15:05:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>This happened to my partner also, very scary experience :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 15:05:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>How is your heart now?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 15:06:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds awful.. what was wrong?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 15:07:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no, I hope it #8217;s nothing to worry about. Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 15:09:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Asthma? That #8217;s terrifying, I #8217;m glad you pulled through</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 15:11:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I hope it doesn #8217;t happen again, good luck to you :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 15:13:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree, a lot of people treat it like it #8217;s nothing. I #8217;ve had a couple before but none serious enough/for long enough to go to the hospital. I hope you don #8217;t have to go through anymore!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 15:15:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s unlucky! Did you need stitches? I cut my hand once as a kid on a can of beetroot ha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 15:15:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s good news, I hope it stays good for you! No problem :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 16:02:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow that #8217;s crazy. You were lucky to survive!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 16:03:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s terrible :( I hope you #8217;re doing better now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 16:04:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow you #8217;ve had an eventful time! Hopefully you don #8217;t have too many more visits.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 16:04:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can never be too careful imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 16:06:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ouch!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 16:24:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was she okay?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Looking to join a fashion house to win rallies</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 16:20:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m level 22 and have 1.3mil closet value, I #8217;d like to finally join a fashion house to win some rallies but preferably with no bitchiness/people who take the game too seriously. I #8217;d love to hear your suggestions :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 16:29:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much for mentioning it I got like 5000 diamonds  #10084; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 16:37:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow that #8217;s awesome! I also got about 20k a few months ago, I just always forget to check when it #8217;s on  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 16:40:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will do, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 13:26:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you do fierce rallies? :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 14:04:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably fairy bread</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I love this colour! Does anyone know what it might be called?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 17:23:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 05:52:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for your help guys!  #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 17:17:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Poop probably</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 17:26:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometimes the reason is that there is no reason</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 13:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Disappeared for hours a day to kill cats and assaulted someone at the local park.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 14:43:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 23:32:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>50% of the reason he #8217;s no longer my neighbour</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 23:33:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s terrible :( nah I #8217;m in Australia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 00:38:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>There was a gorgeous ragdoll cat just up the street from us who was always wandering around outside it #8217;s house, it really worried me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 06:04:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t for sure. Someone posted a photo of him in a fb group in the scrub, holding a dead cat and looking guilty as hell. I assumed it was stray/feral because of where he was in the picture.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 06:11:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this an actual question or an inside joke I don #8217;t get? Haha. No that wasn #8217;t his name though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 06:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not that I know of but he did brag about stabbing someone with a pen in a psych ward and my dog hated him, so probably.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 06:20:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>This guy wasn #8217;t doing it for the greater good. No guns here, so he must have been killing them in a much more sinister way (also considering the fact he was a crazy meth head and probably also a psychopath).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 07:44:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s awesome! He #8217;s very talented</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 10:22:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh I see. Thanks for explaining!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 16:20:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally any Facebook group admin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 09:22:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I threw out an empty tub of margarine and it reappeared in the fridge the next day.. they could #8217;ve at least filled it up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DAE eyes water when talking in uncomfortable/personal situations?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 10:47:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t know why this happens to me but it has for as long as I can remember. Basically, if I #8217;m talking to someone I #8217;m not really comfortable with and I have to talk about something personal or state my opinion, my eyes water.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 12:44:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah pretty much, like I know I would never actually cry in that situation but it #8217;s like my subconscious wants to or something. It doesn #8217;t happen when I #8217;m angry either, only happy or neutral. So weird</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Laza pup</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 06:31:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 10:12:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just set 5 alarms, gotta be on the safe side</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>These synchronicities are getting ridiculous</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 12:14:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every single time (give or take a very small amount) I #8217;ve checked a clock in the last week it #8217;s been :11 minutes. This is beyond a coincidence.. I #8217;m not sure what to think. Anyone have any theories?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 12:58:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems like a strong theory  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 14:45:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought this too, the first couple of times. But it #8217;s got to the point where I #8217;ve been taking note every time I check a clock because of how ridiculous it is, it really doesn #8217;t feel like that #8217;s the cause. Also, I have noticed a couple of times when it has been a different time and I #8217;ve realised this, so I must be doing it consciously. So weird</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 16:25:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dad used to make me put my phone on the table before bed every night, he was really serious about it. One night, I took my phone case off my phone and put it on the table instead of my phone. I never got caught (and felt like such a rebel).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 16:30:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to, but I #8217;m scared to because I get dizzy and anxious all the time. Also, driving into the city is a pain in the ass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 02:38:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll take anything over another Terani Couture dress</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 12:26:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>That our dad #8217;s friend who worked as a mall Santa would eat the kids that sat on his lap. I used to go and hide in my room every time he came to visit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 12:45:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not a stutterer but a speech path student. It annoyed me when I learnt that teachers often assume their students who stutter aren #8217;t as intelligent as the other students. It really shows the lack of speech related info that teachers get during their training.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 13:48:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can #8217;t imagine how frustrating it must be.. Stuttering is an area that still needs so much more awareness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 15:40:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>That smell got stuck in my nose for days the first time I smelt it, so gross</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 16:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember staring at her picture in art class wondering why she was famous for her smile, when she clearly wasn #8217;t even smiling. Definitely looks like a smile to me now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 14:17:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>So how do you know you're following the right "version" of God?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 14:20:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Football</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 14:34:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too. I remember watching her guest star on the Brady Bunch when I was about 10 (this was only in 2006-2007) and feeling sad because she was dead not long after filming. I'm not sure why I would have assumed she died young if nobody ever mentioned it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 15:22:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't sacrifice your own (and your sister's) mental well being for anybody. If you don't feel comfortable/like you can handle having her in your life, it's really not worth it. I imagine she probably didn't put your needs before her own when it mattered (or else she would still be with you) so don't feel obliged to do it for her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 15:38:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think a good method would be to consider what caused your own mental health problems, and then figure out what could have helped prevent it/what others could have done to help you. I know that for me, my parents were pretty distant (amongst other things) and if I was closer to them and felt comfortable talking to them it would have helped immensely. I think the most important thing is to be supportive and patient, and just always be mindful of how things (even if they seem insignificant to you) could affect them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 16:07:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sticky date pudding</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I chipped my tooth. I would love some advice on my options!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 16:06:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Earlier tonight I was eating dinner and chipped my tooth on the fork. I #8217;ve uploaded a pic [here.](http://imgur.com/jEALnYz) I asked my friend who also chipped her tooth and she said her dentist just shaved hers down. Is this something all dentists will do? And if not, what other options would be more practical? (I don #8217;t really mind the cosmetic side of things, it #8217;s on the side of my tooth so not very noticeable). It #8217;s just pretty sharp and really annoying my tongue/mouth. I thought I #8217;d post here just to see if I could get some more info before contacting a local dentist. Thank you in advance! P.s. sorry for the crappy photo quality, my phone camera is below average.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 16:21:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the help :) Are all of these options able to be done in one day? Also, I have health insurance so not too worried about cost but if I have to go back to get it fixed every few years or so it would be a bit of a pain.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 16:55:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m hoping that #8217;s all I need. I #8217;m open to a filling though if that #8217;s what #8217;s offered to me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 02:18:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good point, I can #8217;t seem to find anything in my insurance that would cover a filling either</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[TOMT] [MOVIE] A romantic comedy about a woman who goes jogging and does photography with a group of people</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 16:50:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>My sister and I are trying to remember a movie we watched together (most likely a romantic comedy) about a man who meets a woman in an empty bar where she is singing. After this, they meet up again somehow and she tells him that she jogs with a group of people and they take photos at the same time. Like a jogging/photography group. She invites him to come with her and I'm pretty sure he can't make it for some reason, and then a heap of other stuff happens, and then he makes it up to her at the end with something big (a public proposal/new camera I can't remember). I remember a final scene of them jogging together but this may not be correct. I'd love some help it's driving me insane. Thanks in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 16:53:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes this is it thank you!! SOLVED SOLVED SOLVED</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the worst thing a family member has said about you behind your back?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 14:34:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 14:34:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel you. Dog hair here though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 14:45:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s not a problem</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 14:59:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Narwhals</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 15:18:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>But it #8217;s better if you do. It was the first Panic song I ever heard and I found it on a so fresh(?) CD that I had on my iPod shuffle. I remember listening to it on repeat the first time I flew on a plane when I was about 10 and I didn #8217;t even know who sang it.. very fond memories : #8217;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 09:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nature-y</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 14:34:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess you can #8217;t really blame them, considering a field of corn is probably the closest thing they #8217;ve seen to a vagina.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 03:59:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>11</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 15:18:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was about 10, the next door neighbours granddaughter came over to visit and decided to basically trash my bedroom. She sprayed all of my perfume everywhere until the bottle was empty, threw an exercise ball at my dressing table, and spread my stuff everywhere all over the floor. I did not let her in my room again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 16:02:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mum always responds to me :) My dad knows how to text but is too stubborn to admit it so will only read texts I send him :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 16:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can never be them, so why be hung up on trying to be. Also, everyone has their own struggles. Someone might seem perfect but behind closed doors their life may be a total mess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 16:43:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Egg- chicken period</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A minion fire pit I found for sale...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 07:51:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 11:49:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember being breastfed and being annoyed at the fact I wasn #8217;t able to talk to my mum. It #8217;s such an early memory that logic tells me it must be a dream but it #8217;s so clear.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 11:50:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why I don #8217;t tell many people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 14:15:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rockmelon (cantaloupe for you Americans)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What did you dream that ended up happening?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 14:22:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 14:49:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow that #8217;s creepy  #128556;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 15:32:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I #8217;d heard about this but wasn #8217;t sure what it was called. First time it #8217;s ever happened to me, definitely an odd sensation</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 03:28:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s a message I can get behind</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Some residue I found on the Seek job app. Surely people google quotes before using them?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 07:18:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 14:12:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>No it #8217;s not, it #8217;s  #8220;we #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 14:18:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never knew the quote was said in real life, sorry I thought you meant in the movie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 14:27:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s strange.. makes it seem like it may have just been misquoted too many times</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 15:03:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>These things never go well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Serious] What is your paranormal experience?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 15:17:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 15:19:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/CongratsLikeImFive also fits this description :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 15:28:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s so strange I #8217;ve never heard of that happening before. Sounds like a super weird feeling</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 08:07:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, that #8217;s an incredible experience. Definitely helps keep your mind open. Thank you for sharing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What movie should everyone watch in their lifetime?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 17:22:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 12:06:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>After struggling through my first day of a new placement this made me happy.  #10084; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So, I figured out why my new doona set was so cheap.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 14:49:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 01:36:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>There really is a subreddit for everything</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 01:31:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! She #8217;s very fluffy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 15:18:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only real answer to this question</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is something you #8217;ve experienced that you still can #8217;t believe/explain to this day?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 15:39:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The only creepy experience that has stuck with me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 13:12:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve had a few weird experiences in my life, but this one definitely gives me the worst feeling. I #8217;ve been living in the unit I #8217;m currently living in for about 8 months now. About 2-3 months after I moved in, I had a weird experience during the night. I was asleep and dreaming that the unit was haunted, and the ghost was torturing me (I can #8217;t remember exactly how). I remember feeling paralysed lying on the floor in my living room, and the front door was banging while the ghost was talking to me- I just remember screaming and feeling really scared before I woke up. I have sleep paralysis sometimes and that night I woke up feeling paralysed, and I could hear the door banging, which happens sometimes when it #8217;s really windy outside. My first thought was that obviously the sound of the door in real life had transferred to my dream. Except.. there was literally no wind at all. There are about 4 trees directly outside my bedroom window that I can always hear when it #8217;s windy because they #8217;re so close, but it was dead silent. I was laying there for about 20 minutes listening to the door before it stopped. Fair to say it took me a few hours to go back to sleep that night.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 13:17:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scared probably</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What YouTube video makes you laugh hysterically every time you watch it?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 13:19:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 13:20:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Use sulphate free shampoo and conditioner. Don #8217;t wash your hair more than 2-3 times a week</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 13:23:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha I love this one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 13:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I #8217;ll never hear this song the same way again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 13:29:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would try sulphate free and see if it helps, it could also be your diet though. Also don #8217;t put conditioner on your scalp, just the pony tail part of your hair. Good luck! Long hair can be stressful to say the least</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 13:30:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also- get a tangle teezer! I can #8217;t express in words how amazing they are</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 13:33:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>For anyone wondering, mine is [Harry Potter written by an AI.](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=6rEkKWXCcR4) You won #8217;t regret watching the whole thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 13:33:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>No problem :) happy to help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 13:44:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I won 8 books from a publishing company. I also won a solar panel camping set when I was about 15, from a local solar company.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 13:53:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably not the worst I #8217;ve seen, but it disturbed me. A couple of weeks ago I was grocery shopping and saw an extremely obese woman and what I assume was her mother throwing things off the shelves and laughing hysterically.. while using some seriously foul language. The obese woman was pushing a pram with what looked like a 3/4 year old girl in it who looked so confused. If you can #8217;t even behave in a grocery store I can #8217;t imagine how atrocious you must be at parenting. :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 02:06:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually, you might have a point. I completely forgot but our neighbour (not entirely sure if he #8217;s a reliable source, he seems a little strange) did say that the people who used to live here were pretty crazy and they actually killed their dog here. Not sure how long they were here though, there have probably been many many others living here before them. Thank you :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 06:05:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was definitely awake when I was listening to the door, i only usually have sleep paralysis for about 30 seconds before it passes so I #8217;m pretty certain I wasn #8217;t hallucinating :|</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 02:16:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>No it #8217;s okay, I was also hoping it might have been something like that but sadly not. Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 11:31:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>But it #8217;s better if you do. I heard it on a So Fresh CD I had in my Walkman when I was about 11 so I had no idea who the band was, but I loved them instantly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 10:36:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fallout 4. I #8217;m still struggling to figure it out but I love the atmosphere</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 10:37:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Think about what you need to do before you do it. Make sure you go through every step in detail. Then when you go to do it, it #8217;s easier because it feels like you #8217;ve already done it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 10:39:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thinking about the consequences of not doing the thing. Only really works for important things though.. failing uni is bad but an unmade bed isn #8217;t going to ruin my life so I probably won #8217;t do it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 10:51:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg I came here to write this, glad there are other lemon lime lovers out there  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 11:24:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha well I #8217;m drinking one right now, sorry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DAE have a weird fantasy(?) about society falling apart and having to survive in seclusion in the wilderness?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 15:38:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure why I #8217;m drawn to this but the idea excites me and I like the idea of feeling safe in a world that #8217;s destroyed. Am I the only one?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 16:05:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha I like that, very creative. I usually just imagine that I #8217;m hidden away in the bush land somewhere away from civilisation, and have to make sure I #8217;m not found by any other people (I #8217;m an introvert if you couldn #8217;t tell) and I have to survive. I like to think that I have great survival skills, but in reality they are non existent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 14:59:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not anything by Newton Faulkner?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Having trouble thinking of a concept to use in Metaphon therapy for gliding of liquids</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 05:50:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi guys :) I #8217;m working on a uni assessment task and like the title says, I need to think of a concept to use during Metaphon phonology therapy for the process gliding of liquids. Not sure how many SLP #8217;s use/have heard of Metaphon but basically the first step is familiarising the child with a concept which represents the sounds they need to differentiate between. For example, when working on stopping of fricatives the concepts of  #8220;long #8221; and  #8220;short #8221; sounds can be used (i.e. pointing to the long or short lion tail). Or  #8220;mr noisy #8221; and  #8220;mr quiet #8221; for devoicing. I can #8217;t for the life of me think of a concept to use for gliding of liquids (for differentiating between /j/ and /l/ as well as /w/ and /r/). Has anyone used this therapy before or can help me brainstorm some ideas? Any help is appreciated! Thank you :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Some precognitive experiences my family and I have had.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 14:41:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve previously posted this elsewhere, but a couple of years ago my great grandmother passed away. About 2(?) weeks before it happened, I was with my family visiting her in the nursing home like we did every Monday. I don #8217;t really know how to describe it, but basically as soon as I stepped foot into the building I knew that I would never be coming back to visit her again. It wasn #8217;t an upsetting feeling, I just felt really calm and certain that it would be the last time I saw her. Also, the day that she passed away wasn #8217;t a Monday, but my mum and grandma (as well as my other siblings- I had just moved five hours away so I wasn #8217;t able to unfortunately) decided to go and visit her. Mum told me that she has no idea why they decided to go and see her, she had been getting sicker for a while but that day was no different to any other. They sat and talked to her for a couple of hours before she passed away surrounded by her family. One more related note- around the time that my great grandpa passed away (my great grandma #8217;s husband), my Mum swears that she woke up in the middle of the night and saw him next to her bed. She says that he told her to  #8220;look after Nim #8221; for him- which was his pet name for my great grandma. Anyway just thought I #8217;d share these, I know they all involve death but they #8217;re quite sweet and I think about them often. Individually they could probably all be chalked up to coincidence, but together they make me pretty certain of something else going on. Let me know what you think :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What random thought does your brain always resort to when you can #8217;t sleep?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 14:49:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 15:06:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can relate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 04:32:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Dad gets home from work and walks in the front door*  #8220;I have JUST. SAT. DOWN. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can someone please explain this? I #8217;m lost</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 12:32:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 12:50:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand x rays and radiation and that doctors need to be protected.. I don #8217;t get the Egypt part and how it #8217;s funny</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 12:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I understand how x-rays work. No I do not understand the joke or what it has to do with Egypt?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 12:54:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ohhhh that makes sense. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 14:03:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha no, I #8217;m just dumb</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 14:10:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I #8217;m glad someone else didn #8217;t get it, makes me feel less stupid haha. Thanks :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 14:26:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought this said horses. Was confused about what kind of stuff goes in them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 14:27:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favourite episode : #8217;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 14:30:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just watched this for the first time the other day. Made my cry too, I liked Poussey :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 14:32:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here because I don #8217;t think anyone has mentioned Claire #8217;s death on McLeod #8217;s Daughters.  #128557;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>