<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject9949</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(Spoilers Extended) If you were in charge of casting Game of Thrones, who would you cast? ps. first post, apologies if I'm using the wrong tags.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 23:56:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(Spoilers Extended) Anything that you think the show did better than the books</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-22 22:41:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's some of my suggestions: Arya being cupbearer to Tywin instead of weese. Granted it was out of character for Book Tywin, but it's the show so that irrelevant, and it made for some of the best scenes in season 2. The "It's only for life" quote by Jamie to Jon the extra scene's involving Robert in his bedroom, both with Jamie and Barristan, and with Cersei after Ned's resignation. All of Jorah and Visery's scenes together Robb's arc in Season 2 having Bronn become City Watch Commander instead of some guy who serves no purpose other than to get shanked and be tyrion and Varys' bitch. No Arstan Whitebeard Daario Naharis not looking like someone pressed "randomise" on a character creation screen Talisa being at the Red Wedding further adding to the tragedy. Anything else anyone can think of?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-22 23:36:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shit. I had the "new post" page up for ages as I was busy. fuck sake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(Spoilers Extended) How would the characters be remembered by History?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 19:27:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>What I mean is that if a Maester was doing a retelling of the events of ASOIAF in-universe, how would the characters be remembered as? Would Tyrion be remembered as a Monster? Would the incest of Jaime and Cersei be remembered? idk I'm probably explaining this terribly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(Spoilers Extended) About to read the Red Wedding for the First time.......</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 20:33:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 20:50:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>FUCKEVERYTHING.INTHESHOWITWASBADENOUGH.FUCKEVERYTHINGFUCKYEVERYTHINGFUCKEVERYTHING ps. so what was up with that imagery at the end ps. ps. FUCKEVERYTHINGEVERYTHINGFUCKEVERYTHING</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 21:38:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah it's better in the books imo, simply due to how quickly everything goes to shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 20:28:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've bought it already. Started to read it the first story but stopped and decided to finish the main series first.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-19 14:23:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just how much incest the Valyrians were doing. seriously infertility should've been a MUCH bigger issue than it has been.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 01:12:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oasis - talk tonight</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Something that bothered me about the Reyne-Tarbeck Rebellion (Spoilers Extended)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 00:51:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>What was the crowns response? has GRRM ever written anything about that? Because how exactly does Tytos explain to Jaehaerys that his son wiped out two houses? how did that conversation go?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 01:01:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wiping them out for not bending the knee seems a bit extreme. Jaehaerys isn't Maegor or Robert, he's not warlike (and when he was (Ninepenny Kings), it was justified)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-16 02:10:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi Bill Hicks, thought you were dead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-17 21:57:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Something flew from the brush to land with a soft thump in their midst, bumping and bouncing. It was round and dark and wet, with long hair that whipped about it as it rolled. When it came to rest amongst the roots of an oak, Grimtongue said, 'Rolfe the Dwarf's not so tall as he once was.'" For some reason just how nonchalant the response had me fucking dying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-19 03:35:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sure him and Satin would get along...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 22:39:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aerys and AFFC-era-Cersei both seemed to have the same logic that everyone was secretly plotting against them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 18:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was only a year after ADWD came out as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-07 12:13:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>To me the chorus will always be PETER PAWLETT BABY! PETER PAWLETT WOAAAAAAAAHHH! Cheers sheepshaggers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-13 11:54:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>/rwhitepeoplegifs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 01:24:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'LL PAINT YOU A PICTURE!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So now that the season's over. LETS THE TRANSFER SPECULATION BEGIN!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 13:13:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>*mild applause in the background* What players do your club need? Which players need to get tae fuck? reply and tell all! In my Opinion Dundee United need a new right back, another centre back (not even starting quality, just a better backup than Coll Donaldson), another Winger, a new centre midfielder who can battle for the ball, and a Mikkelsen-esque striker who can play alongside Keatings. Every single player who is out of contract next season can get tae fuck. Every. Single. One.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 14:02:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>do reckon you can hang on to McInnes? do you want to hang on to McInnes?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 14:17:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>seen the picture of him in a hibs training top on Friday? cunt couldn't even wait till the second leg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 16:28:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>apparently, he was at the Falkirk second leg with Keatings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 23:15:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>If Spittal signs for Thistle, they should put him on a 6 month deal, because the cunt only ever performs when he thinks he might get released.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 02:07:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought Cammy Bell and Mark Durnan had saved themselves from the job centre.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 03:28:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Because girls like you are the absolute worst I really tried to like you but you messed it up first" shit lyrics like that are why no one cares about them anymore</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 14:12:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>how would Hearts fans react to a former hibee playing for them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 20:30:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're gonna support Dundee then get ready to talk about Dundee United a lot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 03:32:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>DWELL ON IT NIGHTLY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scratch 21 - "Sorry Jack" from his self titled debut EP</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 02:54:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-20 10:17:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>The story so far - empty space</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Am I an idiot or just unlucky?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-21 21:40:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-25 22:58:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>DO YOU REMEMBER THE FIRST TIME? I CANT REMEMBER A WORST TIME OH DON'T YOU KNOW THAT WE'VE CHANGED SO MUCH SINCE THEN OH YEAH WE'VE GROWN I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU'RE DOING I DON'T CARE IF YA SCREW HIM JUST AS LONG AS YOU SAVE A PIECE FOR ME OH YEA-YEAH OOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-26 10:04:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>YOU - "I swear that was morse code" S.O. - "Are you sure that you're not so delirious from lack of sleep that you're beginning to imagine weird shit" YOU - "Maybe you're right. I've been talking to the unicorn about it and he thinks so" S.O. - "see? There no- wait what unicorn?" *Unicorn burst through bedroom door* UNICORN - "Sup."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-26 10:24:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have an irrational hatred of John Souttar, the cunt was a fat, lazy hair obsessed dickhead so we dropped him from the team. Then he moves to hearts and people are saying he should get a Scotland call up even though every time I've watched play for them he's shown no sign of improvement. I guess my hatred wasn't so irrational after all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Some Questions I have about Nazi Germany in 1945 and the Hitler Youth</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 15:39:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm writing a short story from the perspective of a Hitler youth member in during the Battle of Berlin, and I have a few questions: 1. How deep was the indoctrination for the members of the HY? 2. Were the nazi's still confident of victory in 1945? 3. Were the Germans still confident of victory in 1945? 4. Were the HY members treated just as badly as regular Wehrmacht by the Red Army? I'm sure there are more but this is all I can think of write now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 15:31:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/popheads is leaking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 14:10:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was very helpful. Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Wp] you're in a John Green novel, what's the moment when you realise?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 04:52:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 00:17:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hoping for the Scottish Championship next.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Discussion] anyone else ever feel sorry/guilty over what happens to one of your players?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 00:39:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's a quick example. (Quick note, I still play on FM14 due to being in the 2044/45 season by this point and still not bored somehow) So I bought a player called Davide Miranda for  #163;5m in the 35/36 season in my Save managing Hibernian. He was a decent player who could play upfront and the across the attacking midfield areas. He came off the bench for the first few games and did well enough for me to start playing him first choice. Then he broke his leg and was ruled out for 5 months. Shit. Even worse was while he was out, his ratings dropped to make him my third choice. He managed to recover in time for the cup final which we won and he came off the bench to score, so you know, good signs. So then the next season starts... and he BREAKS HIS LEG AGAIN. Luckily for me I had better players at this point but I still felt so sorry for the guy. Imagining spending 5 months recovering from a broken leg only to either a. Break the other one or b. Break the same one Eventually when He returned he just wasn't good enough so he left on loan to some Qatari league club before going there permanently. I don't know why but that really stuck with me, even though it was fake. So yeah, am I just emotionally strange, or is this a normal thing to get emotionally attached to fake footballers?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 12:09:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had something similar happen as well. Had a player called Barry Soane who was my first choice striker, but i had this younger striker called Martin Robinson coming through the ranks who was only a little worse than him, so I sold him to Arsenal for a fee I can't quite remember but I think it was about  #163;10m. He made 12 apps over 3 seasons for the cunts before being sold to Fulham, who were then relegated... he spent the rest of his career wasting away Ligue 1 for Caen. Martin Robinson would become the record goal score and appearance make for the club I manage (hibs).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 20:52:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>"165 comments" Jeezo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-09 03:40:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stanning for someone is fucking creepy. It makes you look like you're gonna kill the person and wear their skin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 06:09:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is Tankies short for something? I literally have no idea what this word means...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 06:16:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>ANYTHING FOR THE GLORIOUS MOTHERLAND</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 16:35:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hah, that guy went to my school... yeah this wasn't surprising</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cammy Bell: Kilmarnock in talks with Dundee United for goalkeeper return</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 19:04:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 19:05:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Sa8NREI_IPs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 18:39:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kilmarnock looked awful. I don't know why Lee McCulloch thinks Scott Boyd and Kirk Broadfoot will be in anyway a good partnership, there is more pace in Clint Hill's ballsack than in those two.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 04:44:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>this is one of her worst songs what the actual fuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 13:19:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol what. It's a mess, "break up every night" levels of all over the place.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 16:58:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>"?" means uncertain. Premiership 1. Celtic 2. Aberdeen? 3. Rangers? 4. St. Johnstone 5. Hibs 6. Hearts? 7. Motherwell 8. Ross County 9. Partick Thistle 10. Dundee? 11. Hamilton? 12. Kilmarnock (If Broadfoot and Boyd stay the CB partnership) Top Goalscorer - Scott Sinclair Player of the Year - Stuart Armstrong Young Player - Scott Wright (my prediction is that GMS is going to be dropped and Wright is going to come in and star on the wings for Aberdeen) Biggest Surprise - St. Johnstone to still get in Europe Scottish Cup - uhhhhhh, Aberdeen? idk depends on whether or not the Rodgers effect stays in place League Cup - Dundee United... hey I can dream can I? Championship Winners - Dundee United, Falkirk to finally go up through the play-offs League 1 winners - Ayr United League 2 winners - Stenhousemuir?? I don't really know I just think their announcer is funny.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>*inaudible screaming*</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 00:39:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 16:27:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ajax Aston Villa BSC Young Boys CA Osasuna CSKA Moscow Celtic FC Augsburg FC Krasnodar FC Sion Feyenoord Fluminense LA Galaxy Legia Warszawa Monterrey New York City FC Olympiakos PSV Eindhoven RB Leipzig Rangers Rosenborg BK Rubin Kazan SC Braga Toulouse FC Wolverhampton Wanderers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hi Reddit, meet Belle</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 05:52:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 17:21:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>can't speak for his time at Hull, but it only took about 4 months of him playing for Dundee United for most of the fanbase to realise he was too good for us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Story] - Hibernian FC Programme - Matchday 12 - Formartine United - 21st January 2048</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 04:45:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Today is a tale of both Hello's and Goodbyes for the Hibees. While 1st place Hibs welcomes second place Formartine United to Edinburgh in a scintillating top of the table clash, they will also be saying farewell to legend and Hibernian Hall of Famer Martin Robinson, as he announced his retirement from playing during the week to take a coaching role with reserves. Born in Edinburgh on the 16th of April 2012 and raised in Craigentinny as a diehard fan of the green and white of Edinburgh along with the rest of his family. He was spotted by and joined the youth academy at age 12, being handed a professional contract aged 16, foregoing the usual youth contract due to interest from clubs both down south and from Europe. He would be given his first team debut 5 months later, Starting for the club on the 25th November in a Scottish Cup fifth round home tie against Dundee, and it would only take him eighteen minutes to make his mark, latching onto a low Colin Marshall cross to score a diving header past Jamie Barclay in a game that would eventually end 3-0 with the next two goals coming quickly after, Gareth Masson putting the ball into his own net for the second in the twentieth minute before Inter loanee Adrian Aguado finished the game on the half hour mark. Despite this great start, Martin would have to wait a while before he was given another chance for the first team, his appearances were limited to substitutions with the game already pretty much over. But when he got his chance he took it once more, scoring twice in a 6-1 away win against Partick Thistle, with the others goals including another brace from Moussa Bamba, with Laurent Jacquet and Colin Marshall scoring the rest with Tommy Devlin getting the consolation for the Glasgow Jags. He would end the season with two more important goals, the opener in a 4-3 Edinburgh Derby win, as well as a goal in 2-2 draw against Celtic as Hibs secured their sixth successive Premiership. Though Robinson failed to pick up a medal for the league, his appearance from the bench in the 2-0 Scottish Cup Final win over St Mirren meant that Robinson ended his first season as a Professional footballer with a medal, the first of many. Robinson would spend the next few seasons forcing his way into the first team, successfully doing so in 2031 despite the goal scoring exploits of Barry Soane. With Martin Robinson up front, and the attacking midfield three of Fredinho, Dave Pickford and Lee Grice playing behind him, the Hibees would strike terror into the hearts of defenders across Scotland and Europe. It would only get better for Robinson when, at only the age of 22, he was named captain following the retirement of Fellow Hibernian legend Colin Marshall, many players would crumble under such pressure at such a young age, but Martin Robinson finished the season with 43 goals and 15 assists in all competitions as well as completing another domestic treble for his team. Undoubtedly his finest achievement for this club was his performances in 2038/2039 quadruple winning season. Captaining the squad that included fellow legends, such as goalkeeper Mohamed Boussaid (now retired), playmaker Paul Hutchings (Now at Bordeaux), and Left Winger Fredinho (retired), as well other greats like Leonardo Fantini, Gareth Pearson (left for West Brom, now retired) and Mariano Hue (now at Barcelona), the team would go to record victories that the fans would remember for the rest of their lives, including and 8-3 cup semi-final win over Inverness CT, a 7-5 win over Formartine United, and a 3-1 victory over German giants Borussia Dortmund in the Europa League Final. Robinson would carry on as the main man up front as he reached his early thirties, even when a young Gary Moore broke into the ranks, Martin was still scoring twenty goals a season, breaking the record for the most league goals for the club as well as the most league appearances, and would eventually outlast Moore when the much sought after star was sold to Manchester City for  #163;8 Million. It was only last season where it became clear that age was finally catching up to him, as he only scored 6 goals in 21, paling in comparison to his record of 22 in 34 the previous year. With appearances coming harder and harder to come by with the revelations of Bobby Schumacher and Matt Finnie, as well Craig Brown finally showing the ability he had teasing the Hibernian faithful he would show for so long, Martin Robinson announced he would hang up his boots aged 35 earlier in the week, with the captaincy role going to Leonardo Fantini, who was promoted from Vice Captain. All in All, Martin Robinson made 680 appearances and scored 526 goals across all competitions for Hibernian football club. During his time at the club, He would gain the following honours: The Scottish Premiership 18 times The Scottish Cup 14 times The Scottish League Cup 14 times The UEFA Europa League In terms of personal accolades: League Golden Boot 9 times The European Silver Boot The Champions League Bronze Boot Twice named Runner's Up in the Scottish Writer's Players of the year Once named 3rd place in the SFA Player of the Season Award. Martin Robinson would also be remembered well by Tartan Army as he is also the record goalscorer for Scotland, with 74 goals in 80 appearances for his Country.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[screenshot] And I still have the second leg to play!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 18:26:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 18:28:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>My tactics - http://imgur.com/gallery/3sPY9 Also the goal I scored was from a penalty that was absolutely not a penalty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 19:39:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mate I was Hibernian.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hibernian FC Programme - Matchday 12 - Formartine United - 21st January 2048</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 00:58:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Today is a tale of both Hello's and Goodbyes for the Hibees. While 1st place Hibs welcomes second place Formartine United to Edinburgh in a scintillating top of the table clash, they will also be saying farewell to legend and Hibernian Hall of Famer Martin Robinson, as he announced his retirement from playing during the week to take a coaching role with reserves. Born in Edinburgh on the 16th of April 2012 and raised in Craigentinny as a diehard fan of the green and white of Edinburgh along with the rest of his family, He was spotted by and joined the youth academy at age 12, being handed a professional contract aged 16, foregoing the usual youth contract due to interest from clubs both down south and from Europe. He would be given his first team debut 5 months later, Starting for the club on the 25th November in a Scottish Cup fifth round home tie against Dundee, and it would only take him eighteen minutes to make his mark, latching onto a low Colin Marshall cross to score a diving header past Jamie Barclay in a game that would eventually end 3-0 with the next two goals coming quickly after, Gareth Masson putting the ball into his own net for the second in the twentieth minute before Inter loanee Adrian Aguado finished the game on the half hour mark. Despite this great start, Martin would have to wait a while before he was given another chance for the first team, his appearances were limited to substitutions with the game already pretty much over. But when he got his chance he took it once more, scoring twice in a 6-1 away win against Partick Thistle, with the others goals including another brace from Moussa Bamba, with Laurent Jacquet and Colin Marshall scoring the rest with Tommy Devlin getting the consolation for the Glasgow Jags. He would end the season with two more important goals, the opener in a 4-3 Edinburgh Derby win, as well as a goal in 2-2 draw against Celtic as Hibs secured their sixth successive Premiership. Though Robinson failed to pick up a medal for the league, his appearance from the bench in the 2-0 Scottish Cup Final win over St Mirren meant that Robinson ended his first season as a Professional footballer with a medal, the first of many. Robinson would spend the next few seasons forcing his way into the first team, successfully doing so in 2031 despite the goal scoring exploits of Barry Soane. With Martin Robinson up front, and the attacking midfield three of Fredinho, Dave Pickford and Lee Grice playing behind him, the Hibees would strike terror into the hearts of defenders across Scotland and Europe. It would only get better for Robinson when, at only the age of 22, he was named captain following the retirement of Fellow Hibernian legend Colin Marshall, many players would crumble under such pressure at such a young age, but Martin Robinson finished the season with 43 goals and 15 assists in all competitions as well as completing another domestic treble for his team. Undoubtedly his finest achievement for this club was his performances in 2038/2039 quadruple winning season. Captaining the squad that included fellow legends, such as goalkeeper Mohamed Boussaid (now retired), playmaker Paul Hutchings (Now at Bordeaux), and Left Winger Fredinho (retired), as well other greats like Leonardo Fantini, Gareth Pearson (left for West Brom, now retired) and Mariano Hue (now at Barcelona), the team would go on to record victories that the fans would remember for the rest of their lives, including an 8-3 cup semi-final win over Inverness CT, a 7-5 win over Formartine United, and a 3-1 victory over German giants Borussia Dortmund in the Europa League Final. Robinson would carry on as the main man up front as he reached his early thirties, even when a young Gary Moore broke into the ranks, Martin was still scoring twenty goals a season, breaking the record for the most league goals for the club as well as the most league appearances, and would eventually outlast Moore when the much sought after star was sold to Manchester City for  #163;8 Million. It was only last season where it became clear that age was finally catching up to him, as he only scored 6 goals in 21, paling in comparison to his record of 22 in 34 the previous year. With appearances coming harder and harder to come by with the revelations of Bobby Schumacher and Matt Finnie, as well Craig Brown finally showing the ability he had teasing the Hibernian faithful he would show for so long, Martin Robinson announced he would hang up his boots aged 35 earlier in the week, with the captaincy role going to Leonardo Fantini, who was promoted from Vice Captain. All in All, Martin Robinson made 680 appearances and scored 526 goals across all competitions for Hibernian football club. During his time, he would gain the following honours: The Scottish Premiership 18 times The Scottish Cup 14 times The Scottish League Cup 14 times The UEFA Europa League In terms of personal accolades: League Golden Boot 9 times The European Silver Boot The Champions League Bronze Boot Twice named Runner's Up in the Scottish Writer's Players of the year Once named 3rd place in the SFA Player of the Season Award. Martin Robinson will also be remembered well by the Tartan Army as he is the record goalscorer for Scotland, with 74 goals in 80 appearances for his Country.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Message from a Dundee United fan: Cheers for Harry Lewis</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 20:51:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 22:17:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>He was good for us in the match. Made two saves in the shootout aswell. Only downside is that he always comes out for crosses even when he doesn't need to. But he played well and the fact that he signed a 3 year deal before joining us on loan can only be a good thing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 23:20:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know when that happened, but he's definitely improved since then</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 01:09:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's the Scottish Premiership now, for some reason. Think it will be us or Falkirk for the Championship, we just need to sort out right back and get a target man striker, then we're definitely winning it. But for now it's just probably</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 02:44:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>it was a bit concerning how often he came out for them and did almost lead to us conceding in the last minute. Though he did accidentally punch the Dundee captain in the face in one of those incidents so it wasn't all bad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>United open to offers for Cammy Bell</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 18:25:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 22:51:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically: He wanted to go back to Kilmarnock for family reasons, and Kilmarnock were interested in him. There must've been an assumption that the deal was close to completion as we brought in two keepers as replacements. Clearly, someone jumped the gun as Killie weren't willing to sign him unless he went for free and United payed a part of his wage until the planned end of his United deal. Neither side could make an agreement, talks broke down, but Cammy still wants to leave. So here we are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So this is getting interesting</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-02 00:24:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>CAMMY BELL DEPARTS DUNDEE UNITED</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 19:34:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 20:59:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Derek McInnes' Aberdeen bottling a big game? Never...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 15:55:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>He did have a problem with shots from outside the box.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 18:59:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hang on a minute what?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 20:18:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ohhh, I thought he needed protection or something</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Story] The Men of Leith vs The Bavarian Juggernaut</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-05 06:06:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>*This is a transcript from BBC Sportsound on the 15th October 2048. Narrated by BBC Journalist Will Murray* **Will Murray: Hello and welcome to another Episode of this BBC Scotland series where we take a look at great European nights in Scottish Football. In this episode, we will only need to go back one year, when Hibernian faced Bayern Munich at Beckenbauer Park in the UEFA Champions League Quarter Final. All those Interviewed either Played for or coached Hibernian at the time. Unfortunately, Manager James Hawkins was unavailable to comment due to his commitments managing the Scotland Squad alongside his club duties.** Interviewed were: George Parnell, Goalkeeper, Welsh Internationalist Mahmoud Ramadan, Defensive Midfielder, Egyptian Internationalist Danny Ellis, Right and Centre Mid, Scottish U19 internationalist Leonardo Fantini, Centre Midfielder, Captain and Italian Internationalist Craig Brown, Striker, Scottish Internationalist Alex Abel, Left Back, English Internationalist Jose Luis Palomeque, Left Winger, Mexican Internationalist Vijay Ward, Centre Back, Jamaican Internationalist All interviews were conducted separately. BBC Sportsound commentary from Scott Murdoch and Barry Soane. Leonardo Fantini: Going into the match, we were not highly rated. At all. Craig Brown: We had scraped through against Borussia Monchengladbach, we beat them 5-2 two at home then got beat 2-0 in Germany, so we went through on Aggregate. And then to draw Bayern Munich. In both rounds we would play the only teams to win the Bundesliga since 2033. It felt like we had just survived against the toughest guy in the pub and then his bodybuilding mate walks in and charges at you. George Parnell: I remember just thinking, that I was going to be very, very busy in the first game. And I was.  gt;Murdoch: Thank you for joining us this evening as we provide you live coverage of this Champions League Quarter Final Match between Bayern Munich. I #8217;m Scott Murdoch and This is Former Hibs and Scotland striker Barry Soane.  gt;Barry Soane: Hi it #8217;s a pleasure to be here.  gt;Murdoch: Now we have an hour to kick-off and the line-ups have just come through, and by the looks of things Hawkins has sprung some surprises Barry How do you think Hibernian will line-up?  gt;Soane: Well it looks like that instead of the 4-2-3-1 Hawkins prefers, it #8217;s looks like it #8217;s a 4-1-4-1 a. very defensive line-up. The goalkeeper and the defence is obvious. Parnell in Goal. Bonnassiolle on the Right. Ward and Francisco at Centre Back, with Alex Abel on the left. Mahmoud Ramadan in the Defensive Midfield Role... Mahmoud Ramadan: I was given a great honour by Mr. Hawkins. Leo (Leonardo Fantini) and Franny (Francisco) May have been the Captain and Vice-Captain, but Hawkins had made me, Mahmoud Ramadan, in charge of the hole between defence and midfield. Now he told me  #8220;Rama, if you fail in this job, the team itself will crumble. #8221;  gt;Soane: Captain Leonardo Fantini will line up in the midfield alongside Ricardo Rocha. Jose Luis Palomeque starts on the left. Craig Brown goes up front. And on the right, it #8217;s 17-year-old. Danny Ellis #8230; Danny Ellis: The Gaffer pulled me in on the Sunday before the game. He told me to take a seat. And to be honest I thought he was going to tell me that he would be letting me go. I mean I had played in the League Cup Final, against Alloa were we won 3-0, but in my mind, I was still thinking that he was sending me off to waste away in League 1 or something. But then he told that, because Benji (Benjamin Jeannin) was Injured, I was starting, and that was probably even worse! I mean, to go from playing against Alloa, to Bayern, one of the greatest clubs in the world, was certainly interesting. Fantini: The plan was for the FC Bayern to over apply men and pressure, then we would hit them on the counter-attack. Instead #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Zochlov plays the ball to Zaldivar who tries a shot on the edge of box! Which is saved and then Caught by George Parnell. Fantini: ...We just sat back. We couldn #8217;t counter because we couldn #8217;t get the ball. I don #8217;t think Broony got a touch on it. Brown: I just had to watch from the halfway line. I might as well have been with the away fans!  gt;Murdoch: Hugo Lamela heads the ball down to Zochlov! Blocked by Palomeque! And the header from Zochlov again, goes out for goal kick  gt;Soane: Hibs need to come back into this match, it #8217;s been 12 minutes, Bayern have had 5 shots, and Hibs have had none, they #8217;re playing far too defensive.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Luis Filipe storming down the left Wing, and that #8217;s a cynical *starts laughing* challenge by Alex Abel, the referee has given a free kick. He #8217;s somehow not going to book him. And Filipe #8217;s not happy, and neither are the Supporters. Alex Abel: I think all of us conceded about three fouls each, except from me who maybe conceded 7? Maybe more, so I was the only one who got booked, and to be honest I probably should have been sent off. The referee was certainly kind to us that day.  gt;Murdoch: That #8217;s a Dangerous ball in from Somoza- Great tackle by Ward and the ball is pounced on by Fili-But he #8217;s taken out by Francisco! Wow, great last gasp defending by the Hibees.  gt;Soane: Aye, the ball came in on the left from Somoza, it fell almost perfectly to Chrysagis, he pulled his foot back, and that just gave Ward the space to slide in. There was some confusion, Filipe came in from a tight angle on the right, and Francisco was just there to take the ball away from him, allowing Bonnassiolle to clear it to Ellis.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Bayern on the attack again, Esparza bombing down the wing, Abel can #8217;t keep up. Crosses the ball in, Met by CHRYSAGIS! Blocked by Parnell, the ball #8217;s up in the air!... And the Goalkeeper punches it behind the goal. Corner. Vijay Ward: The number of corners we conceded was #8230; ridiculous.  gt;Murdoch: Rocha takes the ball from Bonnassiolle, but he #8217;s tackled by Somoza! Zaldivar is through #8230; and that #8217;s another fantastic tackle by Vijay Ward, and he and Francisco are earning their wages today. It #8217;s another corner.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Zaldivar has the ball here, and slices the Defence in two! Somoza shoots! Saved by Parnell! And cleared by Bonnassiolle, taking out Filipe in the process. Another close scare for Hawkins and Hibernian.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: And that #8217;s half time. An intense match so far Barry.  gt;Soane: Yeah, it #8217;s been a great performance defensively by Hibs but the attackers need to be doing better, Brown has been poor, barely had a touch of the ball. And Palomeque, he looks fuming coming off there, Fantini #8217;s gone to have a word with him. Fantini: Jose was furious, I don #8217;t think I #8217;ve ever seen him like that. Jose Luis Palomeque: I am an attacking player who was asked to do the job of a defender. I am not Abel, I am not a #8230; a Francisco. But I was asked to do their job anyway. Brown: I couldn #8217;t blame him the guy for being angry. We had maybe spent two or so minutes in the oppositions half, which, if you #8217;re an attacking player, is not what you want, at all. Ward: The Gaffer came in, simply told us  #8220;more of the same #8221;. Then walked out again. Jose got up and stormed after him Palomeque: I asked, what I was expected to do if we kept playing defensively? Mr. Hawkins simply looked at me, and said two things. The first thing he said was  #8220;Run #8221;, and he turned to leave, but then he pointed to the Bayern Right Back, Robin Chapuis, who for some reason wasn #8217;t in their changing room. He pointed to him, and said  #8220;and make him mad. #8221;  gt;Murdoch: Brown and Fantini will get the game kick off, and pass it back to Vijay Ward.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Kochlov wins the physical battle with Fantini, plays the ball on the left to Somoza #8230; first time pass to #8230; CHRYSAGIS! Great save by Parnell! Well we #8217;re only three minutes into the second half and it looks like more of the same.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Palomeque has the ball here #8230;  gt;Soane: *Laughs*  gt;Murdoch: Well #8230; Palomeque nutmegged Chapuis before he got *Laughs slightly* thoroughly slide tackled by Leparza. And uh #8230; Chapuis does not look happy, he looks very embarrassed. ...  gt;Murdoch: Hibs are enjoying a rare moment of possession here. Ramadan plays it through to Craig Brown, what can he do with ball #8230; Brown: I got the ball on the halfway line, and could hear  #8220;Craig! #8221;,  #8220;Craig! #8221;, and could see Jose, Tomato faced, screaming at me and sprinting down the wing, I leaned back and kicked it up over their right winger #8217;s head #8230;  gt;Murdoch: The ball is lobbed over to Palomeque... Palomeque: I got the ball, and I did what I was told.  gt;Murdoch: Who is going to run with it down the wing here, Somoza has given up, the Mexican has got to the edge of the box #8230; PENALTY! He was brought down by Chapuis inside the penalty area, and the Right Back is absolutely furious, but it looked like a penalty to me.  gt;Soane: Clear Penalty.  gt;Murdoch: Surprisingly, he #8217;s not even getting booked, but that was a terrible challenge. Brown: We saw our chance and took it. Palomeque: I got up and went to pick up the ball to give it to Leo. Ward: Francisco and I knew that if this went in, the barrage was only going to get worse.  gt;Murdoch: It falls to the captain, Leonardo Fantini to take. The Italian has a great record from the spot.  gt;*Ref blows his whistle*  gt;Murdoch: Can he score here?... Saved!  gt;*Home Fans cheer*  gt;Murdoch: But It #8217;s gone in! Rodrigues palmed it away onto the post #8230;  gt;*Silence, then small cheering can be heard which is quickly drowned by booing*  gt;Murdoch:  #8230;And it has rolled over the line! And in a sea of red, a glimmer of green and white is in delight! Brown: When I saw that #8230; the keeper had saved it; my head fell into my hands #8230; then all the cheering from the home fans just died and turned into booing, and I thought  #8220;What #8217;s gone on here? #8221; Fantini: I just saw it had gone in, saw that our support was just in on corner to the left of me, and sprinted towards them. Ramadan: We had gotten the goal. Now I, with the help of Franny and Vijay, had to stop Bayern from getting theirs. Brown: After the celebrations, I ran back for kick-off, and saw the 4th official had flashed my number and that Shoe (Bobby Schumacher) was coming on for me, I tell you what, I #8217;ve never been so pleased to come off in my life. I knew I was doing nothing for the rest of the match but tire myself. I was glad for the rest!  gt;Murdoch: Esparza, Lays it back to Luis Filipe! And that is an easy save by Parnell, it was straight at him. Parnell: People have said that, it was my greatest performance. I mean, it was only because I had so many shots coming at me. Most of them were poor as well, straight at my chest, and ones like that.  gt;Murdoch: Parnell will wait for everyone to get back in position, Hibs are in no rush here #8230; Ellis: As I took my position, Esparza, their left back went alongside me. And he had been trying to push me around most of the match, but even though he was older than me, I was taller, and stronger so uh #8230; I guess he had just gotten sick of it.  gt;Murdoch:  #8230;He #8217;s finally going to kick the ball back up to the halfway line, and Ellis and Esparza are in a bit of a physical battle there #8230; Ellis: We both went up at the same time, and I felt something hit me in the nose.  gt;Murdoch:  #8230;Well. Ellis has gone down in pain, and from what we can see Esparza elbowed him as they went up for the header. Rocha has sprinted in, he is furious with the Bayern Full Back. The other players have joined in here. Fantini and Lamela, the two captains are trying to split this up, trying to calm their teammates down. The linesman has taken Ellis out of the way. The Referee has come over #8230; everything appears to be calming down. Esparza is being called over #8230; He #8217;s off! It #8217;s a red card for the left back! And there is no complaints from any of his teammates, and it #8217;s a long walk to the other side of the pitch for the Frenchman. Ellis: I was just covering my face, I was in so much pain. I felt someone drag me off, turned out it was the linesman, and I just lay there until I heard the voice of our physio. Fantini: I saw it happen with my own eyes, and my instincts was to go to the ref and say,  #8220;you going to send this guy off? #8221; then I saw Ricky (Ricardo Rocha) explode and charge at the Bayern player, I knew it was going to be difficult for me. Luckily Hugo, their captain, to his credit, wasn #8217;t happy with his teammates, just as I wasn #8217;t happy with mine. Ellis: So, yeah that was the end of the match for me. *laughs*  gt;Murdoch: both Lines and Marcelinho are ready to come on, the former is coming on for Ellis who will take his time coming off, and Palomeque will come off for the Brazilian Centre back #8230; Hibernian will finish the match without wingers, and 5 at the back. Fantini: We didn #8217;t have anyone on the bench who could play on the right wing #8230; the change made sense. And there was only ten minutes of the game left to go #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Parnell, takes the goal-kick #8230; and the referee blows his whistle for full time! Hibernian have ridden their luck here, but when they had their opportunity, Leonardo Fantini stepped up and took it! Brown: When the final whistle went, my first thought was,  #8220;we #8217;ve stolen this! #8221; Ramadan: Our goal was to defend and counter. We defended, and when we saw our chance to counter, we did. We achieved our goals, and won the match. Fantini: I was just focused getting my teammates ready for the next match in the league and obviously the return fixture. **Murray: So, they had won the away match, now it was back to Easter Road for the 2nd leg. Could they do it?** Fantini: To be honest, I don #8217;t think they expected us to change tactics. Away we had played very defensively, so they lined-up to counter that. But we had gone back to the 4-2-3-1 we always played, which they clearly were not ready for.  gt;Murdoch: Abel play a sideways ball to Gayle, low cross to an overlapping Palomeque #8230; Goal! One nil Hibernian, and they #8217;ve deserved this, they #8217;ve been all over the Germans here!  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Gayle will take this Corner here, ball goes up, Ward gets to it #8230; 2-0! Great cross from the Englishman, and the Jamaican gives a great header to going along with it. Surely now, the Scottish team are through to the semi-finals.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Full time! Hibs are through to the semis, what a performance that has been from the Scottish side. They are in the UEFA Champions League semi-finals for the first time in their history! **Murray: They were through, and the next round would prove even more difficult, as it Spanish juggernauts, Real Madrid came out of the pot. Could they do the Unthinkable all over again?**  gt;Murdoch: Palomeque with a great run driving his team forward, he #8217;s in the box. Oh my God! Hibernian 1 Real Madrid 0! What a fine goal from Jose Luis Palomeque, he sprinted down into the box, put the ball through Bousmaha, the right back #8217;s legs, and just cheekily dinked the ball over the keeper. 12 minutes gone, and Hibs are ahead!  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Boukadida, crosses the ball into Schug, who #8217;s lost his man and that #8217;s a goal. 1 all. Well, Ward really should #8217;ve done better there but it was a good header from the Swiss Striker, and that #8217;s why he #8217;s considered the best striker in the World.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Hibs are on the counter here, Jeaninn has beaten his man for pace on the right side, crosses it into the box #8230; Goal! Headed in by Craig Brown. The little striker has leapt higher than the towering Madrid Centre halfs and put #8217;s green and white of Edinburgh back in front.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Guerin has the ball here, plays a through ball #8230; straight through centre #8230; and that #8217;s 2-2. Schug pounced on it. Francisco and Ward were caught napping, along with Parnell.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Only 2 minutes gone since the equaliser, can Madrid strike twice in quick successi- yes, they can! Schug gets on a low cross from Ivkovic, and slots past Parnell. And the Hibernian defence are having a nightmare of a second half, and they #8217;ve left the rest of the team with a mountain to climb in this game, and in the second leg  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Schug is through again! Saved but the rebound #8217;s put in #8230; four goals from the Switzerland striker, a masterclass from him tonight.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Palomeque, in the box, passes #8230; to Brown! They #8217;ve got a goal back here, that could be very important in the return fixture!  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: That #8217;s it. A spirited performance from Hawkins #8217; Hibernian. But it simply wasn #8217;t enough. **Murray: Unfortunately, they couldn #8217;t turn it around at Conte Park, losing 1-0. Despite these results, this Hibernian team should still hold their heads up in pride, becoming only the second Scottish team since Dundee United in 1984, to reach the Semi-Finals of the Champions League. Now with a new season, can they go further? Well I for one can #8217;t wait to find out. From me, and everyone at BBC Sportsound. Please, have a nice evening.**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Men of Leith vs The Bavarian Juggernaut</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-05 06:13:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>*This is a transcript from BBC Sportsound on the 15th October 2048. Narrated by BBC Journalist Will Murray* **Will Murray: Hello and welcome to this another Episode of this BBC Scotland series where we take a look at great European nights in Scottish Football. In this episode, we will only need to go back one year, when Hibernian faced Bayern Munich at Beckenbauer Park in the UEFA Champions League Quarter Final. All those Interviewed either Played for or coached Hibernian at the time. Unfortunately, Manager James Hawkins was unavailable to comment to his commitments managing the Scotland Squad alongside his club duties.** Interviewed were: George Parnell, Goalkeeper, Welsh Internationalist Mahmoud Ramadan, Defensive Midfielder, Egyptian Internationalist Danny Ellis, Right and Centre Mid, Scottish U19 internationalist Leonardo Fantini, Centre Midfielder, Captain and Italian Internationalist Craig Brown, Striker, Scottish Internationalist Alex Abel, Left Back, English Internationalist Jose Luis Palomeque, Left Winger, Mexican Internationalist Vijay Ward, Centre Back, Jamaican Internationalist All interviews were conducted separately. BBC Sportsound commentary from Scott Murdoch and Barry Soane. Leonardo Fantini: Going into the match, we were not highly rated. At all. Craig Brown: We had scraped through against Borussia Monchengladbach, we beat them 5-2 two at home then got beat 2-0 in Germany, so we went through on Aggregate. And then to draw Bayern Munich. In both rounds we would play the only teams to win the Bundesliga since 2033. It felt like we had just survived against the toughest guy in the pub and then his bodybuilding mate walks in and charges at you. George Parnell: I remember just thinking, that I was going to be very, very busy in the first game. And I was.  gt;Murdoch: Thank you for joining us this evening as we provide you live coverage of this Champions League Quarter Final Match between Bayern Munich. I #8217;m Scott Murdoch and This is Former Hibs and Scotland striker Barry Soane.  gt;Barry Soane: Hi it #8217;s a pleasure to be here.  gt;Murdoch: Now we have an hour to kick-off and the line-ups have just come through, and by the looks of things Hawkins has sprung some surprises Barry How do you think Hibernian will line-up?  gt;Soane: Well it looks like that instead of the 4-2-3-1 Hawkins prefers, it #8217;s looks like it #8217;s a 4-1-4-1 a. very defensive line-up. The goalkeeper and the defence is obvious. Parnell in Goal. Bonnassiolle on the Right. Ward and Francisco at Centre Back, with Alex Abel on the left. Mahmoud Ramadan in the Defensive Midfield Role... Mahmoud Ramadan: I was given a great honour by Mr. Hawkins. Leo (Leonardo Fantini) and Franny (Francisco) May have been the Captain and Vice-Captain, but Hawkins had made me, Mahmoud Ramadan, in charge of the hole between defence and midfield. Now he told me  #8220;Rama, if you fail in this job, the team itself will crumble. #8221;  gt;Soane: Captain Leonardo Fantini will line up in the midfield alongside Ricardo Rocha. Jose Luis Palomeque starts on the left. Craig Brown goes up front. And on the right, it #8217;s 17-year-old. Danny Ellis #8230; Danny Ellis: The Gaffer pulled me on the Sunday before the game. He told me to take a seat. And to be honest I thought he was going to tell me that he would be letting me go. I mean I had played in the League Cup Final, against Alloa were we won 3-0, but in my mind, I was still thinking that he was sending me off to waste away in League 1 or something. But then he told that, because Benji (Benjamin Jeannin) was Injured, I was starting, and that was probably even worse! I mean, to go from playing against Alloa, to Bayern, one of the greatest clubs in the world, was certainly interesting. Fantini: The plan was for the FC Bayern to over apply men and pressure, then we would hit them on the counter-attack. Instead #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Zochlov plays the ball to Zaldivar who tries a shot on the edge of box! Which is saved and then Caught by George Parnell. Fantini: ...We just sat back. We couldn #8217;t counter because we couldn #8217;t get the ball. I don #8217;t think Broony got a touch on it. Brown: I just had to watch from the halfway line. I might as well have been with the away fans!  gt;Murdoch: Hugo Lamela heads the ball down to Zochlov! Blocked by Palomeque! And the header from Zochlov again, goes out for goal kick  gt;Soane: Hibs need to come back into this match, it #8217;s been 12 minutes, Bayern have had 5 shots, and Hibs have had none, they #8217;re playing far too defensive.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Luis Filipe storming down the left Wing, and that #8217;s a cynical *starts laughing* challenge by Alex Abel, the referee has given a free kick. He #8217;s somehow not going to book him. And Filipe #8217;s not happy, and neither are the Supporters. Alex Abel: I think all of us conceded about three fouls each, except from me who maybe conceded 7? Maybe more, so I was the only who got booked, and to be honest I probably should have been sent off. The referee was certainly kind to us that day.  gt;Murdoch: That #8217;s a Dangerous ball in from Somoza- Great tackle by Ward and the ball is pounced on by Fili-But he #8217;s taken out by Francisco! Wow, great last gasp defending by the Hibees.  gt;Soane: Aye, the ball came in on the left from Somoza, it fell almost perfectly to Chrysagis, he pulled his foot back, and that just gave Ward the space to slide in. There was some confusion, Filipe came in from a tight angle on the right, and Francisco was just there to take the ball away from him, allowing Bonnassiolle to clear it to Ellis.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Bayern on the attack again, Esparza bombing down the wing, Abel can #8217;t keep up. Crosses the ball in, Met by CHRYSAGIS! Blocked by Parnell, the ball #8217;s up in the air! And the Goalkeeper punches it behind the goal. Corner. Vijay Ward: The number of corners we conceded was #8230; ridiculous.  gt;Murdoch: Rocha takes the ball from Bonnassiolle, but he #8217;s tackled by Somoza! Zaldivar is through #8230; and that #8217;s another fantastic tackle by Vijay Ward, and him and Francisco are earning their wages today. It #8217;s be another corner.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Zaldivar has the ball here, and slices the Defence in two! Somoza shoots! Saved by Parnell! And cleared by Bonnassiolle, taking out Filipe in the process. Another close scare for Hawkins and Hibernian.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: And that #8217;s half time. An intense match so far Barry.  gt;Soane: Yeah, it #8217;s been a great performance defensively by Hibs but the attackers need to be doing better, Brown has been poor, barely had a touch of the ball. And Palomeque, he looks fuming coming off there, Fantini #8217;s gone to have a word with him. Fantini: Jose was furious, I don #8217;t think I #8217;ve ever seen him like that. Jose Luis Palomeque: I am an attacking player who was asked to do the job of a defender. I am not Abel, I am not a #8230; a Francisco. But I was asked to do their job anyway. Brown: I couldn #8217;t blame him the guy for being angry. We had maybe spent two or so minutes in the oppositions half, which, if you #8217;re an attacking player, is not what you want, at all. Ward: The Gaffer came in, simply told us  #8220;more of the same #8221;. Then walked out again. Jose got up and stormed after him Palomeque: I asked, what I was expected to do if we kept playing defensively? Mr. Hawkins simply looked at me, and said two things. The first thing he said was  #8220;Run #8221;, and he turned to leave, but then he pointed to the Bayern Right Back, Robin Chapuis, who for some reason wasn #8217;t in their changing room. He pointed to him, and said  #8220;and make him mad. #8221;  gt;Murdoch: Brown and Fantini will get the game kick off, and pass it back to Vijay Ward.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Kochlov wins the physical battle with Fantini, plays the ball on the left to Somoza #8230; first time pass to #8230; CHRYSAGIS! Great save by Parnell! Well we #8217;re only three minutes into the second half and it looks like more of the same.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Palomeque has the ball here #8230;  gt;Soane: *Laughs*  gt;Murdoch: Well #8230; Palomeque nutmegged Chapuis before he got *Laughs slightly* thoroughly slide tackled by Leparza. And uh #8230; Chapuis does not look happy, he looks very embarrassed. ...  gt;Murdoch: Hibs are enjoying a rare moment of possession here. Ramadan plays it through to Craig Brown, what can he do with ball #8230; Brown: I got the ball on the halfway line, and could hear  #8220;Craig! #8221;,  #8220;Craig! #8221;, and could see Jose, Tomato faced, screaming at me and sprinting down the wing, I leaned back and kicked it up over the right winger #8217;s head #8230;  gt;Murdoch: The ball is played to Palomeque, Palomeque: I got the ball, and I did what I was told.  gt;Murdoch: Who is going to run with it down the wing here, Somoza has given up, the Mexican has got to the edge of the box #8230; PENALTY! He was brought down by Chapuis in the box, and the Right Back is absolute furious but it looked like a penalty to me.  gt;Soane: Clear Penalty.  gt;Murdoch: Surprisingly, he #8217;s not even getting booked, but that was a terrible challenge. Brown: We saw our chance and took it. Palomeque: I got up and went to pick up the ball to give it to Leo. Ward: Francisco and I knew that if this went in, the barrage was only going to get worse.  gt;Murdoch: It falls to the captain, Leonardo Fantini to take. The Italian has a great record from the spot.  gt;*Ref blows his whistle*  gt;Murdoch: Can he score here?... Saved!  gt;*Home Fans cheer*  gt;Murdoch: But It #8217;s gone in! Rodrigues palmed it away onto the post #8230;  gt;*Silence, then small cheering can be heard which is quickly drowned by booing*  gt;Murdoch:  #8230;And it has rolled over the line! And in a sea of red, a glimmer of green and white is in delight! Brown: When I saw that #8230; the keeper had saved it; my head fell into my hands #8230; then all the cheering from the home fans just died and turned into booing, and I thought  #8220;What #8217;s gone on here? #8221; Fantini: I just saw it had gone in, saw that our support was just in on corner to the left of me, and sprinted towards them. Ramadan: We had gotten the goal. Now we had to stop Bayern from getting theirs. Brown: After the celebrations, I ran back for kick-off, and saw the 4th official had flashed my number and that Shoe (Bobby Schumacher) was coming on for me, I tell you what, I #8217;ve never been so pleased to come off in my life. I knew I was doing nothing for the rest of the match but tire myself. I was glad for the rest!  gt;Murdoch: Esparza, Lays it back to Luis Filipe! And that is an easy save by Parnell, it was straight at him. Parnell: People have said that, it was my greatest performance. I mean, it was only because I had so many shots coming at me. Most of them were poor as well, straight at my chest, and ones like that.  gt;Murdoch: Parnell will wait for everyone to get back in position, Hibs are in no rush here #8230; Ellis: As I took my position, Esparza, their left back went alongside me. And he had been trying to push me around most of the match, but even though he was older than me, I was taller, and stronger so uh #8230; I guess he had just gotten sick of it.  gt;Murdoch:  #8230;He #8217;s finally going to kick the ball back up to the halfway line, and Ellis and Esparza are in a bit of a physical battle there #8230; Ellis: We both went up at the same time, and I felt something hit me in the nose.  gt;Murdoch:  #8230;Well. Ellis has gone down in pain, and from what we can see Esparza elbowed him as they went up for the header. Rocha has sprinted in, he is furious with the Bayern Full Back. The other players have joined in here. Fantini and Lamela, the two captains are trying to split this up, trying to calm their teammates down. The linesman has taken Ellis out of the way. The Referee has come over #8230; everything appears to be calming down. Esparza is being called over #8230; He #8217;s off! It #8217;s a red card for the left back! And there is no complaints from any of his teammates, and it #8217;s a long walk to the other side of the pitch for the Frenchman. Ellis: I was just covering my face, I was in so much pain. I felt someone drag me off, turn out it was the linesman, and I just lay there until I heard the voice of our physio. Fantini: I saw it happen with my own eyes, and my instincts was to go to the ref and say,  #8220;you going to say send this guy off? #8221; then I saw Ricky (Ricardo Rocha) explode and charge at the Bayern player, I knew it was going to be difficult for me. Luckily Hugo, their captain, wasn #8217;t happy with his teammates, as I wasn #8217;t happy with mine. Ellis: So, yeah that was the end of the match for me. *laughs*  gt;Murdoch: both Lines and Marcelinho are ready to come on, the former is coming on for Ellis who will take his time coming off, and Palomeque will come off for the Brazilian Centre back #8230; Hibernian will finish the match without wingers, and 5 at the back. Fantini: We didn #8217;t have anyone on the bench who could play on the right wing #8230; the change made sense. And there was only ten minutes of the game left to go #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Parnell, takes the goal-kick #8230; and the referee blows his whistle for full time! Hibernian have ridden their luck here, but when they had their opportunity, Leonardo Fantini stepped up and took it! Brown: When the final whistle went, my first thought was,  #8220;we #8217;ve stolen this! #8221; Ramadan: Our goal was to defend and counter. We defended, and we saw our chance to counter, we did. We achieved our goals and won the match. Fantini: I was just focused getting my teammates ready for the next match in the league and obviously the return fixture. **Murray: So, they had won the away match, now it was back to Easter Road for the 2nd leg. Could they do it?** Fantini: To be honest, I don #8217;t think they expected us to change tactics. Away we had played very defensively, so they lined-up to counter that. But we had gone back to the 4-2-3-1 we always played, which they clearly were not ready for.  gt;Murdoch: Abel play a sideways ball to Gayle, low cross to an overlapping Palomeque #8230; Goal! One nil Hibernian, and they #8217;ve deserved this, they #8217;ve been all over the Germans here!  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Gayle will take this Corner here, ball goes up, Ward gets to it #8230; 2-0! Great cross from the Englishman, and the Jamaican gives a great header to going along with it. Surely now, the Scottish team are through to the semi-finals.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Full time! Hibs are through to the semis, what a performance that has been from the Scottish side. They are in the UEFA Champions League semi-finals for the first time in their history! **Murray: They were through, and the next round would prove even more difficult, as it Spanish juggernauts, Real Madrid came out of the pot. Could they do the Unthinkable all over again?**  gt;Murdoch: Palomeque with a great run driving his team forward, he #8217;s in the box. Oh my God! Hibernian 1 Real Madrid 0! What a fine goal from Jose Luis Palomeque, he sprinted down into, put the ball through Bousmaha, the right back #8217;s legs, and just dinked the ball over the keeper. 12 minutes gone, and Hibs are ahead!  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Boukadida, crosses the ball in to Schug, who #8217;s lost his man and that #8217;s a goal. 1 all. Well Ward really should #8217;ve done better there but it was a good header from the Swiss Striker, and that #8217;s why he #8217;s considered the best striker in the World.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Hibs are on the counter here, Jeaninn has beaten his man for pace on the right side, crosses it into the box #8230; Goal! Headed in by Craig Brown. The little striker has leapt higher than the towering Madrid Centre halfs and put #8217;s green and white of Edinburgh back in front.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Guerin has the ball here, plays a through ball #8230; straight through centre #8230; and that #8217;s 2-2. Schug pounced on it. Francisco and Ward were caught napping, along with Parnell.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Only 2 minutes gone since the equaliser, can Madrid strike twice in quick successi- yes, they can! Schug gets on a low cross from Ivkovic, and slots past Parnell. And the Hibernian defence are having a nightmare of a second half, and they #8217;ve left the rest of the team with a mountain to climb in this game, and in the second leg  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Schug is through again! Saved but the rebound #8217;s put in #8230; four goals from the Switzerland striker, a masterclass from him tonight.  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: Palomeque, in the box, passes #8230; to Brown! They #8217;ve got a goal back here, that could be very important in the return fixture!  #8230;  gt;Murdoch: That #8217;s it. A spirited performance from Hawkins #8217; Hibernian. But it simply wasn #8217;t enough. **Murray: Unfortunately, they couldn #8217;t turn it around at Conte Park, losing 1-0. Despite these results, this Hibernian should still hold their heads up in pride, becoming only the second Scottish team since Dundee United in 1984, to reach the Semi-Finals of the Champions League. Now with a new season, could they go further, Well I for one can #8217;t wait to find out. From me, and everyone at BBC Sportsound. Please, have a nice evening.**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-07 02:28:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>/u/Wt_franjo and /u/Montuvito_G I know you two enjoyed the last story I did on r/fmstories, so I thought you would like this one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-07 03:48:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>About to post on the forum now... never posted on there before so getting with everything first. Cheers, genuinely, I was just kinda sick of the standard "I signed this guy, then I won this match, but I lost this one" FM Story format, and I thought this game had an interesting storyline.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-07 17:22:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use a skin that allows pictures of cities to be shown in the club overview. however, pictures are being shown in the background instead of the area they're supposed to be in. Any help in fixing it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New Ross County signing Ross Draper claims Caley Thistle board told him to submit transfer request to complete move</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 15:49:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 18:12:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>And I'm sure you're enjoying every minute of it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 02:38:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're officially non-profit, with their massive bank account being referred to as a reserve</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 00:42:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't remember Robertson being that good at crossing when he with United...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 00:50:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not complaining, any improvements from him just means he'll better for the national team. Hope he does well for you, deserved better than Hull. And was our best player in his one season with us (his first season in full team football).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 04:01:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unless they're Charlie Adam</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Discussion] Players achieving Legend Status</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 18:32:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Currently got a long save in fm14 currently in season 49/50, managing Hibernian since 2018. I recently sold a player and the fans were disappointed because he was considered a legend. Slightly confused I checked the club info and there he was. This doesn't make any sense to me. The guy, a Scottish striker called Craig Brown, is 25, made 161 appearances and scored 65 goals across all competitions, so not that impressive. He also won 3 league titles, 2 league cups, and 1 MLS All-Stars Game. His time at the club was also dotted with Liam spells at Cowdenbeath, Derby, Cardiff and Southampton, and was just alright in all his spells there. If i compare this to another player Leonardo Fantini, who joined in 36/37 season from Southampton for 10.25 million. Since then, he's been made captain, was given a testimonial, made 588 appearances and scored 121 goals across all competitions, while winning 12 league titles, 11 league cups, 7 Scottish Cups, and won the MLS All-Stars. Yet the game doesn't even consider him a favoured personnel, never mind an Icon or a legend. The only reason I can think of why Brown is considered a legend is because he started at Hibs. That's it Just wondering if anybody has had a similar situation and knows why the game is so inconsistent with the legend status</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 18:38:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Major_League_Soccer_All-Star_Game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 18:47:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>A big European team gets invited every year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 13:44:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>If Andy Robertson gets benched for a fullback duo of Whittaker and Tierney I am going to run screaming into hampden naked with a flaming fucking axe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 08:55:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I started my save unemployed and got hired by Hibs halfway through the 18/19 season, I won the league the season after (and would win the league every season after except for the 21/22 season), but I don't think I beat Celtic once throughout that entire season. Tbh I think I kinda got lucky since the manager before had built a pretty good team that I just needed to make some small improvements to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 20:52:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why does Gnabry look like a 90's Sci-fi villain?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 20:57:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Julian Nagelsmann is the most generic German looking man i've ever seen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 21:06:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Emre Can's hair is fucking majestic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 21:14:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh yeah, neither team can defend for shit. this will be fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 21:22:43</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Moreno needs replacing before the group stages. Andy. Robertson.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 21:27:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. 100% agree 2. nice username</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 22:02:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did Lovren just try and outmuscle his own goalkeeper?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 01:40:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay let me correct that. The oldest REGEN.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Screenshot] this is the oldest Regen I've seen who is still first team quality.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 01:43:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 11:45:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically the latter yeah.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 17:59:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well at least there is always the inevitability of death to cheer me up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 18:17:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uhm... thanks?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 18:45:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>When the decaying corpse that is Daniel Sturridge scores, that's when you know you're fucked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 14:15:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit, thats Dottie James.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Screenshot] First Game in Charge. Think the players are trying to give me a heart attack...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 00:07:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 20:46:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>All I'm going to say is fuck the Jambos</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Scottish National Team does the 5 Second Challenge</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 00:15:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Christophe Berra and Craig Gordon take the Hearts Teammate Test</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 20:45:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anti-Flag - Racists</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 02:42:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Starting Lineup vs Lithuania</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 20:02:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 16:43:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Massive interest in this weeks games, clearly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dundee United launch amputee team, becoming the second team in Scotland to have one.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 11:16:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the name of this planet?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 22:50:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember watching this documentary when I was ten and it had a segment on a planet that didn't rotate on it's axis so one side was scorching heat and the other side was blistering cold, both being inhospitable. but in the middle of the planet, there was this ring that was inhabitable to humans due to it's earth-esque conditions. Can anyone help me find it? I've been looking it up for ages and can't find anything</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 23:16:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah, tbh I'm not entirely sure that "not spinning on its axis" is entirely accurate but that is at least how I remember it being.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>...At least my loaned player scored for them...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-08 00:43:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-08 12:49:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheers for the proper name, I had a feeling that "not spinning on its axis" wasn't entirely accurate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Motherwell's Playing And Coaching Staff Join The Well Society.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-08 18:29:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 16:24:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't wait for league one next season</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When the sugar daddy withdraws his funding...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 19:55:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 19:57:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>They've also been denied entry into the champions league for financial reasons. PS. is administration possible in Football Manager?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 23:24:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah I meant administration, but if bankruptcy is possible then things are about to get very interesting in my save</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-11 15:55:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Old Firm Facts' latest column - Celtic fans, Rangers boss Pedro Caixinha, the Queen and the Scotland national team</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-11 17:27:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 02:18:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>you are correct, Vocabulary is the correct term to use. But lexicon sounds smarter, soooooooooooooooooo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 02:33:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>The yer da portion of Partick Thistle fans are going to be livid at this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Aberdeen's lineup against Hearts last Saturday looks like someone playing FM drunk</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 02:39:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 13:42:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that reference to the fact that game was played at Murrayfield, or does that genuinely look like rugby?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 21:30:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay let's the non-music related one out of the way: pasta is better than pizza Now onto the music one: Man overboard are fucking terrible and them breaking up was one of the best things to ever happen to the scene. They have written three good songs (love your friends, Montrose, and Where I left you) Real Friends and Knuckle Puck are incredibly overrated. The former can't write a Melody and the latter thinks choosing the most complicated word you can think of is good songwriting. The genre has far too many bitter men with chips on their shoulders the size of Everest. If you're on your third album and still writing about Mandy who you dated for three months in High School before she asked if you two could "just be friends", you've got some fucking issues that need sorting out There aren't enough happy pop-punk bands. There is too much of an emo influence on the scene that has led to some turgid shite coming in. the UK Pop Punk scene is now (as a whole) better than the US scene. SCREAMING YOUR LYRICS DOESN'T MAKE THEM MORE EMOTIONAL. YOURE NOT PARKER CANNON, YOURE NOT DAN CAMPBELL, STOP IT. That's all I can think of right now, but there's prob more. Edit: OH YEAH I FORGOT, Knuckle Puck come across as pretentious cunts, seriously, imagine getting offended by a Jarrod Alonge joke?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>7-0 up at half time... raging I conceded</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 01:02:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 01:22:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>what. a. fucking. match. Great goals. Shit defending. sending offs. kingsley wandering about the touchline. Shite refeering. Who needs the EPL?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 03:23:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're fucking great</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 04:51:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck it, it is 3:40 where I am but I will listen to "Hung Up on Nothing" and see if I agree: 1. Again, "Love Your Friends" is a good song, seriously, how can you not sing along to that chorus? 2. Bland, nothing really all the special. 3. the fuck was that 4. blegh. I think I'm just set in my opinion when it comes to this band 5. Always a good start when you can't the vocals over the instrumentals. I mean, the melodies are decent (when I can hear them) but apart from that, not that good. Yeah, just not a fan. Sorry dude</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 12:57:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>a right back but no left back and two centre Backs. a CB at CDM. A centre mid at right wing. and a CDM at CAM. It's more than just the formation to be honest</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 13:08:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would make sense, but the people who were at the match said he was playing like a regular full back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 00:18:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>How was Robertson? That goal Liverpool conceded probably gave him flashbacks to his time at United</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 00:24:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Solly March fifa career mode legend</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 01:53:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>*postman from rick and Morty voice*: MAH MANNN!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 14:58:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone have a stream that I can put on my Chromecast?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 01:56:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>well this is a bit... silly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>St. Mirren - Dundee United to be shown live on BT Sport, on Friday the 29th of December.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 22:01:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 22:03:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm actually okay with this, mainly because it shows that BT Sport still have an interest in the league without the Edinburgh teams and Rangers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 20:23:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>"If you put in a five man midfield, where do you play Kenny Miller?" - Michael Stewart You don't... simple as</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 22:00:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rangers scoring as BT Sport was turning the volume down on the Rangers fans was unintentionally hilarious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 23:13:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>billy boys mate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 13:24:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Neck deep #8217;s  #8220;19 Seventy Sumthin #8221; When all the music cuts except for the guitar and you just hear Ben singing:  #8220;The heart attack was sharp He didn #8217;t feel no pain #8221; That fucked me up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 22:14:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where #8217;s the humour in this? Genuinely this is just a straight fact, no attempt at comedy whatsoever</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 03:32:16</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I realise you might argue that Andy Robertson is better than the rest and deserved to go down south, but Izaguirre was better than him when he moved to Hull, and KT is better than him now anyway. Andy Robertson is better than both those two and I will fight you in George Square over this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 16:01:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t think you understand just how stubborn I am on this issue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 03:31:06</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; D.O.F. does, but I was under the impression that he was the one in charge of recruitment in the first place even under previous managers. I think it started off that way but he ended up giving the coaches more say over time which is possibly what lead to some of the shit signings last January as Cathro was getting say in stuff he obviously wasn't ready to get a say in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 22:40:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Think it was January 07. What a gem that was. The manager mode was fucking great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 03:52:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>According to the official Manchester United website, their most expensive tickets for Domestic matches are  #163;53 ( #163;70), while their cheapest are  #163;13 ( #163;17). Barcelona #8217;s most expensive, again according to their official website, are 157 #8364; so that #8217;s 183$, while their cheapest are 66 #8364; (77$). So even when you look at some of the biggest soccer clubs in the world, the prices still don #8217;t compare to what the NFL are charging their fans</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 03:25:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, I now hate Falkirk even more than I used to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 06:07:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I stayed awake watching porn on my iPhone, it's almost like I don't need you" - "Secrets" by pop punk band Makeout</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Liam Polworth fighting one of the inverness coaches... for some reason.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-07 23:21:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 03:40:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>This worries me greatly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 03:47:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>He can #8217;t be the best looking when Stuart Armstrong exists.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 04:07:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hud on a minute, why does a Scot have a flair of an English team? IMPOSTER.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 05:01:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aye alright then. *squints at you suspiciously as I walk away*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Knockout in the dugout</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 06:27:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Life is poison</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 19:33:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pick a Scotland Squad using only Scottish footballers currently playing in the Scottish Premiership</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 17:45:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty much what the title says. It can either be the full 23 or just the starting 11. Interested in what some of the choices would be. I #8217;ll give my own list when I #8217;m back home and preferably not in that daze you get from being on an 9+ hour flight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 07:28:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>The international break in soccer is one of the most exciting parts of the game and I will fight any of you fuck that disagrees with me on this. Panama and Iceland are going to the World Cup. Don #8217;t you dare fucking tell that #8217;s nowhere near as inspiring as Leicester getting lucky one season.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 01:41:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why did I read that quote in Bojack Horseman #8217;s voice?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 20:52:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>How much impact did his motivation have on the team winning the final against France? since he was out after 30 minutes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 14:05:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know this is a bit late but any idea why I #8217;m getting so badly downvotes?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scottish Facebook is way, way worse than Scottish Twitter.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 16:41:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>BT Sport's Pundits respond to "that" Betfred Cup Advert</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 16:47:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 22:50:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the reason people mention Rangers is because they #8217;re only team with the financial capabilities to realistically challenge Celtic. That doesn #8217;t mean that they don #8217;t think other teams can #8217;t. It just means that Rangers are the most likely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 18:48:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>As It Is - Sorry</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 02:30:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Charlie Puth - How Long [Funk Pop]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 16:20:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Jim Spence is freelyread</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 17:46:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 21:07:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never change.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-30 01:16:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very Staunch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-30 23:06:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>They will be absolutely fantastic, then suddenly become absolute dogshite. It's the Pardew way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 00:11:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's "and all I ever was was sorry"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 15:36:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>On Jason Banton, he was last on loan at Partick Thistle. Here #8217;s what the terrace podcast (a podcast dedicated to Scottish Football) had to say on his time there:  #8220;Why the fuck did we sign him? It smacked of just desperation to grab some striker on loan just in case. We never even put him on the bench. Archie #8217;s made some right pish signings, especially up front in the last couple of seasons, but this guy is the most baffling. I was convinced he was dead because he had his photo taken with the shirt and that but wasn #8217;t seen again until I noticed he commented on something on Abdul Osman #8217;s Instagram. At least Antonio German got game time before we launched him back to the Indian League from whence he came. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>24.7k upvotes on r/politicalhumour...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 01:58:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 19:38:06</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;As Lonely as Laika Up there all alone You miss the atmosphere The stars are now your home #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[ORIGINAL] Stuffed Animals - The River</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 14:34:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Currently watching Steven Thompson and Michael Stewart debate whether or not punching someone in the nuts is a straight red</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 19:34:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I fucking love Scottish Football.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can #8217;t be the only one thinking this is a bit fast?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 13:44:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 13:45:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boys not even played 10 games yet and teams already want to sign him for 6 figure fees.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>As It Is - Upswing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 00:55:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 11:56:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because Dundee F.C. are full of dicks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #8220;Oi Dave, who #8217;s the airdrie manager again #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 11:56:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 23:30:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>bastard. Just about to post this!! to be serious this seems like a decent appointment, I've not seen any Hearts fan say a bad thing about him which is a good thing. apparently, he plays quite defensively which is a bit concerning given how our fans reacted to McKinnon's defensive style, but hey, as long as we get the fuck out of this league I'm happy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 19:04:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://twitter.com/dundeeunitedfc/status/929366303604989952 Check the replies to this. The hard on of hate that rangers fans have for a so called  #8220;Diddy club #8221; is quite something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 00:32:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aye mate, the europa league has totally the same precedent as the IRN BRU Cup. Definitely got me there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 01:09:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aye because you #8217;re one of the two biggest teams in the fucking country.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 01:14:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Too good for us. He #8217;s such a calming influence on the team it #8217;s unreal. I can #8217;t seem him staying with us for longer than his one year contract, he #8217;ll either be our player of the season when we win the title or get promoted through the playoffs or go to a top six team in the Premiership if we fail to do so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 01:39:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aye it #8217;s shocking fair enough but my point was for a fanbase that calls United a diddy team you do seem to love to watch us fail.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 01:19:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'LL PAINT YOU A PICTURE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[TOMT] [MUSIC] Remember the chorus, but when I google it it comes up with nothing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 13:52:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>The chorus is: Woah oh the girl has gotta go The only thing she #8217;s got is falling him from her clothes And her love for the nightlife So count one two What #8217;s a girl to do When falling in love is the worst move for you Woah ooooooo oh oh oh I think her heart just broke. It #8217;s absolutely shite songwriting but it #8217;s been stuck in my head for years and driving me nuts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 00:41:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>"The natural order of clubs" oh get fucked Chick. Dundee United are in the championship because they were shite and got relegated, the likes of Ross County and Hamilton, though smaller than United, are there because they fucking deserve to be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>30 Years of Dominance ended tonight :(</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 02:34:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 02:43:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some Italian tycoon took them over in the early 2030s. Their stadium is now 18 times the population of Pitmedden</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 03:06:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just as disappointed as you are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 13:32:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>:( Though tbf I #8217;m 74 Ingame so it might be time to go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 16:09:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>in the first 10 games, I won 3, drew 6, and lost 1, so already I was on the backfoot. I managed to recover and needed to win the last game of the season against Celtic. I drew 2-2 despite being 2-0 up in the first ten minutes. Some people would say that I got FM'ed though, to be honest, I made a lot of really fucking stupid formation and transfer decisions earlier on in the season so I got what I deserved in the end. Also, mate you commented that twice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 16:50:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup, annoyingly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 18:57:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>The furthest that anyone has gotten was Formartine United and Rangers reaching the round of 16 of the UCL (in different seasons). The best Scottish teams have done in a season is that all 6 teams who qualified for Europe reached the group stages of their respective competitions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 19:05:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually, I forgot to mention that the furthest my hibs team have reached is the UCL Semi-Finals</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 20:27:26</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;With that being said, our D.O.F has been spending the last few months setting up a scouting network, data analysis framework and integrating this into all levels of the club going forward from absolutely nothing. Yes, that hasn't existed at our club since the times of Walter Smith (or in terms of Data Analysis, maybe even Advocaat), so who knows what the fuck McCoist  amp; Warburton were playing at for years. What the fuck. I was going to say something witty to mock Ranger's current situation but... 1. Glass Houses 2. I'm too stunned that a club that size don't have this shit in place already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The next Rangers manager walking into Auchenhowie on his first day.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 20:30:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 20:30:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>bless r/scottishfootball and it's lack of bans for shitposting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 20:36:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alt titles include: Csabo laszlo's first day at United. Paul Hartley walking into the Falkirk Dressing room for the first time. Owen Coyle first day in Dingwall.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 21:45:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>A fair few football subreddits have shitposting banned. respect for being one of the few who doesn't. Makes the sub a lot more fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 22:12:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the fact this post has gone from 3 upvotes to 0 proves that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 23:05:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>It'll be whoever's the manager after Rodgers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scottish Goalkeeper Jordan Archer attempts to out shitfest Sunderland Keeper Mika</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 23:22:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 00:21:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Each was more ridiculous than the last. I wasn't calling Archer shit, just saying that he had a shit game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 13:23:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, I just assumed it was Mika because it wasn #8217;t Jason Steele and he was the only Sunderland keeper I could think of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 20:29:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Laugh all we want, Archer is clearly rated highly enough to get called up to our national team.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shabba's Shaggers body Hartley's Hammerthrowers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 02:20:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 23:39:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>memories do not open by The Chainsmokers... fight me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Si Ferry Meets...Frank McAvennie Episode 1 - Making it Late at St Mirren, West Ham, London  amp; Celtic</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 00:07:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The "Morning Routine" Scene in American Psycho. One of the best character introductions in movie history</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 01:15:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 17:26:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually haven #8217;t read the book yet, but I will.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 20:05:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s kinda what #8217;s stopping me from buying the book. I love the movie but the book sounds excessive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 00:25:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did a double take when I saw Aberdeen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Real Leigh Griffiths Blog is being reuploaded every on the Author's new website, here is Chapter 1:  #8216;Wha #8217;s in cherge here? #8217;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 19:36:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(Spoilers Published) Quotes involving Jaime Lannister being a  #8220;knight in shining armour) in AGOT.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 12:19:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know this is a bit annoying but I #8217;m doing my S6 Dissertation on the character and I need quotes describing Him as stated above. I #8217;ve started looking but any help would be appreciated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 15:36:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t know if this counts for this sub, but it seems pretty trashy to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 18:22:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks to everyone who has posted! I think I've got enough now. Cheers lads.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can we show some appreciation for the Staff Regens?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 01:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like yeah, my Mexican midfielder Argenis Saldana is fucking class, but without my Brazilian chief scout Guilherme Rosa Silva would I even know he exists?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 01:45:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the best answer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 02:38:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t. Remind.me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 16:45:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see the answering of this question went well...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 15:19:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>these two pieces of shit gave me two of my most cherished footballing memories when I was 10. Now they're both ruined. I hope the victim takes these cunts to real court so they can fucking rot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 12:40:57</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; r/conspiracy was always deeply and rabidly antisemitic. always. To be fair, that #8217;s not really a historically right wing thing. Anti-Semitism was always quite a widespread issue regardless of political affiliation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 17:37:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah, that's fair. I was just being a pedantic centrist cunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 17:38:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just being pedantic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 02:32:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aaron West and the Roaring Twenties - Our Apartment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 13:20:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not surprised, that cunt has such a dull personality that being gay is all he has.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 13:31:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>THEY CENSORED FAGGOT! Boooooooo That #8217;s one of the funniest lines ever!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 14:23:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aye I get that but  #8220;your cheap and your haggard #8221; is neither as funny or fits as well with melody</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 23:41:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would it really be a proper railroad system without a obvious major route not being there?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 02:14:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>that I #8217;m the only one You only want your way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 20:51:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why would you even want a manager who got out thought by your development team coach?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 21:01:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>*inception music plays in the background*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 23:42:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brechin City - Managed by Darren Dods Dumbarton - they deserved a lot of credit for being an established championship team despite being part-time Dunfermline Athletic - We always beat them. Falkirk - ermmmmm.... can't think of anything. Fuck em. Inverness CT - They made Coll Donaldson good. Somehow. Livingston - They don't give a fuck what anyone thinks of them and it's great. Greenock Morton - Cappielow should be a shittip but it has this strange charm to it that I have to give credit to. Queen of the South - great name. St. Mirren - Jack Ross told Dundee to get fucked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 09:23:53</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; a notable shortage of documented pedophiles in High Political Office Give it time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 17:11:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Needs Holy Mountain. Genuinely might be my song of the year</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 18:54:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could someone please just take the job already? Graeme Murty looks more and more depressed every game and I #8217;m concerned.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 19:26:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>He doesn #8217;t want it though. Whether he wants to stay academy manager, doesn #8217;t think he #8217;s ready or just be a coach for his career, the reasoning is irrelevant he just doesn #8217;t want the job. If he did, I think he #8217;d be manager now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 19:31:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t think he wants the job to be honest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 19:37:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t think he #8217;s a Tim, I just don #8217;t think he wants the job. Surely if he wanted it, he would have it? I guess we #8217;ll find out later on in the week. If he #8217;s appointed officially, then I #8217;ll eat my words</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 20:48:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aye I mentioned that maybe being the case in a different comment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 20:53:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>At this point, they should just let people apply for the job instead of going after someone in particular. It #8217;ll save the board the embarrassment of more people turning them down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 20:53:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or draws 1-1 with Celtic at Parkhead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 23:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I didn #8217;t know that until I read that Statement the board put out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 23:21:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>My name is /u/accentunknown and I approve this /u/bigyellowline message</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 03:39:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>This has a very Pop music meets Jamie T vibe I like it, but I #8217;m not too sure if either audience of the two mentioned above will unless they already like both?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 15:00:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wanted to make an Minecraft RPG Custom Map</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 18:38:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck is going wrong with Partick Thistle? They finished top 6 last year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 02:11:03</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; You would keep the secrets in ya'  gt;You've been keeping paraphernalia, oh Liam Gallagher - "Wall of Glass"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 03:13:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stephen Thompson getting into a fight at one of the Dundee derbies. Simon Murray taking a picture of himself in a Hibs training top before United's play-off final against Hamilton. Wato Kuate losing his shit at getting substituted, starting on Mark Durnan, then angrily stomping down the tunnel like a baby who had his favourite toy taken from him. Dundee United beating Dundee (it fucking counts)... then being drawn with Dundee again in the next round. United (guess who I support) getting beat 6-2 by Ross County when the away fans couldn't see most of the match through the mist and the fog.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 02:13:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the sake of privacy, let's call him Ian C... no waits that too obvious... I.Cathro.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yeah mate, people are really scared of a singer in a emo band.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 20:33:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 20:38:30</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;and also takes Ryan Dow away fuck off, you're keeping him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 02:59:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably Highhammer Mountain. Well, not Highhammer mountain, more the pathetic assortment of shanty towns that have developed around the mountain itself. doesn't matter how many times King Barbolini sounds out his army to "dismantle them", they will props themselves back up. Funny how gold will always attract the poor and the desperate, isn't it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 03:06:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hah don't be silly, Dwarves aren't always fuc- *remembers that I literally had an entire city of Dwarves get massacred*... you know what, you might have point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 00:27:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>if Southampton call back Lewis I'm gonna cry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 03:43:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>A Bridge, twenty-six miles long, 5 horse carts wide, that connects two continents together. it's always been there, it's made of this jet black stone, and no one really knows when it was built.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Michael Stewart, Chris Sutton, Stephen Craigan</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 18:30:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shag, marry, Kill?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 01:16:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know what, fair enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 22:29:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>What Actually Happened: Salinae, the great Rubritican explorer, embarked on his most ambition expodition yet, to the peak of Volsii Major, to meet the God-Emperor Niclion and his Court personally. He would die, being overcome by starvation and the blistering cold. Twisted Story: Here's the thing, his body was never found, and Salinae made the journey alone, saying that only he had the experience to attempt this. And because Salinae was so loved by the people of Rubritica, they just assumed that the Gods were so blown away of this mortal who had managed the journey, they made him immortal, and gave him the role of "God of the Seas."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 00:17:00</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Do the people think they'll see him one day No. He's a god now, he's above them. Why would he?  gt;Why was he loved by them? (forgive me if this doesn't make too much sense, I'm still filling out the details and I'd some stuff to be up to interpretation because I'm an annoying fuck who likes to keep people guessing) The Rubriticans weren't a sea faring people. Their home city was further inland, and while they were conquering Novitoria, they never really bothered to venture into the Daerian Ocean to the west, The Cold Sea in the north or to the Prasnia Sea in the south east. They didn't use it for trade, there was already land routes through Volsii Mountains to the Gallisian Tribes in the east and the Kingdom of Kelatria in the North West, so why would they bother? Salinae saw differently. (By this point, I am making this up as I go) He was the son of a caravan merchant, and had seen the ships in Deltby Harbour travelling back and forth to places unknown, and he had heard of the far off lands like Prestonia and Quokaire. After some convincing, he and his father invested in a ship that would go from the Borginia to El-Sayyidin, the capital of Prestonia. the trip was a success, garnering a large amount of wealth for his family. Word began to spread of this young man who was making journeys back and forth the South Eastern Sea. Not only that, but he was documenting his travels, and copies of these journals spread far and wide. he soon moved away from a life of merchant trade and became a full on explorer. He was the first Rubritican to see the Pyramids of Victrux, to delve into the Selvian Jungles and meet their mysterious inhabitants and to fight Orcs in the Isolated Highlands with the men of North Strathee. He was honoured for his achievements by the Emperor himself, who announced that the South Eastern Sea would forever be known as "The Sea of Salinae." Though he is now gone, his legacy remains. the Praetor who is charge of the Imperial Navy is dubbed the "Praetor Salinorum" and the Rubritican translation of Sailor is "Salinaro".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 13:33:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Presumably he signed the contract at gunpoint.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The SPFL ( amp; Souleymane Coulibaly) sing  #8220;Let It Snow #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 15:48:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 18:42:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Derek McInnes is shite in the big games.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dundee United 3-0 Livingston</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 00:13:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Video of Dundee United Left Back Jamie Robson driving drunk. Later tweets accuse him of domestic abuse.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 17:11:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 17:44:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apparently, he was drinking a Venom cocktail. I posted this because it was related to Scottish Football, if the accusations are false, then they'll fade. But Logan Chalmers offering a lot of money to remove doesn't make things look good for Jamie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What are some Scottish Football personalities getting for Christmas?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 17:45:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 15:42:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>After Laughter by Paramore</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 01:13:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>doesn't fit into the r/popheads mould, but "Secrets" by Makeout. It's the worst pop-punk song ever written, the melodies are all over the place, the voice is excruciatingly painful and the lyrics are awful and so aimed the song might as well be called "fuck you Rebecca McCallister the girl I dated freshman year in Highschool"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 03:16:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's the:  gt;Fuck You! at the end of the song that makes me wanna give a blowjob to a Barret 50 Cal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 03:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Genuinely can #8217;t tell if you #8217;re a ross county fan or a time travelling Dundee United fan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 14:54:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nadir ciftci</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 01:26:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Especially the shitposters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 01:27:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Happy new year lads!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 19:19:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>You've not lost this season to them yet...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 20:31:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same. though personally I have a bad habit of liking songs just because they're relatively upbeat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dundee United sign ex-Killie centre mid Craig Slater on loan from Colchester.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 19:15:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 03:22:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>A day may come, when Lily Peet comes up with an original title for a video... BUT IT IS NOT THIS DAY!!! (yes I am aware of the pettiness of this gripe)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 03:37:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could Lily please cite her sources? Just once... Just for me...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 18:11:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dundee United losing attracts the same attention from Rangers fans as Rangers losing from Celtic fans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 18:32:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apparently, we're to blame for where they are now because we thought a club should suffer consequences for being liquidated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 18:35:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think there has ever been much love between the two clubs, but United were one of the clubs who were against Rangers being allowed back into the Premiership, and considering their repeated reference to "Karma", that likely is the main reason.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 19:28:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>They #8217;re rangers fans, you could walk into the nerve it #8217;s so fucking massive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:21:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scottish Queen coming for all y'all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 05:12:06</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Inspirational Quotes can get in the fucking bin. no inspirational quotes are actually inspirational. If you #8217;re inspired by 12 words, maybe you #8217;re a simpleton? #8221; - Duncan McKay from Terrace Scottish Football Podcast</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Celtic Twitter is a strange place</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 17:02:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 17:23:43</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Muh SFA conspiracy against team that has won over 100 trophies #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 17:53:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://twitter.com/duncmckay/status/953279834557382656 Was going to post this originally but thought I #8217;d let the original speak for its own mental self</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dundee United sign Thomas Mikkelson on loan and Sam Stanton joins permanently after joining on loan in the summer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 15:45:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.dundeeunitedfc.co.uk/news/5494/MIKKELSEN-RETURNS-TO-TANNADICE.html https://www.dundeeunitedfc.co.uk/news/5493/STANTON-SIGNS-PERMANENT-CONTRACT.html</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 22:43:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>So would the court case after the episode aired</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 01:07:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>just "stanning" in general to be honest. There are artists that I love, sure, but I will still acknowledge their flaws, something that most "stans" don't seem to be able to do. Noel Gallagher makes great music but is a cunt Ed Sheeran's singles typically suck. Blackbear needs to take a year off where he doesn't release everything. just for some examples. also, Stans seem to be unnecessarily mean to people who don't like their faves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 17:30:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're going to absolutely shag us. I'm already getting nightmares of Ryan Christie effortlessly sprinting past Tam Scobbie and Jamie Robson with ease before lifting the ball over Harry Lewis' despairing, flailing arms into the back of the net.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 20:47:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lend us Scott Wright for six months and yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 20:52:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then we #8217;re fucking going down</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 13:59:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dundee United signed an ex-Liverpool striker to stave off relegation... It didn #8217;t help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 16:45:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m onboard this bandwagon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 19:27:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know Souttar scored an own goal but how did he look after that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 13:45:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just stay at Hampden for fuck #8217;s sake. One poor renovation doesn #8217;t mean we should just chuck it into the sea</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 15:16:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just think it makes more sense to keep a neutral venue. Especially when you have a derby as bitterly pointlessly poisonous as the old firm. You just fucking know that if Ibrox was decided to host the Scottish Cup final then every shitebag Bhoy with a blog would give a 1000 words on why this proved all of their sfa conspiracy pish correct Nah mate, fuck that. Keep hampden. Also all of the criticism are fixable. Too far away? Can be fixed The atmosphere is poor? Don #8217;t blame the stadium for your part time fans being wank, I #8217;ve been to Hampden twice and the atmosphere was class.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 15:24:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean... you #8217;re not wrong. Point still stands though, if the atmosphere is poor that #8217;s more on the fans than the stadium.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 19:40:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>the sample of "Maria Maria" in "Wild Thoughts" is disrespectful as fuck... Because it's not even a fucking sample, it's just the same song with worse lyrics and the acoustic guitar removed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 01:48:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>He said acolyte, not Vulkan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dundee United 0-3 Greenock Morton. Kill me. Kill me now</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 18:17:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 16:06:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Flair checks out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 02:18:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>She sings  #8220;fuck yourself #8221; instead of  #8220;love yourself #8221;....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 17:24:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please please please please please please please please</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 17:26:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>He was also in the United end for the Group Stage Dundee Derby.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 17:39:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t quite get why you care to be honest. He was a member of the worst United team of all time. He never scored against you lot once. Apart from the standard dislike of players from your rivals, I can #8217;t see why he would get singled out over say Toshney, who not only was a Dundee fan but also played for Dundee in the past.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dundee United sign Grant Gillespie.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 17:57:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 00:22:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Loved this boy at Dundee United. gutted that LAFC didn't try and go for him but ah well. might try and pick up a SKC top now... off topic but could LAFC sign a Scottish player that isn't Calum Mallace? that'd be great cheers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 00:51:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is a pretty impressive pass to be fair... to be honest, this is my first season getting into the MLS, so I'm basing my opinion on what others have said.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 00:59:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>sounds like every Scottish footballer playing at a decent level right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 01:27:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>*AND IIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIII* **HOLY SHIT** *WILL ALLLLWAYS LOVE YOU* **I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'D DO THIS TO ME GODDAMMIT HOW COULD YOU DO THIS TO ME** (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Sa8NREI_IPs)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 01:33:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>SOME BALD GUY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 03:12:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've read this script somewhere before...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 04:17:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Vietnam-esque flashbacks*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 21:11:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>a lot of players but not that many good ones by the looks of things... I'm quite worried to say the least. Emil Lyng - I actually quite like the look of this guy, but he seems very clumsy... very very clumsy. also he has the widest shoulders I've ever seen. Craig Slater - probably the Fyvie replacement, but you can't really replace Fyvie, so I feel sorry for the guy Grant Gillespie - Like the look of this, hope he kicks Morgan all the way to Parkhead in the next St. Mirren match. Brandon Mason - why? what was the point of this signing? yeah we needed back up for left back, but we needed a right back more and we didn't sign one. Thomas Mikkelsen - No. he did okay at this level last time but I don't think he's gonna get the service and his arrival has split the United fans even further down the middle. Logan Martin and Idris Kadded - the fact that two signings who are on amateur contracts look the promising makes me about as depressed as when Greg Docherty volleyed it in at New Douglas Park. Also Stanton signed permanently which is a good signing. love the guy, especially his inability to run sideways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 21:48:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please God no.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Terrace Scottish Football Podcast for 01/02/2018 - "Goodbye Stewart Regan"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:35:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 13:29:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I support United and I #8217;m not getting this at all. We #8217;re in the second tier and are miles behind first place, the only automatic qualification spot. Why is our owner spunking 3 million on a project that will probably fail and close in 2 years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 01:42:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>The quicker he sells the club the better, sick to death of the Thompson's and their bullshit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 00:14:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why does the commentator say De Bruyne like De BROOOOOOYNE. Is that how you #8217;re supposed to say it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 00:57:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>The BBC aren #8217;t showing the ads and to be honest I #8217;m entirely okay with it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 01:01:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>They go back to the analysts, which as somebody who rarely watches the NFL is way better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 01:06:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely one of the advantages of the bbc having a no ads policy. It helps that the two analysts (Jason Bell  amp; Osi Umenyiora) are fucking hilarious and work great with Mark Chapman the presenter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 01:17:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>While everyone watches the ads, the brits get to watch Gareth Southgate!!!! Why is he here?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 01:25:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah so that #8217;s why Brady #8217;s a quaterback</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 02:22:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh Timberlake baby what is you doing? Just get to Cry Me a River already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 02:32:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>If this happened at the World Cup Final I would fucking hate football. The fuck is this? He isn #8217;t even singing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 03:39:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Welp... R.I.P the city of Philadelphia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 03:40:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes but if they lose they won #8217;t be able to rebuild from the ashes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 03:49:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Feel ya from across the Atlantic buddy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 04:20:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow I can #8217;t believe the sun is out at this ti- oh no wait that #8217;s just Philadelphia.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 04:27:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are some pats fans really calling this shit rigged? Good to know that no matter the sport, the successful teams are always insecure paranoid fucktrumpets when they don #8217;t get success for once.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 19:37:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is Bojack Horseman big enough yet for the reddit circlejerk to fully kick in? The subreddit has just over 100,000 subscribers in comparison to the Rock and Morty subreddit which is well over 700,000 subscribers. Unless the next season of BJ triggers an explosion of fans then I can #8217;t see it happening. Also I really fucking hope it doesn #8217;t.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 17:34:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can somebody chuck the hat back out please?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 14:07:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>How the fuck...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Daniel Candeias #8217; radar. Creativity across the fucking board</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 00:56:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 00:57:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>[tweet that this is from. gives some clarification to what some of it means in the replies](https://twitter.com/thespflradar/status/961715363552681984)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 12:30:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Always confused me when he was put in the same bin as Carlos Pena and Dalcio by the media and Celtic fans. He #8217;s arguably been the best winger in the league so far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hearts at it again with a fantastic programme front cover.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 15:59:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 16:04:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>xA is expected assists [he gives more clarification in the replies to this](https://mobile.twitter.com/thespflradar/status/961715363552681984)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 16:12:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>*stares down at the rain hoodie I #8217;m wearing* **Coughs Awkwardly**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Request] Dundee United Away Kit 16-17 Small or Medium</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 16:29:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Know it #8217;s a bit obscure but if anyone has one message me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 16:29:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did much better in Parkhead game I thought</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 01:12:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Letter to Home Sci-Fi 643 words this is a concept for a horror sci-fi short story idea that I had. I wrote this in order to get a better idea of the world and the main character. https://drive.google.com/file/d/1ibZU1lJRs6CEtDvZPXIiHum4AF9vxO1f/view?usp=sharing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 03:00:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>WE DON'T HAVE TROUBLE SLEEPING</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 03:15:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah he is smiling not doing that duck face pout thing he always does</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 21:03:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it just me or are Davies and Lamela struggling to link up so far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 22:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Victor Wanyama Thundercunt incoming Edit - I stand corrected</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 23:14:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Football teams from Dundee  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 00:37:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>^Nah ^I #8217;m ^good ^thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Roses are Red, Violets are blue...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 14:18:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You finish this punchline I #8217;m too lazy to!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 15:05:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>If he does more songs like Castle on the hill then I won #8217;t be mad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 00:11:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Arab or Derry boy?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 00:24:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not disagreeing with that analysis</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 21:33:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kieran Tierney is whatever the Celtic version of Staunch is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 21:37:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>That goalkeeper was stumbling, just a simple touch and it probably would #8217;ve gone it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The New Saints 1 - 2 Dumbarton - Dumbarton are through to the IRN-BRU Cup Final</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 22:32:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Inverness CT 3-2 Crusaders - Inverness will play Dumbarton in the IRN BRU CUP Final</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 20:11:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 00:06:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just ignore Dundee United losing to crusaders...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Celtic - Imperious Superpower or Accident Waiting to Happen?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 01:46:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is your meant to be this heavy?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 21:40:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 22:02:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ham you! #129305; #129305; #129305;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 22:42:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>How about vodka?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 02:12:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wanna fucking die</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 02:38:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m personally excited for us doing a cowdenbeath.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>LIAM HENDERSON DA CONSEGNARE!!!!!!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 17:30:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Aberdeen's record vs the 5 other teams in the top six so far this season</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 19:29:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Celtic - 0 out of a possible 9 points Aberdeen 0-3 Celtic Celtic 3-0 Aberdeen Aberdeen 0-2 Celtic Rangers - 0 out of a possible 9 points Rangers 3-0 Aberdeen Aberdeen 1-2 Rangers Rangers 2-0 Aberdeen Hibernian - 6 out of a possible 9 points Hibernian 0-1 Aberdeen Aberdeen 4-1 Hibernian Hibernian 2-0 Aberdeen Hearts - 2 out of 6 points Hearts 0-0 Aberdeen Aberdeen 0-0 Hearts Kilmarnock - 6 out of 6 points Kilmarnock 1-3 Aberdeen Aberdeen 3-1 Kilmarnock in total, Aberdeen have gained a total of 14 points out of a possible 39.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stephen Thompson resigns as Dundee United Chairman.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 12:45:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 12:48:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also just to get this out of the way. Dear Rangers fans: Dundee United fans are delighted he is gone, to make this a point of mockery for the club is fucking stupid, nobody likes him at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 12:50:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aye the website crashed after about five minutes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 13:02:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god... fire that boy into the sun fucking hell</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 13:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was announced that he would leave at the end of the season. But instead he #8217;s left now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 13:24:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure, but some rangers fans think this mean we #8217;re getting liquidated or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 13:32:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>we #8217;ll be in the championship another season, but that third season really is our last chance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 15:29:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>That or we have only played at tannadice twice this year and money #8217;s tight so he #8217;s getting out while he can</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 16:29:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>No clue. That is what worries me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 18:00:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aaron Kuhl What the actual fuck was this? this boy had garnered interest from Manchester City and Arsenal at the time, so when he joined us on loan, it's fair to say I was excited, but what the fuck was that? the man could never play a forward ball, had a shocking haircut, could get outmuscled by a dying moth, and was just all around fucking shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 21:55:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you a reading fan? If so, what did the fans think of him?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 22:03:17</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; didn #8217;t like to tackle Or be tackled, or even be in the consideration for a tackle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 22:14:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I await the job offers with baited breath. Though to be fair to those academy coaches, they probably predicted that they could coach some of his bad habits out of him, but he maybe just peaked too early.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 22:51:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe he was just doomed by our bad management if he was decent under Adkins.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 01:18:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a win. Laurent Ciman looks to be some signing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 01:22:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>My only real concern about this match was Urena, he seemed to be the weak link in our attack and he threw a hissyfit when he was being subbed off. But apart from that... FUCKING GET IN LADS!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 01:26:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>If he was, then I have no issue with that, a little bit of piss-boiling is entirely fine with me. But it did look like from the stream I was watching that he was raging.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 01:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just realised we kept a clean sheet despite having to make a last minute change in defence. Now that's encouraging</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 03:02:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I meant Zimmerman getting injured in the last minute and Jakovic having to come in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 03:08:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah nah it #8217;s cool</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"I keep hearing you've got a problem at right back and people have not looked at Richard Tait," - Stephen Robinson believes that his first choice right back deserves a Scotland call up.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 19:00:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 01:58:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lands of Ulstan and beyond (My Fantasy World) - It's not very original. But also kinda is. also secret nazi elf samurai The Cooperation of Planets (my Sci-Fi Universe) - Elon Musk's wank fantasy while simultaneously being a communist's worst nightmare. essentially Corporations own planets and the UN was too late to bring the fuckers under control</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So... anything you guys like about ol #8217; Musky?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 11:27:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m don #8217;t like him either (that #8217;s why I #8217;m here) though I #8217;m just curious if anybody here thinks there #8217;s a positive to the guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 15:40:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who is downvoting this? I was just curious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 20:32:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reckon him launching that Tesla into the space is what caused the rise? It #8217;s certainly made me rethink what I thought of the guy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Queen of the South 1-3 Dundee United - DUNDEE UNITED WIN A GAME OF FOOTBALL! FUCKING GET IN LADS!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 23:53:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 19:02:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>can't believe we've signed an RB to play RB. madness. insanity</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>David Wotherspoon called up by the Canadian National Team</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 01:04:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 02:35:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>not the first time an Escobar's been taken out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 14:14:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>The  #8220;its never your successful friends posting the inspirational quotes #8221; thing has kinda become an inspirational quote.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scotland #8217;s new away kit unveiled. Thoughts?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 10:23:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dundee United 2-3 Queen of the South - Right then, Whiskey or Vodka?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 22:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cursed image</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 22:09:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dundee United 1-1 Dunfermline Athletic</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 19:40:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 03:43:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>HIDING WITH THE BOYS IN YOUR BEDROOM</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 04:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's been long day thinking of this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 18:15:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>he was man of the match, Laszlo's just an idiot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 18:32:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well we started off so well that it seemed like a stroke of genius. Then Fraser Fyvie and Scott Fraser both got injured and the Csaba hype train derailed and crashed into an orphanage for blind amputee children. Better than John Hughes at least.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 20:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>The best way to sum up a fyvieless United is that it was like taking the medication away from an anxiety sufferer. Fyvie was so assured on the ball and was always there as an option it meant that while we had it we were guaranteed a good pass and it allowed the other players to get in position for the next move or to calm down if the opposition had been on the attack. Laszlo simply wasn #8217;t able to find a suitable replacement, Slater, who I assume was meant to be that, is while still a decent option, nowhere near as good as Fyvie, who is far too good for the championship.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Player Spotlight II | Barry Douglas with Stuart Armstrong and Jason Cummings with Callum McGregor</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 21:53:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 04:22:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Somehow convincing them that Edinburgh is our cultural capital.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 02:24:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>believe or not, but in about 4 years, you're not gonna spend every waking moment of your life playing video games!! Also, you're gonna have a 1-month long relationship that's gonna mentally fuck you up for way longer than it should've but you and the person in it will be best friends like 6 months after the break-up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #8220;The fans don #8217;t believe in us  amp; they shouldn #8217;t believe in us. We have given them nothing to believe in. #8221; - Dundee United Goalkeeper Harry Lewis gives a blunt interview to The Courier.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 13:12:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 15:04:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be fair that was a riddy even then.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 22:56:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can think of better ways for it to go to be honest</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 22:59:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Both my teams bottled a win today. I #8217;m just gonna go drink</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 23:07:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Couldn #8217;t watch the game. how the fuck did that happen?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>After 45 in-game years I finally did it</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 00:33:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 02:23:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah once you break the 30-year barrier things get pretty fucking weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 02:24:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't even know what to do now. Do I carry on? Do I finally buy Fm18 and hope it doesn't crash on my laptop? I'm genuinely fucking lost</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 03:03:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is fine it's fine this is fine fine it's fine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 03:55:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>nah this save has been on and off for the past 3 years. I'm not that bad... mostly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 15:19:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>here's the team for those curious: GK: [Nathan](https://imgur.com/wiOuS56) RB: [Antoine Renard](https://imgur.com/kJlDsQO) RCB: [Stefanos Giaoutzis](https://imgur.com/4aaI9dt) LCB: [Bruno Iglesias](https://imgur.com/5HLsaNQ) LB: [Angel Gonzalez](https://imgur.com/iPvVdF2) RCM: [Nicolas Alvarez](https://imgur.com/BCBGWpO) LCM: [Javier Almiron](https://imgur.com/TYZ1fzR) RW: [Daniel Torralba](https://imgur.com/Jda7FSh) CAM: [Jake Moyses](https://imgur.com/hU8LOVo) LW: [Yo Muta](https://imgur.com/tnjuh5M) ST: [Matt Finnie](https://imgur.com/73lVq6i) Substitutes: GK: [Michel Wittkowski](https://imgur.com/8nPcGcS) CB: [Alfredo Lopez](https://imgur.com/CDYcbNg) CB:[Safet Krajnc](https://imgur.com/BCBGWpO) CM: [Ibrahim Aarab](https://imgur.com/uVZbK2i) W: [Tom Smith](https://imgur.com/ArcM64K) CAM: [Manuel](https://imgur.com/QrWHceo) ST: [Mouchcine Yildirim](https://imgur.com/ujNjikI) Formation = 4-5-1 Mentality = Attacking Fluidity = Very Fluid Tactics = none, maybe allow wingers to swap</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 15:20:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here!](https://www.reddit.com/r/footballmanagergames/comments/8alord/after_45_ingame_years_i_finally_did_it/dx0jdeg/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 15:29:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>this hasn't been a good few weeks has it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 16:20:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really don #8217;t get the appeal of listening to someone sing about parties. He doesn #8217;t even write party songs, he writes songs about parties.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 19:28:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I personally never thought that we were the best team. But I didn #8217;t think we were this poor. I we #8217;ll find out properly where we stand in comparison with the rest of the league over the next few months. I #8217;m not that bothered about this season as long as we don #8217;t embarrass ourselves, which to me would being knocked out of play off contention in August or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 21:57:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Football Manager 14</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 02:13:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m Not even a hibs fan but aye GLORY GLORY TO THE FUCKING HIBEES</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Great Goal by Scottish Winger Johnny Russell for Sporting Kansas City against LA Galaxy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 15:23:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Daily Record's 10 minute documentary on Albion Rover's relegation fight</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 18:46:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 18:54:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Surprised this wasn't posted here already so here it is. the best part of this documentary has to be Stuart Malcolm's rant at Gary Fisher, which was described by Shaughan McGuigan of the Terrace Podcast as "a team talk written by Irvine Welsh":  gt; Fuck sake Fish! C'mon tae fuck, what's Happening? It's a fucking lazy leg! You don't fucking work em, we're comfortable in the game, he goes inside and you stick a fucking leg out and give him a free fucking shot at goal! Fuck Sake! the Fucking work we do *inaudible* we're doing the right hings! get tight, don't fucking sell yersel! Fucking lazy leg is fucking lazy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 18:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Albion Rovers'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dundee United 1-0 St. Mirren</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 22:40:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 15:23:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>that would be hilarious. though your going to lose to us last game of the season so it won't happen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 04:51:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Title: The Men of Leith vs The Bavarian Juggernaut Genre: Sports Fiction Word Count: 3848 Link: https://accentunknown.wordpress.com/2018/04/12/the-men-of-leith-vs-the-bavarian-juggernaut/#more-654</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dundee United 1-0 Falkirk</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 19:05:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Brechin City 0-5 Dundee United</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 23:27:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 01:04:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>there was this song that I listened to when I was about 8. I could never find it again but the entire chorus is superglued to my brain:  gt; WOAH THAT GIRL HAS GOT TO GO  gt; THE ONLY THING SHE'S GOT IS FALLING FROM HER CLOTHES  gt; AND HER LOVE FOR THE NIGHTLIFE  gt; SO COUNT ONE TWO  gt; WHATS A GIRL TO DO  gt; WHEN FALLING IN LOVE IS THE WORST MOVE FOR YOU?  gt; WOAH OH OH OH OH  gt; I THINK HER HEART JUST BROKE I wouldn't mind so much if it wasn't Simple Plan levels of fucking gratingly catchy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Queen of the South 3-0 Dundee United - United battered by Queens but are guaranteed a play-off place thanks to results elsewhere</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 18:02:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 18:03:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I fucking hate Nicky Clark for prolonging this torture further.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 23:52:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hamish MacAlpine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 02:54:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Think it's for the best. I can't imagine how they'll manage to get the aliens that aren't the Asari or the Quarians to look good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 01:25:48</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;How do You Visualize Your World? Badly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 01:40:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>All of them, well at least the original rough drafts of the cultures are all based off of real cultures \(this for a medieval\-esque fantasy world. Strathee = Scotland Westershire = England and Wales Lothor = France Rodmark = The Nordic Countries Kelatria = an Amalgamation of Eastern European kingdoms and powers Torintila = Iberia The Dunstone Isles = Ireland and Venice The Rubritican Empire = The Roman Empire I've expanded on them so now they're pretty different to what I based them off of but you can still see the inspirations, especially in the names of the towns and people</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 01:44:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>**THE COOPERATION OF PLANETS** "How would the colonization of space look if the privatization of Space flight was allowed to continue"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dundee United 2-0 Livingston</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 18:36:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 19:03:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>First one is Dunfermline vs United on tuesday, then the 2nd leg on friday</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 03:53:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>[My Comment from the last time this question came up](https://www.reddit.com/r/poppunkers/comments/70a6fr/unpopular_poppunk_opinions/dn20xy1/) Turnover are the pop punk band for people who are too Hipster for The Wonder Years. Sister Cities does not deserve the backlash it's going to get in about a week or so. Some people really need to realise that Pop Punk is called POP punk for a fucking reason. What did you expect from State Champs? did you expect a fucking metalcore breakdown or something. Matt Skiba is a better vocalist and Lyricist than Tom Delonge, but a weaker Guitarist. on that subject, Tom's voice isn't *Iconic* it's shit. Joe Taylor is a terrible lyricist The Wonder Years have gotten better with every release People only hated 5SOS due to it's fanbase Ya'll slept on Transit and now they're gone. Are you happy now? Now we have fucking Makeout, I hope you're fucking pleased with yourselves. don't complain about Pop Punk all sounding the same then get pissy when a band changes their sound and Finally \- People who hate Unpopular opinions threads only hate them because they get upset when people don't agree with them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 16:19:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you ship worldwide?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 03:41:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Taylor's writing just doesn't do it for me, sorry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 03:42:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>which opinion are you referring to?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 23:41:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Title: Heavenly Cemetary Word Count: 533 Feedback: General thoughts Link: [https://accentunknown.wordpress.com/2018/04/30/heavenly\-cemetary/](https://accentunknown.wordpress.com/2018/04/30/heavenly-cemetary/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 00:22:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>First time poster. What #8217;s Leeching? If it #8217;s stealing content. Then no. And the fact the blog has the same name as my reddit username should be sufficient proof surely?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sam Nicholson joins Colorado Rapids from Minnesota United as part of swap deal</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 19:14:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 19:15:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>A weird move from MNUFC, as he #8217;s been playing well for them recently and they have injuries in his position.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 01:27:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>[The Menzingers \- After The Party](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ghTYSXQnqbg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In the banter years, are Dundee United the Blur to Rangers #8217; Oasis?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 17:38:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 19:33:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>To drag this metaphor out further, are Raith Rovers Pulp?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 16:09:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>just 2 inches taller. that's all. then i'd be over 6 foot and happy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 23:15:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't have much to say about this. What I will say is that I fucking hate our fans. Clapping off Flood? are you fucking serious?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 15:17:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>whoever the worst starting player for Ross County has been</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 17:13:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd buy this. maybe not for the summer but it'd be a fucking great winter shirt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 17:34:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>90210 acoustic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 18:07:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>We Know</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 18:15:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who will Billy McKay relegate next?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 02:29:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>dinnae</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 02:31:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Willo Flood.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 02:33:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Staaaaand and Deliverrrrr Your money or your life!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 21:51:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t even want to look at mine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 22:55:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope! Did get to watch Bilel Mohsni tho, so minor victories.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 01:52:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Loving the tentative opening of the window by the camera guy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Welcome to the Championship Thistle.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 15:18:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 15:19:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>[source](https://twitter.com/leeceeexvee/status/998550658054807554?s=21)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 21:14:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cove rangers and Cowdenbeath in the same group  #128064;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Partick Thistle playing squad update - Keown, Storey and Edwards top departure list.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 21:16:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 14:24:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>This comment came straight from 2008</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 03:22:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scott McTominay, I #8217;m so sorry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 03:25:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you tried r/soccerstreams ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 18:50:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>hope he does well, just not as good as us and we win every time we play against each other.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 00:20:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>**I HAVE MORE YOUTUBE MONEY THAN GOD I CAN AFFORD THESE THINGS**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 00:21:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>also *Jesse Cox:* I can't get the nurse to get into my house. *Totalbiscuit :* Right... Have you tried Chloroform?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 00:31:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>A song like this needed Kyle Thrash or someone like him to direct the music video. this is just... bland.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 17:49:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I CANT READ AND I CANT WRITE BUT IT DOESNT MATTER COS I SUPPORT THE ABERDEEN AND I CAN DRIVE A TRACTOR</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just Finished High School...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 19:31:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now What?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 19:32:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but... in between that bit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 20:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>this is incredible. I'll say it now. Adam Hann is a fucking genius and may be one of the greatest guitarists of this \(or any\) generation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 23:48:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stoke fans get what they deserve</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 23:56:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>But it isn't After the Party by The Menzingers tho...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 12:15:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t watch basketball, ELI5?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 12:27:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just watched this and seen a more detailed explanation. Still baffled to be honest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 12:31:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>How did he not know the score. Basketball stadiums have scoreboards surely?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 15:48:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>All time low - dear Maria count me in or blink 182 - Feeling this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 21:04:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>What has the executive producer actually said?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 21:09:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Presumably they #8217;re called the dominion because the dart didn #8217;t land on federation or empire.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 21:11:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>No loot boxes? Hmm I don #8217;t buy that, I wouldn #8217;t be surprised if they #8217;re called something else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 21:14:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be honest I #8217;m just being pessimistic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 21:15:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has any gameplay demo been improved by having scripted voice actors? Edit: turns out that was in game voice acting. Dear god.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 21:16:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>In fairness, flying looks a lot of fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 21:17:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>If the quality of the writing here is on par with the finished game then I #8217;m playing this muted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 21:19:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh ^oh ^no</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 21:20:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.reddit.com/r/Games/comments/8pud8r/comment/e0e96t1?st=JI7SBLD9 amp;sh=1f70e907</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 21:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lil yachty doesn #8217;t give a single fuck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 21:23:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>To me, it sounded more like a bad script than a bad host.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 14:19:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those shorts are so baggy I thought he was wearing a kilt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 03:45:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check YouTube</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 16:33:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would #8217;ve preferred T.a.t.u., thought that #8217;s mostly because they #8217;re the only Russian musicians I know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 16:36:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because the game doesn #8217;t start at night...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 16:45:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually agree with you there, the opening match should be at night.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 13:57:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has Fernando Muslera just been around forever?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 15:27:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Suarez looks like he #8217;s player In a charity match who retired fifteen years ago</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 12:11:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>This looks like the movie poster for a film with an ending that would make you cry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tannadice Times - Dundee United Season Review 17-18</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 16:03:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 18:57:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just completely inept in every department.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 02:15:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The author of Peter Pan was born here. And so was the original lead singer of AC/DC.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 19:02:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stick your thunderclap up your arse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 21:01:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Germany please win. The English media is insufferable enough already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 21:58:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>[thank fuck](https://www.reddit.com/r/soccer/comments/8tbhud/comment/e16bcxu?st=JIRTTBIW amp;sh=0a136565)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 04:34:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>After the party is one of the greatest pop punk songs ever written and it has my favourite music video of all time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 17:14:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every Dundee United fan is not shocked in the slightest by Kawashima's incompetence so far in the first two games.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 17:44:37</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I don't want my nations league to become one-sided fiesta like Scottish League for example :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 16:36:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Pretends to be shocked**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I managed to get a signed version of  #8220;The 59 #8217; Sound #8221; for a  #163;1. Any way that I can find out for certain that the signatures are genuine?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 22:34:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 00:57:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>[is this any better?](https://imgur.com/gallery/BoMN9GF) I agree the black on black is annoying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 00:57:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll check it out. Cheers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 01:07:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just to be clear about my intentions, I #8217;m not gonna sell the CD, I #8217;m keeping it. I just wanna know if the signatures are real or not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 01:08:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 01:21:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Comparing them with mine it looks like mine is legit. Thank you very much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 01:28:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>More luck tbh. The shop was struggling to sell Gaslight Anthem cds which is why they were so cheap. Guess the the band isn #8217;t that big in Scotland.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 01:32:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>They #8217;re big in some parts, smaller in others. Scotland seems to be a country that likes its rock strictly Indie, specifically arctic monkeys first album style indie, so it doesn #8217;t surprise me that much that they wouldn #8217;t be that big here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 02:05:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Go ahead, make me the bad guy" \- Pretense by Knuckle Puck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 14:26:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably go support one of the Angus clubs. Probs Forfar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 05:44:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey look it #8217;s the only Good Charlotte I actually like.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 04:40:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was about 7 or 8, I remember listening to this song, which though I did like a lot at the time, in hindsight was very generic, pretty douchey pop rock, but the fucking chorus has been stuck in my head since. I've googled it constantly and found nothing. the band must've removed it from the internet because it's like it didn't exist. here's the chorus for those curious:  gt;Woah oh  gt;  gt;those girls have gotta go  gt;  gt;the only thing she's got is falling from her clothes  gt;  gt;and her love for the nightlife  gt;  gt;so count one two  gt;  gt;whats a girl to do?  gt;  gt;when falling in love is the worst move for you  gt;  gt;woah oh oh oh  gt;  gt;I think her heart just broke Hey I did tell you it wasn't gonna be good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Carling - Second Guesses [Pop] (2018)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 04:49:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tannadice Times - Review of June (and May)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 19:11:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 22:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do think that late burst of form under Strachan was also helped by many of the players coming from celtic, which meant that many of them already had a bond going in. I mean that was part of the reason why Forrest was chosen over Ritchie to start, because he played with Tierney at Celtic and would be further protection for Tierney in a position he's unfamiliar with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 22:54:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>not for long, hopefully. Scott McKenna and Jack Hendry both look decent, as well as Ross McCrorie (though he looks to be a centre mid now)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 02:49:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>is Travis just the unluckiest man on earth?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 02:53:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah they were a thing. He's definitely Halsey's type (White musician with tattoos who critics could accuse of both pretentiousness and being a bit of dick, which even though we all like Blackbear here, people who don't like him have accused him of both).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 03:08:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Noel Gallagher worst thing - [called Corbyn a communist](https://www.nme.com/news/music/noel-gallagher-fuck-jeremy-corbyn-communist-2166527) Best thing - [Secretly donated to Ariana Grande's charity to help those affected by the manchester attack](https://www.nme.com/news/music/noel-gallagher-donates-dont-look-back-anger-royalties-manchester-fund-2085083)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 03:14:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>That all these predictions will be wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 03:38:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think he refers to himself as a socialist, he #8217;s definitely never outright stated he is thats for sure. It #8217;s more that Gallagher believed that being one was an inherently negative thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 03:41:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>But an important line none the less.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 12:51:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>See I thought you were joking, but they literally just took Jupiter and put a blue filter over it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 17:21:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>that is the least Alpha thing I've ever heard in my life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 19:15:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Andy Robertson without a doubt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 01:20:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, in 2005 mainstream rap was two guys shouting about a stripper so I don #8217;t think I get your point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 01:34:19</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Bilel Mohsni Don't you dare put God alongside that filth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 02:01:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aye and we actually appreciated him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 02:03:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh. Fair enough. I had assumed Rangers fans hated him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 02:17:52</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; we just recognise he is a shite player though Some cunt hold me back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 03:17:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s borderline self parody at this point</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 13:52:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>who is this even for? Aren't most Elon Musk fanboys people who do basically no exercise whatsoever?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 18:53:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Using big words don #8217;t make you intelligent mate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 03:54:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Demi Lovato doing a pop punk album would be good. She #8217;s got a good voice for that kinda genre imo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 04:46:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>The menzingers - after the party Fucking poetry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Neck deep - In Bloom: Versions - features a redo of  #8220;In Bloom #8221; with the addition of a saxophone and an acoustic version.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 04:49:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 16:33:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>The video is definitely part of why I love that song</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 02:55:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>!seepoints</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 14:26:32</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; waterparks are trash TAKE MY UPVO-  gt; As It Is are trash Wait a minute.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 20:26:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's a bit of a different one. There's not enough dickheads in the genre. And what I mean by that aren't like actual bad people, like abusers and pedos and shit. Trust me, this genre has far too many of that. I mean people like Noel or Liam Gallagher, people who don't give a fuck and will give their opinion about other bands without worrying about the consequence. Imagine how funny it would be if Ben Barlow or someone gave an interview to Alternative Press where he called Waterparks "a bunch of untalented dye-haired cunts", or something. Similarly, I wish there was more Band Beef. that As It Is vs Palaye Royale stuff was okay but I'd like more. And yes, I did just complain that this scene is "too nice" on the surface.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 13:24:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course that exists</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 18:28:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Our players aren #8217;t the issue. It #8217;s who #8217;s managing them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 18:43:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>World War Z. The book that made me love reading.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 20:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>she is trans, but in her earlier videos she identified as Genderqueer I believe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Close game, could've gone either way.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 14:44:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 20:59:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Read the thread, you #8217;ll see</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 18:20:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>All I #8217;m gonna is say is thank fuck I already had a definite offer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nononononono YES! wait...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 22:26:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 18:32:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favourite team Dundee United. I can #8217;t be any worse than who we have in real life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 18:05:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scotland. The land of 0 zero good pop punk bands.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 19:31:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Give me a half hour</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 19:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. 1 good pop punk band</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 12:02:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idk where your from but in Scotland at least one kiss is pretty much played at almost every party and nightclub so it #8217;s definitely a  #8220;straights #8221; anthem here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Queen of the South 1 - 2 Dundee United</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 18:06:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 18:07:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice to see the new formation working, and the new striker scoring. Though Queen of the South are shite by the looks of things so we best just take it with a grain of salt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 18:19:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Played today. Scored last week. Been decent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 21:07:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wonder why  #129300;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 22:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Getting sent off In the play-offs was his best moment last season.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 19:24:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like this song, but the video feels really... boyband-y? I mean it's not full boyband (because the music video puts equal focus on each member), but they're a pop rock outfit, not a boyband and their music videos should reflect that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 19:39:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Been destroyed by injuries. This might be his last chance at a decent level. Hope he does well considering how well his first team career started.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 20:35:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm stunned that Shotgun is doing so well but it's great to see that it is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 00:27:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>He definitely deserves it, but the fact he #8217;s going up against Drake and holding his own (for now) is mental. It really showcases to me just how good  #8220;Shotgun #8221; is (also, the dreaded  #8220;straights #8221; like it so that probably helps).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 03:40:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>huh, I'm blocked by Clyde on twitter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 03:44:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes actually. That #8217;s probably the reason. Weirdly childish.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>As It Is - The Great Depression - Album Review by Spectrum Pulse</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 04:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 22:16:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that #8217;s frustrating. I hope that rangers and Hibs can pull through on Thursday. To be honest the more I think about it the more it makes sense why Lawwell wouldn #8217;t want to sign more defenders when Rodgers has already signed 6, 5 still at the club, 3 centre backs (Ajer, Compper and Hendry), and 2 full backs (Izaguirre and Gamboa). Of the five, Ajer has been a success and that #8217;s it. So why should Lawwell trust Rodgers with funds to bring in a good centre back when he has a poor track record of signing them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 22:33:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually agree with everything you #8217;re saying. I think one thing I didn #8217;t get across in my first post was that maybe Lawwell also doesn #8217;t have faith in Rodgers to get the best out of who he can buy. Defending is clearly Brendan #8217;s week spot and stacking the club with centre backs isn #8217;t going to fix the issue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 22:37:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh. Wikipedia said he was signed in the summer but yeah Deila did the deal in February. Wow Rodgers is bad at this defending thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 22:38:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why are you getting downvoted over a joke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 22:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nevermind, you #8217;re not getting downvoted enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 22:42:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pot. Kettle. Black.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 22:43:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Already posted this in the r/scottishfootball thread but here #8217;s my thoughts:  #8220;Well that #8217;s frustrating. I hope that rangers and Hibs can pull through on Thursday. To be honest the more I think about it the more it makes sense why Lawwell wouldn #8217;t want to sign more defenders when Rodgers has already signed 6, 5 still at the club, 3 centre backs (Ajer, Compper and Hendry), and 2 full backs (Izaguirre and Gamboa). Of the five, Ajer has been a success and that #8217;s it. So why should Lawwell trust Rodgers with funds to bring in a good centre back when he has a poor track record of signing them? #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 22:49:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh ffs. Someone pointed that out to me on r/scottishfootball but I forgot to change it. But that its even more damning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 23:16:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>He #8217;s still a part of the wage bill.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 23:36:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>What #8217;s more weird for me is that couldn #8217;t this be fixed by hiring 1 or 2 decent defensive coaches? He must know by now that this is something he isn #8217;t good at.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 00:13:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. I don #8217;t know anything about coaching but couldn #8217;t that at least be fixed somewhat by hiring a coach or 2 that specialise in defending? Or at least have a track record of coaching teams with good defensive records?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 21:13:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>he's an attractive guy and so a lot of young girls love him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scottish Twitter on Queer Eye</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 23:24:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Queer Eye.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 05:55:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 13:00:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can relate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>