<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject5984</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tomorrow Is My Independence Day From Cigarettes.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 06:52:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tomorrow is the day that I quit smoking. For me, for my kid, for my family. I don't need these damn things. I've lived without them and I can do it again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This sucks.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 18:27:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never smoke in the morning because my son is up. First thing this morning when I wake up is I want a cigarette and I wouldn't even be smoking one right now!  #128533; I don't know if I can do this..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm really struggling right now. My son is about to go to bed and that's when I would do most of my smoking. I'm so tired of saying I'm going to quit and then going and buying a pack, it makes me feel so weak. I just wish it wasn't so difficult to tell myself no.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 02:57:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 03:09:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could understand how the difference in wording could trick your brain. No, I haven't. What is it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 03:15:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok thank you. Yeah, this is the first time I've tried to quit and have support groups on Facebook, a smoke free app and Reddit. I feel much more positive this time around, it's just I already feel like I don't wanna do it. I know I need to do it, just I don't want to.  #128577;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 03:16:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome. I'll look into it tomorrow. Maybe I'll get lucky and it will be at my library as well! I appreciate the help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 03:41:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for this. I needed to hear it. I've been smoking a little over a year but it's been about a pack a day to a pack and a half a day. The videos would be a good idea, but I'm a hypochondriac so if I see something I'll somehow convince myself I have 3 days to live.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I woke up this morning and realized it's been a whole day! I've gone 24 hours cigarette free! And I feel good today and proud of myself! I'm gonna take control of my life this time, cigarettes will not win!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 18:34:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Night Time Sucks</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 05:09:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's night time again..  #128555; The days I'm good and don't have terrible cravings, but damn the night time. I have to find something to do.. other than eating! I just lost a bunch of weight and I don't want to put it all back on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 06:27:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't justify getting a gym membership because I don't go. I might go for a week or two... I wish I enjoyed working out.  #128577;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 06:29:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which thinking about it now, that's a really silly comment because I would spend almost $9 dollars every day killing myself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 07:19:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to. But I can't find any new ones that I like..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yay Guys!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 05:23:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>So so proud of myself. The only thing I've done differently is join support groups like this one and a few on Facebook. I can't say it's just coincidence. Getting notifications from people all around the world telling me I can do it and how they did it and tips and tricks to help me. So thank you guys!  #128513; I have only thought of cigarettes twice today. Once this afternoon and once when I decided to write this post. Taking my life back!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Question time! *stoners!*</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 06:22:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I'm quitting cigarettes obviously, but I'm still smoking herb and I'm not planning on stopping ever.  #128514; Anyways, my questions: What are some of the positive things I'll gain from stopping cigarettes? Will I notice it because I'm still smoking weed? I'm planning on it to not be as exact as most cold turkey quitting stories go because I'm still technically smoking something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 06:59:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude really? That's a super dickhead thing to say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 18:02:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. I hardly ever roll, it's pipes or bongs mainly. So no nicotine ever. But you answered exactly what I wanted.  #10084; #65039; it can be done!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 18:06:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! I haven't had a decent nights sleep in 4 days. My legs are super restless! But I try not to complain, I did it to myself I can deal with a week or two of shitty sleep.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 22:55:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It will!!! Keep it up bro  #10084; #65039; #128077; #127995; #128077; #127995; I wake up in a good mood now because I know that I can be stronger than a fucking death stick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 23:00:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right?! Now I don't have to wash my hands and change my clothes and hope I don't still smell. I can't believe that I forgot how good I could feel all because of cigarettes. The more days I go without one, the more I see how my whole life was literally revolving around when I was going to get to smoke again. How sad is that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 23:03:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go you! I'm on Day 4 almost 5. I love my Mary Jane.  #128154; and I feel like a cigarette after would always make her better, but after the first day of no cigarettes, I realized I enjoyed the high sssoooo much more not worrying or trying to speed through the bowl to hurry and get a cig. It's sad that I didn't even see myself doing that. Thanks for the info!  #9786; #65039; #128077; #127995; good luck with your journey bro! You got this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 23:17:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>And dude! I can hit the pipe, bong, blunt, joint etc. so much harder since I've stopped!  #128525; #128525; #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 23:21:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know man. It's sad. Buuut.. there's a happy ending. We learned our lesson and we are stronger for it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 23:59:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's all good bro. I'll attribute it to withdrawal rage.  #128514; Apology accepted.  #10084; #65039; #128154;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's been 7 days, 168 hours, 10,132 minutes, and 607,928 seconds since I have had a cigarette! A week #128513; Fuck you cigarettes!  #128405; #127995;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 20:06:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've fucking made it a month guys! It was really hard the first 2 weeks but I stayed strong. I can officially in my mind, call myself a non-cigarette smoker!  #10084; #65039; #128293; #128153; #128525;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 21:49:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-07 23:40:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You got this. It feels great!  #128516;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 06:10:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s awesome!! I just hit 3 months myself. Stay strong  #128170; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Weed Delivery</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 22:47:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whenever I get my weed delivered, I never have them meet me at my house, its always in a public place like a gas station or local drug store. What is the law on this? Or is there anything that I need to look out for?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 22:53:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m in Cali and I have my mmj recommendation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 22:59:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well the problem is I live with my in laws or I would have them deliver to my house. The in laws are more paranoid than I am and they don #8217;t smoke  #128514; #128514; But I can #8217;t wait to get my own place to do that. Lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Laws in Delivery in CA</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 22:59:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whenever I get my weed delivered, I never have them meet me at my house, its always in a public place like a gas station or local drug store. What is the law on this? Or is there anything that I need to look out for? I am a legal mmj patient and as far as I know the delivery people that I go through are legit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 22:38:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Weed  #128076; #127995; #128077; #127995; #10084; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 18:47:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your smoking some good shit #128514; I love Joe Rogan!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Some Trainwreck and Skywalker OG. Make for a great afternoon.  #128154; #128154;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 20:50:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 21:09:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude it is the most  #128076; #127995; comfortable! And warm af! It #8217;s so cold outside right now  #128553;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 21:12:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wanted to be an ER Nurse or a Peds Doctor. I was a CNA for a few years and then lost that license. I am currently in school for cosmetology. NEVER!!! Would have said cosmetology when i was little.  #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 21:13:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bin Laden. Hitler would die before he could find him.  #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 21:15:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve been without a car before and lived through that #8212; been without a phone, lived through that #8212; the only thing i don #8217;t think i could do with out is showers #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 21:17:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Be considerate of them. Just like i would anyone else. Maybe do a little more research on autism to know possible triggers and avoid those when dealing with that person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 21:18:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Twitter!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 21:19:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Straight to Woodstock  #128154; #128154; #128154;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 21:20:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Skywalker OG  #128514; #128154; #128293;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 21:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>If people can believe in Scientology #8212; and other various cults/religions.. then the earth being flat isn #8217;t that far away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 21:25:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just can #8217;t get into it. I don #8217;t like all the butchering of words because people try to abbreviate. Drives me crazy!!! And the ridiculous amount of hashtags at the end of the posts. I don #8217;t get it man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 21:28:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe if I started smoking weed earlier than I did, or maybe not having gone to high school and continued with being home schooled.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 21:30:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mental illness can be hidden. Just because you haven #8217;t been made aware of it doesn #8217;t mean it isn #8217;t there. And therapy is amazing, not for everyone, but if your open to it. It works wonders. Also, it could take a couple different therapists before you find the  #8220;one. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 21:31:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>My son. And it #8217;s pretty clear why. #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 17:33:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah those tolerance breaks.  #128514; i just don #8217;t think i could do it lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 20:02:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>For real though!  #128154; #128293; #128079; #127995; going from looking like a douchebag to a guy that looks fun as fuck!  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 20:34:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you have to ask and have even a little bit of suspicion. Don #8217;t do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 01:08:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d sit on it. Lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 01:10:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Epsom salt or table salt?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 01:10:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Epsom salt or table salt??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 01:14:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d probably be on so many pills to the point I #8217;m a zombie... or dead. I truly do believe that it has saved my life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 01:24:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good to know. Thanks  #128076; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 01:36:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Huh?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 07:08:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks man! Me too!! My husband and kid think the same thing. Lol i appreciate the positivity.  #128154; #128154;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 07:16:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>2</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 07:18:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s the fun part of being single. Embrace the power of feeling that sexy! There will be a time when you can no longer do those things. Let your freak flag fly!  #128076; #127995; #9996; #127995; #128154;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 17:32:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah i meant in a relationship not age. Also, after being in a relationship for a while, couples end up having a baby and then you #8217;ll never be able to do any of that again #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 20:27:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Step Brothers!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 20:29:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Masterbation. #128514; #128514; or reading a book. Tbh lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 20:32:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine are down.  #128514; #128514; I love correct grammar!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 01:16:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>My bad. Oops.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 01:42:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Usually when someone has an anxiety attack it #8217;s because they smoked a lot of THC which is the psychoactive part of the drug. Research your strains if you can, i don #8217;t know if your in a legal state or not, and look for something with a lower THC and a higher CBD percentage. Hybrids are where you should be looking my friend.  #128154; #128077; #127995; Happy smoking, and may the paranoia fuck off.  #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 01:47:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah a Sativa would for sure do that! I don #8217;t fuck with Sativas.  #128514; I #8217;ve never done a damn thing wrong in my life- - smoke a Sativa and I think every police siren is coming for me.  #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 01:53:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Be careful if you ever dab bro!! It #8217;ll be like that but worse if your not careful.  #128514; Of course! Lol any music is good music with Mary J. i mean if a Sativa is what i can get, best believe I #8217;m smoking it and just telling myself i can get weed in jail #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 02:10:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;d turn yourself in. For that one time when you were 5 and you accidentally forgot to pay for that candy.  #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 04:35:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s taken me some time to figure out what works for me. First, it was to acknowledge that failure is another step in the learning process and that everyone does it. Failing is nothing to be ashamed of, it #8217;s quitting that #8217;s shameful. As far as depression, marijuana is what helped me. I tried numerous pills, changed my diet, tried god.. you just have to find what works for you. I also meditate and use hypnotherapy sessions on iTunes before i go to sleep at night and those are surprisingly very helpful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 20:39:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Throwing up in random places and then walking away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 20:46:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m sorry, but that looks gross.  #129314;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 20:49:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are dead though.  #128520;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 20:52:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>In the healthcare department, it #8217;s the CNA #8217;s.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 20:55:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looking into my weed jar and seeing the bottom  #128559; Still some nugs, but running low man..  #128531;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 22:13:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are rotten.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 01:18:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am ashamed to admit that i didn #8217;t get it, until, i read the comments.  #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I recently started dabbing.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 17:14:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>So i recently started to dab and just there is so so much to have to learn. I #8217;ve tried shatter and that #8217;s about it. What #8217;s the difference between: live resin, budder, crumble, and sauce. I feel like I #8217;m wasting a lot too because there #8217;s always black stuff at the bottom of the bangar when I #8217;m done. Thanks for the help in advance!  #128077; #127995; #10084; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 17:35:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok, so a puddle is a good sign. And i have a carb cap but i just throw it on there randomly. I don #8217;t understand what it #8217;s really for.. sorry i know i should know this stuff before i started dabbing but i was so excited!  #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 17:38:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks so much! Yes it makes lots of sense. What i hear is i have to practice dabbing all day today.  #128536; #128514; I count about 35 seconds until it starts to get red and then i usually wait til it #8217;s not red anymore which is maybe 3-5 seconds after. So I #8217;ll start playing with my times and count to 8 maybe. Thanks so much for the help!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 17:47:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve tried the pens and they make my lungs hurt..  #9785; #65039;And there #8217;s two ways to look at it, i feel like a fucking scientist with my torch.  #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 17:51:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I gotcha man. Thanks for the help.  #128077; #127995; #9786; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 05:19:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just letting you know! I #8217;ve since used your advice and have had some amazing hits and nothing black at the bottom.  #128077; #127995; #10084; #65039; Appreciate the help so much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 05:20:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve started counting and paying attention to how hot the bangar is. I #8217;ve since had some pretty killer hits and no black stuff on the bottom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Skywalker OG x Orange Sunshine and some nice hot coffee to go with it. It #8217;s gonna be a killer day. Much love everyone  #128293; #128076; #127995; #128154;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 19:20:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 20:49:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats! Those first time patient deals are the shit huh? Enjoy your meds and stay lifted my friend!  #128293; #128293; #128154;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Being an agnostic in a family of Christians is the worst.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 06:09:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 06:46:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>In my case it does. My family are Christians when they want to be now. When i was a kid we went every Sunday and Wednesday whether we cried and kicked the whole way there. It was full of people who did nothing but judge and criticize me and my family. As a result of all of their ugliness, i no longer want them in any part of my life. There is of course a longer story that would make more sense but for this conversation this should work. I now have moved out and have since had a son. He #8217;s almost 2 and they want to take him to a Christmas program at the church that i used to go to. I told them no. I gave them my reasons all of which are valid to anyone but them. My dad called me and asked again if my son could go, i then told him no and went through my reasons again, listing the same exact ones i had previously without slipping up. His response was to call me selfish. I understand that the people at the church are their friends, but i also feel that my parents should respect my reasoning and leave it alone. And without fail when i tel them no i get told don #8217;t you care about your son, you don #8217;t want him to go to hell do you...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 06:49:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah it #8217;s just hard when my son is in the middle of it. And the frustration of letting them be them but them not letting me be me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 07:02:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with you. But the Bible also teaches so many other terrible things, on top of that, those are basic morals, i don #8217;t need a big scary man threatening me with hell to do what #8217;s right and i don #8217;t feel i need to teach my child that way. The problem i have with any kid in church really is that is the first step to brainwashing. How is a person supposed to have a unique thought about the afterlife etc. if from the day they were born they were forced to be in it, most of the time with out being able to question it. Sounds like a cult to me.. My kid is almost 2.. he won #8217;t comprehend the message that #8217;s being taught so why do i need to force my highly active kid to sit still for an hour and a half for something his mother doesn #8217;t even believe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 07:21:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d agree with you there. Glad that #8217;s not my situation, but i feel like sometimes my mom is that extreme.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 21:42:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. And they don #8217;t see it because of how far their heads are up their asses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 01:15:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>It makes me happy. I feel like when they laugh at their material, it really represents them and shows they still enjoy what they do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-26 19:31:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good job man! Keep up the good work. It #8217;s hard to lose it and keep it off. You look great!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It #8217;s been 5 months and 20 days since I #8217;ve had a cigarette and I #8217;ve never felt better or more proud of myself. It can be done.  #128154; #128076; #127995; #128077; #127995;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-26 19:33:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 19:28:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Super Glue or GDP... very relaxing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 19:30:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get half an ounce every two weeks... and that #8217;s about as long as i can stretch it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 19:43:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe you should try dabbing for alittle? It #8217;s a higher thc level and you don #8217;t have to use a lot of it. I know people who can go two weeks on a gram.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 19:44:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah that #8217;s what I #8217;ve been smoking on the last couple days. I feel so chill after and super go with the flow, which is the opposite of me before i get medicated.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 19:46:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bro watch Big Mouth!! It #8217;s on Netflix! Great show to watch stoned!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 19:56:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Neptune  #128153;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 20:02:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why did the chicken cross the road.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 20:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s not as heavy as GDP but they are very similar so I #8217;d definitely check it out! Good luck in your search my friend  #9996; #127995; #9996; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 18:18:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Filled it out for you :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 21:37:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blew my fucking mind right now!! At first i held my breath, then i realized.... i need to breath or I #8217;ll die in two minutes!! Waaaaay too high right now haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 21:38:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Smoking some ganja  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 06:38:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>When i took it from the back of your throat!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 06:40:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Smoke a bowl :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 06:43:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Marijuana #8212;not even a contest dude</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 06:44:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whether it #8217;s PC or not bro haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 06:45:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is exactly what i thought haha but i am pleased to learn about the inappropriate trees haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 06:51:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ginger helps with nausea!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 04:33:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I usually end up with popcorn or cereal lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 04:35:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like your not wrong... but..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 05:06:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude me too lol kettlecorn to be exact :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 05:08:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can dig it :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 05:25:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You look pretty today.  #8212; why do i just look pretty today? Don #8217;t i look pretty every day? Haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 05:26:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good luck and be ready to smile and feel good about life!  #128154;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 05:27:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Becoming vegetarian.. i am slowly going to move towards being vegan but baby steps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 05:29:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>That looks so yummy!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 05:33:45</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128514; #128514; #128514; #128514; #128514; #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Glass from China</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 21:20:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I #8217;ve recently been hearing a lot of people talking about glass that #8217;s made in China or American made glass.. is there something terrible about this China glass or is it more about wanting to support local people?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 22:00:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haven #8217;t got to try that one but Skywalker OG is definitely one of my favorites.. so if it #8217;s anything similar I #8217;m envious of you right now. Lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 03:08:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>The pain in my back and the crazy hormone changes..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 03:11:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>What kind of strain are you smoking...  #128514; #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 06:24:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>No i can #8217;t feel veins and sometimes i can feel the condoms but those are hardly never used  #128514; but the pulsing after a guy cums i can feel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 06:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Among other things  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 02:27:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Twice last night  #128578; and I #8217;m thinking it #8217;s gonna be at least once today.  #128536; #128536;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 21:48:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>The presidency</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 21:57:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Um... i guess  #128514; #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 21:58:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s like the lawn is smiling at you  #128513;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 22:00:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you really smoke weed?  #128514; #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 18:28:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>That we aren #8217;t all racist...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 03:31:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Get some cannacaps</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 04:50:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck is this...????</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you had a good night and the weed hits just right  lt;3</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 23:48:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 23:59:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I for sure was! Lol i think that video was the first time i smoked a blunt in months, so i was haaapppyyy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>She #8217;s all clean  #128525; #128525; #128154; #128293;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 00:49:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 00:54:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>In my non op car at my house. I #8217;m good.. lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 01:08:59</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128514; #128514; #128514; that would be cool though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 03:17:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope, i only smoke indica. My body hurts a lot of the time.. so my body felt pretty good, therefore my mind feels good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 03:17:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Always!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 05:47:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I #8217;m quite fond of her!! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It #8217;s been 8 months and 24 days since I #8217;ve touched a cigarette. I still get cravings but I AM STRONGER than them.. fuck yeah!!!!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 20:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 21:09:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Truer words have never been spoken my dude. Thanks for being happy with me! :D :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 21:27:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, it #8217;s still hard sometimes still because a lot of my friends still smoke.. so i smell it on them and feel jealous almost that they get to smoke and then i check myself and realize how absolutely ridiculous that is. I #8217;m so proud of myself and have more pride and respect for myself than i ever have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 21:55:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>They always are the ones that get crazy first.. facts make them uncomfortable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 03:56:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Having a kid</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 04:54:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>The majority of the time lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 06:07:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Laughing too hard</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 06:08:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Smoke weed with them :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 06:42:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last night, soon to be in a couple hours</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 07:14:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every day something new hurts. Lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 07:15:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 07:15:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those look soooo yummy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 07:17:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t care so much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 07:18:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I might as well go hang myself if that was the case lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 07:19:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You forget how to breath, the air around you is suffocating, you feel like your drowning but there #8217;s no water.. and there #8217;s no telling how long this feeling will last. It can bring you to your knees in a second.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 07:20:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>It all ends.. nothing is forever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 07:22:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Use hand sanitizer, spray deodorant, lotion, gum, shopping trips and needless reasons to leave the house... cigarettes are one of the worst things in the world. Fortunately.. I #8217;m clean now. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 07:23:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah it #8217;s the circulation coming back, it #8217;ll be uncomfortable for awhile.. i recommend getting toothpaste for sensitive teeth for the next couple of months. It helps a lot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 07:24:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahahahahahahahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 18:44:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Non slip?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 18:47:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ooh no hahahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 18:49:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Realize that they will let you down at times</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Some fire Cookie Glue! the smell coming out of this jar is straight gas!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 20:24:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 20:23:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>To quit smoking cigarettes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Some Candyland and Cookie Glue this fine rainy morning. :)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 20:24:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Big ass nug of Cookiewreck!! :)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 18:34:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 07:04:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tofu is super bad for you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 07:06:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Laced with something or was grown with too many pesticides- - check for mold as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 07:08:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I finally was firm on my stance with religion... and they still talked to me like i was a person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 07:11:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it old? And maybe yeah... just a smaller dose, weed has gotten stronger lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 07:14:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well good luck, just be careful :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 08:03:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cursive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 08:03:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just know she #8217;ll get over it soon.. lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are these the magic kind? I got 3.5 g #8217;s.. how much should i take? It would be my first time. I would appreciate any and all info :)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 01:52:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 02:03:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!! I #8217;ll for sure update you after! Any recommendations??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 02:17:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s a good tip for the weed.. because i probably would have wanted to smoke at some point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 03:15:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friend got them for me, I #8217;m from Cali.. i just wanted to make sure i wasn #8217;t getting played when i asked if they were magic ones or not</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 03:25:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>So do i eat the whole mushroom or just the tops?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 03:44:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even with it being my first trip? I was thinking of eating like a G maybe 2..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 03:44:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does height and weight make a difference??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 03:46:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does height and weight play into the dosing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 03:52:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I meant like my height and weight  #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 04:24:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah... i think for my first time i just want to see how it #8217;s going to feel before i just jump into it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 06:05:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha i was like he must think I #8217;m stupid or something..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 07:02:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just took a little less than half and am currently giggling at everything.. so I #8217;m ok with where I #8217;m at.. but i also smoked weed too.. so that could have a little to do with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Some help or advice would be great  lt;3</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 21:48:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>A little backstory, I used to self harm in high school, it was for short period of time but my parents did find out. They are aware of my tendency to cut. I haven't done anything since high school and have been relatively happy. However, I went through some severe post partum depression as well as a bad reaction to some weight loss pills I was taking, which resulted in the relapse back into self harm. It's been two years since I have self harmed and my cuts have now healed up but have left some pretty noticeable scars. Anyway, this Fourth of July we are having a swim party at my Grandma's. My scars are on my legs. There are a few people in my family who I'm almost positive have seen them.. but it's still a big step to go out in a bathing suit with all of my family and some friends. My kid, I'm sure, will be swimming and so will everyone else. I would love to get into the water too.. but I'm just scared, I guess? I don't really know what of.. Has anyone else had any similar stories and how did you deal with it? My future plan is to get it tattooed over we just haven't got the funds for that yet..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any advice or what you have done or gone through would be great!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 22:03:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>A little backstory, I used to self harm in high school, it was for short period of time but my parents did find out. They are aware of my tendency to cut. I haven't done anything since high school and have been relatively happy. However, I went through some severe post partum depression as well as a bad reaction to some weight loss pills I was taking, which resulted in the relapse back into self harm. It's been two years since I have self harmed and my cuts have now healed up but have left some pretty noticeable scars. Anyway, this Fourth of July we are having a swim party at my Grandma's. My scars are on my legs. There are a few people in my family who I'm almost positive have seen them.. but it's still a big step to go out in a bathing suit with all of my family and some friends. My kid, I'm sure, will be swimming and so will everyone else. I would love to get into the water too.. but I'm just scared, I guess? I don't really know what of.. Has anyone else had any similar stories and how did you deal with it? My future plan is to get it tattooed over we just haven't got the funds for that yet..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>