<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject2678</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 22:49:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is freaking great!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 17:35:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry to be dense but I just recently joined this community; what censorship edits are you referring to??? I'm confused and outraged!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 02:44:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just ordered a Galaxy edition for my daughter; full disclosure: it arrived not working! I was excessively irritated, But i have to admit they were extremely helpful with the refund/return process. The new one arrived 4 days later and worked perfectly. Love all the new features the XL offers, the face-tracking is cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 05:04:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Think Free beer has one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 17:54:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Couldn't agree more! Before the spotlight hits and you see all them standing up there.. man I gotta see them again. Only band I'll still get in the pit for</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 00:30:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>He must've gotten in with Lt. Fudge who's just out of frame in his wheelchair.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hoping beyond hope that we get some J. Walter moments in Season 5!! "And that's why.. You Always. Leave. A. Note."</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 18:42:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 18:43:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey I heard that was a band that rocked pretty hard in the late eighties..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 19:17:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no!! RIP And that's why you always. check. IMDB</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 19:21:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow! You guys are so fast! My excitement was short lived lol. I'll be ready for the next one. Thanks for doing giveaways like this. Very very cool</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 01:57:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>ATTN: I am a Netflix Marketing Executive monitoring social platforms, I would please like everyone reading this thread's personal addresses DM'd to me so you can receive a Bluth Company Forget-Me-Now. Take immediately upon receipt with some Hot Ham Water</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 20:11:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome!!! Very well done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 20:15:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Daaamn! Great video!! Nice work threading the needle there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 13:53:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>No way!! So you dove in and were able to cradle it in to your hand before it touched the surface?!!! That is unbelievable! Glad you saved it. We Salute You Sir</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 00:28:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Welcome to Klimpy's! Anywhere you like! - This does not bode well..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 03:23:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>The way he slowly turns and cautiously peers outside after he says that it's too windy.. gold</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why are you trying to get me out of the house? :: Happy Mother's Day ::</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 17:16:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 02:15:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ball cam all the time. Makes me miss some crucial shots but what a rush</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 01:44:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Too funny. Too real. Our support group meets whenever ping is really bad at the local gymnasium.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 01:56:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hest? No..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 01:58:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I didn't even know there was a cabin he wasn't taking me to!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 14:23:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Frank, you were a boy too. It was war! It was a crazy time for everybody</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 14:30:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where was Pesto 5 years ago?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 02:49:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's a beaut, Clark</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 02:53:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought that was excellent! Good job man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 03:43:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm gonna start doing that!! Seriously; not to get off topic but my top disliked has to be Teammates r trash. So utterly useless and childish.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Discussion] Impact Vs. Triumph (when they first came out) also: what have been your great pulls from Impact??</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 03:48:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 05:04:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>That looks badass!! Nice work!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 05:11:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did this remind anyone else of the Game of Thrones opening credits???</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 14:38:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha yea the only ads that really get to me are the ones for 1800flowers and Sherries, and any specific ones leading up to Valentine's or Mother's day. This past Mother's day I swear there was one every break for a week. Gave me a strange brand of anxiety.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Watching Belmont stakes, getting ready to call my bookie and put down some serious dough..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 23:27:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 01:36:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>His mother was a mudder?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Um.. so is Complexity's logo making anyone else inexplicably hungry???</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 19:03:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 02:13:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you kindly state the distinction between celebratory hot-sauce and punishment hot-sauce?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 02:49:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to read one hundred more comments like this right now lololol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 02:58:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmaooo that poor doggo.. he still looking rn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 03:53:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chat disabled for 3 seconds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 21:57:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 15:27:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>"You there, on the motorbike: sell me one of your melons!!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 16:19:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep! It was revealed by either a producer or one of the main actors in an interview when the DVD's we're first coming out in those big box-sets. Jerry Stiller is funny to his bones, the outakes and bloopers w him from Seinfeld are so damn funny.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 20:04:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Listen, don't take this personally, but when I come back, I'm sitting over there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 03:03:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great part of a funny episode. One highlight I believe has been overlooked: Phyllis using 10+ button presses whilst making popcorn  #127871;, and when asked why she isn't using the microwave in the kitchen she sheepishly replies "because it smells like popcorn..."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just an early evening shot from a park near Grand Rapids MI. About 65m up.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 02:00:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 03:34:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey!! This is from Riverside, specifically closer to the middle entrance. It was food truck night. Upload yours!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 03:48:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice. I was actually at the ballpark tonight, had the drone with me and was itching to take it up in the back 40 of the parking lot. But I haven't registered it w the FAA yet and I was paranoid that I might be approached by security or a cop since there was one hanging out at the entrance of the stadium. I really dont know how lenient they would be but I would much rather not pay a fine. Shame too because you know you'd get some good shots of the river and the field.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 14:07:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy Stone HS100</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 01:43:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Daaaaang. I watched this 4 times in a row. So sweet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fallout concept art i had printed on acrylic and added glow-in-the-dark vinyl on the back to give it that irradiated look  #9762; #65039;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 01:41:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 14:50:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very low, 2-3 according to my Pip-Boy. No worries tho, I always keep some Rad-Away on hand. It's right next to my Abraxo and Dandy-Boy Apples</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 04:46:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why don't you fire him? That's my *son*. I'm your son now. You can visit him on holidays.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 03:54:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>And his Hung Jury?!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 19:57:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>This has me so hype for you. Enjoy that eerie atmosphere and perfect sound track! You may have just inspired me to do the same. One of my absolute favorites.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 19:58:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Buy somethin already!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 19:27:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or perhaps a ice sculpture of the post surrounded by various chocolate covered fruits. *Strawberries*? That's inspired.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 19:29:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well yes, we're not barbarians.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Still one of my favorite scenes!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 04:13:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 05:59:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which one's supposed to be the funny guy?  #160;We had a funny guy with us in Korea. A tailgunner. They blew his brains out all over the Pacific. (Uncomfortable Pause) There's nothing funny about that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ok the jury might actually like that.. Happy Fourth AD family!!  #127878; #127881;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 18:38:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 16:55:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is my name champ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 16:56:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>No there's no more banana-grabbing, no more car-grabbing.. throw that away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 00:00:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man I can't say I understand the debate over demo-goals; bottom-line: this was a moral victory. He was being a self-righteous jerk and you bopped him on the nose. This deserves 10k upvotes. I can't stand toxic players. Good on you man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 15:45:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It doesn't matter! It's Moors! There's no moops!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 02:06:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agree wholeheartedly. The gaming God's smiled upon you today! Enjoy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 16:34:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because important things go in a case. You got a skull for your brain, a plastic sleeve for your comb..and a *WALLET* for your money!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 16:54:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's not gonna be good for anybody..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 02:58:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agree! I JUST popped this in for my 7-8th viewing a few days ago for my gf who's a casual Wes fan and she loved it. The claustrophobic ornate sets of the train in between gorgeous wide shots of rural India are so artistic and beautifully done. As always his signature attention to detail and character development. I just realized other than Jack being a writer we never really know what any of the brothers do for a living. But their emotions and reactions are so fleshed out we feel like we know them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 04:38:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, while you've got your check book out, how about forkin a little over to PBS? I mean, you watch the station don't you? Don't be a freeloader!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 20:53:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where have you been? You were supposed to fix the stove! I've been waiting for hours! I fell on some Fusilli. You know, the corkscrew pasta. It was a Fusilli Jerry. It got stuck in me. Had to go to the proctologist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 18:52:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll tell you what: if pigman shows up... we'll squeeze him in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 00:31:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're gonna play that FPS, you're gonna have to do it outside..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 00:35:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>So when are you gonna be able to go out?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm afraid the problem with Zach is more serious. He's back on the horse, Elaine. Smack. White palace. The Chinaman's nightcap.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:30:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 14:16:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You take back your tales you vagabond!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 16:43:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lolol "and an *I*!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 13:08:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agree! When he gives Colonel Potter Driver's Training is golden. "This, is a vee-Hickle"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 13:13:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jerry these people aren't going to let themselves be flicked into the ashbin of society!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fennec Fox  #129418; i need him as a pet!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 00:27:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 20:53:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>It won't let me edit the main post for some reason so I'll jus say it here: I in no way condone or endorse reckless or negligent ownership of any critters, including exotic ones people with more money than brains get and then mistreat. I only wanted to emphasize how cute I found this little guy. I might be able to care for him properly but it doesn't justify taking animals like these out of their natural habitat and ecosystems. But having said that: I honestly I do want to love him forever and go on adventures with him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 15:13:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love when BJ calls him this when they're first introduced and he's barely standing. "What say you"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 22:01:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stay away from Rita!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 02:20:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not so fast.... pretty boy.. There's more to this sordid little affair. This photo clearly indicates your involvement in some.. ill-conceived, mail-order pornography ring!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 15:13:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this or is this not *your* signature?? As a matter of fact it isn't! Uncle Leo? ... this case is closed pending further evidence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 19:25:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love this line.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>George Washington's Crossing of the Delaware River, Dec. 25-26 1776. Artist's Rendering.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 15:11:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 20:26:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, the fact that they would blame it on a nice man like Osama Bin Laden is..pitiful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 20:29:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy Cow!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 22:09:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like a refund</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 01:00:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha that's an oldie. God I miss the old intros. Took me a second to remember Gottfried's response. Do u remember the "Ugly Club" intro?? I went through all my old podcasts trying to find it and couldn't. My favourite line is Eric talking about Hot Wings and saying: "What an ugly man! My God look at you, what a disaster. It's a miracle anyone ever even had sex with you, you stupid idiot."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>People that were throwing shade on Season 5..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 03:41:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 19:52:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, and uh, you mentioned that you never got a G.I. Joe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 00:51:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am having a love affair with this thread, I really enjoyed reading the opinions! I enjoyed it but I have fan-boy glasses on and overlook the imperfections and continuity issues</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 19:47:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>They don't have a decent piece of fruit at the supermarket! The apples are mealy, the oranges are dry, and I don't know what's going on with the papayas!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 21:25:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because important things go in a case! You've got a skull for your brain, uh.. plastic sleeve for your comb.. and a WALLET for your money.  #128176;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 22:11:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>the asking price is a million and a half dollars..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 17:50:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel your pain brother. They're going to radio camp in Chicago.. they're off Thursday and Friday. It's funny to me too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 04:27:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hot damn! That's frickin great! Great work sir</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Quite sure Betsy's brother Timmy would be infuriated by Tostito's *laissez fair* attitude towards the social acceptableness of the double dip.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 05:23:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 22:04:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Word on the Twitter was he was becoming "fussy" haven't listened to today's podcast yet.. can any elaborate??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 03:00:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for sharing!! This was a really interesting video. I enjoyed the analysis of the soundtrack.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In the episode "The Pool Party" did anyone else just want to keep seeing more of Robert's tour of the house??</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 13:02:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When somebody's Office post makes you want to immediately run and watch that episode:</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 04:26:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 18:11:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>(breathing heavily) I must have that banner!! Nice pic, hope you had fun!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 21:28:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't like this waiter... Look at him- *Snaps fingers* He sees us</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 14:31:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're too harsh of a critic on yourself! Looks great! Hope we all get to see the finished product</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 21:49:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>And what, praytell, did the *doorman* say?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 17:08:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Elaine, "shiksa-ppeal" is a myth like the. Yeti. Or his North-American cousin the.......... *Sasquatch*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Listen Jerry, I've been doing some thinking.. I want my suit back.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 13:21:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 15:06:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>DEAR LORD! Are those fuses a centimeter long??! Lol what a legend. I aspire to light small rockets an inch from my face without a care</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 16:44:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Soup's not a meal! You're supposed to buy me a meal!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 16:45:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>(excitedly) You work out with weights??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 18:58:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh: well ya should!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 19:23:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>(smile slowly fades, turns to troubled stare)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 20:14:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>(regains composure) who left the door open?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 01:32:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is really good work. Unique subject matter! I don't think I've seen a vid quite like this. Awesome upload OP. Also I definitely thought it was sunrise before I read the whole description</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 18:14:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great thread!! I enjoyed reading all of these, my absolute favorite comes from "Moment of Silence": "So tell me: how long do you think you can go before you lose it all? Before they call your bluff and watch you fall. I don't know but I'd like to think I had control at some point, then I let it go and lost my soul. Sit tight 'cuz the revolution's years away. I'm losin faith and I'm running low on things to say, so I guess I have no choice but to regurgitate the tired anthem of a loser and a hypocrite. Oh to have died that night, I realized it wouldn't last, your days are numbered and the reaper tipped the hourglass. The final mayday of our sinking ship has come and passed.."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Who absolutely must have ambient noise, like a fan, to be able to sleep at night and how did this start for you?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:55:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:59:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg yes! Silence is unacceptable for me now. It's almost like I imagine going crazy would be like. Definitely a ringing. Lost power briefly last night because of a huge thunderstorm and it was silent as anything could ever be. (Shudders) nope. Can't do that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:06:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Woahh I never knew this!! That's really interesting. Also, agree with your second statement. I'm the same way and I need reassurance that I'm not a weirdo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>