<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7698</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Theory regarding Zaheer and friends</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-14 18:18:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally, I think Zaheer was trained by Aang at one point as an Air Acolyte. It makes sense. He has vast knowledge of airbending and can handle the spinning doors with ease. He is very well rehearsed in mediating as well and knows the ins and outs of temple on Air Temple Island. I think that once he was trained by Aang to be an airbender, Aang tried to use his chi bending to give him air bending but was unsuccessful. He becomes resentful and we see all the conflict he has with Aang's ways come out. Then after his death he became extreme and tried to take Korra to mold her to become a stronger more action oriented Avatar and fix the world. In the process of the kidnapping, he kills Sokka and that is why they are all in prison and Sokka is gone :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>inFAMOUS First Light TRAILER | #PlayStationGC</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-12 20:38:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Spanish warn independent Scotland would get euro not pound - Telegraph</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-16 15:08:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are the Istari aware they are Maiar?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-02 19:11:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand that the Wizards have been sent to Middle-Earth to inspire the people to fight against Sauron, but how aware are the Wizards of their actual nature? They are angels in mortal bodies right? So do they know this? Do they have memories of their time before being sent to Middle Earth? Do they have knowledge of Eru and the other Gods that no one else does within Middle Earth? Would Gandalf and Radagast be able to meet up and discuss old times? Or do they believe they are just Wizards and nothing more? Hopefully these questions make sense, the lore of this world captivates me so much it's just difficult to get my head around. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I just ended the beta on an all time high</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-13 11:40:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Who says the Rebels can't win?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-13 12:49:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Question about onsite tickets</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-20 18:14:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even though Saturday preshow tickets have sold out? Are they able to be bought at the door on the morning of the Saturday? Me and my friend have just bought our tickets for Friday and Sunday and we would like to get the full experience. Thanks :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How's your head? It's beyond this planet beautiful</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-09 23:13:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Finally defeated Defiled Amygdala!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-08 19:21:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry for the humble brag, but I just have to tell everyone about it. After being one shotted so many times and wasting insight to be hit as soon as I entered the arena, I came on to here to see what guides you all had to offer. Thank you to everyone who helped with their guides and videos! I may have cheesed her but honestly the thrill of not having to do that defiled chalice dungeon ever again makes it all worth it. I'm gonna add a video of how I did it as well in case any other future hunters want to see that it can be done along with some luck and good timed dodges. One step closer now to that platinum :D https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aO29scMblbQ</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[CD] [107] [Great Pthumeru Ithyll Layer 2] [HBLB][luukey92]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-12 16:33:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any help would be appreciated, I'm so close to pulling my hair out. Password is: plshelp Thanks guys edit: as soon as I posted this I ended up killing him, thanks anyway :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Miss Pernille Andrews does NOT mess around</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-13 16:19:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Willam serving you trade</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-15 11:41:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>After five years, the Shrine of Azura still makes me stop in awe</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-08 22:51:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-23 22:58:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want Kim to get the most saves so the house can collectively gasp</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:03:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are they shouting get Jedward out? I never get the crowd</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:05:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I swear Colleen lives on that smoking sofa</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:08:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is Stacy justifying herself hoarding all the food?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:11:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I swear they are looping the footage of Colleen walking to that smoking sofa. Her arse must be super glued to it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:12:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kim there's a mess on a bed in the bedroom, please clean it up with bleach</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:16:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stacy is pathetic and off her head</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:17:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes Jessica. I love how she defends herself so calmly and eloquently</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:19:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like Stacy will be going tonight, she's getting that psycho edit. I'm OK with her leaving but I want Jamie gone cause I don't think he will be up again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:24:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes Kim spilling the T</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:26:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jamie looks so greasy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:27:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've muted this until it's over. I don't want to hear their heavy petting and breathing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:30:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Big Brother needs to turn the hot water off everytime someone says babe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:31:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nicola is a bully</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:33:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>She wanted to make a scene, she couldn't wait to run there and argue with them. She was smiling the whole time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:36:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Danielle Lloyd and her fake crying is awful. Why are these therapy adverts so stupid</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:39:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stacy as two voices. Her Disney Princess thank yew and her WHY THE FUK U STARTING WITH ME voice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:42:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>They weren't loud enough for my liking</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:47:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hear we go with this new people bullshit again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:54:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like this is the longest interview ever</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:56:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jamie and Callum to go on Friday please</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 18:58:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jamie and Callum final two, watch this disaster happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:01:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is Jamie going on about Bianca having a boyfriend? He was flirting with Nicola, a married woman, and talked about having a sexual dream about her. Nob</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:03:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jamie is such a 13 year old teenager going on about being horny, Christ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:05:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Colleen back on her spot whinging about people again. She talks shit and walk away all the time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:07:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nicolas loose women audition is going crap</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:07:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone who gets their boobs out for the newspapers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:10:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>An ADULTERER crying about someone not being honest. Hillarious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:15:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>When is BB going to replay the footage of Jamie and Callum being gross and derogatory towards Jessica?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:17:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think Nicola can read</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:20:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's his natural slime</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:24:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg Jamie stfu, you and all your drama is so tiresome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:26:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I hear babe one more time...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:28:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shaat ap</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:36:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Joker for a joke of a person</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:38:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck of Colleen fake ass hoe hugging Jessica after nominating her. Why does no one have conviction in that house?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:40:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too Callum. Your humble brag is annoying me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:44:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kim giving us Angie Bowie breakdown in the diary room realness and I love it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:46:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Channel 5 is trying so hard to make Danielle Lloyd a thing. She keeps popping up everywhere, and I've had it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:53:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lord save me from this boring fucking TV. Going on about these feelings. You are a 30 year old woman talking about a man you have known for three weeks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:54:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's trying to get that greasy stench of Jamie off her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:56:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jamie always walks like he's shit himself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:58:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Channel 5 announcer: *For all the sadists out there, keep watching for more boring Jamie drama.*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 21:19:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Oh I've had a wonderful evening* *Oh I've had a wonderful night* *Oh I've had a wonderful evening* *Oh it's been a fucking delight* Get this bitch a grammy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 21:59:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please keep her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 22:05:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so over this shit showmance taking up loads of air time now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 22:06:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're a perfect couple of ADULTERERS then</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 22:08:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>This crying is just beyond ridiculous.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 22:10:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>The editing of this makes it seem like Jamie is expecting a call from beyond the grave</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 22:11:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone call 999! I've not seen Colleen on that sofa yet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 22:18:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Such sik skillz m8</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 22:20:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jedward sounding like the stoners who smoked and chatted about life outside my window at uni</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 22:25:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did Nicola just make an incest joke? ^*Shadenoise*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 22:33:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is Shangela in that box???</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 22:37:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where is Kim to bring down these gang handlers?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 22:38:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nicola is so aggressive to Jedward</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 22:40:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Heidi has perfected the 180 degree walk away from drama this season.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 22:42:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nicola calling them mean spirited?? Haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 22:47:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>This season has been a shambles</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 22:53:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel physically disgusted at all these kissing sounds. This is like anti ASMR</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 22:53:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>No one cares Colleen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 22:54:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well this episode was a waste of time, I feel like it's going to be a long and slow drag to the final</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 21:57:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>GET JAMIE OUT.. oh wait. Maybe next time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 22:00:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry to get your hopes up, I'm trying this new thing where if I wish hard enough it comes true. But Jamie is still in there and I'm poor so I've still got work to do</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 22:07:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jamie wishes his was as big as that bananna</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 22:10:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bully Nicola bouncing to the scene</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 22:11:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why are they acting like Jedward are making a mess of the shopping list? Heidi is there as well and it looked like she was doing most of it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 22:12:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the thing with Jedward that I don't mind is that they seem harmless. Yes they are annoying, but there is nothing malicious about them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 22:24:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mary Berry is triggered by the disrespect for the bread</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 22:26:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am so uncomfortable watching Jamie dance and sing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 22:31:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually feel like the house is really boring right now and as horrid at is it, that vile showmance is all that's happening</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 22:39:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel ill. Why couldn't we have a double eviction last week when Jamie is up. Losing Kim or Speidi is a shame.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 22:44:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't wait for Bianca, Nicole, Callum and Jamie in the final. This is the end of cbb</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 22:50:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was her entire stint on the Apprentice so I wouldn't be surprised</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 23:21:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Regardless of who goes, my interest in this series has diminished greatly. I don't want to be that stroppy fan who gives up when it doesn't go their way, but the show has become incredibly boring and it's 90% Jamie and Bianca drivel and I don't know if I care enough to keep going. But I will because I enjoy shitposting with you lot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 23:37:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Speidi is me wanting to run away from every nob head in that house</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 21:58:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apparently Vanessa and Nicola hate each other, so I'm hoping for some drama</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 22:03:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's alternative footage obviously. He's a gentleman</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 22:05:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Should've brought back a proper loose woman like Denise Welch or Carol MacGriffin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 22:10:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Colleen telling people to stop sitting on the fence. Lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 22:16:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>James C looks permenantly dead behind the eyes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 22:20:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>God bless you Luisa</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 22:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>James C asleep is me during this season</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 22:23:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only adult you are acting like Jamie is acting like the ADULTERER</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 22:27:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Luisa is one of us</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 22:32:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a successful attempt at creating drama from the outside, instead of the usual shit they do</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 22:36:09</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128567; #128567; don't wanna hear about it Jamie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 22:38:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Callum backtracking. I can't wait to hear the buzzwords, gentleman, banter and babe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 22:40:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>John McCirick the Library is closed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 22:42:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's in the criteria of Jedward and pensioner, so I'm sure Jamie would 1v1 him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 22:42:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why should Jedward have to apologise and make the effort? Anytime they have spoken she has always shut them down</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 22:45:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is Jamie gonna cry about this the same way he did when James J called him a washed up footballer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 22:47:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't be arsed with your relationship either Jamie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 22:48:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder who will cheat on who first. Both are notorious adulterers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 22:58:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bianca is trying to find a nice way to reply without saying I love you back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 23:00:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's the Daily Mail of TV. Every show is literal trash</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 16:30:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shame it wasn't a double so Callum could fuck off as well, but I'm very glad. We won't have to be triggered anymore by hearing kissing sounds</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:03:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish they'd read some of the posts on here instead of tweets lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:03:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's only immature when Jedward do it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:04:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I aspire to be a filthy pensioner like Kim. Fifty shades of grey hairs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:08:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>The worst thing is that they think they're being entertaining.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:09:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's got more personality as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:17:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not subjective James, you're fucking boring</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:18:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like I'm watching a celebrities read mean tweets video where they try and come up with unfunny comebacks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:21:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm convinced Jamie is part watermelon, he's always red and sweaty</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:23:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not even a month. A horny divorced dad of three with a psycho ex isn't a catch. He makes Stephanie Davis look stable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:25:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is Colleen so pressed about Jedward? She's offended that they aren't</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:28:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so excited. I want dramatic reactions like when Lateshya was evicted</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:32:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Callum will you please shut the fuck up with your no producer knowledge mouth</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:35:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could you imagine anything more boring than Jamie in a secret house?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:35:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>James C you are so shady saying it would be Jedward or Kim.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:37:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>They didn't give a shit when Austin got booted out. Why is it cruel for Jamie?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:38:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>He will leave here more liked than disliked HAHAHAHAHAHHAHAHA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:41:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sad wave to which the other housemates ignored gets me every time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:43:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a one sided conversation James because you don't speak</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:51:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Walk then Callum. You won't be missed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:54:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last Friday night needs to be Callums eviction music</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:55:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Callum this isn't very gentleman like</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:56:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think Callum made more noise then shouting than anyone else</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 22:56:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg Callum staring at the window with his cap on was fucking terrifying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 19:38:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>In Prison: Calum Best</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 22:03:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jamie dresses like a vampire from the victorian ages. That shirt and velvet jacket creeps me out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 22:07:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think she's as hard with people sometimes, and she just said she liked Bonka/Jamie so she's now public enemy number 1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 22:07:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>TOP BANTER BABE LOVE IT KEEPIN IT REAL 100</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 22:19:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Callums Madonna accent will never not piss me off</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 22:34:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like we just got a tl;dr version of Callum Best in therapy there. Now one one needs to watch it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 22:37:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>That act of vandalism was incredibly cringey Bianca</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 22:40:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Callum was SHOOK</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 22:47:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would love to know in what world Callum thinks hes a household name where he feels the need to change his reputation. In the words of the BB crowd, HU ARE YA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 22:49:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Have you shown your respect for Callum today?](http://imgur.com/a/ivcrN)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 22:55:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh I thought it was a double eviction. Well this episode flew by</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 22:57:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>KEEP JEDWARD IN GET JEDWARD OUT please sshh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 13:05:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just in time for Kim to win</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 20:14:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only a Kim win can save this incredibly mediocre season. It's such a shame, it had high potential. Hopefully they learn from their mistakes and improve it in the BB legends in the summer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 20:46:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I honestly feel like that they created this BB legends out of the blue just because they want to get Tiffany back for ratings. It seems so odd that theyre creating another all stars series after another. I bet Speidi are fuming that they were on the shitty pilot trial of the true all star season.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 21:57:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same. That kind of pettiness sustains me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:01:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes warning!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:06:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're always dreadful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:09:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually love Nicola role-playing as the pirate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Big brother has successfully made this look like a fun season</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:16:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good start so far. Colleen next</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:24:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bet living with Bianca is like living with a hairy pet. Extension hairs lying around everywhere</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:25:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always find it so funny and insulting that Jamie lectures Bianca about being truthful in a relationship.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:28:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I miss Davina grilling everyone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:35:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least if Nicole falls down the stairs her boobs will bounce her right back up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:36:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree. Her, Jedward and Kim have made this season because they have done something other than gather dust and chain smoke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:37:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least he is consistent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:40:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think a lot of middle aged women viewers see themselves in Colleen. They need more interesting role models</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:49:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nicola is reminding me a bit of Amanda Lepore right now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:52:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Colleen saying what is going on. I know hun , you should have left ages ago</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:54:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Colleen needs to go because I want her to explode at the thought of a Kim and Jedward top two. Watch as she states them on loose women on Monday as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:59:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>QUICK HOW DO I TEXT FOR KIM TO WIN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:01:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Done ! Thanks hennies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:02:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>This Santa is obviously from the darkest timeline</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:09:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>RIGGA MORRIS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:10:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Colleen is so undeserving if she wins but the worst bit is that it'll make her ego even worse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:13:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>All Colleen has gained from this series has been lung cancer and all she has given is second hand smoke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:16:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm really hoping that they've gone through every loose woman now. They are such boring and self righteous housemates. I don't want to see another one unless it's a drunk Carol McGriffen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:20:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I fear BBOTS is going to be everyone vs Kim</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:25:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>JEDWARD OR BUST</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:26:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm done. Get me my pocket book. I'm leaving.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:27:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>See you all in the Summer. It's been great chatting here with you all, I cba with this shite anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:29:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Colleen Nolan done fucked up Celebrity Big Brother.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:32:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd rather throw myself down the stairs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:34:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It'll be hard to find her behind all the haze from the smoke</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:37:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Angry middle aged women who think they are all therapists but they really just enjoy slagging off men and making themselves feel better under the guise of a panel show</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:38:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>First Brexit now this. We as a nation are suffering too much. I can't wait for Colleen all over the news talking about how big brother saving her marriage</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:42:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm on the phone to OFCOM right now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:44:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Colleen will probably float down the stairs considering she's 95% smoke</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:47:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's gutted there were no fireworks so she couldn't suck the fumes in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:50:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I always thought Colleen was delusional but I guess not...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:52:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm taking a tip from Bianca Del Rio and channeling my rage. Thank though  #128536;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 23:56:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think we might have our first televised gang murder. RIP Queen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-04 00:03:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd rather watch Callum best in therapy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 20:44:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pumped and dumped</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 12:09:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have to find special glowing blue books in the world that give you xp for the mage guild. You usually get a new quest for the mages guild every time you level up in that faction.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 14:46:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last year the Ezra, Hera etc. badges were for children, which I assume is the same this year, hence them not being posted here. Most people on here either got the 4 day pass (Rey) or the individual day passes like you have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 20:59:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Jedi Master/VIP pass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 22:39:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mournhold for sure. Easy access to all the crafting sites right next to the wayshrine, but the best bit is the massive tribunal temple in the background. It makes it feel very unique.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 22:59:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree. I've only been in there since for the odd Dark Brotherhood assassination mission, and everytime I've been it it reminds me of how underused it is. A shame really.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 07:15:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>/u/opfeels /u/subject7698</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 20:50:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like most first games in the series, the majority of the stories brought up are setting up for something down the future. Same with the Reapers in ME1 and the Protheans, we had to wait to find more about them. As fun as it would be to know everything right off the bat, we have to wait. I believe the Quarian arc will be DLC for sure, it fits in with how Bioware have done DLC before. A little nod in game that eventually turns into a big DLC story pack and I believe that it will be started on Meridian and will be started by the NPC who mentions it, otherwise what is the point in the Meridian base? what exactly is the scourge and who is/was behind it? It was mentioned its the aftermath of a weapon detonated at the Jardaan. We don't know if it was created by an enemy of the Jardaan or amongst the Jardaan themselves. Again, we have to wait :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 21:07:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>are we safe anywhere???</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 22:26:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I felt the exact same. When I unlocked the memories I thought it was going be something cliche like Sam being the mum. Then I heard the Turian sos and the alliance one and finally Liara and it made me a bit misty eyed. I want to know so much more about what else happened and what it's all like now, but with 600 years gone I doubt it would be as familiar to us anymore :( I assume we will get more little moments like those encrypted logs when the benefactor is revealed, so there's that to look forward to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-08 16:01:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you edit this as a spoiler please? I didn't need to see this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 20:13:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's likely going to be geth that snuck aboard, but another fun theory is that it's being chased by a reaper. That'd be more interesting than an Arc being captured by the Kett again. Either way they'll be fine and safe as Blasto will save the day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 20:23:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some people think it would be a bit forced, but I think it would be interesting. The delay for the Quarian arc meant they were likely around at the start of the Reaper invasion and managed to escape just in time, but we've seen Reapers travel in dark space so its not out of the realm of possibilties. The only question is how to kill the last Reaper.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 20:26:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah as much as I think it would be fun, I doubt it will end up being a Reaper for the reasons you said along with the fact that they will likely want to keep away from them besides the little mention in the benefactor storyline. I just hope its something more than a third mission revolving around an arc and the Kett.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 17:03:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>An EU code would be fantastic please! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 22:53:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, I didn't see the bug thread, i'll report it in there. Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 22:54:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jean Grey's unleash the phoenix talent is bugged and is unable to be used before level 32, like the other talents</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 18:24:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This part](https://youtu.be/eIl0H2yF3aY?t=4m48s) from the battle of endor. It's the part where Luke lashes out against Vader and defeats him. It's such an underrated piece of Star Wars music in one of the most important scenes of the series.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 20:31:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its iconic how Coco unashamedly photoshops her limbs into some sort of doctor who alien realness in every photo. She just doesn't care and I live for that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-09 03:03:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>This election is giving me alexis vs peppermint and we all know that Jeremy is peppermint right now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 08:38:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I need the inevitable Oscar, Grammy, Tony and Nickelodeon choice award winning music video now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 21:49:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pete would have made a fantastic judge with his no shit attitude and lethal tounge. RIP icon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 08:32:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Drogon be like.. ](https://media.tenor.com/images/2223e60dc3409f1e29960f56384f7530/tenor.gif)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 20:16:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>This photo is a hate crime.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 20:31:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where is a good starting point for Midnighter? Is his solo series a good point to start?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 11:14:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brillaint! I've been looking to getting into Midnighter for a while, thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 09:05:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Phantom Menace game. It was surprisingly very good and had a lot of depth to it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Snake bro is best bro</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 12:20:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:04:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imagine how the poor girls who have to act in them feel. It feels like they're at gunpoint</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:06:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maggie would be the perfect person to have a lil goss with. Shes so cute</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:08:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>India hun, its not that you're trans its cause you have a shit personality</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:09:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>In bright salmon shorts no less!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:12:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please tackle me to the ground Andrew</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:19:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maggie is me being that nosy bitch trying to look busy when I'm actually earwigging</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:21:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Malika is so refreshing after the previous kardashain-lite bores. Love her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:26:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is courtney wearing red velvet couture?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:35:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anne "When was inflicting pain entertainment" from the lady who's party is constantly trying to bring back fox hunting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:37:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anne might need a shock just so we can see if she can feel anything</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:38:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney thinking of the time when ru blocked her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:39:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>This music and courtney crying is Oscar worthy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:45:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm waiting for Courtney to drag Ann worse than the time she was on that floor on strictly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:47:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>"how Colleen won" This will NEVER not trigger me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:49:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wayne is me during lad banter</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:52:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wayne is also me trying to fit in with the lads by being really gay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:54:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi 999 I'd like to report a serious dragging at Borehamwood</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:57:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>He has a pierced nipple and I know it means nothing but....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 22:59:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thankfully no and I hope it continues</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 23:00:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>When it's right, it's right</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 23:03:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Channeling our Queen Kim Woodburn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 21:52:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>The most important question for tonight is will Andrew be tucked?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:02:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wayne towards Andrew is this thristy sub</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:05:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Does Rachel remind anyone of Laura Dern? Must be the massive hair](https://i.imgur.com/UHU1UDZ.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:08:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>TMI India Jesus...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:13:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You must have never watched a season with the loose women in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:17:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Think of how much extra footage we could get instead of these annoying drone shots with crap music on top</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:20:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann is that woman who says girls don't poo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:21:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's Jamaican</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:24:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dan proving once again he is as funny as a toothache</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:30:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Me when the shower door isn't see through ](https://i.imgur.com/euv0RqW.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:33:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love yourself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:35:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everyone is so disinterested in Indias "phobia"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:37:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney is educating the British public on tucking. What a great start to the year</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:42:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>That zoom in on Betty's meaty tuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:43:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think India could learn a lot from Courtney on how to paint herself. I feel her bitterness is jealousy tbh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:44:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's deffo my aesthetic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:47:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thay acting is more raspberry awards than Oscar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:48:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Andrew feeling his oats is so awesome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:49:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank God for 24/7 cameras</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:51:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I meant that Courtney makes wigs and knows make up she can give her some tips. Not that she had to copy her beat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:52:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is too hetero for my tastes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:53:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>9 kids aren't enough???</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>*[Wumining intensifies]*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 22:58:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>India is not mentally stable enough to be on this show. Her anger is unresolved issues and this place will make it worse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ann coming for Courtney with some eclipse level shade</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 17:02:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 17:18:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jade Goody before the racism series</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 20:34:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This should work](https://tvplayer.com/watch/five)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 21:58:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>India gonna accuse people who nominate her of misogyny because she's a WOMAN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:02:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's 9.01 and adverts are still on. Gonna call ofcom</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:06:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Surprised there was no crowd reaction to Courtney..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:08:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>India is tired talking about gender but she's the one constantly harping on about it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:09:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unless India is shouting I'm a STROOONG GAAAY WOOOOMAAAAN I'm not interested</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:11:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ashley and Genuwine is the most random thing of the year so far</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:11:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spill that political tea Rachel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:12:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank yew</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:13:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>All Daniel has contributed to this show is scoring and ranking women. He is married and disgusting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:16:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>And it's been as successful as Phi Phi on AS2</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is predatory. I need an adult</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:20:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wayne is that drunk gay at the club getting all the girls on the stage</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:23:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish Andrew got to see Ken doll Courtney he'd be greatly interested</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:24:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann is beat henny</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:25:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney is so fucking refreshing. It's so nice to see her educating without raised voices. She's attentive and not patronising</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:26:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>If Andrews talent isn't stripping then cbb is cancelled</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:28:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>[When Shane "sings" ](https://i.imgur.com/1AF3BW7.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:31:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>There has been a severe lack of SHPOCK tonight</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:36:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is Andrew dressed like Lito from sense8?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:36:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Johnny's talent **BOOT**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is giving me dryer than your vajoina war flashbacks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:38:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've muted this section. The car noises are more interesting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:39:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Noa I know why Ann wants the death penalty back. To prevent Daniel doing "comedy"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:40:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shame she isn't singing same parts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:41:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney dedicating this to Andrew</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:43:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maggie and Amanda proving one again they're gay icons</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:44:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish Bianca was in there. She'd give India something to be scared of</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:49:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>BLOCKDT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:50:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>He did say he was mostly a dancer in yesterday's show and he wasn't lying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:51:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>After Courtney wins this I want her to go win the next gayest show on the planet: Eurovision</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:53:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney and India looking like Marilyn Monroe and Michael Jackson having a good kiki</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:56:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Malika is the true all seeing Queen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 22:59:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are gonna get another Makosi hot tub baby soon and I am gagged</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:01:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>India was the one back stabbing people behind their backs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:02:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which one of you gays just screamed "We love you Courtney?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:03:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney in full geish sitting next to her man is my aesthetic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:06:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hopefully it's televised</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:08:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your stairs are TERRIBLE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:08:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't heard anything as iconic as chicken livered shit in a very long time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:11:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Live shows are always all over the place</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:11:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Malika WHY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:14:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rachel like her brother is a liar</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:15:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>These noms are a mess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:16:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>India literally nominating Genuwine cause he won't dick her down</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:18:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Too much sass to Queen Emma. I didn't like it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:19:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Channel 5 is so desperate for coin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:20:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Indias reactions have been top /r/sadcringe material</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:24:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney flashing a little bit of khut khut to Andrew is me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:26:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jonny should go only because India has been a watchable disaster. Johnny is meh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:27:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>What sort of loser stands in the cold cheering for Johnny? Smh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:28:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>*cackles in gay*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:30:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Art</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 23:31:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>The real irony is that panto is full of drag Queens</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 16:52:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is cute. Right, that's it. Jonny is allowed to stay **ONLY** if he continues to make CourtDrew a thing. Real talk though, I just love how casual this conversation is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I need Sunday to be over so I don't have to see anymore Adam Sandler adverts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:03:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>ANDREW CALLED COURTNEY SEXY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:06:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>India sat there thinking of a way to trump racism with transphobia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:07:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>CALLED IT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:09:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>India you're also a 53 year old woman with the attude of a 10 year old. There is no world where that is attractive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:11:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>When will Andrew flirt with me tho</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:14:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>India is a late bloomer. After spending her entire life not being who she is, she's trying to catch up on those normal life stages that women go through like being chased after romantically. She doesn't realise it's not going to happen and that's not shade it's just facts. She will never get those experiences but she could have plenty more if she stopped being a sulky brat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:16:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann grimacing in the mirror is me when I get my haircut and I realise how ugly I am</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:20:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Malika using this task as the perfect opportunity to get rid of India</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:23:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>[What Courtney is thinking when Andrew asks her to come into the toilet to talk about condoms ](https://i.imgur.com/ptWIltO.gif)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:24:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hetero flirting is so boring</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:26:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney bout to pop her tuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:28:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ashley calling him G? I'm over this now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:31:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>And India disrespects the struggles they went through to allow her to be who she is. Disgraceful tbh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:34:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maggie and Amanda gossing is deffo me talking about people at work</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:36:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>When will these fucking awful drone shots end? We got it channel 5 you bought a drone....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:39:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally called him a filler queen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:41:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ashely looking very Sharon Needles tonight</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:43:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good girl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:44:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Indias war speech was cringe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:45:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>She doesn't want to get strangled in the middle of the night</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:46:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>The straights</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:51:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Drone shots have replaced IM A WUMUN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:51:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jess needs to be a good friend to Ashley and say stop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:54:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Daniel is such a twat. Glad Courtney called out his stupidity</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:55:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't drink anymore because I'm jess when drunk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:56:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't with this groping. Good night everyone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:57:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney please take me under your wing. The last man to be nice to me was the bus driver</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:58:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>He can be the cameraman</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:59:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im a mess. I was thrown out of a pub quiz once how embarrassing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 23:00:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's because the friendship Andrew and Courtney have is Genuwine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 21:58:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>India has a major problem with this task apparently. Consider me shocked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:03:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've already seen enough Ashley and Genuwine action from that one second clip.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:05:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann is me wearing black and being miserable at everything</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:07:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>The real tragedy is that Courtney isn't in full 50s drag being a doting housewife for her man. Where can I complain?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:09:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amanda has had it. Officially.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:14:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney being so masc4masc</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:19:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Andrews rolled up sleeves. Lord have mercy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:23:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's not a lady she's a WUMUN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:24:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck you bb over hyping that Amanda dragging</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:25:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that was awkward India...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:27:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney smart AND beautiful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:29:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's chaotic evil so I'm not surprised</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:32:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann is me falling to sleep out of sheer boredom by being near Ashley and Genuwine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:36:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vile image</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:39:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>BB needs to punish those who try and make gashley a thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:42:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>India just sounds so bored and uninterested in this conversation</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:43:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imagine if India went full kinga and flashed her goods to Andrew</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:46:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I blame all this gashley crap and drone shots</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:47:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's always tomorrow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:49:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vagina has beens said too many times</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:52:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm too gay for this conversation jesus</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:57:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ashley you have been evicted please leave the big brother house immediately</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:58:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>SHIT EPISODE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Red alert ladies: Andrew calls Courtney hot and says he doesn't know what would happen if he was drunk</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 13:42:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 13:48:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>#relatable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 20:42:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney choosing her word wisely "You need to think *harder* about *coming out* of this house."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 21:58:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Things I don't want tonight: 1. Gashley 2. SHPOCK 3. Drone shots Things that will happen tonight: 1. Gashley 2. SHPOCK 3. Drone shots</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:03:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>The full frontal is Wayne girls and gays, false alarm.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:04:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>You better have got chocolate hobnobs otherwise you better sissy on back over there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:08:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maggie and Amanda are so cute. I wish we saw more of them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:11:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann is my nan when I brought up Brexit over Christmas dinner.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:12:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm straight now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:13:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann for fashion photo ruview</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:14:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>What showmance??? It's just awkward hand holding</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:18:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I thought nothing was more annoying than SHPOCK but those singing ladies deffo tried</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:23:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Davina was better</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:25:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Andrew looks like he should be in a 90s boyband with that hair and I'm here for it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:27:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>And Andrew is his daddy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:27:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Marcus is so shady to India and I love it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:29:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd love to have a cuppa with Amanda she's so cool to listen to. We need more of her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:33:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>And flairs!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:37:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>She did that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:38:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's her twin Derek</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:40:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the future liberals want</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:40:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck off Daniel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney better come back in full face and wig to shove Ashley away</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:43:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wayne is every 14 year old gay boy in front of the mirror</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:44:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>LIZA MINELLI LIES COURTNEY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:47:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me to Andrew: That's a piece of wood</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:48:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Moan on here every night instead of getting an early night</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:51:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>~~Dida Ritz~~ India looks a mess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:54:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>GURLS WHAT JUST HAPPENED</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:54:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also Andrew has to wear that onesie. Dark salmon does a body good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:55:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was not consensual at all Genuwine omg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:57:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Emma 'the cock tease' Willis</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:58:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Channel 5 about to see a massive ratings drop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 23:01:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not as short as Colleen Nolan the living cigarette</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 23:32:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>CHICKEN LIVERED SHIT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 23:33:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is the crowd low energy? Sad!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 23:35:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Without any WUMUN drama we are gonna have gashley thrown at constantly now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 23:36:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is this weird eulogy thing of India on the big screen lmfao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 23:37:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>The good news is that we are now gonna get Queen Kim confronting India with those twitter pictures</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 23:38:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>#This new formate is shite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 23:39:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's her whorecrux</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 23:42:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>This eviction was boring. [This](https://youtu.be/mE8TfPf9Skk) is how it was back in the day. I miss it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 23:44:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Her throwing a glass of water will never not make me gay gasp</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 23:46:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>India really needs a stylist she dresses like a cheap hooker, but if that's what you like India you do you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 23:48:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks like the free one you could get in those little girl magazines</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 23:52:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Emma is giving you supernatural tyrant realness ](https://i.imgur.com/ddaJYI2.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 23:54:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just like this show and sub lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 23:56:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>[The most iconic video on the Internet](https://youtu.be/thJA5uIgxug)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 23:58:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>After the football? No ma'am. We didn't get equal rights to go after the footie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:02:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>[For those who don't know of our Queen Kim, and why she is so iconic, enjoy. ](https://youtu.be/HQ4aE5jt8cY)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:09:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>We need another drag queen only audience edition again. So many great moments in that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:10:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>And I will NEVER forgive the idiots that let Colleen win</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:10:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kim spilling the T as always, forever an icon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:11:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Add Farah Abrahams for a real riot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:12:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think she only had one contact lense in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:13:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>GANG HANDED</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:21:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Politics from Rachel... Ann found dead</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:23:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder if the children coming in are Genuwines. He has enough to offer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:28:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only good thing about kids coming in is that I can see Courtney and Andrew being a power couple playing mum and dad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:30:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't talk about India like that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:32:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney's promo is just gorg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:33:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>No one wants to share with strangers. I'd fight a bitch for a single bed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:36:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>And some conditioner. It's dryer than your vajoina</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:37:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shivering in anticipation!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:38:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I found the word for drag phobia in the dictionary hun, its called BULLSHIT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:39:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>The audience grumbling at gashley is us</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:43:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>And her hair is so big that a wig wouldn't fit on her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:45:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>No I don't want to see a man grabbing Ashley and forcing her to kiss him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:48:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm loving this Ashely dragging</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:51:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>My gaydar is all over the place with Andrew and I just don't know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:54:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Andrew and Courtney are so hot together I can't cope</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:57:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>India ruining herself by saying dapper is gorgeous</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 00:58:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have been robbed of a potential good housemate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 01:01:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those who voted India out are ringing up for a refund</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are the Tribunal just three very powerful mages?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 20:17:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was playing the Clockwork City DLC for ESO and Divayth Fyr mentioned something along the lines of Sotha Sil not viewing himself as God, just a very powerful mage. Which brings me to my question, what differentiates the Tribunal and powerful mages? Is there anything they can do that a really powerful mage could not for example? I know the heart of Lorkhan is basically cheat mode and they gained access to an immense amount of power, but could someone study very hard to be as powerful as them? Or did the heart remove any 'mortal limitations' that would stop a normal mage from being as powerful as them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 21:22:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>That makes perfect sense thank you for that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 10:18:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sort of annoyed how it was edited last night to look like Courtney was getting jealous of Andrew giving Malika a hand massage. There probably is no doubt that Shane might feel a little attraction but I don't believe for one minute that Shane thinks that there is something more going on than what it is. I looked at the Facebook page out of curiosity, bad choice I know, and I saw [this](https://i.imgur.com/wTLKVGM.png) and the last thing I want is Courtney getting a predatory gay edit when it's Andrew who has been leading all the flirting and innuendos. Courtney is a smart cookie though so I'm sure she will know when to call it a day and call it for what it is: two people just having a laugh in what's probably a very boring place.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 19:34:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is Courtney shoving her face in Andrew's bum at the end?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 19:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eeeeeuuuuuueewwwww!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 21:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's usually about 5 or 6 in the end and its a vote to win for all of them and the person with the least votes is usually voted off every half an hour. It's a long final.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 21:57:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank God its Sandler Sunday. We never have to see this shit again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:04:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Genuwine is so creepy but ashely has deffo enabled this gross behaviour</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:07:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why does Daniel sound pressed by Courtney and Andrew??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:10:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think we needed this chat so people outside know it's just fun and not a predatory gay taking advantage . The predatory gays are posting on this sub anyway</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:11:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's been banned from opening his mouth since his "singing"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:13:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rachel probably moans that the food isn't from waitrose as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:20:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really have no sympathy for Ashley. She could easily tell him to fuck off instead of hugging him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:22:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so fucking weird. Put Shandrew back on so we can see how harmless flirting should be</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:23:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rachel is so upper class. Do you reckon she knows what spagbol is?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:24:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Big brother? Punishing on c5? hahahahahaha good joke</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:29:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm nominating Ann for continously talking while eating</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:31:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>*When Daniel starts talking* #FAK OFF ~~GILLIAN MCKEITH~~ DANIEL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:35:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Big brother sounding like a fake hoe when Daniel came on Hiiiiii Daniel  #128530;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:36:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jessica how are your skills? Average #ME</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:39:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jess is so stupid I love her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:40:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where is Andrews ass shot???</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:43:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jess is so cute!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:44:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>If the next warning doesn't mention rimming then Marcus isn't doing his job</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:45:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thats a lotta fucking money</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:49:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>These episodes really should be an hour and a half long they go fast with nothing much in it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:51:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I ship Ann and sassy big brother</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:54:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love this gay trio</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:56:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Daniel you were egging them on though so fuck off</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:58:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>We haven't had a good alcohol argument in a long time. I miss Farah and Jenna screaming about kosher wine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:59:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're drunk and I'm nervous!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 23:00:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Big brother confirmed homophobe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 23:01:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mildly aroused</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 13:48:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>My issue with the people going online about wanting Courtney to get a warning is that I don't want fun to be censored. Context is incredibly important in situations like this and I would argue that Ginuwine was more deserving of a warning because Ashley was uncomfortable and she even talked to others about it. There was no indication from Andrew that he was uncomfortable and he continued to play around with Shane - and even the Huffington post article mentioned on here said he didn't care. The whole what-about-ism of "well if this a man with a woman...." is not entirely relevant because there is no power of the man over a woman. This is two guys doing what guys did all throughout my years at school and uni - being comfortable with each other and having a laugh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 18:14:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for that Gahsley promo BB, good to know I can avoid tonight's episode.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 21:51:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>That shocked me too, and the top comments were saying how cute they were. The gay agenda is working</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:01:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I see all these channel 5 adverts for the programmes I can really see why C5 is losing money...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:02:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I HATE KIDS GET OUT OF MY HOUSE REEEEEEEEE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:04:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boring</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:06:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ashley and Shane look like the bitchy twins from high school musical</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:07:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I too am praying that Gashley are launched out of the house by a cannon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:09:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Malika looking like one of the cheetah girls in her cute pj's bless her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:12:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want Courtney to go in full drag and confuse the kids</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:14:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah and that's why I want it. I love a good right wing melt down</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:15:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bitch if those eyes ain't creepy as fuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:16:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>The editing on this is so petty and award winning worthy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:17:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maggie is me cleaning the fridge by eating everything in it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:17:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is this music??!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:19:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think they confused her age with IQ</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:21:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is actuslly cute what is wrong with me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:23:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>BB better be getting these kids to slut drop to toxic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:26:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Daniel was good at that task because his normal audience of annoying freshers are also children</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:29:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann giving you Mrs Clause today</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:30:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann acting like a dance expert when she was literally dragged on the floor on tv.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:34:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wayne and Ginuwine have more chemistry than the entirety of Gashley</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:35:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like it when the house all sits together and chats it feels so cozy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:37:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think they enjoy triggering her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:38:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>PUNISH THEM</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:39:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where is Ann with the rule book to scold Gashley for removing their mics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:41:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's Ms. Widdecombe if yer nasty Andrew</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:42:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gashley needs to be cancelled immediately</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:45:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nasty gal has some nasty clothes what a shit ad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:51:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ashleys unicorn onsie should have won that immunity</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:52:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann it's just a hairy arse sit down love</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:53:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Andrew dresses so well. Toot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:54:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't accept the idea that Ann is an old woman. Amanda is older and she's been filthy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:55:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I miss the daily WUMUN screaming</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:56:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never realised how dull this show is when it's not Andrew and Courtney eye fucking</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:57:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>When Ashley is crying tomorrow that she's creeped out I hope someone says fuck off</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:59:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Their shipping name is literally Ann in the house: Annuwine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Courtney after last night's episode</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 09:43:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 18:18:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I now remember why I don't get crates anymore. 80% of what you can get is actual trash. They really should remove a lot of the rubbish in them because opening crate after crate of junk doesn't entice you to want to buy more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:00:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope there's a roundabout to truly fuck with them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:03:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>NOBODY SAVE DANIEL OR ELSE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:04:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shut up and drive is a bop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:05:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone else feel like Ann is playing up to the cameras a bit? Her theatrics are getting annoying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:06:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I was in that house I'd deffo run over Daniel a few times</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:07:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Being shaded by a bot! This is a black mirror episode</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:12:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Marcus you shady bitch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:19:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Daniel is so full of himself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:23:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Daniel looks like a sex offender in those glasses</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:24:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney and Andrew being an intellectual power couple</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:26:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>This question is rigged against the gays. Who knows that??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:28:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Posh people like Rachel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:32:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney that outfit and lighting is not transvestite friendly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:34:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>TUNE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:35:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jonnys hair always looks so good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:36:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>YES DANIEL DIDN'T WIN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:37:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ashley you are cancelled for not choosing Daniel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:42:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amanda is an icon. I need her to be my tea BFF</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:42:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ginuwine, a serial pumper and dumper, is giving you relationship advice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:45:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Andrew dishing out the T</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:47:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Andrew talking about Ann](https://youtu.be/GPDt6cMYvoM)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:53:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not that's serious ~~Jaremi~~ Ann</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:57:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tbh if Ann wanted a good kip she shouldn't have signed up for BB</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:58:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jonny always sounds drunk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:05:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Finally an episode with bitchy drama. It's been too long</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:08:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's no wonder Ann is a lonely old woman. She can blame it on being busy but I think it's because she's a rude cow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:12:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ashley the gay rights activist</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:15:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>All ladies voting for Daniel love it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:15:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Daniel is so fucking vile. I can't believe this is a grown man and a father</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:17:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I only wish he could be booed so we could see a little part of him die. He's gagging for positive attention</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:22:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wayne is me describing the current pop star I'm stanning</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:23:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nominating Amanda is an actual hate crime</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:24:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney doing her nails cause she is so over men</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:25:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>WHY IS NO ONE CHOOSING ANN WHAT THE FUCK IS WRONG WITH YOU ALL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:27:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol Daniel is dying inside hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:30:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Daniel is such a stroppy bitch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:30:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm getting my life hearing Daniel have a melt down and Courtney tops it by not giving a shit about him. Icon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:37:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you imagine Ann being in the same house as Tiffany or Farah? Or with that geordie shore girl who pissed her bed more than once. Ann doesn't realise how lucky she is with these housemates. God I wish Ann was in an earlier season...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:39:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Him molesting that window naked and moaning would have been iconic with Ann in the house</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:41:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney has sellotaped her dick to her arsehole. Holding a feather is nothing in comparison</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:43:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol Daniel really makes everything about him self. Fucking ego maniac</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:45:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cutsey factor doesnt make you a target</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:46:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ashley is so grotty with Ginuwine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:52:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maggies shining influence on Amanda has gone. No wonder she's cranky now shes only got that miserable old bat for company</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:57:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney has literally been sent to sleep by all this heterosexuality</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:58:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Used to be Daniel.... OK lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Daniel trying to cram that rudemption arc quickly. Look I'm a recovering mysoginist</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 21:10:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm really confused. How is it a live eviction if we don't even know who's up?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 21:18:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mess. I don't want to sound like a conspiracy theorist but with all the recent Ann wankery it wouldn't surprise me if it's a delay to stop people from evicting her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 21:37:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/cringe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:01:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>A rushed short episode that hasn't started because adverts are still running. Channel 5 is a mess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:05:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I'm so glad youre here ](https://i.imgur.com/rpv3LIg.gif)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:09:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann is a SNAKE. She saved Daniel and said he needed a chance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:16:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me tbh. This season has been a downward mess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:20:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>John Barnes reveals all about his time in the house #NEXT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:23:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Conservative party members are embrassing. One of their favourite swear words is darn and the other likes running through wheat fields.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:25:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>We literally just had a shit break. God I wish BB was on BBC</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:30:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why are we wasting time on this interview?? Channel 5s time management is shocking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:31:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is John incapable of one word answers? It's a never ending spiel of shit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:32:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>John is me when a cute guy says hi and I don't shut up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:33:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>"we've all been teasing Andrew and Shane..." that's the issue you nob</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:35:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do my fellow gays feel about John telling us what homophobia is and why we wouldn't take it personally</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:36:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bring back Davina. Emma is so passive it's boring</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:39:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>This countries worship of footballers is so boring</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:42:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not even Andrews ass could have saved this shit hour. Our highlights have been literally noms and nothing else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:42:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>If control means not shutting up then yeah he does</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:45:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>If Ashely isn't on the floor howling in anguish over Ginuwine leaving then it's so fucking fake</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ashely looks devastated!!  #128580;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gag</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 22:57:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was a waste of time. I could've got an early night</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 23:00:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bet they all get put up so they can deflect people away from Ann</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 19:31:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Except for Serena</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 22:36:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>For a show who has a large gay following, Channel 5 has disrespected the lgbt fans by the blatant bias towards Ann.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 22:39:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I honestly don't have the energy to continue with this bullshit anymore. I can't wait for Emma to go on about how Jonny and Daniel were great housemates.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 22:40:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is Ann's country now. Swearing is sinful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 22:46:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sarah Harding already did that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 22:48:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly it's a win/win if Courtney goes. She gets away from the toxic homophobia of the house, she can enjoy a good private bitch with her new judy Andrew but more importantly we can all stop watching this fucking shit show.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 22:50:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm gonna go in the audience, grab a megaphone and howl CUNT at her all night</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 22:55:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally a segment on Johnny White knighting Ann and causing shit between the two. Honestly fuck this show and fuck you Emma</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 22:55:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate respect your elders. Ann has shown NOTHING but disrespect for others</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 22:57:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah we should allow homophobia to go unchallenged Emma...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 22:59:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Johnny, jump</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 23:00:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney looks so good in her all stars 3 promo lewk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 23:31:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like the sad bunch of violin players in the titanic saying goodbye to their friends before they all drown. This might be the last time a bunch of us watch this shit series together and honestly I can't wait.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 23:35:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some Ann Stan has broke in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 23:36:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I'm deffo not watching this shit interview so good night everyone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 21:54:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope that Courtney voters don't rely on her being assumed safe. She's made it so far she has to win this otherwise this entire shitty season was a waste of all of our time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:04:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I miss when the audience was a proper panto screaming get x out. This neutered audience is shit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:08:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omgggg ashley is so boring</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:09:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are malikas eyebrows tattoos? Cause they are always right</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:11:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shane L not being a stereotype at all</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:17:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Winners segment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:18:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney looks so good. I'm straight now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:18:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jump</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:20:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann just fuck off you old bat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:21:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>This task is rigged for Courtney csuse every gay boy has practiced being a spice girl or Beyonce</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:22:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann is cunty spice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:24:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann better sing 2 become 1 or else</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:25:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shane L looks like noel fielding</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:26:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Malika would be such a good kareoke partner</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:27:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why isn't everyone on their feet going crazy for Beyonce??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:33:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney living her gay fantasy and I'm so proud</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:35:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>It just didn't happen or it just didn't happen csuse I'm a cantankerous old miserable witch and no one wants to be with me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:36:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann forgetting the drag race fan base... For shame girl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:37:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why does Ashely talk like that girl on Google translate when you put random words in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:40:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>BB really going for that good vs evil final</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:41:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because old racist homophobic old women remind people of their grannies so they're cute</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:42:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Malika deserves this entire interview and exit to herself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:43:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Malika was robbed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:44:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol at no one chanting for ashbot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:47:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd give Ann a hug to terrify her with my gay germs. I'm petty</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:50:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Emma I want them all to stay: Except for ~~Serena~~ Andrew</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:53:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Ashleys long interview ](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=M7HJH0IH3dc)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:54:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmfao the gag of Genuwine there she looks terrified. Twat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:55:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>SPEAK TO MALIKA FFS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:55:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that Ashley's parents next to Ginuwine loool?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 22:56:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Car crash interview</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 23:01:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is this Ann redemption spin ? Why is no one allowed to call her out for what she is</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 23:02:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Malika bout to slap a bitch up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 23:02:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why didn't they ask Malika about Ann? Fucking shady whores</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 23:05:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know it shouldn't bother me but I'm really wound up that Ann is untouchable. She can't be criticised and her nasty views are spun as "oh she's just stubborn. The lack of impartiality is just awful. It should be the housemates causing drama not the producers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 23:07:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Emma can't speak because she's been deep throating Ann all season</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 23:17:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>And here I was thinking Ashelys interview was cringe...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 23:18:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 23:19:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Giving me flashbacks to Emma trying to interview Gary Busey</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 23:21:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so over it now. It's just boring how everything is always about Ann</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 23:24:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't wait for CBB to be cancelled. Ann was the last nail in the coffin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 23:25:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amanda's partner low key not haply about Ann</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 23:26:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Emma: Let's talk about wayne *one second later* Thank you Amanda you were great</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 23:29:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's been boring since India left sis</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 18:41:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Anything the legendary icon Pete Burns said and did. Truly one of the best housemates ever. Rip legend ](https://youtu.be/2YCoM-oBZyw)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 21:39:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me and my manager at work spent all day talking about how cute Courtdrew are. I can't escape them and I don't care!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 21:58:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only thing I dislike about Courtdrew is that they make me realise how lonely I am  #128557; *cries in lonely*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 21:59:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's channel 5, everything on here is weird</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:06:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you reckon Ann hates anything with a bit of skin csuse she is literally a 70 year old virgin and doesn't know how to react. She has a child like mentality like how bots and girls go ewwww at each other when they're 5 years old.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:07:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm surprised Anns boobs didn't whack her in the face with the speed she flew out of that room</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:10:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann confirmed a cheater by grabbing the ball</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:14:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>If India doesn't scream WUMUN at some point then she shouldn't have been invited back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:16:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fake ass hoe Ann playing up to the cameras</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:17:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>The straights not clocking a stunt bless them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:19:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the clip they chose for Ann? OK werk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:21:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope India goes full ring and crawls out of the TV</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:22:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>India cunt off you're giving Ann ammo and legitimisation</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:23:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>WUMUN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:24:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is giving me flashbacks to Farah Moan and her awkward roast</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:24:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god this is a disaster. Thank you India for being the mess you are</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:26:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Daily reminder jess is a 30 year old child</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:28:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney being the respectful dickpig. She's a better person than me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:29:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Emma better know first aid for when Ann clutches her pearls at the sheer obscenity of it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:34:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Me when Andrew called Courtney fit](https://i.imgur.com/pAYlCn4.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:35:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I need an interactive Andrew on my wall</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:37:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is emmy, Grammy and brit award winning levels of amazing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:39:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so cute. Andrew is so cute</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:39:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOTS TO TELL YA. THEY FUCKING ON FRIDAY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:41:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god I love Rachel. She's so cringe she was robbed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:43:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jess not giving a shit about Maggie. snake</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:43:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank God Andrew is nearly naked. Less for Courtney to take off</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:45:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>India what are you on about</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:46:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Andrew and Courtney are so beautiful  #128557; #128557; #128557;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:46:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>India is the cool mum from mean girls</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:48:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blonde casino girl is me sshhhing everyone when Courtdrew are on</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:52:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maggie on the pole is me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amanda get away from them!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:54:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus christ they couldn't resist gashley</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:54:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why are Ashley and Genuwine talking like they haven't spoken on the outside yet?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:56:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Malika is us. God save our Queen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:57:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bitch why am I crying? That was so nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 22:57:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aww I love this cast.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 23:00:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd also like to report a robbery. Courtney stole my man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 23:02:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>We need an /r/Courtdrew to survive the drought</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 21:41:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sis I didn't even know??!! This is great news. Only Courtney winning can top this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 21:43:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Before the night gets crazy and hectic I've enjoyed moaning on here every night with you bitches. Thanks for being a great sub to have a laugh with xoxo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:01:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>All stars was great, the spice girls are returning and Courtney is going to win. God loves the gays</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:02:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bitch I'm quaking</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:03:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney getting the most cheers. When it's right it's right</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:04:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Emma's look is a toot tonight</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:05:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Andrew keep doing what you're doing sweety. You look good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:07:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those cheers just made me so emotional. We can't have another trump /brexit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:08:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>WUMUN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:10:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mute</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:10:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>THIS IS OUR SEGMENT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:14:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>This show is making me stress eat. I've had three creme eggs already</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:15:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>To quote Bianca on BBBOTs a few years ago YOU'D ONLY KICK HIM OUT OF BED TO FUCK HIM ON THE FLOOR</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:17:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I LOVE THIS GAY CROWD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:18:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney suits pink hair so much. Flawless</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:21:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:23:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wayne is so adorable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:25:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Andrew knows his audience showing all that skin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:26:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Malika can't wait for this to be over so she can get back to her LA life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:26:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>This interview is amazing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:27:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love that Wayne is showing his man off. Glad Ann isn't there to roll her eyes at love</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:33:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'M CRYING AT ALL THE LOVE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Emma and Jess look like two gorgeous sisters</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:41:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maggie is so precious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:43:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>My blood pressure has risen again. We are so close!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:47:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm having the sweats. This is too fucking intense</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:48:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>That took too fucking long Emma jesus I nearly died</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:50:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>She has the crowd and Andrew. Girlfriend needs nothing more</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:53:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I might!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:54:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Malika is so bored lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:56:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>They literally have no other clips to show him. He has seen this before</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:59:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>FUCK OFF WILL AND GRACE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 22:59:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmfao this is so awkward</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:02:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's been one minute and I've already aged about ten years through stress. Hurry the fuck up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:05:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann your performance was more... Poorformance. Now sashey away</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:12:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excellent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:19:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Leslie Jordan, you are gayer than the fire island production of Rent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:20:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fake news</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:31:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>HERE WE GO BITCHES</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:32:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm shaking and not just in anticipation but from fucking stress</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:33:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm dying!! Quick Andrew do emergency cpr on me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:34:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I CNT XOPE OMG</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:35:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>MAKE BRITAIN GAY AGAIN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:36:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I LOVE IT I LOVE US I LOVE THE GAYS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:37:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>BIG BROTHER OFFICIALLY UNCANCELLED</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:41:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>All these Facebook tears are like water sports to me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:44:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Emma is a spider spinning all this Ann bullshit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:45:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Andrew isn't even smirking I love him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:46:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Malika so stuuuninngg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:48:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why couldn't we have had half an hour of our crowned Queen instead of this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:49:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>All the gays booing her I LOVE IT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:50:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Andrew shaking his head. True ally</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:50:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Emma as Rylan is one of your bffs and a married gay man, you are being too lenient on someone who would happily have that marriage illegal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:51:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>QUEEN QUEEN QUEEN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:52:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm crying I am so proud of her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:53:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Andrew going mental is all of us</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:55:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Emma seems very bored compared to Ann's interview</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:57:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:58:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just snog already</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:00:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is everyone so low energy in there?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:03:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann had a longer interview than the winner</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:04:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who's ready for a hour long Ann wankathon while Courtney hold her tounge?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:07:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Lol... So fragile ](https://i.imgur.com/l59ju8j.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:09:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg Rachel I love it such a mess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:10:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is like the gays winning the world cup. Everyone is off their tits</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:12:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Malika hates every minute of this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:13:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Malika not even standing up to clap. I live for the nerve</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:14:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Emma's hair is about to jump</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:15:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rylan confirmed to be muzzled by channel 5</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:16:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Malika hates all of this haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:18:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Davina back when?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:20:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bianca would give Ann something to actuslly be shocked about</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:21:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Our next cbb winner</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:23:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shane invented sandwiches</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:26:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can someone get Ann a pair of ear muffs or a fucking taxi out of there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:27:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg I said muff she's gonna scowl at me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:29:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tom acting like he's walking in a Courtney Act museum. True gay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:30:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann loves a good muff</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:31:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The audience is actually laughing at her putting her hands in her ear. How embarrassing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:33:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is just ridiculous and not funny. Five Gs girl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:34:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>If looks could kill Andrew...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:34:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg she's so rude</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:35:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't remember Ann putting her fingers in her ear when she left the house. The crowd was louder</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:35:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>This looks like some kind of anime power couple</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>No she's just a cunt. She wasn't putting her hands in her ears when in the house of commons</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:39:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Andrew looks like one of those waiters who seduce you when you pay your bill</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:40:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love a gay icon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Andrew is popping Courtneys tuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:43:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just two winners having a kiki</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:44:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Non sexual life partners. That's cute</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:45:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ann currently putting her ear muffs on at all gay positivity</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:49:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:51:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is valid tame wasted on what could have been Courtney time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:51:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>OK that woman line was great</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:53:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Malika is smiling cause she knows she's minutes away from her flight back to LA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:56:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney gave you lewks every night. She was robbed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:57:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>This entire hour was choices</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:58:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think malika might have gone home already and we are looking at a cardboard cut out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 01:00:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that was shit. Thanks everyone for being a good laugh see you all in the summer x</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 17:41:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>God they make me feel ugly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This random comment on a BBC news article.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 17:53:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 18:03:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can confirm, I am currently hospitali**s**ed from the comment section.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 07:21:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was a gif of someone shrugging their shoulders</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Assassin has wares... if you have coin</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 17:03:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 17:06:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I finally got around to buying Origins and I am enjoying it so much! What a gorgeous game. I thought it wouldn't be as impressive as the previous games due to it being mostly desert, but it's so good. I can't wait to see how the rest of the game goes and what other ridiculous armors there are to pose in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 15:00:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Senu and photomode are the perfect combination](https://imgur.com/a/QLLM0)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 14:41:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish we spent more time listening to Monique and the other black girls discuss being gay and black more. I'm neither American nor black and that little bit I heard was so interesting and heartbreaking. We deserved more and the girls deserved to get more of their message out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 09:12:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure about the ghost horse but I think the dark stag pops up whenever the date is Friday 13th.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 09:24:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're after an exclusive (and expensive) mount I reckon loads will pop up in the store when Summerset is released. Besides that it seems to be quite random unless they're themed mounts like Christmas ones.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 20:34:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tried MUA:1 the other day and it was playable but extremely frustrating. My controller kept disconnecting even though it was wired in which is shit because this game is unplayable with keyboard and mouse. I found the video settings shit as well as it wouldn't change to the resolution I wanted, it just stayed the same. I ended up getting a refund.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 21:29:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone check on the Aussies, they might have fallen back to sleep after this song.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 21:34:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is peak Eurovision mess and I love it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 21:38:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Singing and crying into a rose is dramatic, even for Eurovision</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 21:46:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Black eyed peas look different</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 21:50:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>That pink blouse is horrendous. BOOT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 21:52:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>This sounds so 2000 and late. Very outdated</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 21:55:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is reminding me of when I #8217;m drunk and dance to myself in the mirror and awkward especially with zero noise from the crowd</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 22:05:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>She #8217;s brave wearing a white dress with paint on her hand</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 22:14:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is with the random fingerless glove? I love when Eurovision brings back weird 20 year old fashion trends</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 22:15:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Currently having an eplileptic fit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 22:17:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Budget Britney with a Joanne hat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 22:21:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cmon gays! Let #8217;s get eurovisoning!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 22:22:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Giving me a major case of boyfriend that look like twins</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 22:25:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>God is a woman and she is from Cyprus. Sent down to give us FUEGO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 22:26:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shakironc #233;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 22:40:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I miss Petra Mede</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 22:50:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love me some camp, but this  #8220;comedy #8221;? Prison, honey.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 23:01:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m currently on the phone with Jon Ola Sand over the painful levels of cringe from these hosts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 23:03:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Surie is thinking Brexit isn #8217;t that bad now after those jokes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 23:08:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brits are buzzing that we have some guaranteed points now. Well done Ireland</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 23:11:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that was fun, see you on Thursday girls and gays.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:04:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve pressed the mute button and I think you all should too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:07:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like I have this seen kind of production at least twice every year since 2010.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:09:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>This crowd is so low energy! Sad!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:12:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you #8217;re low key into BDSM but you have to keep it family friendly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:14:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>No comment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:15:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Serving you god of war soundtrack</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:17:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate that I don #8217;t hate this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:21:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey hey hey put ya lighters out owwwww jenny b in the haaause okkurrrr</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:23:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Praise be to Thor</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:28:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Estonia about to sue as that mountain looks suspiciously similar to her stunning Tuesday dress</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:30:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>hopefully Russia follows Azerbaijan and their new hobby of breaking traditions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:31:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>OUR LADY OF FUEGO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:33:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>The level of cringe.. far too much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:34:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so gay that China is about to censor it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:36:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>They deserve to through for being the only visually interesting act</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:39:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Netherlands taking the message America First a bit too literal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:41:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>That crowd is so lifeless</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:42:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am sure.... Shady fucking whores</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:43:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Smoko is a banger and I won #8217;t allow anyone to say anything different</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:45:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Australia thank you for proving it #8217;s not just The UK that is boring in the Anglosphere</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:48:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jon ola sand save us</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:52:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>This 2007 era club beat is so bad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:55:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thicc lorde</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:57:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Animal and human relationships</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:58:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>If the next six are anything like the previous six I can #8217;t cope</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:03:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s not a ballad so I #8217;m feeling it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:04:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol Hungary won #8217;t be able to sing on Saturday after smashing the fuck out of this vocal chords</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:04:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg the tone deaf band members STOPPPP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:05:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lana del Latvia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:07:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>This just sounds like every girl singing a generic song at a karaoke</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:08:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmfao at that shit hairography</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:10:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why does this sound like he #8217;s lip sychning to Bruno mars?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:11:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>He was hot until he opened his mouth and sounded like a 14 year old boy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:14:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lady turquaaaaahhhzzz with that jacket</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:15:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>He looks like he can #8217;t wait for this to be over. Me too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:16:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m more interested in the super dramatic telenvoa faces the backup singers are making</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:19:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>She #8217;s giving us energy which is more than most people we #8217;ve seen so fair play to the girl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:20:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m so gay. I love a tight coreography. Werk miss Slovenia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:21:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Beyonc #233; about to sue for that single ladies hand swish</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:23:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is looks a real life anime scene</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:24:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>2018 is the year that Eurovision went emo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:27:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>tfw we have half an hour of repeat montages and cringe humour</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:32:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>SF2 should be cancelled and everyone from SF1 should go into the final it was far better</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>END THIS FILLER AND PUT THE BORING SONGS ON REPLAY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:38:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Massive respect for these hosts for just getting on with be being actual cringe goddesses</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:40:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rylan would be a great host tbh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:45:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>OI OI OI</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:50:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you bbc for not making us watch attenburger</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:52:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Big up Eurovision blocking China from airing the show cause they blocked Ireland #8217;s performance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:57:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>The beeb would rather us watch their trash than attenburger and I am so grateful for it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 23:00:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Monsieur France is fiiine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 23:02:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>JUST REVEAL THE RESULTS SO I CAN GO TO BED</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 23:11:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>No Russia and Azerbaijan!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 23:11:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope it isn #8217;t spun that Russia didn #8217;t make it cause they had a disabled singer cause that #8217;s cruel, she was just shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 23:30:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Romania I think. The one with the creepy mannequins</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The real star of last nights semi final</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 11:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 21:00:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>IM SO EXCITED</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 21:54:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>FUCK THAT GUY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 22:39:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is peak Eurotrash and I love it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 23:06:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why these words weren #8217;t put on the LED screen behind then I will never know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 23:16:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bit shit that Hungarys chorus wasn #8217;t shown in the repeat. That was the best part</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 23:19:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really really REALLY miss Sweden #8217;s interval acts. They always put on a great show.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 00:02:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Surie deserved better</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 00:06:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>IRELAND WORST ALLY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 00:11:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>New voting system is wank</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 00:16:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>NO POINTS FROM AUSTRALIA. MORE PENAL COLONIES REQUIRED</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 00:22:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wtf I love Montenegro now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 00:44:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bet 4chan is going mental that Israel won</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 17:46:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here's an image of all three Princes from the trailer.](https://imgur.com/a/HmSzhnX) I really hope we get to see them in game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 18:27:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 19:04:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read this in her voice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 19:10:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another batch brother! I have met hardly anyone else that calls them batches</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 08:17:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep  #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 19:59:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just follow the quests from Bleackrock Isle onwards and you'll progress through the Ebonheart questline as it's meant to be played out. Try and do fighters guild/mages guild as you go through the zones as they each have a quest in each zone. I also liked to do a main quest story line each time I entered a new zone which helped with the pacing. Once that's done, you can play the DLCs in release order.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 20:08:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can do them at anytime, but there will be a way to do them all at the end of the ebonheart quest line that makes sense if you want to play the story it's "meant to be played"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 19:58:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Divine Conundrum is the first quest for the Morrowind main quest line</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 07:33:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Willam's look of pure disgust always gets me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 07:52:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is true. I appreciate that Wiliam didn't drag it out for cringe and educated Hemmy straight away, but that micro-expression doesn't lie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me wearing my shirts this week</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 21:34:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 07:46:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I felt the same. I said to myself I will try it once and if it goes terrible, I won't do it again. But everything went fine and I didn't self-combust so I tried the next day again and it felt a little easier. I think it also depends on what you're wearing. I had a plaid pattern shirt with chinos so I could look a bit more casual but if I had to look formal I probably wouldn't do a French tuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 12:11:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here's an image of the original tweet for those who never saw it ](https://i.imgur.com/Zqcrna4.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 00:30:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>The University of Kent in Canterbury is a good choice. It's a good sized popular University in a nice and quiet city, but one that has enough nightlife if you care for that. It's marketed as the European University as well in that interests you. I went there and loved it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 18:40:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I reckon that Rodrigo will be the one we all scream at this year. I can't wait</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 19:04:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a shame. I was hoping for some good cringe, but if the rumors of Sinnita are true then I'm sure she'll provide loads.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 14:20:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Phi Phi, Kim and Perez!! There is a 100% chance of a scrap tonight</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 21:58:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've missed spending my nights bitching with you lot, hopefully this season will be good!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:02:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Emma girl, your hair....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:06:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Emma out of breath just by walking hits too close to home</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:09:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remembered why I normally skip launch nights  #128580;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:11:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>This diary room... **BOOT**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:11:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fergie looks rough. Girl really took double duchess flopping to heart</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:13:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>CARS, HIDDEN STAIRS IN THE HOUSE! We are just missing davina</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:14:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would totally keep telling her my name is Xenu</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:16:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love that Kirsty matches the chair.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:19:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is boring considered being controversial? If so, he's perfect</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:19:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>CHICKEN LIVERED SHITS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:22:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh I remember Scotty T winning for being boring. Never forgive, never forget</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:27:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unless this footballer is an ADULTERER I'm not interested</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:28:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm loving Emma's channel 5 celebs in rehab narration</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:29:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bad boy translates to bad housemate  #128580;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:31:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tea. It's the most selfish thing you can do</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:31:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus christ, they're really scraping the barrel. The local Swan that keeps attacking people in the chippy near me is more famous</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:33:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Courtney Stodden on more xanax</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>He'd get my vote cause he loves a scrap</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:35:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>American Horror Story: ~~Roanoke~~ Rodrigo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:36:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly this man has a mental illness and he needs help, not more money to be wasted</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:38:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Giving me Gary Busey vibes where no one knows how to handle him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:39:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly though imagine waking up and seeing him in the night. Prison, honey</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:40:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh yeah 100%, they're just as bad. But he needed an intervention a long time ago</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:43:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's shit. I enjoy BB being a big panto. I don't like how scared they have been in recent seasons of audience interactions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:45:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most of us know you from that gif of Tom Daley staring at your dick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:46:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boo boo my life is hard cause I'm a cheat. Fuck offff</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:49:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Camera panning on Chloe. Over this showmance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:50:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Girl, it's love Island. It's not a real relationship  #129315;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:51:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry the old gabby can't come to phone right now. She's dead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:54:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>You missed NOTHING. Don't worry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:55:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bare jokes cheeky... Kill me. Now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:56:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did this advert say WUMUN?!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:01:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let's put a pervert in the house! They couldn't Trump so they got this guy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:03:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfunny pervy man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:04:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>OFF OFF OFF OFF</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:05:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thankfully he didn't try and out do courtney with her dress stunt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:06:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why does Rodrigo look like he can spit acid like that dinosaur from Jurassic Park? I hope he can</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:07:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm hoping the twist is a meteor strike</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:08:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Emma sis, go to the security man. NOW</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:09:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are they all snorting lines in those cars?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:11:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus Christ. These sob stories are x factor tier level of pathetic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:11:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>But we already had Gary Busey?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:12:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>This girl is the living embodiment of "omg ur so brave, thanks for sharing"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:13:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did she come in in her PE kit?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:15:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Slap your titties girl on camera</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rodrigo went in for the vampire bite</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:17:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>The show wouod have been taken off air</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:17:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>This cast and episode is dryer than your vajoina. It's so dull</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:18:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Roxanne been sharing the drugs with her bf, those eyes don't lie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:20:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll finally see the appeal of vore if that happens</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:23:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't say that name! If she's back again I'll scream</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:24:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're a fraud, bitch. Sue me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:25:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>NURSE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:26:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mystic Meg or nothing. I won't acknowledge these charlatans</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:27:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ghosts? Don't tell Gemma Collins</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:28:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let me tell you a story about flats. NO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:29:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>MIA bad girls is a tuuune</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fight night part 2 electric bogoloo featuring Natalie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:31:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live for a trashy tiara and matching dress. Icon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:33:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meee! It looks like he lost his fight with Natalie though but he's a twat so it's all good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:33:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>That twirl into the house! Stunning, flawless</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:35:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perfect for chinning her haters</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:39:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>FUCK OFF CAPITALIST SCUM. YOU AREN'T STORMY DANIELS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:40:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Send Corbyn in for a good fight with this guy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>As if I stayed up late to watch a literal fat cat be hyped up as a housemate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:42:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>White collar crime is the most boring shit ever Emma, how can you want to hear those stories</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:43:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Housemates probably thinking the producer was sent in to top up the drinks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:45:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Channel 5 is broke hence why literal whos are in there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:46:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>The biggest storm in the world right now is the rage on /r/bbuk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:47:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rodrigo is me with one glass of rose</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:48:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol the crowd is so over this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:51:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>India about to sue Calvin klein for monetising her catchphrase</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:53:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>David Cameron is on it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:53:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fresh from a horrible car crash? Is Emma describing the show</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:55:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love Kim so much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:57:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that hit? HAHAHA HAHAHA FUCK THIS SHIT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 00:00:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even ofcom are complaining</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 00:01:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>That header will be the title of my autobiography</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me @ing channel 5 over this poor cast and stormy Daniels drop out</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 07:46:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 10:03:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Channel 5 press team thinking of excuses ](https://giphy.com/gifs/bianca-ryan-EzQt0eRU2SVa0)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 14:50:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty much this. Also adding to this the fact that channel 5 themed the entire series around her and nearly used all their budget to get Stormy to sign up, who was reported as the highest paid housemate ever. Then the gag is that she quit before the started so the storm theme they built the series around is now a dud and the big juicy gossip they were hoping for from Stormy amounted to nothing. She probably wouldn't have been an amazing housemate, but she would have provided a lot of attention that channel 5 wanted and that isn't happening anymore. This series is the textbook definition of why you shouldn't put all your eggs in one basket.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 19:36:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>She would be a great housemate. [Even more so if there was a talent competition csuse you know 100% she'd win. ](https://youtu.be/e21pVw2_75U)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 12:22:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think channel 5 were hoping for attention from Trump himself rather than any major goss. The way Kirstie is now in the task playing a Trump character was built around Stormy to do and provoke Trump for an angry tweet and therefore more viewers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 12:29:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>*tap tap tap* hi channel 5, are you hiring today? Oh great, /u/masc-4-masc will be down there and fill up an application because that is a perfect cast and I'm very upset we will never see the warzone that will be that season. You could also add Frenchy and Megan Mckenna for even more screaming</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:01:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still not over celebs on a farm having a better line up than this season</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:05:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm surprised Hardeep hasn't been bottled yet. So fucking annoying and desperate to fit in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:07:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you also ran through a field of wheat sally? Naughty girl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:10:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was Hardeep trying to get the footballer to out footballers?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:11:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love islanders going on about their literal showmance will never not bore me to death</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:13:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Natalie knows she can't drop kick Trump so she's going for Kirstie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:14:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Queen Natalie, tear down that wall!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:19:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually forgot Nick existed until this task</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:22:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone needs to tell Natalie that Kirstie didn't come up with this idea and would rather be reading about dianetics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:24:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gooch alert</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:26:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>For a reality TV Pro, how can Natalie be so stupid and not realise this is a producer stunt not Kirstie?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:27:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Natalie giving me Tiffany I would like to tell Gemma she is a fat cunt flashback  #10084; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:28:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>This task is so stupid, I love it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:30:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm scared that the next trump guy to run in will get throttled by Natalie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:30:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everyone fake laughing because its awkward as fuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:32:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ew callum best</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:33:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>USA vs UK CBB was a better American themed season. God I miss Farrah</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:35:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>She annoyed me the moment she came down the stairs pretending to be lost and slapping her titties. Girls trying too hard</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:36:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually thought that was Dan and Gabby lmao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:39:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes Natalie, spill that scalding tea</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:42:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>How did Sally not sense ryan behind the door?  #129300;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:43:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does Rodrigo have contact lenses or has he fucked his eyes up?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:46:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hurricane Natalie living up to the storm theme, she's on a shit stirring rampage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:46:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>SHPOCK</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:48:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>If he wasn't so pervy he wouldn't piss me off as much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:52:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hillary Clinton finally wins something</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:55:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like I'm on /r/UnitedKingdom with this bitter England/Scotland bitching</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 23:04:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Says it all really ](https://youtu.be/grIOioq5DdQ)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 11:04:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Send Leah Remini in!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 15:09:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>If they're gonna axe it I want them to go out with a bang with the ultimate all stars season. Tiffany, Kim, Perez, Farrah, Courtney etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 10:44:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmfao this is a complete disaster. The only housemates that were actually doing something have left. The rest of them are boring as fuck and it will be nothing but dull and cringey showmances. RIP CBB</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 11:12:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>This show is beyond saving now. I think they need to have a good break and think what made the show enjoyable in terms of cast, tasks, design and even live feeds. CBB has been very stale in recent years relying on one or two members of the cast to hold the show and it's just not doable nor enjoyable anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 12:37:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I stop watching for a week and all the drama kicks off! What a mess that girl is though. How did she get past the pysch eval? Glad she's been booted out though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 17:40:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Roxy when the cameras are on her](https://images.wetheunicorns.com/images/14715?crop=16_9 amp;width=660 amp;relax=1 amp;signature=rO8JQ6lPSzs2AZGRGx9rmUkiTic=) But seriously, she's an actual psycho. Also, how the fuck was she hired for anything as an actress? I've seen more convincing performances by my dog's shit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>