<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7581</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My vet bills me $0.00 for a "Thank you."</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-14 22:30:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Schnauzers have mastered the art of sleeping</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-04 07:02:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Saw this while walking my dog today.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-03 03:28:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Was directed to post this here... Yeah, I'd say this is pretty bad.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-04 04:28:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"Is this how you do it?" - my dog wasn't sure about this bench</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-11 19:27:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"Is this how you do it?" [x-posted from r/aww]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-11 21:43:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Best way to conceal as a slim female?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-12 07:09:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been carrying my Walther CCP in my purse for a couple of months now, but I know that I really need to switch to on body carry. I looked at an IWB holster the other day and printed pretty badly. I'm a petite female with a fairly slim build, about 5'2", 105 lbs. My clothes tend to be on the more fitted side, and I don't really have an option to drastically change my wardrobe. I've seen the Can Can Concealment, though I haven't tried it out to see if it alleviates printing. Any thoughts? People with the same build as me... What have you done effectively (without changing my weapon. I love what I'm carrying). EDIT: Thanks guys! Lots of great suggestions and things for me to check out, so I'm going to spend some time looking at each option. I see a few posters suggest I try a smaller pistol, and I may look, but I REALLY love my Walther! Nevertheless, I've gotta go with what works, so if all else fails I will be looking at finding something else I love ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I caught her mid-shake. I love her ears!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-26 08:05:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Question] Changing sentences from colloquial speech to literary speech</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 22:51:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm using a book for self study right now, and the instructions of one particular exercise are as follows:  #44396; #50612; #52404;  #47928; #51109; #51012;  #47928; #50612; #52404; #47196;  #48148; #44984; #49884; #50724;. A few of the sentences: 1)  #45208; #45716; " #54620; #44397; #49324;" #46972; #45716;  #52293; #51012;  #51069; #50632; #50612;. 2)  #54620; #44397; #51032;  #50669; #49324; #44032;  #54620; #45576; #50640;  #48372; #51060; #45908; #46972;. 3)  #45208; #45716;  #50668; #51088; #46308; #51032;  #49373; #54876; #50640;  #45824; #54644;  #49548; #44060; #54620;  #48512; #48516; #51060;  #44032; #51109;  #44592; #50613; #50640;  #45224; #50500;. So does it basically want me to change these sentences to  #51316; #45843; #47568;? i.e.  #51200; #45716; " #54620; #44397; #49324;" #46972; #45716;  #52293; #51012;  #51069; #50632; #50612; #50836;.  #54620; #44397; #51032;  #50669; #49324; #44032;  #54620; #45576; #50640;  #48372; #51060; #45912; #45936; #50836;. etc.?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>happy birthday to our lemgthy friemd (he's 7)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 19:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>blurry still frame of a dog</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-11 00:21:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I found this puppy "popcorn" at a dog bakery. Ella is very pleased.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 06:42:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>s a v e h e r</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 20:46:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Witness/Friend] That Time My Father-In-Law Was Wanted by Police (long)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-18 22:19:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>My husband and I both come from middle class families and everyone on both sides are very straight-laced (we met at church, no one was into drugs or alcohol, etc.) My husband's dad is retired now, but when we first got married he held a fairly high position at a hospital. When he wasn't at work he was the Deacon at our church, always involved in leading Bible studies and so-forth. We'll say his dad's name is John. We married young so in our early years of marriage we were living in the not-so-great part of town. One day my husband was at school and my class hadn't started yet. As I was leisurely getting ready I hear a pounding at the door. Looking out, I see two police officers. I crack the door:  gt; Can I help you? Is something wrong? "Yes," they say. "We're looking for John. Is he here?" My first thought was, well why the heck would they be looking for my father-in-law at my house...? I'm thinking he's hurt or missing or something, so I ask no more questions and immediately respond:  gt; No, he should be at work! Is he okay? "Well," the officers respond, "he's wanted right now. Where does he work?" I'm panicking. What would my father-in-law be wanted for?! Some kind of... financial embezzlement?! After all, my in-laws just took a nice vacation... I tell the officers where he works and immediately start trying to call him, but he's not answering. Not much later, the officers are back. "We were just at XYZ Hospital and they say John doesn't work there. Can we come in and take a look around?" WHAT. THE. HECK. Are these guys even real? Here I am, a month past my 19th birthday in a seedy part of town... So I asked the officers to give me a moment so I could call dispatch and I shut the door. At this point, I imagine they thought I was trying to hide my father-in-law. After confirming that the officers were legitimate I let them in. They looked around, under beds, in closets, etc. Finally I asked them what my father-in-law was wanted for, but they wouldn't tell me. Now I'm thinking it's REALLY bad. They asked me again why my father-in-law works. I told them, the same as before, XYZ hospital. There's some back and forth, me saying  gt; Talk to Matt, the security guard! I was JUST there last week! Finally, one of the officers says, "We DID speak to Matt, and he says John Doe doesn't work there!" Wait. John. Doe? My father-in-law's last name is Smith... I showed the officer's my marriage certificate to confirm the last name, and they said they had some additional checking to do. I never heard back from them, so I assume they realized my father-in-law was innocent. But, for half a day at least, my super straight-laced, church-attending father-in-law was a fugitive from the law.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cat Cafe Blep</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 04:25:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 18:01:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>longboye and birb mlem</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-05 05:05:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>o no!! where he spots go?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 23:51:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>puggo blop</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 05:14:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>h o r s e b o y e has a vvv happy birthday</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 19:46:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>rare stuft animal pupper do a heckin BIG bite on a couch</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 20:00:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>LONGBOYE does a heckin trot in the park</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 16:08:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Waiting for her Peanut Butter Man</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 16:49:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We went hiking this weekend, and Ella climbed her own little mountain</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 04:38:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Blurry picture of a dog</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 20:36:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>heckin wind does a B I G gust</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-06 13:59:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Who wants to see more Hopper segments?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-22 20:00:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do!!!  #128154; #10084; #65039; #128582; #127996;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I love it when she sleeps like this</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 19:00:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>sleep tight little schnauzer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 16:39:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"hey, i was sleeping!" loaf</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 05:38:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New ink day! J. Herbin Poussi #232;re de Lune</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 05:49:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>golden blepper and striped tiger woofer do a BIG happy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-15 03:24:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Did I hear someone say "treat"?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 08:29:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Playing with new ink - Diamine grey with Pilot Plumix italic nib</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 18:54:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A new addict - just want to share my excitement!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-20 09:37:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Skyrim came out while I was in the military stationed overseas. I remember all the guys in my unit obsessing over Skyrim, but I couldn't be bothered. I had more important stuff to do like... I can't even remember. Now my husband just got a PS4 and I saw the remastered Skyrim on sale for $30. He needed to buy one more game to get some special deal, so I said "get this one. I'll try it, even though I'll probably hate it." Now, a mere week and a half later, I've leveled up to level 18, bought a house in Whiterun, have slayed countless dragons, killed giants and mammoths, enchanted items, trained at the college of Winterhold... it's never ending! And it's beautiful! And amazing! I'm thrilled to join in this subreddit and ashamed that I never gave this game a chance before! And I can't believe I've only scratched the surface  #128558; By the way, any idea on when Elder Scrolls VI is coming out? Haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do you bribe your Schnauzer to come back home? Why, with a sausage, course! (x-post from woof_irl)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 02:52:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Struggling with FO4 - need tips and direction for a newbie</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 20:41:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>ETA: answered. Many thanks for the good tips! Hope it's okay to post this here, since I mostly see posts more intended for game comments and stuff... if there's a better sub to post my question in, please direct me! So I recently got FO4 because I was enjoying Skyrim so much. But I'm really having a hard time with it. I love the story and gameplay so far, but I'm having trouble with some basic things. For example, the weapons. There are just *so many* choices. Is there a decent weapon that I can use as a "every day carry" type gun and then just switch to a special gun for special situations (e.g. find something really long range for those times when I'm fighting raiders who are at a distance from me or something). Any weapons that are just basically useless that I can drop/not pick up? Also, the perks system... ack, I'm just overwhelmed. I'm curious to hear other people's experiences with how you upgrade your perks (evenly across the board / focus on building up just a couple). Finally, does anyone play without using chems? I have a ton that I've collected but I'm kind of confused about whether or not I should use them because they're "addictive." Are they detrimental if you use too many? I know these are probably kind of dumb questions, but I'd love any input! I'm not opposed to trial and error, and I love the open world and just wandering around... so if it's just kind of a "play a ton and you'll figure it out" type deal, I'm cool with that. But if anyone can give me some "must-know" tips, that would be helpful. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Your dream TES game: where would it be set?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 20:07:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking last night that I would love to see a prequel-esque game, set in the early days of Tamriel (probably Morrowind with some DLCs added later to include other locations) before the downfall of the Dwemer. I'd like to be able to play as either a Nord or Dwemer, and the acts of the game would follow the downfall of the Dwemer society. (I don't know how popular that would be, since you can't change the past and no matter what you did if you're playing as a Dwemer, you essentially lose in the end). I think there would be a lot of potential in the game, since the Dwemer were known for being creative and industrious. I bet it could take a lot of the building and creating aspects from FO4, where you could essentially build parts of the city-states that now (ruined) dot the landscape of Tamriel. I think it would also be a neat, immersive way to learn some of the backstory, which is still shrouded in mystery. I'm curious what others would like to see, location, era, lore, etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I told my husband to put pants on, but he was wearing pants</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 20:36:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>My husband and I were getting ready to go somewhere and I looked over at him. He was sitting at his computer and he was wearing a shirt but not pants. I told him I was almost ready to go so he should go put pants on. Except he was already wearing pants. He was wearing khaki pants and they blended into his skin in the dim light.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I made this new friend today. He lives in a record store  #8211; lucky guy!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 04:31:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lutherans and the Early Church Fathers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 05:58:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The "I'm moving and don't want to buy food" Special</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 21:38:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Antique store kitty wouldn't stop asking for love long enough to get a picture so I had to get one while petting him</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 22:47:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Antinomianism and Legalism: Three Streams of Confessional Lutherans</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 06:43:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When all you want is a schamko but your human tells you to stop begging for food</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 03:14:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof #128542;irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 03:16:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>blurry picture of a dog</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 04:30:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My Ella says "hello"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 23:28:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Rocky Mountain National Park ranger ready for action (~1937, colorized)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 07:19:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Perhaps Brady writes under the pen name Robert Wernick?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 23:14:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The security guards at his publisher's office demanded to see his ID</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 19:13:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>State Fair Pig Blup</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-11 00:16:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bath Babushka longs for warm days and cozy nights</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-11 00:40:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>blurry picture of a dog</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-11 08:05:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Humor] Getting into a conversation in a language you don't actually know that well</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 07:59:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Basically me whenever I try to practice my Korean](https://youtu.be/T_PuZBdT2iM)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Despite acquiring more expensive fountain pens, I still love the way my $3 Platinum Preppy writes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 22:21:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Despite acquiring more expensive fountain pens, I still love the way my $3 Platinum Preppy writes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 22:31:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Humor] If you're good at something, never do it for free</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 19:01:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>A friend shared this with me and it [gave me ideas for my future](https://imgur.com/a/0RZBA). I'll be a millionaire in no time!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>shoob blop</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 06:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wink!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 18:23:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>pibble wink!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 18:24:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>t w i n k l e CLOUDBOYE</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 20:50:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>schnauzer girl shares a kiss with s l o w b o y e</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 21:30:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>gotta catch  #8216;em all!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 07:43:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Celebrating fall with my Sailor Lecoule (on cheap paper)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 21:38:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me #128054;irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 20:29:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>anime_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-24 00:36:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>thot i was lion but am shoob, ha! heckin bamboozled!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-24 20:00:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>rare corgo admires magic orbs</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 19:50:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>smol schnauzer girl looks heckin concerned</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 01:17:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 02:18:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>sosage boye does a deejay</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 04:42:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Would you listen to this radio station?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 16:48:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>NID - J. Herbin Emerald of Chivor</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-02 21:01:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know this is a popular one, but I #8217;ve been wanting it for a long time. I think it looks great even [on cheap paper](https://imgur.com/a/JYLgN).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>he cute, he smol, but most importantly he t a l l</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 01:57:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 01:59:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>heckin fluffy shoob</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 07:20:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>E X P L O R E G I R L E climbs a mountain</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 16:49:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>haha!! Worth it!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 20:24:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>post-TP rampage blop</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 20:25:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hey frens!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 03:52:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>he just lookin for some chimken nuggers!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 03:09:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>i screamb, you screamb, we all screamb for shoob screamb</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 05:06:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 23:59:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>smol cloude does an awoooo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 00:07:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ground control to major pom</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 00:14:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>let #8217;s play femtch fren!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 12:39:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>up up up he go, where he go? no one know</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 04:59:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>rare curlytailed shark spotted in natural hambitat</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 06:47:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ella exploring the Monument Rocks in Western Kansas</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 07:30:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Another of Ella at the Monument Rocks</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 07:36:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>From barely recognizable to beautiful boy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 08:07:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Florida dog groomer opens late to give this pup a new lease on life</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 08:17:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>teeny tiny smilin cloude</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 20:01:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 03:00:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 06:46:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 18:22:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I dunno how to drive, haha!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 01:23:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>he trot :)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 02:51:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>l o n g b o y e in sheeps clothing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 00:33:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>travelin shoobster</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 03:57:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>halp!! stone pupper chomp shibe #8217;s paw</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 07:14:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>squeamky clean pupper and doggo await post-bath boops</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 04:21:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>schnauzie give her new carseat from [amazing online retailer] a test ride</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 04:27:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ella eagerly awaits her walk with wagging tail</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 06:46:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ella has fantastic eyebrows (and ears!)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 03:18:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>two AWOOOOs in perfect harmony</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 17:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First booster seat ride!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 21:23:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ella #8217;s first ride in a booster seat :)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 21:24:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>3 pugs, snug as bugs in a rug</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 04:40:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>meirl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 17:52:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>meirl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 03:07:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>cottonball sleep peacefully in silver donut</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 17:27:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>meirl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 19:55:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>meirl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 23:41:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>heckin SPOOKY spiderboye</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 03:39:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mid-rest from post-bath zoomies</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 20:08:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A beautiful oldgirle in the forest</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 04:49:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My neighbors have one of the best displays I #8217;ve seen</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-30 01:21:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>EZ-peasy shoobie</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 04:20:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hula shoob ready for luau</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 15:13:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>BEHOLD! he cromch the spikey apple</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 17:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Worth a try</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 23:10:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>financial genius boy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 23:11:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>s a v e him!!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 19:01:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>biG BrOwn bEAr SquEEzE sHiBe tO dEaTh!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 19:19:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[H] Large amount of $1, $2, $3 floppies [W] $$$(Paypal) or Trades</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 21:37:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here's a table](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1L_h2buloYiqStP-k7aGQb0nTlzqY1tLGeaQAfn_YpzI/edit) with each comic and an estimated grade/condition. Pictures of specific comics on request. Discounts for bulk purchases, free shipping over $25. Interested in trading for [these comics](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1-nkg5QZb9D7HaAALhDJ6gZWlz3KLIK6-WZeWcgMXuPY/edit?usp=sharing).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I love this ink! (J. Herbin Emerald of Chivor)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 21:57:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Your Uber has arrived</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 21:38:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[TOMT] [SONG] Can anyone identify the music used in this video?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 22:26:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like the music in the background of this video posted by REI. [Video here](https://youtu.be/ZHrhB0cUkfU). It could just be something they recorded for the video, but if anyone knows of an actual song title that'd be awesome. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 05:52:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why do people make up conversations with their 8 year old kids when they want to try and tell a joke?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 03:36:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I love that the mouse is staying dry under the Schnauzer #8217;s ear  #9786; #65039;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 03:13:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>heck the snow</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 18:27:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hungry cloude BEG for soup  #127836;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 00:48:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>cat-proofing Christmas</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 19:44:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>meow #127876;irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 19:56:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MANY goodbois wait for schmackos</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 03:28:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>GGGG</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 18:28:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SO HAPP!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 00:18:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>a snooze in sweater</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 01:12:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>HAPPY girl!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 05:09:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>vvv rare snow pupper</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 18:53:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>meirl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 19:21:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 01:05:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>enjoy this pile o #8217;pugs, frens</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 01:46:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why Reunification of the Koreas is Unlikely</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 04:22:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 05:16:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>heck</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 05:18:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>yeLlow LaB geTs HecKin sAWeD iN hAlF bY eViL bLiNds</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 23:14:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So I planned to snowshoe over Christmas...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 21:52:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I booked a hotel in the summer with plans to snowshoe in Santa Fe National Forest over Christmas. By all accounts, there was sure to be snow. But now it seems that it #8217;s been very dry and there possibly is no snow? Does anyone in the area have some suggestions where I might find enough snow for snowshoeing?  #128533;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Where do you go for sushi?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 05:10:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jacky Chan #8217;s used to be my go-to before he moved to Harry and Rock. For some reason I feel like his quality declined after that. I have yet to find a good replacement. Wasabi is okay but they seem to emphasize their overdone Americanized sushi a lot. What do Wichita redditors think?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bedhead Blop</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 19:02:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>she beg</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 18:27:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[TOMT] A Japanese children's website from the mid-late 90s</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 20:30:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>A recent AskReddit post brought this site to mind. It was a children's website based in Japan but had an English translation. I don't remember much about it unfortunately, but I do remember you could submit drawings and sound recordings (like .wav clips of yourself playing the violin or piano). Other than that, I kind of can't remember much. I think the homepage was set up like a "town" where you would visit the other areas. Not sure if this is enough info but maybe someone else remembers it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sprint will not unlock my phone</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 07:13:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>UPDATE and "What worked": I think a combo attack worked here, using advice from both /u/T-MobileCustomer2017 and /u/stylz168. The rep in OKC was more helpful than any of the other dozens of customer care reps I'd spoken to previously. He took the time to look through my entire account, see all the tickets, and find out why they were being rejected even though on the surface everything showed that my device was eligible. He fixed the problem, only to have another "unlock denied" email follow 30 minutes later. At that point, I was confident that *nothing* should be holding my devices in Sprint limbo anymore. I contacted Marci's team who called me at 10PM (after getting my permission to call me after 9). He reviewed everything and confirmed that there was absolutely no reason my devices should still be locked. He assured me that they would definitely be unlocked within 48 hours, but probably sooner. When I woke up this morning I decided to give my new SIM card a shot and, lo and behold, they were unlocked! **TL;DR:** Do *not* let Sprint bully you into keeping your devices locked to their service! Go through the proper procedures to unlock your device first, but if they are not unlocked within 48 hours, try the OKC/Marci approach! --- I got my phone last December on a lease from Sprint. My Sprint service has been very bad and only getting worse, so I decided to pay off my phone and the lease and everything so I could switch to Verizon. But I have been dealing with getting my phone unlocked for five days. They keep saying they #8217;ll unlock it, but then I get an email saying my device is ineligible. Then I call and they say it #8217;s eligible and they #8217;ll unlock it. Then the email. I went into my local store and they were completely unhelpful. Today (day five), I had someone tell me I owed them for this month #8217;s service but my account balance is 0 and Sprint actually canceled my service yesterday without my consent. So I don #8217;t even have service now. I #8217;m at the end of my rope. Online searches conclude that many, many other people have encountered these same problems. What do I do?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thanks for dinner, looks delish!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 09:47:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #8220;Bone #8221; app #233;tit!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 09:48:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>h a p p y b o y e waits for his burger and fries</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 20:48:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 01:57:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 01:58:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"How can I help you?" - the friendliest police officer you'll ever meet</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 21:21:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 02:17:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>reindeer mlem</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 02:48:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 22:18:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MRW Bluebear breaks into a fan dance next to me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 20:42:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 22:51:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>shibes doin a big heckin concern</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 22:52:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #8220;don #8217;t talk to me or my son ever again  #128529; #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 04:27:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>2meirl4meirl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 22:57:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>he float</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 04:48:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Question] Did Tom Mahood take down his site?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 06:59:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry in advance if this is a stupid question. I spent hours reading Mr. Mahood #8217;s writeup on the Death Valley Germans several months ago, and it #8217;s been on my list to read the Bill Ewasko story. So I got all warm and cozy in my bed, ready to read some mysteries... only to be prompted for a username and password on otherhand.org. Does this happen sometimes? Or does anyone know if he #8217;s locked down his site permanently?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>goodboye does a GROW</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 18:12:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Blurry picture of a dog tail</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 21:13:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Gggg Gggg</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 23:52:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>purple tongue blop</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 02:47:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>why he body so smol?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 04:25:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 04:26:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tucked in bat / doggerito</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 05:13:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>these snowdogs doin me a big bamboozle</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 02:07:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Handwriting practice with John Milton</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 19:00:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>goldenboye does a taste</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 12:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Redditor ruins 38 year old woman's Christmas by revealing that Santa isn't real</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 03:56:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 01:55:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>are we good dogs? answer: yes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 01:56:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anyone see tonight #8217;s sunset? (Taken at 21st and Rock)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 00:44:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #8220;Church is where we can be angry with God #8221;?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 06:30:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I met with my pastor today and he said something to this effect. Later, as I was thinking about it, I realized that I #8217;m not entirely sure what he meant. Of course I can ask him to clarify, but I don #8217;t know when I #8217;ll have a chance to sit down and discuss with him again for awhile, so I wondered if anyone could provide some insight. What does this mean?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guess I #8217;m part of the fence now</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 18:20:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>HECC</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 20:04:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Let's take this risk that says our love is young, that says we're foolish - let's prove them wrong</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 22:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>like doggo like pupper</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 00:15:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When packaging does this</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 14:31:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I was told you guys might like this</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 17:18:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me #127829;irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 22:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 02:53:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>he eat the yum cream  #127846;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 02:55:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 06:36:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Painfully accurate</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 19:55:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 00:16:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A fast  #8220;minimum #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 05:03:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I can #8217;t get over this ink #8217;s sheen!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 17:25:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 03:09:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Primary duty: desk warmer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 01:45:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Noodler's American Aristocracy... just way too wet</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 05:53:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love the color of this ink, but it doesn't matter what pen I put it in - it writes so wet. I've put it in an EF Pilot Kakuno and it's still horrible. Can I do anything to ... fix it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It started out with one pen, how did it end up like this? (Currently inked)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 19:39:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>he shlurp :)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 23:39:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>he go round and round</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 19:43:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>shibe loaf blops for dinner</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 04:58:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>NID! Monteverde Horizon Blue, Robert Oster Fire and Ice, Diamine Sherwood Green and J. Herbin Rouille D #8217;ancre</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 19:59:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>sumtimes puppers just needs a teacher</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 02:21:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>G L A M B O Y E</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 03:07:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 17:00:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>great trick portalboye!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 17:04:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>lil corgo blop and lil corgo paws</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 20:57:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dip pen practice</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 05:41:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>coolest cloude around</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 05:36:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Practice practice practice</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 19:09:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Robert Oster Fire  amp; Ice</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 02:43:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 05:40:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>a longboi was snuggled, all warm in his sweater</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 17:38:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>golden shibe does NOT want to be in the family photo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 14:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>did you ever seen such a gorgeous pupper?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 21:23:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>the only starter pack you'll ever need</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 22:15:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 06:07:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 17:37:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 20:10:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Diamine Sherwood Green in an eyedropper converted Preppy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 00:48:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[WSIB] a PS4 game with beautiful scenery</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 21:59:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve finished Horizon Zero Dawn and I #8217;m stretching out Skyrim to make it last. I want another open world game with beautiful scenery/atmosphere. I #8217;m open to various styles of gameplay, like it doesn #8217;t have to be an RPG for example. Unfortunately I only have a PS4. What else should I check out?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Electrical Engineering in Wichita</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 22:49:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>My husband will be graduating with his BS in electrical engineering with a minor in computer science from WSU this May, and he #8217;s running into roadblocks finding places to apply at. Everything here is aerospace engineering (of course!) or mechanical. I #8217;m starting to wonder if he picked the wrong emphasis... Where should he be looking? And how soon should he realistically expect to find a job? I thought he #8217;d have employment lined up by his last semester, but I guess I don #8217;t know how any of it works.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Brady Haran #8217;s cameo on tonight #8217;s Jeopardy (what is  #8220;tough as nails? #8221;)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 02:07:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>L I C C</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 16:19:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>He wait for his ride</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 15:02:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Something I like to remind myself of when I #8217;m going through a hard time</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 05:50:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Something I remind myself of when I #8217;m going through a hard time</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 16:15:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sometimes I can #8217;t see it as a game  #8212; what we #8217;re playing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 05:53:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MRW I'm browsing FF's "Charts Like Mine" and someone enters a positive test at 4DPO</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 23:43:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When I wake up from a dream in which I finally saw 2 lines on an HPT and suddenly come to the realization that my dreams are likely the only place I'll ever see that...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 04:49:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MFI  amp; success with acupuncture?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 05:31:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did a search to see people #8217;s experience with acupuncture and I saw that the topic was just discussed within the last month, but all of the responses were from the woman #8217;s experience. I #8217;m kind of curious to know if anyone #8217;s male SO did acupuncture to help with MFI. My husband has been taking various supplements religiously since about May/June (multivitamin, CoQ 10, vitamin D, and iron; recently added L-Carnitine). He #8217;s also lost 70 pounds since Nov. 2016. He wants to try acupuncture now. I #8217;m kind of unsure about it. I guess I #8217;ll be more on board if I can even hear anecdotal evidence that it #8217;s worth while. Also, any other supplements we should *definitely* add?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>NP(aper)D - Rhodia pad and Tomoe River</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 17:41:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Searching for an article re: grief  amp; infertility</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 20:08:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read an article some time ago, I feel like it may have been posted here, that discussed how the grief experienced in infertility mirrors the grief that accompanies death/loss. I've spent the last three days searching for it (off and on, not obsessively of course hehe) but have come up empty. Does this ring a bell with anyone?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Street scene, 1958. Unknown city, midwest or southwest US.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 02:27:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guys, we #8217;re doing this all wrong. We #8217;re supposed to use a towel!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 04:36:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>NPD Conklin Duraflex (my first flex pen!)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 18:59:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>To die will be an awfully big adventure</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 20:01:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Oh well, I guess I #8217;m a snowball now</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 21:03:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A visual summary of me TTC</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 19:30:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A break in the clouds is a break in my day</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 22:29:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #8220;we do not know how this happened #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 03:17:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>woof irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 06:48:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Check out my dog #8217;s bed beard</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 17:41:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Currently inked. I might have an obsession.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 18:05:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>J. Herbin #8217;s EoC works beautifully with an EF nib</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 21:18:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>