<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7692</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 01:04:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>My Team: 3* Yellow jacket level 3 3* Guillotine level 3 4* Captain marvel level 1 4* Black Widow level 1 4* The Vision level 3 Other characters i have: 3* iron fist level 3 3* Dr. Strange level 3 3* Duped spider man level 2</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-19 06:23:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read some article in my psychology class that said "In our dreams, all the people/faces we see are people we have seen in real life" so maybe. MAYBE we store those faces for later in life when we hit the age where we start dreaming.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-29 03:05:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, Ill ask there. (Im new to this if you cant tell)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My collection is...rocking!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-13 23:31:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pear pressure</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 00:40:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Local Hospital put pink dye in the fountain for Breast Cancer Awareness month</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 06:00:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 07:59:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can see it being harmful in wildlife, but this is a controlled fountain with a filtration system that is not releasing any harmful dyes or toxins into the ecosystem. (I asked the nurse at the front desk.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 08:49:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thought I'd post it, was looking for a more...fruitful response though ;);););)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 19:34:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Correct, you from around here?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-17 23:02:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good thing it's not a repost then, I actually took this picture when I was in Las Vegas, Nevada.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Question: If you were like Achilles and had to choose a spot on your body that is your weakest point, where would the most logical spot be?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-19 18:25:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-19 23:53:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm gonna go with yes, it does have to be on the outside of the body. If it were able to be on the inside of the body, don't you think Achilles would choose some place like a vein or some small part of the body that is physically impossible to damage on the outside.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-20 01:28:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you are familiar with the Percy Jackson Books, he has to swim through the River Styx and his "Achilles heel" is put into the small of his back right above the waistline and I have always thought that to be a very vulnerable place. Theoretically, wouldn't you want the spot to be somewhere on the front of your body so you can deflect any attacks towards that certain area?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-20 05:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's been awhile since I've read the books, you're probably correct on that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is your favorite lyric from any song?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 02:28:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Which of the five senses would you be most willing to lose, and why?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 06:25:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 06:55:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>You would never be able to watch a movie or television, see your family/loved ones, see the world, experience color. Being easiest to adapt to, maybe, I think it'd be easier to adapt to loss of hearing though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 06:56:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same could be said with sense of touch, "Hey Andrew, go touch that burning stove and I'll give you 100 bucks." Easy money.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 07:47:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I give you special permission because you referred to me as OP and I like that, makes me feel cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-22 00:43:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>You....you people have dirty minds...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any advice for boot camp?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-22 23:51:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I ship out in July of next year, how can I prepare myself better to survive boot camp?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-23 23:35:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>A lot of the people I've heard from/talked to said PT is easy, but exercise and fitness have never been easy for me. Do you have any recommendations that can ease me into that? I've been doing like 10-15 push ups a day since my first DEP meeting but I don't feel like that's enough</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How possible is an Earth-2?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-24 18:19:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-24 20:44:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>No I have not yet finished the season, apologies for not adding that in the OP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-24 20:44:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>In real life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-24 20:47:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really appreciate your explanation, very well written! My original post is to question the possibility of their really being an "Earth-2" in real life. Say for example if another earth (like ours) exists but vibrates at a different frequency.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-24 22:36:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you think I'm better suited asking this in r/science then?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[S1E3] Why didn't the lieutenant just shoot the weather balloon?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 00:12:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 00:13:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>His gun is clearly visible in its holster.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 00:28:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I'm a trained police officer with a sidearm, I'm gonna empty a clip at that balloon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 00:36:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Possible. But even if it did, the balloon was probably a good 30-40 feet from the lieutenant. Maybe even more than that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 01:18:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I doubt that is a situation that is even considered, I'm not saying that it wouldn't be scary and challenging. Yet as my light research has shown is that what you DO learn in police academy is Firearm Skills, Stress Prevention/Managment, Conflict Managment, and Problem solving. A combination of that skill set should more than help you be prepared for any situation, like being tied to a weather balloon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 01:44:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't underestimate what fear does to the body. It just seems completely illogical that this character died like that. I understand the other deaths because you can't really do anything without a way to take down the balloon but if you have a sidearm the logical thing to do is shoot the balloon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 04:22:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>In that case, when the other detective attached himself to the vigilante that got stuck to the balloon. Why was he able to yell to his partner to shoot the balloon down? They were both cops, he was scared as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"Let me hear your war cry!"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 07:31:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 07:33:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate your detailed response, I am able to agree with you on the information you presented in a logical and easy to understand way. Thanks for your contribution :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 17:14:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm definitely not say that they or kind people, the cop was obviously dirty and I didn't even like the character. Also, mind you that we are talking about the lieutenant of the police force in Gotham. Not some new rookie cop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 17:53:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Too much catnip!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-29 02:32:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chemistry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How can I be best prepared to ask for a raise?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 06:02:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm 18 and I currently make $10/hr at my local Grocery store. I am a supervisor for the Maintenance department and do a lot more work than the new employees. I recently was informed that they would be hiring one of my friends as an employee below me for $10/hr as well. With my experience and heavier work load, I believe that I should not be making the same amount as a new employee. I am seeking any advice on how to ask for a raise. I have never had to approach my supervisor and ask for a raise so this is a situation that is foreign to me. Any advice is much appreciated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 06:22:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Noted. I'm a little nervous/confused on how I should approach them though. Do I just knock on his office and say something like, "I'd like to discuss an opportunity for a raise."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 06:29:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm aware that other supervisors with my title make $11/hr or a little more. However my store doesn't do as well as some of the other stores in our chain.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 06:36:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Minimum wage is $9.40</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 07:01:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you think it's wiser to do this in person or is it something that could be done over email? I find it easier for me to get the best version of myself written through an email and when I am in person, I tend to get nervous and rush things to get out of the social situation as fast as possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 07:19:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for your time and advice, I will bring it up when I work next.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Arch Enemies</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 15:37:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 19:47:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a Pen....I have an Apple...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You're also half alive.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 22:18:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>My grandmother is in the hospital due to her health declining (though she is said to be out of the hospital by Wednesday). She said to me today whilst I was leaving that she feels like she is practically half dead. I looked her in the eyes and said, "Well grandma, that also means you're half alive." You chose how you see the world, you chose your outlook on a certain situation. Look forward, not behind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 23:20:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>My pleasure, my mom told me that what I said was very mature and that my grandma needed to hear it. It is a lesson that I didn't even mean to teach, but a small message goes a long way!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Decreased Gravity; Teacher pulls an April Fools prank on a whole 5th grade class.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 04:33:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 06:15:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wonder how many of them are actually aware of the existence of this video.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 06:46:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>But it's an Apple flip phone so it's already 100x better!! (he says in a sarcastic tone).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why do some women still have/keep their Tinder or other dating profiles when they are in a relationship?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 19:22:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 20:08:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Started off strong, finished stronger. Nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 20:10:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>To able to ask them they have to like my profile back so we can become a "match." Plus, there's no interest in swiping yes on their profile if you can see the male kissing the female. It's a dating app, not typically used for friendships.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Father of the year award goes to...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 20:39:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 21:30:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, that's true. I still think it's adorable, the little girl was walking down the plane isle with a lady bug outfit on</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 23:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah my friend got screwed because he wanted to get out so he rushed through the paperwork and lost all the benefits the Navy provides like the GI bill for example</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-03 01:58:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh, maybe they exaggerated a tad then. XD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-03 17:51:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Woah I didn't see that one coming, almost...Unbearable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 19:56:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Attractive"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 21:51:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just never heard a fish described as attractive, that's a new one for me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 22:08:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahhhh, the context makes me understand now. Here, take my pity laugh!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 22:28:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but I mean, I wonder if there's ever been a cow named Betsy that I've had the same milk from... yah know?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Serious] What would happen if someone was wrongfully incarcerated and sent to prison for five years and they found the person who committed the crime? Would the state pay the person wrongfully committed?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 04:11:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 05:15:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that sum totaled by what X person would have made in the workforce if they weren't convicted?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 05:38:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also adding onto that, will that wrongful conviction stay on your record even if false?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 06:08:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Appreciate the information, will definitely read these articles when I find some spare time!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 21:29:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great movie, however to me, Dormamu didn't feel as villainous as the one man who was his follower (forget his name).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 21:52:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dormammu! I've come to bargain!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 22:18:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dormammu....I've come...to bargain</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 23:07:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dormammu, I've c- [Insert stabby stab here]</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 23:16:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dormamm- [insert death ray]</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 23:38:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree, I also enjoyed how Dormammu's full power hasn't been shown completely yet. Doubtful it's the last we see of him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 23:55:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dormammu, !he venido a negociar!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-06 00:44:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dormammu, I've come to bargain?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-06 02:00:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dormammu, I've come to bargain?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-06 02:01:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would've got a laugh out of me for sure!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-06 02:03:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>THERE WAS A SECOND END SCENE? I only stayed for the first one!!!! Nuts!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-06 07:19:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>The loop that never ends meets the gif that never ends.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-06 18:51:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dormammu, I've come for the perfect loop!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 01:14:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bargain I've come to, Dormammu</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>To my fellow people with medical training: does it frustrate you also when nurses or doctors in television take off their gloves the incorrect way?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 17:07:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 17:24:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly, I have some medical training and I work in maintenance now and even then I still use gloves and I take the gloves off correctly and then I watch television and I see it done incorrectly. Irks is the perfect word to describe how it makes me feel!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 18:34:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Neuroscience</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to Wear Fragrance.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 19:45:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-08 04:15:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine is also Shawn and Gus, but a close second is Steve and Danny from Hawaii five-o</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 05:15:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Innie or an outtie or none</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The incline in the amount of google searches there is to "move to Canada." November 1st-present.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 08:41:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 09:31:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I agree, I'm actually curious as to who and how many people will *actually* move. Even if they do not like the elected president, they still have established their lives in America and have homes, families, jobs to sustain.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 22:06:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Other</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 05:26:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only the freshest of memes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Glockamole</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 05:51:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 08:26:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>To hang clothes you silly!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the word that you can never spell correctly no matter what?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 20:33:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 21:31:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>A+ for trying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 23:00:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>What exactly do you do because I'td be really embarrassing if you typed something like, "just type in your acunt number and we'll be good to go."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 23:00:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>An attempt was made.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 23:20:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very wise, can you imagine the message HR would send yo?u xD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 23:51:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you mean quickueueuey?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-12 01:56:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Other</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-12 02:49:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jewlwrey!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-12 21:23:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in Minnesota as well, setting a reminder to never go to the Theatre. I've been once on a field trip but haven't gone back since.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-14 01:39:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm using a Nikon D3200 and I can't figure all the settings out. There is a SuperMoon tonight and I want to try and get a picture of it but I have no clue how to get a good picture of the moon, any ideas?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-14 06:15:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm your neighboring state in Minnesota, I'm guessing the 23rd of November.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-14 16:13:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I usually walk to them during that time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-14 16:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you know about them. Who are you? Did they send you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-14 17:16:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>So that was you when I overcooked my pizza yesterday?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-14 17:17:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I'm aware I spelt caramel wrong ok. Gosh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-14 17:49:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>How you contain these ants? They can climb the walls of the pool</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-14 18:13:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yuuugeeeeee</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-15 15:08:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for your time Dr. Do you believe it would be possible to create skin tissue that does not tear or scratch and then have that be transplanted onto a human to make their skin tougher and more durable?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Insane trick with 23 Kendama's</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 19:33:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 19:51:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>He went to a place all men dream of. God rest his soul.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Insane trick with 23 Kendama's</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 19:59:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 20:20:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Such a shame, had his whole life ahead of him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 20:58:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mwhahahaha I figured someone would catch that when I did the counting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 21:23:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depends on your involvement in using Kendama's. Some people make a job out of using a Kendama. I've never used one but it's possible that some may have different weights that is better for a certain trick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 22:16:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen friends try with just one Kendama and it's taken them 2+ hours to get just one of them. So I'd say insane is a good representation of this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-17 01:57:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, magicians are whores? Your logic is flawed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-17 05:18:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>You let me know your findings if you're serious. It could be different for you than for my group of friends that tried.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-17 05:20:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>So do you want me to PM you my P.O box or??????</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>University Runner gets BLASTED by a deer during a race.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-17 06:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-17 06:50:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone get this person an award.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-17 06:57:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>"fellow senior Matt French, from Bensalem, Pa., who stopped to make sure DeLuzio was OK and finished the race by his side." -Taken from a CSN Philly Article.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 02:53:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>But...but... I posted this in the morning??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 09:44:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>The IPhone app could use some updates.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 09:58:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>-Better graphics card (hoping to get something in the 800+ range). -New watch. -Better headset. -Different camera lenses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 09:59:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've always wanted something like this done with me as the muse, nice work dude!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 10:01:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a thing called "Instant Gratification." People want likes and they want them now. If they get a lot of likes on a selfie (which they crave for) that makes them feel good on the inside.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 17:10:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>How easy was it to obtain your job at Google and move up in the ranks?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cat plays tug of war with human</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 17:59:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>By far the most creative use I've seen for a Fire Extinguisher.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 18:36:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 19:24:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>You alone could bring the Mythbusters out of retirement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 19:40:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Big brother is watching.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 20:49:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>It really is sad, I watched a video on his journey during this experience. The way he was handled just felt wrong to post it. He definitely looks happy here though in this moment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>That's one way to inflate a tire..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 23:34:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 23:57:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean yes it works, but what is the right way to do this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-19 00:46:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just the way he was handled by people, they obviously were not trying to harm him but he was just floating and being pushed/pulled by the people keeping him stable. It was necessary, but unsettling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-19 05:29:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had a elderly woman say to me, "Can you help me put my jacket on, daddy?" I was 16 and I work at a grocery store.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-19 05:32:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It really just means a group of people who like to play video games together, if you had a list of more specific questions I'd be down to answer them. You can always PM me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-19 05:37:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because we need water, it's not about the planets needing water. Human beings need water to survive therefore a "hospitable planet" would have water.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-19 05:43:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>To have money, always reassuring to lookup your account and know you are financially stable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-19 05:55:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>What class is this for, is it just a research paper? And I am happy to help whenever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-19 08:26:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dontcha know there buddy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-19 08:44:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm shipping off to boot camp in late July, how can I get my cardio up and overall fitness up in time to be ready? I do not have access to a gym.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Jack Johnson was born with a genetic disorder, his wish was to walk out with the Nebraska football team. His wish was granted.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 01:34:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 06:59:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then that normal kid could get rich by all the lawsuits he and his family could file.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 08:16:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Nonono you seem to have things mixed up, the money in that bank vault belongs to me. While I get my money, it would be nice if you could disable all security cameras and delete the footage."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 08:20:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Context would be nice, if you're gonna post in /r/funny Make. It. Funny.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 08:24:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've had this thought. It might surprise some of you. Have you ever thought about letting Trump get into office before you shit talk his ability to be president? You can't say he's going to be a bad president when he hasn't been given the chance. Just my two cents.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 08:28:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Amazing Spider-Man had a good soundtrack.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 11:36:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sep'd?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Risky wall run is an epic success!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 01:22:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Risky wall run pays off in the end!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 01:23:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 05:23:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I made the executive decision to leave the end out and get the slow motion wall run back. Dang 15s limit for gifs I tell yah.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 06:59:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome picture, inspired me to ask some questions about your profession. What are your day to day tasks? When you clock on what's the first thing you do? Does a park ranger make enough to be financially stable?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 07:21:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>How often are you able to get out and explore, do you ever get sick of the area you're in?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 07:37:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>THE HORSES NAME WAS FRIDAY!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 07:38:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I went from pushing carts to telling people to go push carts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 08:09:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>The original Ghostbusters</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 08:14:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I once stole a piece of jewelry from my moms jewelry box and put it in a girls backpack that I had a crush on in 5th grade. I left a note but I have no clue what it said. She never talked to me s that was an investment that did not pay off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 09:35:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something along the lines of, "I can make it, I can make it! .....shit, I can't make it."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 15:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Research purposes" right?? xD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 15:26:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Percy Jackson book series. It's about a Greek Demi-God. I highly recommend it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 15:40:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have your opinion and I respect that. The book has a different meaning for me though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 15:59:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have yet to hear/look into the book Brave New World so I can't comment as to what I see in that. But the Percy Jackson series is what I grew up with, I started reading the books in 6th grade and have kept reading/re-reading them when I can. It's just a part of my childhood that I found and still find intriguing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 17:39:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am very agreeable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 17:53:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>The window</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 17:55:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>To finish 2016 before I can set goals for the next year first.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 18:02:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool photo OP!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 18:10:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>My family has a sword taken off of an Officer in Japan during WWII.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 21:59:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I respect your opinion! To me however it's still impressive, I could barely break a board of wood when I took Karate classes. To me it's still impressive!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 23:01:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>How thick were the boards? That makes a huge difference</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Human spooks Tiger!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-22 03:19:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-22 19:12:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a question not a thought</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-22 19:18:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/LifeProTips</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-23 15:07:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got up early in the morning for school, I felt sick and expressed to my parents that I wasn't well and did not want to go to school that day. I went back into my bed but could not get back to sleep. After I got fed up with just laying in bed I got up and threw some shoes on and went for a walk. The morning dew on the grass was perfect and it was the perfect shot. I got down into the grass and aimed the camera towards the grass with the perfect amount of sun coming in from above. That's my perfect shot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-23 17:22:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Draw a squirtle! It's a cute lil Pok #233;mon!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-23 17:46:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>#SquirtleSquad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-23 19:24:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Human Body</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 08:35:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cancel my 5:00 session, ugh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What leg day looks like in Russia</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 22:34:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dutch duo plays a Ping pong match with 5 table tennis balls!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 01:33:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 08:50:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ba-humbug</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 23:26:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would assume so</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I thought that legendary skin looked familiar...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-28 00:19:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-28 05:59:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>A friend posted it in our group chat and I said I'm gonna post it to Reddit and he said, "sounds Gucci g."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-28 08:32:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could you provide an example of this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-28 08:35:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not more than $20.00 at any given moment. I have three wallets: one I carry one me with little cash, one in my dresser with all my big dollars, and then that one I lost when I was 15 and still can't find.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 07:32:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Harambe is dead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 19:05:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a question better served for Google, not Reddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 19:44:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>An $177 dollar watch. I can't even tell time without a digital clock. I just liked the way it looks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 19:59:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah my go to is to be like, "Hold on I got a message from my mother." Then pull out my phone and check the time there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Crazy boat traffic in Amsterdam</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 21:28:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 23:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rhett, how long will you grow your beard until you shave it again? And have you ever thought of a new hairstyle because Link got a new one not too long ago?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 00:51:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes it is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pizza Pancake!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 07:57:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 00:16:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks mom!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 10:52:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Poor lighting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 10:54:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>What did you talk about? Was it recorded/are you willing to share it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 18:26:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you do that allows you to work from home? That sounds nice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Robotics club creates a stunning machine.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 22:08:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-03 19:23:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hit me up with a truth fam</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-03 20:27:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>He doesn't, however he is the man I would approach to ask for a raise and then he passed that on to the union.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-03 20:30:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>The thing is im not a team player, I'm a supervisor for the team that trains them and what not. I'm making more than the other employees in my department however I still don't think it's enough, there are people who work here that have been here shorter than I have and make $11.00 an hour and they have worked here for a year maybe; I have worked here for three years and am at $10.25 an hour. I don't feel like I'm making enough money per hour to do the tasks that I do. That's why I'm asking for a raise, just saw this as a good time to bring it up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-04 09:19:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>How to throw an axe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 18:40:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't smile and I watched it 23 times. That'll be $115.00 please</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 18:41:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>This guys girlfriend</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 18:42:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks more like a volcano eruption</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 18:15:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please specify if we are talking about the food item or the country.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 19:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>No</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 19:57:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>They will be shocked that we drove cars in the first place!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 19:59:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Sure...I can wait 15m to use the restroom till I get home" -Me after Taco Bell</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 20:47:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you do much luxury activities? As in partying, going out to eat a fair amount, buying accessories or items. One way I personally save money is to have two wallets. I have $30.00 in the wallet I carry on me everyday, my second wallet is what I put what I don't need for the day and all my big number bills. I don't expect to spend more than $30.00 a day and that should last for a day or even four. Personally, if I know I have money to spend, I will. If I know I only have $30.00 then I will be more wise and limit my spending.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 22:10:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes my pleasure! Also, have you looked into any scholarships that require you to write an essay or something? I personally have not entered any because I myself already am in a program that gives me a free first year of college and I also have a $2,000 scholarship waiting for me when the free year runs out. Those essay scholarships could really benefit you as well. Since you are going into the medical profession there should be a lot of opportunities for you because people look for people going into those fields.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-11 02:55:25</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;:D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-15 06:37:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>In my opinion, the blurred background is too heavy. Good composition though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-15 08:28:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a cat too, his name is Scooter! My question for you is what's your cats name and can you provide a picture of the cat? Maybe your cat and Scooter can be internet cat friends!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-17 07:05:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>If this is gruesome you definitely have not experienced enough internet yet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Looking out for my boy Benjamin</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-17 07:16:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-19 01:11:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like the background and for a portrait it is decent, the one criticism I would like to give is the pose/posture. The subjects hands just seem awkward and limp, pose is something that could be worked on for the next time you attempt a portrait! Overall I do like it though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-19 06:27:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>To answer the question, I dont see the sadness. If you wanted to capture sadness it should be a close up shot. There is too much background that negates the sadness in my eyes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 05:28:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I personally haven't seen this gif on Reddit ever before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sea Steam</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 00:14:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 00:43:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep! Duluth, MN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 00:51:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It sure does! @Levi_Drevlow_Photography on Instagram is the source, he has amazing artwork!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 00:52:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Been there many times, haven't seen anything compared to this though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 01:09:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favorite time was when I went up there during the winter and walked on the ice to the lighthouse from the pier! I also live in MN and my sister attends college in Duluth so we make fairly frequent visits!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 01:53:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like it doesn't it?!? In reality it's the middle of the earth in good ol Minnesota!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 07:11:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm surprised it doesn't have as much fame as some other cities, it has some AMAZING sites to see. Some black rock beaches, gooseberry falls, spirit mountain, the lift bridge and many more sites and activities.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 17:54:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have never gone over the bridge actually! I will have to next time if the traffic isn't as bad as it has been in the past!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 23:08:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>My sister has said the same thing, she goes to college there. It's fun to visit her, but I'm ready to head back to the cities after a week.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 23:23:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imo I think there wouldn't have been outrageous protests that lead to violence and people being injured. There would've been protests guaranteed, but I believe they wouldn't have been violent ones</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-24 00:46:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wasn't informed of an armed revolt anyways. To assume I forgot is just trying to make a jab at me, it came off as pretty hostile and rude when I stated my opinion in a (what I believe) nice matter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-24 05:37:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>*dun dun dunnnnnn*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 09:13:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>The shot itself is awesome! The only thing I can advise is some cropping and adjusting the exposure. Awesome job!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 09:15:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>In my opinion the coloring is too heavy. just the picture alone without the vibrant purple, pink, and blue tones would be a really cool shot. It just seems over edited</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 09:18:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with you on this, black and white does not work with a photo like this one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 00:25:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, I'll ask you anything! Why did you post in the wrong sub?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 06:39:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello, my name is Andrew or subject7692. My interests are as follows;  #8226;Playing video games (cs:go, Minecraft, club penguin (jk but I used to play club penguin a lot))  #8226;Photography!  #8226;Money and finances  #8226;Leadership development. I currently help maintain a team of 17 employees who work in the same department as I in the grocery store I work at.  #8226;I really like watches and hope to grow my collection of them more in 2017.  #8226;Travel! I want to go all sorts of places and visit the world and do interesting things.  #8226;Entrepreneurship.  #8226;Fulfilling my goals on my bucket list (I have a big list of goals)  #8226;Making more lists! (I like lists!!!!!) Yeah that's a brief synopsis of me! I like making new friends so if you ever want to strike up a conversation I am more than willing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 06:48:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I concur! It is nice to meet you, I would love to participate in the playing of video games together !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 07:12:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah but I thought adding no line breaks would make me seem like I'm cooler :////</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 09:23:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will add you in the morning when I get to my computer! What's your rank on cs?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 09:28:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow! From what I read it seems like we could really get along! I love mythology as well, mostly Greek if I will be honest but Norse and roman are still very interesting to me. What work will you be doing in Southeast Asia? Sound like an awesome opportunity!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 10:04:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>What kind of mythology do you like/study? My favorite is anchor Greek/Roman and some Norse</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 10:07:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sarah, have you ever tried combining two of your interests of: Making art and Other people so making art of other people?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 10:09:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>What made you want to look into anthropology? Also what year are you in highschool? Also (yes Ik I ask many questions) what is the focus of the book you would _like_ to write?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 19:41:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I understand that! Greek will always be my favorite. I grew up with the Percy Jackson books and they are what got me really interested in mythology!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 19:43:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have similar interests! Also, Iceland is somewhere I recently I added to my bucket list after seeing some beautiful pictures of it! It's my dream to travel there someday :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 19:45:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is good, very good. I too also like lists. We can work with this and develop a friendship!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 19:51:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was starting out (I consider my self above amateur but not professional) I only used my iPhone before I got my gear. It's the photographer that makes the photo, not the gear!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 04:59:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're good at it. Anything</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 05:01:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trickshot park jobs only.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 05:02:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Biased question is biased. You can't ask who the worst person is and give only two options.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 21:23:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember that book! I read that in 6th grade I believe for one of my classes, I wrote a short story kinda loosely based off of that but it was 6th grade work so not anything great!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-01 01:44:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've tried writing my own book based on something completely different but I never find the time to just sit, there's so much else I could do that I find it hard to write in my free time. I have tried writing a book for so long but I only have a chapter ish done</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-01 02:24:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is a good schedule, I will do my best to keep at it in the new year!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 00:01:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks like something you would see in the television show The Flash.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 00:03:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with this 100% my criticism is that I get more from the shot without the reflection. If it were my work I would crop it out (thats just me though)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 00:05:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. The subject matter is the woman, not the scenery. The way it is cropped makes it seem like the woman isn't as significant as she should be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 00:06:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not personally a fan of the way it is blurred. A certain degree of blur is acceptable but I feel the way it is now is very heavy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 02:56:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>To me it's just that since the subject isn't singled out and he blends in that is what gives me the impression that the blur needs to be lifted a hint</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 06:12:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>My advice in that case would do a little cropping on the right side, that would make the blur still have an effect but the subject still be the thing that stands out. Just my personal opinion! Overall the picture is interesting though and I do like it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 20:04:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Went from G-Shock to Fossil.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 09:17:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Overall I really like this photo, it is very unique and caught my eye. Some things I noticed was that the right side is much darker than the left and the sky could use some extra blue in my opinion to make it pop a bit more. That is my personal opinion but as I said before, really good photograph!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 09:20:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could you explain your thought process in why you decided to make it black and white? I (personally) don't see the need to add more dullness to an already dull photo based on the conditions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 20:38:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for explaining. To me however I still can't look at this and have the black and white add anything to it. Could we see the original to compare them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 04:21:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't really change it about this picture and I'm sure it was an in the moment quick snapshot and you didn't have much time to prepare. However, you could benefit from using the rule of thirds in photos like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 04:21:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>The subject is very dark compared to the surrounding environment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 05:19:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>He shouldn't be</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 05:22:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>This photo really doesn't benefit to being black amp;white</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 07:51:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bought a Fossil watch and it was too big for my wrist, local shops will size it for you. It cost me $8.75 to size my watch ( a bit pricey for a sizing but oh well).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 08:38:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do not recall offhand, I have very small wrists. A "snug" fit for me is a 38mm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 08:59:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe it was 44mm. They took about 4 links out to fit me decently.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-05 08:38:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree that it could be very rare, OP you should try and find its worth. Definitely looks like it is worth more than the purchase price.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-05 08:41:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seeing posts like this make me sad that no one in my family was an avid watch collector. I'd love to be just handed a Rolex.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-05 21:40:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I certainly appreciate your feedback and will follow your advice about the cropping! I agree with what you were saying about the focus and I wish I could've spent more time taking pictures; however this one was one of the later ones I took so I was just going fast to get back inside! If I had more time I would've set it up better but oh well! Thanks again for your feedback :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-06 08:15:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>You going for Master at Arms?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-06 08:21:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I cannot offer any financial advice on this one, although I think it's good to continue working. If I were in your situation I would plan to continue work as well. I would like to offer my condolences however. If you ever need anyone to chat with or someone to hear you out just shoot me a PM!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Fossil] Longtime lurker, wanted to share my first watch!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 03:42:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 03:48:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello /r/watches I just wanted to make my first post in this sub! I've been lurking here for awhile, admiring watches and scrolling through the most recent posts. I just wanted to share my first watch (of many to come). I was gifted an Apple Watch and have stuck with that for awhile, I was introduced to a website that showed off watches and I have been hooked ever since then! I did my research and found that I really liked the look of this Fossil Townsman automatic watch. It came in and I have been wearing it since. So far, I have yet to have any compliment me on this watch but I think it's gorgeous. I think one of the best compliments to receive is when someone says, "Hey nice watch!" Most people don't appreciate watches as much as I and you all do so it's definitely nice to hear it in real life. Anyways, just wanted to introduce myself and my watch to this community!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 05:04:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favorite watch is my only one that I have, I'm hoping to grow it soon. The watch I currently own that is my everyday wear is a Fossil Townsman automatic stainless steel- Black. My dream is to (someday) own a Rolex but those are $$$$$$$$$ a tad bit pricey!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 05:19:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll be able to post a wrist shot tomorrow! Personally I like the Roman numerals for this specific watch but for some it doesn't work, that's just me though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 05:48:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate it! My parents thought I was crazy for spending the money on it, but I couldn't pass it up!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What would you sell your soul for?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 04:51:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 06:24:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Darn... I heard about this social media thing and had to try it out!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 08:02:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>But... who else do I call when my waffle press isn't working right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 15:58:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>You will have magic powers, I swear!!!!!! *huehuehuehuehu*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 08:28:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>The idea of the subject is fading away is good, however the way the angle is tilted really throws me off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 08:30:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The expression and that one little branch in the way of the subject are the two things that throw me off. Could you explain your reasoning behind having the subject choose that facial expression?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 08:51:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>The edit is very poor and under-exposed. Composition looks decent but I can't appreciate it fully when the edit and exposure are so poor. Fix those and go from there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 15:36:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>The pose is good and the lighting is good as well. My one criticism is the watch on her wrist how it has fallen sideways on her wrist. It's a small detail but small details matter</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 18:34:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's okay! I myself have never dabbled with portraits yet so I am trying to give my best critique!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 19:40:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like this photograph! The lighting and editing is superb, I really like the perspiration on the bottle. Keep up the good work!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Good answer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 21:22:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 03:50:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I concur.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 06:06:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>You *get* me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 10:32:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could literally google this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 10:34:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is beautiful! Amazing work OP :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 10:34:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Adding this place to my Bucket List!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 10:37:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>You guys like to garden as well?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 10:39:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>This isn't the place to ask questions you can google</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 10:40:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>*grunts*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Amazing Roller-Blade skills on the boardwalk!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 16:22:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 17:54:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was my thinking as well!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 18:48:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>_silly_ ????? I'll have you know I graduated top of my class in the meme academy with a memegpa of 5.0</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 19:30:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. This is good, I like you, I can work with this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 23:31:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>_welcome to 2017_</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to tell if baby is awake back there.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-14 04:16:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Special forces training!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-14 04:18:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-14 05:22:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>She completes it iirc when I was editing this gif file</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-14 05:42:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>_they know_</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-14 18:39:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have never seen one with this many as well, I am astounded! I appreciate every one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Proper "LAB" equipment is necessary!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 00:07:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 00:18:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't unseen that now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 03:20:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's definitely not my Reddit username. _huehuehuehuehue_</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 03:24:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>No it is not, I am a tall 18 year old man. But now to Reddit I am perceived as a young woman with a kid. Great!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 03:36:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>No thankfully! Many requests for my snapchat and other forms of media</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 07:45:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like they will do a good job with the editing. I mean, it's Marvel. I feel like after the movie comes out if this doesn't make big news that a good portion of the viewers wouldn't even know it was a body double.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-16 20:17:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>My criteria for watches are ones that aren't too bulky, I don't hate them it's just that I have small wrists so I can't pull them off. I like the brands off Fossil, Rolex (obviously), Bell amp;Ross and more! As for lists I have a lot, my notes app is filled mostly with lists. Ex. Bucket list, Dream list off all the dreams I remember, invention ideas, lists of things I need to do the next day. I really just like creating lists, it's something I recently learned about myself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 19:41:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello Andrew too, that's an _interesting last name_ huehuehue</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 18:13:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>This ones a tear jerker</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 18:45:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>This looks stunning!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 18:51:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those are pretty expensive dominos</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 21:51:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone! my first post here and I plan on creating an INTRO thread soon. Wanted to come here to chat with you all, one question for anyone who sees this comment: Whats your best childhood memory?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 22:22:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds like a great childhood memory!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 22:23:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>What...what kind of pizza?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 22:47:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the welcome :) I am doing very well! I only had one class today and now I'm at work, I get off of work soon also which is fu to look forward to! How are you doing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 22:56:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friends and I recently got together and actually played laser tag and went bowling! I hope to remember these moments when I grow up. I'm 18 and I can definitely see these guys being the ones that will be my "group" for the rest of my life. I hope at least</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-21 00:31:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I'm glad I found this community to be a part of :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-21 23:39:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey everyone! I had a really good day because I found out that I might get the chance to study abroad this summer. My sister recently went to Italy to study abroad and i've been jealous ever since so this is really exciting news for me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-22 02:38:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd love to go to Iceland, I heard it's very beautiful and it's a dream of mine to go there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-22 20:19:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shoot me a PM! I'm interested</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 14:07:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favorite book series is and always will be Percy Jackson. I have yet to find anything similar, does anyone have any suggestions?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 14:27:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>QOTD: I would love to be good at all track events or mainly running/sprinting. I just don't have the endurance for running yet!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 14:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd love some nice long sleeved shirts for men. I can never really seem to find any that both fit well and look good. Also, shoes are always nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 15:01:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>We _have_ the meat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 15:04:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is really interesting, thanks OP!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 17:55:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can I swear just once? FUCK YOU JACK</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Intro] Finally got around to typing up an intro :)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 18:05:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone! My name is Andrew! I'm fairly new to this community and just found the time to being able to write my introduction!To begin, I am 18 years old and I am a first year college student, I am going to a community college atm for my AA degree with an emphasis in photography. Currently I work at a grocery store and am a shift supervisor or what we call a  #8220;team captain. #8221; I'm an open book and like to make friends and get to know different people. Following is a list of things about myself that will help you get to know me better. -I like to make lists. -I was once briefly on the Ellen show, It was a matter of me being at the right place at the right time. I was a target and there was a live feed to her show, myself and some others got to chat with her for abit. -I have been on two cruises so far in my life (One to Alaska and one to some islands in the Caribbean). -I am interested in Greek Mythology. -I have one hundred trillion Zimbabwean dollars. -My favorite television show is Psych, but I also enjoy many other shows such as Chuck, House, Burn Notice, White Collar, Royal Pains, Arrow, Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D, Numb3rs, The Flash, and many more. -I would love to be a Voice Actor. -I love to travel. -I am planning on taking my first solo vacation this summer all by myself. -I love to play video games. -I love watches and am planning on growing a watch collection in 2017. -I love music. -I love Marvel movies. -I like making budgets and saving money. -I love communication and have taken 2 communications classes so far while at college and plan on taking more. -As stated in my first paragraph I am a Shift lead, but I help manage and train a team of 8 employees in my department. Anyways, that's all of the things I could think up about myself at the moment. As I said before, I love to meet new people and make friends; shoot me a PM if you want to talk more. I am an open book so if you think of anything you want to ask me, then leave a comment and I will respond to it ASAP! I'm glad to become a part of this community, I have lurked for awhile just haven't found the time to introduce myself yet so here I am! I hope you enjoyed getting to know more about me :) Thanks much, ~Andrew</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 18:36:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favorite Greek god would have to be Poseidon, I'm a typical Percy Jackson fan! Edit: Adding Hermes to a tie for my favorite with Poseidon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 18:37:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have come to found that! I've been here for maybe a week or abit more but just never found how to word my intro until now. Thanks for the warm welcome :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 18:43:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've actually taken courses of Greek mythology so I know how much of a brute and savage Poseidon actually is, he's done really horrible stuff. But I relate Poseidon to Percy Jackson and he is my favorite but wasn't an option so I just rolled with Percy's father.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 18:47:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really enjoy [this](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/c9/ec/00/c9ec00721e78249801a85f84abe826ad.jpg) color! I would give a woman a compliment on their nails if they had this shade and wore it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 18:49:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm fairly new here as well and just posted my intro today as well! Let's be buddies! I'm andrew but most call me Andy, either works! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 19:13:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi Mari! I like to browse many subreddits like: Wholesomemes, Photocritique, gifs, mildly interesting and many more! I'm glad I could give you the push to make yours:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 19:48:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't really name why I like it. The story just takes the ancient world and makes it modern and provides a good plot to follow. I like when a character has powers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 19:49:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah! I don't remember it vividly but I've been trying to see if my parents will find the old VHS recording of the show if we still have it. But it was from a long time ago</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 20:18:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be really awesome! I love Ellen but personally I would like to go to a Jimmy Fallon talk show m</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 20:35:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Too bad I'm in Minnesota! Not near any of the big name talk shows sadly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 00:50:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm at work now so I'm not able to change the address on mobile so far from what I can see. Do you know if there is a way to do it on mobile? EDIT: just got home and added my address, I appreciate you letting me know Sam :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 03:57:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a really great color, I'm not the best guy to consult for makeup and stuff but I just really liked that color! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 13:53:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmmmm, I really like those lava cakes that you can get from places like Dominos pizza!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 14:40:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone said If they don't look you in the eyes. However, it is a common misconception that if someone doesn't look you in the eyes they are lying. In fact, maintaining eye contact is a good way to tell if someone is lying to you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 16:39:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>oooo I like these questions and it gives me a chance to type up a mini list which I love. 1. The last Film you watch in Black amp;White: Probably an episode of Leave it to beaver, had to watch that for a class I took. Haven't seen many movies in B amp;W so I rolled with television. 2. The last book I read (excluding textbooks) would be The Prose Edda for a mythology class I took. 3. Craziest thing that happened at work: There are so many that I have actually thought about doing an AMA on my work life. Anyways, we have those sprinklers that are on the ceiling in about every facility. One of them burst and it was raining down water in the middle of one of the most popular aisles in our store. I was fairly new at that time and completely taken aback by what I was seeing. Good times</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 18:42:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel for you. You know, ill eat one for you! :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 19:05:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi Tim! Simple question/thought: Do you realize that when you leave this earth (die) that you can be referred to as the Dead Pool?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 19:49:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi, I'm new here as well but I love the community and it's good to hear that you are doing well now!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 18:06:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This](http://m.imgur.com/NMOAwHj) really was delicious! I am glad I ate it for you :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 18:59:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anything for a Reddit friend!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 22:55:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good for you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 23:40:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree! And I blame the pizza man who is nice to me and gives me good deals!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-28 21:44:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>WASD. Always.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-28 21:44:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nothing to see here, folks. Move along.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 05:39:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't tried anything other than WASD. I have pretty good sized fingers so I can hit all the keys I need to. At this point I think it'd be too hard to try and learn a different way of hand placement</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 15:07:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>@Andyq9433 I'm an intermediate level photographer who wants to share my view of the world!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 14:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is very interesting, thanks for telling your story OP! The part about you and your mother is what got me in the feels. Appreciate you sharing your story!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 19:05:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I fucked Xander Cage</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 19:08:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is awesome! Thanks for sharing OP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 19:22:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I usually just watch it on my phone, that way I can be in a comfortable position and switch without having to keep my head in one place</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-01 00:50:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>You've reached the 5th dimension. Hotdogs are the key, scientists have been trying for centuries to reach the fifth dimension. What an astonishing find.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-01 14:53:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>With this poor quality of picture there's no way anyone is going to be able to identify it IMO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-01 15:33:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good morning everyone! I made the decision last night to try and go this whole month without drinking any pop. For as long as I can remember, I've had at least one pop a day (some days I wouldn't have one if not available but I can't remember a time of my young adult life without having a soda a day if not more than one on some days. I dont know why I decided to do this but I am going to try my best at going this whole month without a single soda. Wish me luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-01 16:37:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I am really excited to see if I will be able to, originally I was gonna do no pop unless i don't personally pay for it but I figured why not go the whole way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-01 19:15:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Diet Coke has been my go-to, and I too drank an embarrassing amount of it per day. Sometimes 3-5 a day depending, which I hate to admit but it was that bad. As far as I can see I might go back to it because I really enjoy it at the moment. This month is just to see if I can, hopefully the results will be good! Thanks for the reply:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-01 19:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really appreciate it! And it will be really hard</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-01 19:52:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favorite Romance movie has got to be Deadpool by far, such a tragic love story! Be my valentine?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 05:27:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not to mention the actors are both hotties so that helps just a tad!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 16:33:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you need any photographers/Videographers because I am looking for with in both areas!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 16:38:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make friends! On my first day of work I took a tour of our store and got to know everyone in all the departments, now my job consists of walking around and chatting with these people everyday!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 16:39:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is your most memorable smell based memory?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 16:44:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>L.S. Luxury Session Session Infinity (have the infinity sign be your symbol) Genesis Signal Essent The Chapman Collection The Collective I love these watches! I have incorporated your initials into the first two, I think L.S is really simple and elegant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 16:49:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Notorious Validity Serenity Opious Covenant (Still figuring out how to use Reddit on mobile so I think I sent two different messages)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 18:38:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone reverse it to turning a Bowl into a log</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 19:34:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sequence Gemini Omni Terrestrial Ark</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 19:44:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brb, mom said I could get a new monitor when pigs fly. Showing her this, thanks OP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 19:47:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you mail me a paw print from some of the puppies? I want their autographs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 19:49:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Always has my best interests in mind, ty vm Captain</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 19:52:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You heard it from me first! I expect to be one of the first to get one!! ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 19:54:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you do in your months after the Puppy Bowl is over?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 20:03:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Done! Thanks for answering :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 20:11:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Insert top level comment  lt;--- Here. Good luck to everyone!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 00:05:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>So will you be giving out 3 prizes to this subreddit and 3 to the other ones you have posted on? Still confused how this will work</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 01:24:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>:D I just really like puppers :) :) :) I am really excited to potentially receive some puppy prints!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 01:47:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have been summoned! Thanks for bringing me to this contest, I will participate when I get home and am able to have access to my computer! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 02:15:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am grateful that I have the job that I had since I was 15 (18 now). I have progressed so much in the company and have worked my way from grunt work to managerial type of work! I love it! The random list gave me /u/AnnaDominii</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 05:18:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a site bring the bomb</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 15:50:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ello ervry boudy wvelcom to my labvoratori wer sefty is numba 1 priority</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 15:57:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Day 2 of me not drinking any pop for this month, Its harder than I expected but I am still going through with it. Normally I wouldve already probably had 5 pops in these two days combined so its been challenging. Still kicking though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 16:33:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do not believe so, I've tried looking for sources on this situation but have not been able to find any. My assumption was he is unconscious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 18:28:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I was informed that and took it down immediately. You have my sincerest Apologies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 18:29:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah you are talking about Charles Trippy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 20:02:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Welcome! I'm fairly new her as well and have just recently been able to become more active on here! I hope you enjoy your stay here and it's nice to get to know yah!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>No yo can't do this with runts, my sister won't fit in a Petrie dish</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-04 05:03:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/mildlyinteresting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-04 23:22:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is it so expensive and how can I look for the right deals for it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-05 05:44:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a huge fan of Pok #233;mon and your drawings look amazing! Could you do a Squirtle?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-06 05:58:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Counterstrike global offensive and Minecraft are my two main ones but I also play H1Z1 KOTK and Dishonored.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-06 06:00:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Woah! I also live in Minnesota, that's awesome!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-06 06:02:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wowza! Scrolling through the intros today and I have found two people also from Minnesota! This is awesome, also from Minnesota myself!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-06 07:14:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's nearly 12am and I'm half asleep and I read this and misunderstood you saying Spite as Sprite, the soda</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-06 15:48:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome, I'm from Bloomington!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-06 15:50:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used Audacity but don't know if there is anything that's better than that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 03:05:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I submitted an application to a guy and had my demo reel given. I have yet to hear back from the guy, hopefully I will by tomorrow! Thanks for bringing me here:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 17:46:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Welcome to the sub! I've always wanted to go to NYC! Maybe someday!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 17:47:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Forever salty!  #128075; #127996;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-08 16:52:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please tell him that he is a good boy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-09 14:38:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was obtaining a job at Google as difficult (and as rewarding) as everyone makes it out to be?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Crazy bite power behind this Alligator snapping turtle!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 15:34:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Corgi is spooked by toy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 15:35:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 15:55:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Considering it looks like he bit through the core I would say yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 16:12:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, forget attack dogs! We need to invest in these turtles!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 16:37:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are correct, that's why the title is Alligator snapping turtle. It's just a different type of turtle I believe!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How the Mississippi state baseball coach found out the gender of his baby!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 18:25:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 19:56:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what made it for me, he's so happy but he has to try and act cool!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-11 00:03:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. I need to see this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-11 00:26:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, it's officially two days past the end date and no winners have been awarded/chosen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-11 05:46:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you /u/shark649 _Thank you_</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 17:59:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Welcome! I'm fairly new here too, made my intro a few weeks ago and have hit it off well with the community!! I'm happy to welcome you here :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 18:00:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think a good goal is at 45-55, that's what I'm shooting for!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 18:03:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like the fact that I get to see a teachers perspective on grading papers and I am currently making many grammatical errors in this text just because I know how much it annoys myself and it is definitely a run on sentence but I thought it would be funny so please laugh at my joke</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 05:21:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>_there there_ *pats back*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 05:27:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've never had a valentine, as a socially awkward male who does not like confronting women this "holiday" saddens me more than it does make me happy. MiniRant over.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 06:01:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>:o yes! I must call mother asap!!! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This picture of Chris Pratt is monumental!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 14:59:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 16:02:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 14:36:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello everyone, my name is Andrew! I am interested in: -Communications -Photography -Cuddling with my cat, Scooter -Making friends -finance -Travel -Completing my bucket list -Pineapple because it's a good food and yes I do eat it on pizza!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 01:35:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like you, we are friends now because not one of my friends likes pineapple on pizza!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 06:27:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>About everything under the sun! A few things are: -Go in a sensory deprivation tank. -Jump onto a moving train and see where it takes me. -Climb a water tower. -Get a star named after myself. -See the northern lights. Just a few things but I'm always adding more! Do you have one? Also, what let's you travel a lot/where did you go last?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 08:41:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>The best Pineapple Pizza I had was when I was in Hawaii in 2010. There was a pizza place in the hotel that we stayed at (which I forget the name of) but it was the best pineapple pizza ever! I do have a photo of my cat on hand, I'll PM you a picture of him! I am super envious of your lifestyle! I hope I can live like that when in a few years, it sound spectacular!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 13:55:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably getting my drivers license! I'm way behind on that, I've been lucky enough to have everything I do be not far away from home so my parents have been able to drive me from here to there but now that I'm 18 it really is necessary for me to be able to go out on my own whenever I need to. If it's not that it would probably be my grandmas birthday, it's her 80th this year and we tend to do something big every 10 years for her like for her 70th we went on a cruise to Alaska. I don't know if it's a vacation yet or not but I'm excited anyways!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 16:39:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey Jack! I also enjoy playing Minecraft, one of the games I've stuck with since childhood. Do you enjoy singleplayer or multiplayer more? If so what servers do you go on? I love music as well, I enjoy some rap and mostly hip hop!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 19:59:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would love to get a single player world started one day in the future, I mostly do multiplayer though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-20 07:56:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>This must be weird for people who read from right to left</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-21 15:53:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would you consider getting your people in touch with me to do a voice reading for your books?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 15:10:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi my name is Andrew, Im a photographer who takes pictures of the world around me and just wants to gain experience and become a better photographer. Here is my page: https://www.instagram.com/subject7692/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 15:16:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good to see another photographer from Minnesota showing their work here! Just followed!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wholesome pupper just wants a friend</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 16:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-24 04:40:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>_woof!_</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 07:35:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Monday night</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I just found out that Archeologist were recently digging in the Pyramids of Egypt and found a mummy covered in chocolate and nuts.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:13:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Experts on site identified the mummy as Pharaoh Roche.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 18:26:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello Mr. Gates, You collaborated with a wholesome amount of Youtubers to spread the awareness of your annual letter. Which YouTubers do you feel did the best at portraying the message you and Melinda wanted to send? And why?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 19:17:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bill you are an inspiration, what was one of the biggest setbacks in your lifetime and how did you overcome it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 20:22:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have been having a good day! And now that you told me to have a good day that means I have two goods which equals a great! So now I am having a great day!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 21:46:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>_claps with an approving head of motion_</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-28 00:28:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wowza did they laugh!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-28 04:48:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>That makes me happy:) you are a funny person!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-01 19:15:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could you PM me your account name? I'd love to check you out! I only have 1.1k but I'm growing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 16:40:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds delicious! I have eaten the worlds hottest pepper and that was an experience!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 16:49:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds really amazing! Have you thought about marketing your product?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 17:05:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Interesting! That's good to hear:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 17:26:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey good for you! It sounds like a very good and fun thing to do on the side</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 20:39:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you provide an example of when they have tried to get away with it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 00:00:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im glad that she is getting help, I hope everything turns out alright!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 03:49:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey my Instagram username is Andyq9433 and I do travel photography and take pictures of my area! I'd appreciate a follow and if you dm and say you're from Reddit I'll check you out!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 16:43:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I prefer my lava over-easy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 18:50:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're all winners.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 08:16:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I prefer the way Danny Rand is portrayed in the Ultimate Spider-Man cartoon series vs how he is portrayed in the television show.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 14:28:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are smart human, someday I hope to be like you but my only quarrel is that I have 1.2k followers and a lot are bots from my old hashtag and using fake like/follower apps. Do you recommend starting over and creating a new account or how would you personally recommend I boost my account. Is buying a shoutout something that is really worth it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 15:26:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey I'd appreciate if you could drop by my page and leave a follow! I do photography mainly of my area but love to travel so my travel photos are up there as well! @subject7692 on Instagram!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 15:32:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sent a PM</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-21 16:51:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>This has easily earned my esteemed updoot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Defenders has officially finished filming!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 18:56:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 20:43:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just wish we could've seen Danny in his famous costume! I was looking forward to that but it didn't happen in season 1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 05:35:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you a cat?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 21:57:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello! I just saw a post on the popular page about dropping a camera from a plane. It was very interesting and it got me to thinking; would it be (relatively) safe to drop a camera from a plane/ helicopter with a parachute attached so it would glide down instead of fall? Idk I just thought that could be interesting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 22:18:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is true....did not account for that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The circle is complete, begin the ritual!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 16:26:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 17:55:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi you are the best thing I've seen all day :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 22:21:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is okay, the smile I brought to your face is enough gold for me :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 17:35:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Appreciate the feedback, are any of these things something I can fix in Lightroom? I'm fairly new to the program</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 17:51:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here is the original photo if that's what you mean by RAW. http://m.imgur.com/9Dr4pF1 I use a Nikon D3200</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 18:11:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want critique on the whole photo not just a little aspect of it, that seems like an odd rule when the community is about critiquing a photo. Edit: that is meant in the nicest way possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 18:11:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will do that, certainly appreciate your help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 16:22:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>One word replies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Amazing glove catch by Cam Ward!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 16:30:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 17:45:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was at the game last night, proud Minnesotan and Wild fan but that was a spectacular save! The crowd was intense, we all thought it went in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 18:47:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have good seats?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 18:54:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amen to that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 19:22:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>My aunt got 4 free tickets for the game because her boss didn't want to go. It was a pretty awesome experience for a college kid who's putting all the money towards school right now!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 23:49:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do not hockey much :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 01:09:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well hey der dontcha know :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 16:41:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey Jack! Since your life is focused around travel and it is now your job, how much travel do you do yourself?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 23:54:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey Dave! What's been your favorite memory from your career before rap stardom?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-13 17:24:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know it's still a WIP but I'm on mobile viewing this and some of the letters overlap and makes one thing more difficult to read. Otherwise I love the design and color choices</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-13 18:40:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only 1-2 more days till he is free from his cone! I will definitely give him belly rubs from you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 23:54:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this that one judge from American Idol?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-20 19:51:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey that is my state on the popular page! Cool!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 15:20:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm very excited! I have been reaching out to people to do free product photography so I can gain experience and I got my first reply/ maybe!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 15:25:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>This messed with my head! :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 16:59:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would like that, I really hope the guy follows through because that would be very good for me! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 18:46:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is very correct!!!! Wowza I would like that, it's a dream!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 19:05:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will! Keep being nice because it is very much appreciated! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 19:12:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>A very good trait to have!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 07:29:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a very fat cat named scooter, he weighs 23 pounds! Remind me! 2 days Donation for /r/millionairemakers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 03:01:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't add anything more than what the others have already said, I really like this concept and this is a unique take on it! I haven't seen anything like this yet! Very interesting:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 23:07:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope you find love some day Fred :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 08:05:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Usually I just smile at funny comments, but this one made me giggle. I am pleased to present you with my gratitude. /u/edge231</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 08:58:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did this at my old job. Was one of 2 shift leads for the maintenance department of my store. Worked there for three years and due to min wage being raised I lost out on some money because my raise would go away due to min wage being raised also. Wasn't happy with that or the pay in general so I talked with co workers about leaving, they talked with their co workers and so on until it got to management. They couldn't afford to lose me and have to train in a completely new person for my role so I was offered a 60 #162; pay raise which I was pretty happy with!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-07 05:16:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-27 14:51:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually quite like the color processing in this photo. It's very "in" right now. However, another thing I'd like to note is that (I believe) a tighter crop on the subject would really make this photo 100x better and get rid of some of the dead space.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just act natural..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 22:47:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 10:37:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Girlfriend...what's that like? asking for a friend..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 09:34:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>More is better. If I were you I would say something along the lines of "this account is valued way more than [X] and my asking price is [something higher than what you were offered and what more than what you would be willing to sell it for but not too much more] HOWEVER, I am willing to negotiate with you and determine a price that is suitable for both of us. (That is if you actually want to sell the account)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 09:40:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use that now but have not noticed anything, would you provide the name of said app? (You may in pm If you dont wanna expose them but I'm just curious)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 10:20:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>@subject7692 I know I'm late to the party but I'm a photographer that loves going on adventures and taking pictures of the scenery around me. I would greatly appreciate if you checked out my page and follow! This is my passion and I would love to keep being able to do it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 09:28:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>This hurts me on the inside</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-13 08:35:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Instagram.com/Andyq9433 Photographer who does his own thing whilst trying to make it to the top. I do product photography and have worked with many companies shooting their products! Dm you are from Reddit and I will follow back to show support! (Ps. If any brands/companies see this hmu I'd love to do product shots for you)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-13 09:54:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Instagram just didn't get the full story. The guys name is Tristan Tales and has the full thing on his profile, Instagram pretty much fucked up the formatting on it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 08:51:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>How are you contacting them? DM's or email?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-24 08:02:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>[@subject7692](instagram.com/subject7692) I do proud photography for companies as well as post my own material. Trying to grow my following and engagement. Let me know you're from Reddit and I'll follow back and we can chat! Would love feedback and your thoughts on my page! Much love, [@subject7692](instagram.com/subject7692)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 10:02:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ghost Rider got a new whip.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 06:52:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wonder if something like this would work for stuff done strictly in Lightroom since Photoshop is foreign to me at the moment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 06:55:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Give me something! Sounds like a really cool opportunity and would love to pay it forward if I am the lucky one chosen :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 06:57:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would love to hear more about this, send me a PM with further information! Thanks, Andrew</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 08:44:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>This satisfies me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 09:25:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm gonna start this off by firstly saying thank you. Even if I do not receive anything off my list that is perfectly, it was kind of you to host this and I appreciate it. I'm a college student, can't say I qualify as a child (although my father might say I act like one sometimes) but all of the money I am making from my part time job has been going back into my tuition fees and book fees. I don't have the income to be able to buy all these things that are necessary for a college student like a good backpack or a nice calculator (which I know are usually pricey sadly). Furthermore I also can't ask my parents for any money because their income is going into a complete remodel of our home so they don't have much left over for supplies for me. Here is the wish list I compiled of things that I would like to have this fall semester for school. https://www.amazon.com/gp/registry/wishlist/Z118J3ZNUGWW Some of these items are luxury that would just be nice to have like clothes and other stuff is more pertinent like a calculator and backpack. I don't care if anything on the list is bought used if that's an option and frankly I don't know if you are still continuing with this thread. However I would really appreciate it if I were chosen but understand if that's not possible since I'm somewhat late to the thread. Much love, Andy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-05 05:52:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be more than splendid if you would be willing! I'm just gonna be starting my math and science classes this fall so it will definitely help! Start up a private message thingy and we can talk more :) I appreciate it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 11:57:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't believe that is the case. I think since it's your account viewing their follower list that you always show up first (might not be the case but that's what I've noticed). I don't believe it goes in order of first following to latest following.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 12:00:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now that's a good article!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 21:56:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you ok??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 22:54:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're name is Liam I will throw a party for myself! At this point im just looking for anything that allows me to throw a party for myself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 00:04:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see clouds!!!!!!!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 14:34:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really hope they get the iron fist and like cage bromance developed further.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 15:47:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually really like Iron Fist as well. Makes me sad to see how everyone (a majority) dislikes it/him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 15:57:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure if this will apply or not. However, I am a photographer looking to get my name out there more so I have been offering free product photography to businesses/companies to build their brand. If anyone here is interested in that let me know and we can work something out in private! This is a great community and this is my way of being able to thank you all for the knowledge I've gained from this subreddit! -Andrew</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 17:49:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm interested, sounds awesome!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 22:57:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe I did, not sure if it went through or not because I've been in class so I haven't had time to check</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 06:34:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's not a deer you silly!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 02:56:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>[@subject7692](instagram.com/subject7692) My name is Andrew and I am a photographer based in Minnesota. I post travel pictures and do product photography for companies. Would love if you followed and checked out my page. If you DM me you're from Reddit and I like your content I will most definitely follow back! [@subject7692](instagram.com/subject7692)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-08 21:33:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>A Rolex</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 20:55:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey Adam! I've always been curious when watching Tested. What is the watch you wear in most of the episodes?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Almond Tree Shaking</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 16:56:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Almond Tree Shaking</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 16:56:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 17:17:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just a little longer...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Volcano Eruption</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 17:36:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Volcano Eruption</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 17:38:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 23:40:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you  #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 04:23:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>That indeed is very interesting! Thank you for sharing that fact !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 04:24:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're welcome, sir *tips fedora*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 04:29:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I allowed to change my name to shockwave?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 18:56:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's nothing spectacular but I just really like this one: https://instagram.com/p/BYvs1EZhM96/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Peeling a Watermelon</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 16:38:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Peeling a Watermelon</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 16:39:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 19:07:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are u ok</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 19:28:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>But are you good now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 23:58:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>How difficult was the application process for Nat Geo? How many years did you wait to apply/were you contacted by them having them offer you a job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 14:59:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Long exposure tips on a Nikon D3200? I have been researching for a while now and have not found anything on how to do it correctly. Or Since I have the D3200, what #8217;s the next camera body that #8217;s a step up but won #8217;t break the bank.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 15:32:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m having difficulty figuring out the settings to have it at so long exposure is possible. I don #8217;t know where to navigate in The menu/settings to get to where I can open the shutter. Also I did not ask for opinions on if I should or should not upgrade. I asked a direct question about what the next step up is from the D3200. I know I am not ready for an upgrade, I would #8217;ve asked opinions on that if I wanted them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 15:39:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where I #8217;m having trouble is when I have tried in the past, the photos on manual mode I #8217;ve taken have always turned out blue. I suppose it #8217;s all trial and error and I just need to do it a lot of times. I am able to set up the tripod, get the focus set to where I need it to be but just have yet to get the long exposure outcome that I see others achieve Edit: I want to do steel wool photography with long exposure. (Idk if that helps)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 16:01:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would love to experiment with steel wool long exposures, there are also many areas near me that have flowing water which I heard makes for good long exposures!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 16:24:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks very much! I will try it tonight!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 17:50:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you very much, your information has helped me understand it more!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 20:53:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>This one is my favorite response yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 07:57:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reminds me of my trip to Chicago!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 08:15:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d contact some people and demand credit for it or something, you reached millions of people with that post. They should know its your work!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 01:43:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>No way, I #8217;m in Minneapolis and have thought about interning there if they have any opportunities as a forensic photographer!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 05:15:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Interesting, I #8217;ll definitely have to research it more!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 17:35:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>An account with 90k followers doesn #8217;t mean anything when all of them are bots. You #8217;d be lucky to get $5 for that account</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 17:36:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>My plans for this weekend are to go to a watch expo and then I have a photoshoot for two shoe company #8217;s who like my photography and wanted to collaborate!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 14:30:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe she was... _BAMBOOZLED_</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 19:30:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>How to spot bots you mean?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 22:37:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some might be genuine. However, there are many of the same comments  #8220;Nice sharing!  #128568; #128568; #8221; and even some of the comments even though they look normal, the account is still a bot. You just have to care enough to look further into the people</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 00:27:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>My pleasure! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 16:42:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would have loved to see the process that got you to this final product!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 05:46:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely interested in making my life more productive, any chance to become better is something I want. Looking forward to your PM when it #8217;s finished!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 19:38:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're not getting anything for this account, just accept that you've lost before I have to take it further and report your account for being a botted account and then you lose all the followers, comments and likes that you paid for</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Baby French Bulldog is sleepy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 17:06:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 17:23:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for thanking me! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 05:56:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or does he? I might #8217;ve left you all on a cliffhanger ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 17:44:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lighting McQueen really let himself go..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 01:23:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am in Minnesota as well and am 100% down to help you organize something!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 08:09:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I also am wanting to do something like this as a experiment. I just have to find the right niche still..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Etched Damascus Steel Pattern</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 18:58:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 20:55:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;d be more than cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 06:25:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure if this is valid but i thought there was a rumor about someone who helped create vine making a platform for users to express creativity or something. Could be false though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 17:29:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally i would have love to seen a different perspective of this from another angle. If I were taking the photo i would position myself in the middle of the path that #8217;s on the right of the photo and get down on the ground and angle the camera up. That #8217;s my personal take on this, it would also theoretically give you the composition of leading lines going somewhere. In your photo from what i am interpreting, the path follows the leading lines composition but it is leading me away from the photo; typically you want to lead towards a subject or the center.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 15:15:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was a calculated risk and also I #8217;m not good at looping things :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 15:26:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>+1 for being wholesome :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scared by a Mop</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 20:27:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 22:31:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I assumed it was because it was a prank and someone was controlling the broom to spook the man!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 15:12:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Interesting theory but they can all be circumstantial (not sure if that #8217;s the right word). How do you know he didn #8217;t look at the camera maybe because he was curious as to why the other person was holding their phone up at them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 15:16:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could be right though! I just wanted to put that out there :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 18:41:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Soon enough two years will turn into 6 years.. i has that happen and it #8217;s emotionally draining. It #8217;s like a band aid, just rip it off and whatever happens happens</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 15:55:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow you must not have had a good and balanced breakfast today!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 16:10:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you just assume my gender?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 07:57:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>This has become one of my favorite giving back videos i have seen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Spotted this gem today at the game</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 22:06:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 02:28:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is perfectly fine! I was in row ten!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 03:41:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Found the packers fan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 03:46:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>To each their own, i hope you had fun at the game though! It was an amazing game!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 04:05:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>This specific picture i had to retake multiple times because it was right after a touchdown and everyone was standing and i saw this guys jersey and had a giggle as well! This was also my first Vikings game with my father as well, that #8217;s really awesome!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 06:34:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>My father would do this daily when he worked for target. I #8217;d ask for Caribou Java Chunk ice cream and he would say,  #8220;I can get two tubs of vanilla for the same price #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 17:04:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was that 4 hours time paid?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-26 00:44:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks reversed to me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 11:25:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bdubs is making a YouTube comeback he said. He #8217;s not making videos for us, he #8217;s making videos for himself which is good. His family seems to have had a lot of stressors this year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 20:13:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I still do sometimes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 03:45:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Syrup sandwiches.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 03:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Marvel hire this human.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 01:09:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Collaborate with 20+ new companies doing product photography</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 02:27:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or is it a step for one railing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 14:53:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go up to all middle aged/older women in the grocery store and say,  #8220;mom? #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 15:02:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now just wait about a couple months before those buzzfeed blue guys do a story on this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 16:01:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Getting Rick Rolled.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 01:17:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheese-Wisconsin. No question about that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 04:09:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>SKOL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 06:14:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>This one is a tough loss.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 13:02:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey poster, how to google?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You have the opportunity to renew/revive any television show. Which one do you bring back on air?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 13:06:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 13:21:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve been meaning to watch that, it #8217;s been highly recommended by several people but I have not found a platform that shows it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 13:22:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>My personal answer to this would be Psych. (Yes I am aware they just made a movie but there was something about watching that show weekly with my family that just resonated with me.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 13:58:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, it #8217;s fake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 14:01:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Inertia is a property of matter. Creds to Bill Nye on that being ingrained in my mind forever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 14:04:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>My cat, Scooter, has a tendency to bite and chew on any wires (headphones, phone chargers, headsets.) We have to shut our doors to make sure he doesn #8217;t get in to chew them but somehow he finds a way to do that and has costed me personally hundreds of dollars and my family around the same. But I still love him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 14:06:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have not cared to watch it. I have heard all it was is self promotion of some sorts. I like the memory of the old Bill Nye and I don #8217;t feel like that can be fabricated again. If you #8217;ve watched it I #8217;d love your take on it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 15:53:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be my second pick. I didn #8217;t watch it when it was on air but have seen it kn Netflix probably 3 times now and would love to see a movie made out of it. Thank you for saying this, being reminded of a story that you fell in love with is a great way to start the day!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 05:14:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m almost 20.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 16:05:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>There #8217;s a place in Destin, FL that is called McGuire #8217;s Pub. They also do this and allow you to staple the bills to the walls, doors, booths and what not. The waitress was telling my family about how they did have a fire in the back of the restaurant. Fire hazard, yes; but they put their insurance on maximum for fire damage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 22:49:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>The emotion in this picture is great and feels genuine to me. However what i would work on in the future is posing; the subject has their arm in front of themselves which conveys a feeling of being closed off and not open. Great photo though just a few things to work on for your next time shooting!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 05:05:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like photography:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 05:27:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aurora borealis, Golden Gate Bridge with fog, a smile from everyone i meet, Cheddar Gorge and more! Edit: it is also my goal to do performance photography for at least one artist this year!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 05:29:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am really into product photography as of recent but i love to capture landscapes. I want to be well versed in all divisions of photography so my least comfortable thing right now is portraits which i just recently did and i am very pleased with how they turned out :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 05:43:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>PM SENT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 05:46:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>My family went on a cruise to Alaska for my grandmas 70th birthday when i was young and my dad had this old video recorder and really low quality point  amp; shoot camera and he was taking videos and pictures of the scenery and i just thought that was so cool and I #8217;ve been fascinated by it since that moment!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 05:47:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some companies/venues/artists look for content to be made about them for social media so they take on some photographers and allow them to photograph a concert/performance. I was so close to doing it last year but the artist i would #8217;ve done it for cancelled my hometown on their tour route :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 05:51:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes you may!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 05:54:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Digital, I have done film but that for me personally takes away a big portion of why i love photography which is the post processing. I do admire it though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 05:54:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>That does sound interesting! I wonder if it #8217;s been done before? Hmmmm!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 05:56:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>An experience in some cases is better than a photograph; I #8217;m glad you have that memory :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 05:58:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be an experience i would like to have !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 06:04:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Landscapes mostly! Although recently it #8217;s been product photography since i haven #8217;t had the accessibility to take many landscapes that i have liked!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 06:05:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love you, you are important and valued. Thank you for being you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 06:08:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s climbing on my bucket list, i would imagine how magical it is!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 06:09:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anything and everything that allows me to get out and shoot and be uncomfortable! What kind of camera did you go with?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 06:11:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am located in Minneapolis, Minnesota. The Super Bowl host this year! Let me know if you are near or far and maybe sometime down the road we can work something out!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 06:13:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have not, i am fascinated by long exposure photography but it #8217;s something i have trouble learning, sadly!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 06:15:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mmmmmm yes i like how you think</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 06:19:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for this tip i will remember it and think of you when i get the opportunity!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 06:20:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow i just googled that and it is BEAUTIFUL!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 06:22:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will most certainly look forward to that opportunity and I would love to meet and take your picture! Thank you for your kindness:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 06:24:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Interesting approach! I would have never thought of that before but I will certainly attempt it! Thank you for your advice :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 06:26:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would like to explore that but i get very nervous, i think i would need to start out as an assistant to someone first before i did it myself!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 06:28:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am indeed under 30, I #8217;m coming up on 20 years old later in the year! I will have to look into that work holiday visa! Thank you for the advice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 06:42:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes there is! I #8217;m not sure if I #8217;m allowed to say it in the comments but please feel free to PM me and i will let you know where you can find me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 06:44:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes [here ](instagram.com/subject7692) is where a majority of my work is posted! I have a professional portfolio that is not included in that page though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 07:01:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Iceland is my #1 travel destination on my bucket list, second is Greece!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 08:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>To me that sounds like a dream! Do you have an Instagram, email or something where we can go back and forth about product photography? At the current moment that is what seems most promising to me so I #8217;d love to actually talk with you about it and have the chance to ask questions! Feel free to pm me any info about correspondence!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 08:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s uncanny to me how much this resembles Youtuber, Peter McKinnon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 18:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>No way!!! PM me, let #8217;s talk!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 19:01:37</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Awh fuck, I can #8217;t believe you #8217;ve done this #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 13:53:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m curious about the stats of your account. How many followers, how many posts, when was the most recent post and stuff like that. I #8217;m going through the opposite of where I want the name of an account and they are indeed inactive, but reporting them has not worked. Would like to hear more about your situation!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 20:47:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah there #8217;s no way to get an account from someone inactive unless you have connections or money. It really is a poor system</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 09:02:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Washing cars for the elderly. I didn #8217;t even charge them for it but they were so persistent in wanting to give me money for it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 09:08:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like a Moodonna to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 08:24:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make this kid a meme sure. But he #8217;s already doing something right if he gets to go to a game where the average seat price is $3,100 which is 4-5 months rent for some. My math is probably off but the point still stands.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 16:07:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:18:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! I like to prepare 342 days early! Keen eye :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 18:37:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wish I was technologically savvy to include the full video as the. However, I only know how to do 10-15s gifs and this clip is about 20s. He makes it to the top (/r/gifsthatendtoosoon )</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cars of the future can blink.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 18:38:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 06:26:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you able to live comfortably that way?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 20:07:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Lightning Thief by Rick Riordan.and the series after. They made me actually _like_reading. Reading before those books was just something you had to do for school. Also got me extremely fascinated and interested in Ancient Greek mythology and history. Thank you Rick Riordan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 20:14:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes you are :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A wholesome moment with SuperMan</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 14:34:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 14:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Update?!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 14:39:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m curious, what was your portfolio you submitted? How well developed did you become before submitting a portfolio</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 14:43:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are but I still don #8217;t think we will see an alternative that competes with Instagram for a good while. Hope I #8217;m wrong though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 15:42:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you #8217;re willing I #8217;d love to see it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cute ball, Corner pocket</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 16:03:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 18:18:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because then more people will smile!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 00:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ty that last quote from your daughter made me smile!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 02:53:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can #8217;t just say there is a subreddit and not link it!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 08:59:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think this is a very good start but could use some improving. I like the lower aspect of the shot but i do not like all of the clutter and power lines in the shot. I feel like finding a better composition is something you should look at when taking a shot like this again!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 05:40:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just wish it was level</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 08:50:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do this a lot too. It #8217;s for me a way of making up certain situations in my head that make what I #8217;m currently doing more entertaining. For example, my Astronomy class is one hour and 50 minutes long and I get very bored about halfway through. When i get bored my mind goes to make up interesting/intense/weird situations. Last class, I imagined what i would do if the room started flooding and the doors were locked from the outside.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 08:51:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d go to Hawaii and write a novel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:39:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bill, what is your favorite place in the world to be?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:41:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are you doing to making sure your legacy will live on for hundreds of years to come. What is the one thing you hope to change by the time you die?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:42:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bill, do you see yourself continuing to participate in Reddit #8217;s Secret Santa for the future years? I am always hopeful I will get matched with you but that has yet to occur! Thanks for your time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 05:39:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>They #8217;re well known in London. The more people they have to talk to equals a bigger chance of being recognized. That #8217;s my theory at least</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 08:08:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you Canadian or from up North? I did not know the  #8220;eh #8221; was something people typed in; i thought they just omitted it from the sentence like everyone does with  #8220;uh #8221; and  #8220;uhm #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 08:12:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go for it. I missed out on a concert because no one would go with me, i wish I would #8217;ve gone now. Who is it for?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 08:43:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It certainly does add more character, that #8217;s a very interesting tidbit of information!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 07:23:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll let you know when I get invited to one. heh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 07:35:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tom and Jerry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 16:19:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Going back to school after spring break</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 16:22:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I went on a cruise with my family and didn #8217;t think about school once. I have 2 assignments due tomorrow that I haven #8217;t even looked at yet; it #8217;s just gonna take some adjusting to get back into the swing of things!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 07:54:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amazing! I got to finally see Black Panther and I got to do so with my best friends since Highschool!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 15:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depends on location honestly. I #8217;d rather be super hairy in Russia than super hairy in Ecuador</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 18:12:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/personalfinance is where I would go if that happened to me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 18:14:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>This hurt me to read</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 21:33:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;ve been in the shower too long, time to come out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 07:04:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably just bad jeans</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 00:01:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would be forced to constantly wear wet socks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 08:03:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would be interesting to see your shots to give advice on them instead of giving advice on this photos look. Just a thought</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 20:19:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wet socks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 16:00:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>If what you are trying to do is emphasize the subject in the middle which I am presuming you are, I would recommend blurring the background more because without the blur it just seems hectic and you really have a lot of options to pick as the main subject. Hope this helps!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 16:17:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>This should be in the next Doctor Strange movie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 21:27:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my goodness I remember this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 21:38:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know what you mean! That one stuck with me too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 16:29:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t you mean Bumblebee Cabbagepatch?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 08:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m late to the party because I #8217;m just now watching but I truly feel like Hogarth has brought nothing to this season so far. Please inform me if she does of later but as of now I feel like I can skip all of her scenes and not lose anything important in the show.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 08:25:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, there is art and then there is Art.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 14:31:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>What specifically do you want a critique on? The post processing, composition, subject matter...etc</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 14:41:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll start with the post processing because I #8217;m not entirely sure how to handle the composition critique. Overall it #8217;s a very blue toned (dark blue) photo which if that is what you are going for you achieve it very well. However, I am finding myself noticing a bunch of smudges on most of the right half of the photo which could probably be edited out to give it a more smooth feel (this is what I would do personally but if you like them that #8217;s okay). Also, I #8217;m noticing that the color of blue changes at certain points in the photo (darker in the middle and lighter on the outside). I understand that it #8217;s due to the lighting and shadows but if you want the color to be consistent you could perhaps try adding a dark vignette to the photo which might make the corners of the photo darker. Interesting photo and i hope my critique helped in some way!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 16:10:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>How can I get the name of an account that has been inactive for years?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 15:28:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I #8217;ll start it off by saying the composition of this (to be a portrait) needs to be worked on immensely. To me you #8217;re in between a landscape and a portrait. Portraits are supposed to put emphasis on a person. I would maybe try and re edit the photo to make the subject stand out more. You could achieve that by adding a blur around the landscape and cropping it so we get more of your subject in the photo. I would also recommend changing the coloring so they don #8217;t blend in with the tone of the landscape as much. Thanks for allowing me to critique and if you want any elaboration on anything please let me know!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 18:05:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is a true statement, did you have a test today?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 18:10:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel the same way, I had a test last Thursday that I unfortunately did not make time to study for. Luckily, our professor drops the lowest test grade (which will be this one).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 20:45:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hogarth does mention the Rand Company but nothing comes of it just a name drop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 06:33:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would agree with this, the pose doesn #8217;t work with the composition. Everything about the background of the photo is pretty linear and then the model is doing w contrasting pose that #8217;s shows curvature it throws me off personally.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 06:34:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rotate the photo so the horizon is level, that #8217;s my main tip for this photo and it can be done in Lightroom!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 06:38:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think this photo could benefit from being taken literally two steps back that way we could get the top of the head and a good amount of the body back in the shot. Also, i know it #8217;s common to have black and white photos when it comes to boudoir photography but I feel like this photo could benefit well from being in color as well; that #8217;s just my personal opinion though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 06:41:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m away from my computer right now but if you search how to rotate a photo I #8217;m sure it will show you where the setting is to change that!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 06:45:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really love this photo! A few notes that I have is that at the moment it feels very dark to me and i find myself squinting while looking, i would recommend raising the exposure just a tad! And the second thing I saw was that your shadow is casted on the steps of the staircase. It #8217;s a pretty nitpicky thing but it #8217;s something to keep an eye out for next time you #8217;re shooting in an environment like this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 06:53:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would love to look at more of your photos! Do you have a portfolio that you can PM me?!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 07:04:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my goodness! You #8217;re doing so well for your first shoot! I #8217;ll keep an eye out for your username for sure! I #8217;m open any time for critiques on photos; they are a great way to help teach but also to learn yourself!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 22:47:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lightroom is the easiest option and there is a Lightroom Mobile app. Another well known one is called Snapseed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 22:56:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The framing on this shot is great as usual, I do think that the greens have been desaturated too much and I would like to see this photo with more vibrance in the grass and leaves! Great capture though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 20:00:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You answered your own question in the title. It doesn #8217;t matter if the blur ruins it for another viewer if you like it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 17:35:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is a relatively big gap in between your subjects and that makes me focus my eye to what #8217;s behind them rather than the subjects themselves which I am assuming are supposed to be the main subjects in this photo. They sort of (to me) are creating an artificial leading lines composition that makes you look past them so I would be more aware of the posing of them because that correlates to composition. Hope this helped!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 19:33:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>He was so fascinated by the fact that he could, that he never took into consideration if he should</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 20:36:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>So quick question or theory, don #8217;t know if this needs it #8217;s own thread though. Wouldn #8217;t Black Panther be able to hold an infinity stone? I know that sounds crazy but isn #8217;t his suit able to absorb the damage/hits he takes and then he can use that power and release it. So wouldn #8217;t he be able to hold a stone and just absorb all the energy/hits taken from holding the stone? Or is that a crazy idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 06:24:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I was kinda disappointed/dissatisfied that there was only one post credit scene. There was so much potential there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 06:27:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The eight years was a mistake/error. Kevin Fiege confirmed it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 06:31:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>You think he #8217;s coming back in the og outfit? I wouldn #8217;t have guessed that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sharing is caring!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 14:43:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 20:49:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Small world, that was actually my post! It is to my understanding that these are two completely unrelated families but I could be wrong! Would be neat if someone could confirm if it #8217;s the same family!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 02:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 06:12:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any theories on if Aunt May was dusted at all?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 06:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe Korg is dead :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>One person can change the world</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 15:08:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 16:02:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s a semi-popular/popular meme that was started from an episode of Spongebob Squarepants. In the episode, Patrick Star is asked by Squidward Tenticles is teaching an (I assume musical) seminar and he asks the group,  #8220;has anyone here played an instrument before? #8221; Patrick Star responds to his question by saying,  #8220;Is mayonnaise an instrument? #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 14:50:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s interesting, for me it says I have reached 100,334 Karma. I wonder why that is!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 06:17:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn #8217;t even say I #8217;m advanced just pretty experienced! I #8217;m also pretty good with communications so I #8217;ve been able to talk my way into things!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If you could only smell one scent for the rest of your life what would it be?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 18:46:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 18:57:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Coffee beans always smell better than what coffee tastes like!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 07:28:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve recently got a Nikon D810 and it did not come with a manual. Are there any good online ones that anybody has used or knows of that they could link me? I #8217;ve tried google but all I get is articles on focusing and not shutter speed changing button and aperture changing buttons which are the most important. (I #8217;ve already found the ISO button though!)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 08:01:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Many thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 18:41:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Overall this photo has a very dark tone and feeling. If that is what you are going for though I believe it could be done better because at the current stage it is dark but also dull. Maybe adding a darker vignette on it and bringing the exposure up a tad would benefit this photo. Also adding some contrast and clarity around the river might make it more interesting to view. Composition from my first glance at this photo looks really well! Great work and keep shooting!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 00:27:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would recommend perhaps moving to a different location. I find it odd that this was in the middle of a parking lot it makes it seem less professional. The photo overall is also pretty dull as for the color and the photo is not level (all of which can be fixed in post besides location). Great start! Keep shooting those are just the tips I can give you right now!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 16:09:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is just a really well thought out Taco Bell advertisement</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 14:35:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually really like the angle and I think you #8217;re 100% in the wrong to say  #8220;never shoot from this low of angle for portraits. #8221; I don #8217;t know where you came up with that idea but a lower angle is perfectly normal for portraits and it #8217;s sometimes even preferred. It #8217;s best when critiquing people to be at least somewhat nice; instead of saying  #8220;awful #8221; you could say something like  #8220;composition needs to be be paid more attention to #8221; I also really like the fact that the hair is in the way of the subjects face, to me that adds mystery and intrigue. I, however, think my best critique for this photo is that it could achieve the same thing if it was taken from one or two steps back. I think it would look more complete if the right hand/arm wasn #8217;t cropped out. Great shot and keep shooting!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 18:16:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would not classify myself as a portrait photographer but I do take them sometimes. I am lucky enough to be around a lot of creatives that do take portraits so I have learned and watched them grow which is where a majority of my knowledge comes from when it comes to portraits. The ones I have taken I #8217;m not really keen on sharing them; but that shouldn #8217;t determine if I #8217;m a credible source or not, I think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 20:26:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very well said and I agree with you on most of that. I think a good point to bring up is that a portrait does not always need to include the subjects face. In my light research, a portrait is a photograph that is intended to depict the personality or mood of the person. Even though the hair may be distracting, I believe that gives the subject more intrigue like I have said before. I agree with you on the hand in the corner could have been either placed better or not cropped off. Thank you for offering to give me advice, I #8217;m always looking for more knowledge about photography so that I can get better so I appreciate you offering guidance to me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 13:52:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t think you should, they literally just broke your trust and even if it #8217;s genuine you should take the time to find out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 22:59:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like the colors in this photo and how the red pops. However my criticism comes when I am trying to find the main focal point of this photo. Since the red car really pops my attention is drawn their; yet a portion of the car is blocked out so my criticism is more aimed towards the composition of the photo rather than the colors! I think if you moved to the left just a bit to get the vehicle fully in frame that it would make for a much more complete photograph! Keep shooting and try becoming more focused on the composition/framing of a photograph!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 18:11:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would say My critique is that not all of the Spider is in focus and just maintain a cleaner focus around the whole subject rather than just a part of it is something I would like to see you improve on for your next shots! Great job though and keep on shooting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 05:37:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>The best moderator I know and I would highly recommend him!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 13:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I already put my name in the random generator. I was spared already and lord thanos will save me once more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 07:47:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spare me oh great bots</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 00:06:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you find a clip of the shot?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 00:08:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Darn, what a cool but terrifying story to have though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 09:48:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Long ago, the four nations lived together in harmony. Then everything changed when the Fire Nation attacked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 11:54:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, i remember this from when I posted it months ago! /r/karmacourt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Who #8217;s the best side character from a movie that deserves their own standalone movie?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 19:22:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Requesting /r/MasterReturns, no active mods</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 23:42:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>