<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7669</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-01 01:51:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can confirm. Property Underwriter here, and we recently had a similar loss in Australia due to fire burning up a run of exterior aluminium cladding (http://mobile.abc.net.au/news/2015-06-01/victorian-coroner-asked-to-investigate-docklands-cladding-fire/6511724). As an Underwriter we rely heavily on our risk engineers to determine the EML (Estimated Maximum Loss) of a single risk or structure. If our risk engineering team tell us to stay well away from a risk, well to be honest we'll still quote it,just maybe with no discounting. Insurance market in Australia is pretty crazy, at present.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>House Fire in Hawthorne?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-20 06:30:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-20 06:30:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone have a closer look at this one? Looks like a house fire in Hawthorne.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 23:01:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. It's more forced evolution of the entire human race, and society itself changes with it. Think 'The Culture' by Iain M. Banks: a post-scarcity pan-human egalitarian utopia - with big damn nukes. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 03:31:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just love the places he took it. Sure, they're a big bunch of space hippies, except for when there are Special Circumstances. And ain't that a euphemism and a half? Player Of Games needs to become a film. It really lends itself. The Grey Area (aka. Meatfucker) on the other hand needs to pay our planet a visit. It'd have a great time here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 03:18:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I made the jump myself. I started in general insurance recoveries and successfully applied for a role as an SME (packages) Underwriter within 18 months. I then hopped around various disciplines for around 8 years and am now doing global/corporate fleets. Not sure what you have in the States with regards to professional quals in insurance, but over here in Australia we have the Australia and New Zealand Institute of Insurance and Finance (ANZIIF). I did an underwriting course with them to boost my profile. In your position I'd look to do a similar course, then apply for Assistant Underwriter roles. Claims CSR experience isn't going to help too much, but if you can try and get a junior property claims adjuster role as quickly as possible. This will give you much more exposure to the technical aspects of policy construction, and forms a much better baseline into underwriting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 22:23:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excel Saga. The whole series is a parody / trope buster.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 14:34:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can see Zeugma to the right near the feature you're describing. Zeugma is a historical location in south eastern Turkey near the Syrian border. The feature appears to be on the Euphrates River, most like between Birecik in Turkey and Al Tabqah in Syria. It may have been a large natural island of sorts that would be backfilled by the Euphrates when in flood. It is likely now lost, not to time, but to engineering. I'd suggest that location is now deep under Lake Assad in north eastern Syria.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 22:13:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi, I'm an Australian motor underwriter. Demurrage is also know as financial or consequential loss. You can claim for demurrage, but only when you are not at fault, and even then it is something you generally have to do yourself via a notice of demand or through a small claims court. This us because consequential loss is generally not covered under the 'own damage' section of a policy. An at fault driver will have cover on their liability for losses incurred by a third party, so if you are not at fault ultimately you could get something back if the other person is insured. The issue you have is really more to do with the time taken to repair your vehicle. In that case you would need to go though the complaints handling process with your insurer to enquire about the possibility of compensation. If you get no joy there you can go to the Financial Ombudsmen Service. Fair warning: This can take a significant amount of time and stress, and you have to be careful not to accept any payment as 'full and final settlement'.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-19 10:18:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Regarding full and fin settlement, it's about both, however it is more about finalising settlement with the at fault party in this instance. If the at fault party is insured, you need to pursue them for demurrage, as it cannot be recovered through your own insurer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 14:54:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It does exist, and I believe it is offered in Australia by a couple of the international underwriters, possibly Beazley? I've heard of it being used to offset potential loss of income when a force majeure clause triggers on a delivery/supply contract, such as in the coal or gas industries in Queensland. Not easy to get, very strictly underwritten and expensive, but it's around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-05 09:21:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>This looks like an attempt by the Workers Comp insurer to effect recovery from the homeowners liability insurance to me. It's like half of r/insurancepros has turned up for this thread.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 11:56:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're not necessarily allergic to them, it's just that they are often processed on the same equipment. Cross-contamination is common, so common that people frequently avoid both just to be safe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 05:11:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>White with a dark tail? Iggy Azalea confirmed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 11:02:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always invest in a premium-grade insurance policy. It costs more money, but you know you are covered for just about any conceivable act. I'm an Underwriter, and I've seen enough seriously big claims to know that when a real disaster comes about you want to be with someone big, well resourced and well organised so you've got access to emergency funds and accommodation as quickly as possible. No mess. No arguments. No haggling. You just make the call and they get it fixed for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 11:10:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, good ol' proximate cause... I love the old cyclone/hurricane driven storm surge argument. Cover for cyclone damage? Yes. Cover for storm surge? No. Cover for storm surge caused by a cyclone? Erm... Maybe? But until a court or someone says otherwise, no.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 11:13:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aaaaand now everything is on fire. Because gas lines totally never bust during major earthquakes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 22:49:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>The fire following flood situation is quite straight forward in Australia, too. It's regarded as a completely separate event, as these fires mostly start when flood waters are receding. You see one or two following each instance of major flooding.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 13:29:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Work in insurance and forgot to copy across a specific exclusion so that it was on the contract schedule. Ended up having to pay out on a claim that should have been settled under a different policy. $5,000,000. Oops.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 10:10:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seconded. Check the definitions of 'you/your' and 'insured' in the policy of your fiance. If you are living together and have been for long enough to be a defacto couple, then they may not be able to subrogate against you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-02 09:50:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>As an Australian: Fuck that for a joke. They may not actually try and chase you like a King Brown, but this still goes firmly in my 'Yeah, nah' column.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 12:09:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>PRIMUS SUCK!!! ;P</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 14:17:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Feck off! You'll never take my Jack!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 14:18:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be an ecumenical matter!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 08:37:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>And as a fleet underwriter, have an updoot from me. Breathalyser interlocks are old tech. They should be moving ahead with eye tracking tech like Seeing Machines, or possibly both. Breath test at ignition, and then the Seeing Machine system can facial matching and eye tracking from there. You leave the seat, open the door, etc, then it asks for a breath sample. Hell, you can even set it to track of the driver is drinking something and ask for a sample at that point. Edit: *if the driver is drinking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 08:58:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Again, it depends. What's more likely is that they discover that your vehicle isn't anywhere near as 'stock' as it may have been declared. That is grounds for voiding a policy due to non-disclosure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 10:46:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi. Motor insurance underwriter here. Got a lot of experience watching these for insurance claims. The biker is 100% at fault. If you watch the Armco barrier you can see it is going great past at a consistent rate, which means the car was staying at the same speed. The back and forth relative motion in the clip is entirely due to the biker accelerating and braking. Biker tried to be an arsehole. Forgot about physics. Biker lost. Biker would also have to pay for the damage to car. And a fine for reckless driving.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 10:49:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Watch the Armco. The car is staying at the same speed. It's the bike that is repeatedly cutting off and 'brake testing' the car. I am not an armchair lawyer, but I am a motor fleet insurance underwriter. Bike is 100% a fault.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 10:50:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It hurts me every time I read it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 10:52:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>This. Check the centreline; check the Armco. The car is travelling at a constant speed. Cruise control, by the look of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 11:11:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you watch the video, and not just the gif, you see that the motorcyclist cuts off and then repeatedly brake checks the car. That is reckless/dangerous driving. I work in motor insurance, and if one of my clients did the same as that motor cyclist I would: 1. Hold them at fault 2. Deny their claim due to reckless driving The motorcyclist is 100% at fault in any jurisdiction you care to name.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 11:20:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for having a sane, reasonable and evidence based opinion. Im an Aussie motor insurance underwriter, and after seeing the video the rider is 100% at fault. Car remains at the same speed when the rider cuts them off, brake checks, accelerates away and then brake checks for a second and more final time. Dangerous driving; insurance claim declined for the rider. End of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 11:42:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>The driver wasn't trying to pass, he was trying to evade. The rider comes from the right hand lane, brake checks once, does his little rude gesture to the driver and then accelerates away. At this point the driver has every reason to believe the rider is done with their BS road rage powerplay, but then the rider brakes checks again, and this time he slows down seriously quickly. The driver has no reason to expect that sort of conduct, and in turn has no culpability for events transpiring as they did.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 11:45:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is from Russia... Because all the good dash cam footage comes from Russia, anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 12:38:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a genuine cause of pane.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 14:52:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Underwriters are the front end. The job is to assess and price the risk, taking all factors into account. What they do, have, where they are, history, business practices, risk management, and so on. You can then tailor the cover a bit to better fit the client's business needs, or limit it if they do really high risk stuff. You need to know the policy wording back to front, and you get called on by the claims area to make judgement calls on occasion. Yep, people take insurers to court pretty often, and if the case is doubtful then generally insurers settle pretty quick. Why? Two reasons: to save money on legal fees; and to try and avoid setting legal precedent if it's not in our favour. If you win against an insurer in a local court, it's no biggie. You take your cash, it's done. But if you win against an insurer in a district or supreme Court, then that sets a common law precedent, which can have all kinds of flow on effects down the line. So yeah, sometimes we think we have a good case, but we'd rather hand over a smaller amount of cash than risk an adverse judgement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 21:16:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good thing I'm not an agent. I'm a carrier, and you better believe we get to assign fault.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 21:22:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ordinarily you would be correct, but you need to watch the full video for this one. There are events that occur prior to the start point of the gif that demonstrate the rider was driving recklessly. He cut into the lane directly in front of the car at very close range and immediately sought to cause a confrontation. Rider is stuffed in a liability sense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 21:30:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>The two second rule is a good basis to start from, but the longer video clearly shows it was the rider's intent to cut the driver off and compromise the safe stopping distance. The rider's conduct was reckless, and his own actions of cutting the driver off then repeatedly accelerating and braking hard in a short space of time caused this whole incident. You aren't following to closely if the vehicle in front intentionally cuts you off and then slams on the anchors.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 22:26:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the thing... LE does not actually determine fault. That still lies with either insurers or the courts. LE investigate - sometimes - and provide their opinion on who is at fault, but most of the time they simply care about if a traffic infringement needs to be issued to someone. And the infringement itself doesn't necessarily extend to being liable. Insurance companies will take LE findings on board and use that info in court if it escalates that far. So, LE decide who to fine, but a judge will ultimately decide who is at fault.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 09:38:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>What an amazingly handsome elder statesman. They give so much love. My beautiful Sam, a 10 year old Golden, shall be remaining with my ex-wife now that we are separating. I will miss him more than I can express in words alone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 12:55:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Contact the other insurer in writing if you have the details. Provide them with the following: 1. Detailed version of events. Eg. 18 March, 2018. 8pm. Travelling eastbound on 5800 block of Ruby Ave. Car pulled out of driveway... 2. Describe damage points in detail, and provide photos if you have them 3. Assessment of your damages or repair invoices if you have already had the car fixed. If you genuinely believe you are not at fault then you will need to push them for a response. Aside from that, get independent legal advice. As you only have liability cover, unfortunately you cannot rely on your insurer for assistance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 12:54:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dear God, that is a huge chuck. I mean, in a chuck to body weight ratio sense that would be like a human after a tomahawk steak, baked potatoes and a skin full of beers. In one, smooth movement. No half baulks, no dry retching, just boom. Empty, now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 13:00:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Former...". Well, figured that would have to happen. It's moments like that where I ponder the most important question in British politics: "What would Malcolm Tucker have done in this situation?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 13:04:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just let your ex-wife assert her anti-vaccination views to an open court. Winning a custody battle the easy way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 11:25:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>sudo make me a sandwich.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 16:38:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>As some other comments here have already stated, that amount actually is fair and reasonable as far as repair costs go in Australia. The impact has most likely cracked the bumper under the number plate holder. It may be a lot of money, but I can safely say you aren't being ripped off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 16:53:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's nice when people truly understand umbrella liability. So many don't. In truth they are much closer to a multi-line excess layer than a 'I'm covered for everything' policy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 09:48:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I regret that I only have one downvote to give this cherry-picked assassination piece that's been stripped of all context and broader meaning. And since when the fuck did BuzzFeed have anything even approaching the necessary level of credibility to be linked for World News? BBC or Washington Post in future, please.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 10:55:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly the vast majority of conservative politicians don't give two hoots about abortion or any other women's issue. What they really care about is pandering to their voter base. Issues like abortion and access to family planning services are easy points on the board in much of the south. Now if you where to ask the conservative constituents themselves, you'd get a whole raft of responses that basically add up to 'It's always been this way and I don't like change.'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 15:03:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ground level louvres like that will be either safety glass or plexiglass. Or at least they will be in most parts of the developed world, as building codes mandate accordingly. I'm assuming this is more modern construction due to the black adonised frames. They've only become popular in the last 10 years or so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 09:30:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've stumbled across this late, but the concept is fascinating. The 'Huh...' reaction you have been receiving thus far is what I would be expecting. Straight out of the XKCD 'Nerd Sniping' post, when a keen intellect is suddenly confronted with the conceptual equivalent of a brick to the face.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 11:20:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no, you don't! Not falling for that... again. :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 10:59:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any push back in this may potentially come from what you have been using the vehicle for since repairs were effected. It sounds like you may do genuine off-roading judging by your description of the vehicle and customisation you have had done to it. If this is the case, and they did do a frame check / measure at the time of the claim, then you could be in trouble. What may potentially have occurred is that the initial impact introduced a weak point into the frame without immediately visible damage. If you have since used the vehicle off road it would have been subjected to torsion and strain beyond what you see in regular road use, causing further damage to the weak spot. tl;dr: Accident could cause weak spot in frame that has slowly twisted over time through usage patterns.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 06:41:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>You do have to mine and refine all the materials for the solar panels, too. And don't forget about energy storage! Solar energy is great, but when you really start to look at total lifetime costs over a 50 to 60 year period, plus an allowance for storage and reprocessing of waste, nuclear energy absolutely thumps solar across emissions, reliability and capacity factor metrics.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 14:01:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>^ This. Also a lot more supporting case law over gender discrimination, at both state and federal levels. Going down the path of seeking a judgement based on orientation would be helpful to further establish case law, but it would be significantly more costly and time consuming.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 12:27:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>It might not be the best idea to have your place of employment on your Tinder profile. Especially if you work in the insurance industry, because we're a bunch of borderline-functional alcoholics that live to gossip and grind over the rumour mill to distract ourselves from the fact that we work in fucking insurance! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 15:48:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Big move by Danny Ric. Race strategy move to be the only driver to run Q2 on supers. Hope he blasts a hot one in Q3 and gets second row so the gamble pays off!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 09:15:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would this be a metric or imperial fuckton?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 17:13:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Crocodiles would be the most legitimately dangerous if you happen to be in their territory. Not many people are because it fucking hot, humid and an all-round shit place to live. Kangaroos are dangerous in that they can end up through your windscreen at 100kph, and do so pretty frequently. Several people are killed each year in road accidents with roos, or by trying to avoid hitting them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 17:20:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh yeah, forgot about the Cassowary. I'd say they are the closest living relative we have to a Velociraptor. They are very rare, and tend to stick to dense rainforest, but fuck me they are scary if you happen to stumble on a father with recently hatched chicks. You have to run away, or they will kick you until they don't think you're a threat anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 13:48:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was everyone else thinking 'why didn't he just keep the ball at home plate and defend'?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 01:03:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't understand why he would move to seize the funds. I can see where the cop is coming is from. Couple, woman heavily pregnant, significant sum of cash and gift cards, heading to a casino? It has several red flags for potential money laundering. But why seize it? If he was suspicious, then put something in place to try to follow money. If it's nothing it's nothing, but if it is money laundering then you could possibly net a whole syndicate from the bust. Small minded small town cops stuff it for everyone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Kansas City Chiefs running backs coach, adopted at birth, discovers biological father is his life long mentor.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:14:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:22:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>And after they've already known each other for nearly 30 years. Blows my mind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 10:01:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's kinda why I posted it here. I read the article and there were happy tears working very, very hard to bust out of me. I mean Smith has been acting as a mentor and a father figure to him since he was 16. It's beyond heart-warming.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 10:04:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's one of those 'truth is stranger than fiction' moments, but in the most joyous possible way. Someone's going to option this as a script in a heartbeat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 10:08:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a title. It's meant to be short. It's meant to give just enough info so that you actually click through to read the article, because it's bloody well worth reading. I'm sorry if I interrupted your Reddit trawl-through by actually suggesting you read something of substance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 10:19:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>And that's fair enough. I appreciate that you actually took time to articulate your criticism. I'm always open to constructive criticism and advice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 10:40:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Take the time and enjoy. This story is worth the read.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>