<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject733</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 19:04:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>New York has beautiful castles that not enough people know about ! http://www.newyorkupstate.com/alexandria-bay/2015/04/boldt_castle_hours_admission_tours_and_more_information_on_the_alexandria_bay_la.html http://www.singercastle.com/brief-history/ THERE IS SO MUCH MORE TO NEW YORK THAN THE CITY! Seriously . I grew up in the thousand islands area (a real place on the border of New York and Canada. There are actually more like 1800 islands. ) and it's absolutely beautiful in the summer , and completely neglected by the state in recent years . Plus We have poutine !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Every husky needs a best friend !</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-15 21:22:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-15 21:28:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>My husky (Groot) is just over a year old and a typical ball of energetic floof. After our friends visited with their dog for a week , we knew it was time to get him a friend . He was so depressed after the other dog left ! Soo , we adopted Gamora , a husky shepherd mix ! As you can see , the two have become inseparable . Fellow husky owners - I highly recommend getting them a friend . His behavior and energy levels have improved drastically !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-21 18:57:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I grew up here ! It's a beautiful area -in the summer - that no one seems to know about . Nothing like waking up and seeing Canada everyday out your window ! Also, there's [Singer Castle](http://www.singercastle.com) , which you can rent out all to yourself for about $2000 a night . Party on an island , anyone ?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-21 20:10:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey , same here! I'm from Morristown ! I moved away about a year and a half ago ago to Colorado and absolutely love it here , but I do miss home occasionally ! Don't miss the rampant hillbillies, heroin, or road blocks at all, but man those St. Lawrence Sunsets ...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-21 20:12:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>My thoughts exactly! The hardest part is coordinating even 20 adults to commit to something on the same weekend . And you need a boat to get out there .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-21 20:15:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never understood why people think wind turbines are ugly .. And That area DESPERATELY needs the high paying jobs that those turbines brought in . Plus .. Renewable energy ? There's 1700 other islands to look at if you don't like that one :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-21 20:19:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omaha is really cool ! Do you do the thing where people ask you where you're from and you say "New York , but no not that New York . Northern New York . No - not Buffalo - more North . Basically Canada . No not Niagara ! Never mind "</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Happy to oblige, sir ! Don't test my customer service skills .</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-21 21:29:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-21 23:42:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a neat area , but certainly has seen better days. I worked in tourism in Abay for about five years until recently, and it's a struggle for nearly every business there to remain open . It's sad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 03:28:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>We just used a cheap frame we had lying around . They'll probably end up taking it , but hey they made us all laugh so totally worth it !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 04:45:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>False . This was absolutely a first for me and I've been working in hospitality for six years . People can be really mean . I greatly appreciate those with a sense of humor .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 19:26:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well , that's a good question. I wasn't expecting this to get so many upvotes. I actually did comment the name of the hotel originally , but was instantly trolled so I took it off . I posted it from the hotel's Facebook page also, but we've only been open two years so we don't have a ton of likes . It's a small privately owned boutique hotel in Colorado. We are in the process of expanding into a larger full service hotel. It's absolutely the most beautiful hotel I've ever had the pleasure of working at , in the middle of the Rockies two hours from Denver. Photos don't do it justice ! [Surf Chateau](http://www.surfchateau.com)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is what girls are talking about when guys aren't around</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-23 00:07:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Let me tell you bout my best friendddd</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-23 00:23:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-04 20:38:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>When we showed her photographic evidence of her boyfriend cheating on her. He had been going to bars and hooking up with random chicks using a fake name . One of them was a friend of a friend and made the connection after seeing his real name and picture on Facebook. We told my friend all of this and she didn't believe it . There was even a photo of the boyfriend and random girl grinding posted from the bar's Facebook page. Nope. Still doesn't believe us . Accuses us of sabotaging their relationship because we were jealous. Haven't spoken to her since . They just got married. *Eye Roll*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sent my state tax return (CO) through certified mail- told it was never received. Help !</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-06 21:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I moved from New York to CO this past year, and had to file taxes in both states as a partial resident . My federal and New York taxes went through without any issue (e-file). (Apparently you can't e-file in CO through these third party tax programs ? -idk) I sent my state tax return (prepared online through turbo tax) via certified mail before the April deadline. I sent my boyfriends and mine on the same day, to the same address, and his was received . After being told that the state is notoriously slow in sending tax returns here , I patiently waited for my check ($426) to come In the mail. Fast forward to now- Still no check. After checking the Irs website for the status of my refund, it says my return was never received. It's impossible to get anyone on the phone, and the irs website offers no answers. I'd rather not pay a tax professional or any late fees since I did file on time and have proof (certified mail receipt) I also really want my $426 as soon as possible. It's a lot of money to me! Any advice is appreciated ! Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-06 22:00:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will do that ! Really don't know why I didn't think of that myself as an otherwise intelligent human :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-09 00:43:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tomorrows my 24th birthday. This really fucked me up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-15 19:34:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for posting this! Please email the commissioners everyone! Vertex was goddamn magical, and we need to fight to keep it in our town .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-26 02:14:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>My very straight and manly fiance has recently started saying "that's homophobic" instead of "that's gay" and I just really love that and hope it catches on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-29 21:56:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmao yes , it's garbage . The worst hotel management software in all the land. We will be upgrading soon when our fancy new hotel is complete !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ELI5: Why is it so hard to kill flies with anything other than a fly swatter?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-29 21:57:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-29 22:01:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Physics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-05 04:19:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh this comes at a great time. Hopefully they will get St. Lawrence County D.A. Mary Rain. [An absolute shitshow of incompetence.](http://m.huffpost.com/us/entry/12085240) *TL;DR:* If any person exemplifies the futility of trying to discipline a New York State prosecutor, it is Mary E. Rain, District Attorney of St. Lawrence County in upstate New York. Rain is the most dangerous prosecutor in New York State. She fabricated a statement she claimed the defendant made to the victim - "How do you feel now that you've been taken by a real man" - as a word-play to incite the jury to say to the defendant: "How does it feel to have a guilty verdict from a real jury." The appeals court found that despite strong efforts by Judge Richards, who admonished Rain repeatedly to desist from her misconduct and instructed the jury to disregard her comments, the severe prejudice from her conduct could not be cured. Rain asked prejudicial questions without a proper foundation to inflame the jury; asked Hillary's 17-year-old daughter, in violation of the attorney-client privilege, to disclose what her lawyer told her; expressed her personal opinion about the evidence and Hillary's guilt; bullied witnesses with improper questions, sometime asking the same question thirteen times; asserted to witnesses that they could not possibly disbelieve the prosecution's "Proof" that the defendant was guilty. After Judge Richards dismissed several cases for Rain's failure to timely perfect several appeals, Rains attacked Judge Richards in a press release for dismissing a sexual assault indictment, saying that the judge's decision "Made no sense" and that the judge "Failed to follow New York law." Rain said that her office would "Relentlessly fight to protect the rights of crime victims by appealing decision." Rain's public attack on a judge is a serious violation of professional ethics. To my knowledge, Rain's understanding is not shared by any other prosecutor in New York State or anywhere else in the country. Rain was elected in 2013 after a vicious campaign in which she accused the incumbent District Attorney Nicole Duve of incompetence, mismanagement, and the failure to investigate the Garrett Phillips killing even though Rain knew nothing about the investigation and had never seen the file in the case.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-12 01:41:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll start ! Once, while I was really hungover my boyfriend made me a sandwich. I was so grateful and excited for this sandwich in my pathetic state. I took a huge bite only to discover that he had put 140,000 scoville unit ghost pepper sauce on it. I was instantly gagging and crying, it was awful. He didn't realize how intense it really was so I insisted he try it for himself. After seeing my reaction he refused. Shortly after I left for work . I receive a text from him -"I'M SO FUCKING SORRY, YOU WERE RIGHT, NEVER AGAIN" I laughed, assuming he had tried it for himself. Nope, he decided to beat it without first washing his hands.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 21:08:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks - I know I'm not a bad person, but this really did just happen today so I am still feeling the soul crushing guilt. Mostly I just feel bad for this poor little girl! She just wants to included . I will say, her parents are great people and wonderful, loving parents. It must be very hard for them to try and uphold their traditions while seeing their daughter so upset. Agree or not, they are just doing what they feel is best for her and I respect it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 21:45:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>The real monster over here ^^</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 21:55:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Into the Wild. "Happiness is only real when shared." That line really sticks with me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 22:01:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, no birthdays either . Basically all fun things are outlawed. After finding out, I did some research on Jehovahs witnesses to make sure I wouldn't fuck up again . A very odd religion for sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 22:34:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>This seems like a great compromise ! Your stepmom must have really loved you guys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Michael loves talking about his deck !</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 19:11:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 21:01:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, it's definitely real ! It's written in red pen, and legally teachers are the only ones allowed to use red . It's in the Bible .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Spotted on my local Facebook garage sale site.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-06 14:04:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-06 21:22:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had tickets to this festival in 2013(I think?), when it was shut down for the venue being run down, and one of the festival workers tragically passing away. We started our own mini -festival at landers campground and it was absolutely beautiful there and one of my favorite memories ! Where was this relocated to? Good to know it's still happening ! Legalize NY!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-06 21:25:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you liked Telluride Bluegrass fest, you should really check out Vertex! It's held in The tiny mountain town of Buena Vista, CO on the most beautiful venue called the Meadows . Last year was the inaugural year. Sprawling mountain views, a private swimming beach with an island dj booth, cottonwood creek running along the entire venue. It's put on by Madison House, who does Electric Forest- so you know it's quality !!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 23:58:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>My heart is broken. I live here and this was an extremely brutal fight that essentially split the town. The amount of hatred and vitriol spat by both sides was ugly. The festival itself was a magical, beautiful occasion. Many locals attended and are very upset by this news. It's not over! We just elected progressive county commissioners and Madison House promised to try again in 2018. I know the landowner personally and this is his dream, he bought this land specifically to preserve it and host a festival. Vertex 2018!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-10 00:01:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bad news- No Vertex in 2017. I live in the goddamn footloose town. Hopefully it'll be back again in 2018!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Now I'm not one to delete people for having different opinions, but this was the last straw for me today.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 03:07:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 20:16:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I did, I would need to delete just about every single person from my hometown! And obnoxious as they are, those crazy rednecks are a lot of fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Beware, this Facebook friend of mine is actually employed in a shop somewhere.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 02:06:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Queer Whisperer absolutely DESTROYS homophobia with a hug</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 17:46:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Unhappy Thanksgiving</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-24 16:49:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-24 17:01:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>You better be shoving truths down it instead of turkey!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>BIG celebration happening at my local Dairy Queen.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 01:44:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-28 05:20:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>In 2016 I got engaged, bought a house, got a puppy.. and in four days I'll be going on my first ever plane ride to Aruba. Hell yes 2016!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 03:59:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a fake news article I'm always seeing that never fails to make me laugh "see how these 10 child celebrities grew up" and it's shows a comparison photo of Minkus from Boy Meets World and Chanel West Coast. The similarities are actually uncanny.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I made this [homemade] giant crunch wrap supreme! Banana for scale</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 03:51:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 04:06:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe, but how else would anyone be able to tell how big it is?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 04:11:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>The banana bread I'm going to make with it will be!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 04:17:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seasoned ground beef saut #233;ed with onions, bell peppers, garlic and jalape #241;os, layered with cheddar cheese, chili cheese Fritos, mozzarella, green onion, and diced tomato. Delicious!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 04:21:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll be leaving tomorrow to spend the next ten days in Aruba! Currently trying to use up everything in my fridge..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 04:23:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are much, much happier than they would be if I had a Taco Bell within in a 75 mile radius.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-03 15:27:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fellow native northern ny-er here . Do all of your friends work at sun mount? Mine seem to.. a severe lack of high paying jobs up there ...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-03 15:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>You sound like you're from Ogdensburg. Me too! and it's definitely bleak up there in the winter. There's basically no sun for 4-5 months out of the year. I live in co now, where it's cold, but at least we have sunshine!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-03 15:36:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>My old stomping grounds! Do you like live music ? You'll have lots of fun at the Java Barn! Definitely avoid the tick tock. Get very intoxicated and order a Sergis pizza roll. Maybe two. You'll want another when you're hungover in the morning .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 21:53:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone know if it works at high altitudes? Baking is a bitch at 8,000 feet!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Have a safe, wholesome new year friends!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 21:25:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 21:30:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>R/wholesomememes is the light at the end of the dark tunnel that has been 2016.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Facebook friend of mine charges for "artistic engagement photoshoots" such as this one.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 17:28:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 17:42:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, they are infuriatingly bad. The actual photos of the people are even worse than this travesty. Hold up while I blur some faces out..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 17:52:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, although I can't understand how as a client you could be happy receiving this level of work out of someone who claims to be a professional.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 21:27:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/gallery/V3DfH I did not blur those children's faces out. That was her "artistic effect"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 21:27:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I promise you that is not what happened here .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 01:47:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's like that on every photo, I don't believe she actually knows what a watermark is or its purpose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>All hail the trash princess</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-08 18:27:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-08 19:24:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like this belongs in r/fellowkids</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Credit Karma displays entirely wrong person after creating account with my own information.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 20:24:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>This seems to be exclusively a problem on credit karma. My information does not show up at all, only hers. When I do my annual government mandated credit report, all of my information is correct and this mystery person is displayed nowhere. I had no problems getting a mortgage and all of my reported financial information to the lender was verified and correct. What should I do? I just purchased my first home and got my first credit card, so I would really like to use the service. It's also quite disturbing that I am able to access all of this person's personal and financial information using my own social security number, birthdate, etc. Edit: formatting Edit 2: Here are the steps I've already taken: -immediately pulled my credit reports from www.annualcreditreport.com. All reported information was correct. Mystery person was nowhere to be found. -Reported the problem to credit karma. -They deleted the account, and told me to reapply. I did, and the same wrong person showed up. -told them the same thing happened again when I signed up a second time, they told me to call transunion. -Called trans union. Explained the situation to four different supervisors. Verified all my personal information with them. Mystery person is, again, nowhere to be found. I am told the only thing they can do is send me a copy of my credit report. They are not too concerned with the fact that I have access to all of this persons information. Currently awaiting a higher level manager to call me back. UPDATE: The CEO of credit karma sent me a pm this morning . They are looking further into the issue. Thank you to the user who tagged them!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 20:55:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think that's what happened here. This seems to be exclusively a problem on credit karma. When I do my annual government mandated credit report, all of my is correct and this mystery person is displayed nowhere. I had no problems getting a mortgage and all of my reported financial information to the lender was verified and correct.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 21:19:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have submitted several requests already. All they seem to be able to do is delete my account and tell me to reapply. When I reapply, I see the same incorrect information. I was hoping the great reddit gods may have a suggestion to help escalate the problem with them..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 22:29:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've got her mailing address and all of her personal information , and could easily steal her identity . I've been on the phone with transunion for the past hour having essentially this conversation and they don't care . I'm about to call her employer so I can speak with this poor girl directly and let her know what is happening.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 22:31:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just got a capital one card, all of my information is recorded correctly..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 22:58:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>You only input the last four, and I was never asked for the full. My guess is this is exactly what happened . I'm just having issues trying to get anyone to acknowledge or address the problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 00:58:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dear god, it's wonderful to have someone finally understand the problem. They seem to be so confident in their algorithm never doing this, that they refuse to acknowledge the possibility it happened.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Update: CEO of credit karma has reached out to me personally; software glitch caused wrong person to show up when I registered for credit karma</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 19:36:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Original post : https://www.reddit.com/r/personalfinance/comments/5mzpgk/credit_karma_displays_entirely_wrong_person_after/ Thank you Reddit and the user who tagged u/Credditkarma . My identity, and the other persons, are safe. The CEO reaching out to me personally was a nice touch. However, credit and security are very sensitive matters. It should not take a post on social media to resolve this serious issue. At the very minimum, there should be a dedicated customer service line to report errors. UPDATE: my last message from the credit karma CEO states that it is a "data consistency error from transunion." And there is "not much they can do" to fix the error. At this time I still have full access to this other persons personal and financial information. Good thing I'm not an identity thief! As a side note, I've already reached out to transunion and my data is all correct with them, and since this other person shows up nowhere, they cannot give me any other information or even contact the other person and let them know what's going on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 19:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for tagging them ! The CEO sent me a pm this morning and hopefully they will be resolving this issue!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 20:46:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, yes. Jr. should definitely be taking business advice from his successful father. It worked out so well for him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 19:37:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>MY THOUGHTS EXACTLY. Their customer service department was not concerned, and my last message from the CEO stated that there's "not much they can do" to fix the problem. Wtf?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 19:47:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, I can't attest to their friendliness or not, as they don't have a customer service line for me to actually speak with Anyone. From my last message from the CEO, it doesn't sound like the problem will be fixed. I would not recommend their tax software based solely on the fact that i would not feel that my information is secure with them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>She thought it was a racial slur...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 00:59:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sexy chickens</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 19:38:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 19:46:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Slay Clitoris</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 21:03:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's supposed to be a name, "Seay Adams" .. the wreath is cute, they just ruined all their hard work with that font choice .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 22:39:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It requires owning some sort or property together, not necessarily a house. We lived together for the entire year and own a vehicle together so the requirements are still covered.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 22:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>We meet all of these requirements for common law marriage. We refer to each other as husband and wife. All of our finances our entangled. Eventually we will sign the official paperwork but until then we are happy to be common law married for the foreseeable future. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 23:01:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! This is the type of answer I was looking for, As I already know we qualify to file jointly and are common law married.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 23:03:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, that's very helpful! We will likely run it both ways and see which has the better outcome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 00:27:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>At my university, getting a student job in food service was as easy as walking into the student union, looking at a giant whiteboard, and filling your name in on whatever shift you could accommodate. If that shift no longer worked for you, you erased your name from the board. This happened all the time, so there were always new shifts that needed to be filled. Shifts were usually 3 hours at a time . At my university, they paid two dollars more than minimum wage. Look into something like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 02:46:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know.. this is kind of awesome. It would be so much easier to get a stubborn asshole kid into a batman car seat than a regular one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This would be my dogs tinder picture.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 19:40:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Heckin good husker needs bella rubz aSaP</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 19:43:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Black cats are often the last to get adopted from shelters. One of the reasons is because they are not "photogenic." Let's show everyone this is a myth!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 16:28:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 18:04:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let me see dem kitties  #128527;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 21:00:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why the fuck is this a life pro tip? Is there anyone who doesn't do this? Who is up voting this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Today's the day!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 23:07:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I run social media for a boutique hotel..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 17:18:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My grandmother was born on a farm in Upstate New York in 1932. Despite her father's disapproval, her and my grandfather traveled the world, even passing through the iron curtain to visit the USSR in the 60s. Hong Kong was one of their favorite places.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 18:34:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 18:44:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>She passed away this week at age 84, as bright as she was the day this photo was taken. Unfortunately I never met my grandfather, as he passed away before I was born. In addition to traveling the world, she was valedictorian of her graduating class (my grandfather was salutatorian!) raised 6 children, took care of her sisters, and ran a successful dairy farm for 35 years. She was an avid gardener and the best grandmother to her 13 grandchildren. She treated all of us as her favorites, including my half sister who was not technically her grandchild. That never mattered to this wonderful woman. She knitted over 100 unique quilts, one for every life event(graduations, weddings) There were four grandchildren who are not yet married . We learned at her funeral that before she passed, she made four more quilts to be given to each of us on our wedding day. Here is a photo of just some of her quilts, draped over the pews at her funeral. https://imgur.com/gallery/Qby5c</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My Grandmother's handmade quilts draped over the pews at her funeral. She made over 100 for every special occasion. Before she passed, she made four more, one for each of her unmarried grandchildren to be given to us on our wedding days.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 19:05:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 19:27:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have two, which I treasure dearly! She was truly an amazing woman and I am reminded of her every day when I look on my couch and see my beautiful quilts!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 19:32:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>She passed away this week at age 84, as bright as ever. She was born on a farm in upstate New York in 1932. Despite her fathers strong disapproval, she traveled the world for years with my grandfather. They even passed through the iron curtain to visit the USSR in the 1960s. Here is a photo of them in Hong Kong in 1969: https://www.reddit.com/r/OldSchoolCool/comments/5tmou3/my_grandmother_was_born_on_a_farm_in_upstate_new/ In addition to traveling the world, she was valedictorian of her graduating class (my grandfather was salutatorian!) raised 6 children, took care of her sisters, and ran a successful dairy farm for 35 years. She was an avid gardener and the best grandmother to her 13 grandchildren. She treated all of us as her favorites, including my half sister who was not technically her grandchild. That never mattered to this wonderful woman. She knitted over 100 unique quilts, one for every life event(graduations, weddings) Her quilts adorn our couches, beds, walls, and are a constant reminder of how much she loved us. She is my role model and I love and miss her dearly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 20:25:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I put this on Imgur solely to add it to my original tribute post in r/OldSchoolCool, not expecting it to gain any attention. After some positive feedback I decided to upload it here too . I'm glad everyone seems to enjoy it as much as I do. I'm not sure how she would feel about it, honestly. I have just been thinking of her so much I felt I needed to share with others how wonderful she was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 20:29:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha, well fortunately after a while the kids double as farm help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 20:32:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahahaha, luckily I've already got my wedding date picked out! We picked what we thought was a random date about a week before her passing. Coincidentally, it was also her and my late grandfathers wedding anniversary. Really amazing how these things seem to work out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(X-post from r/pics) My grandmothers handmade quilts draped over the pews at her funeral. She made over 100 for every special occasion. We learned at her funeral that before she passed, she made four more for each of her remaining unmarried grandchildren to be given to us on our wedding day.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 21:29:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 21:42:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmaoooo this is hilarious  #128514; I'm not sure how she was able to finish so many. She did everything herself and didn't start until she was in her 50s.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 21:59:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is amazing ! I cried like a baby when I found out she had some saved for us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 22:11:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! Posting this and reading all the replies has been very cathartic for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 22:45:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Morristown, NY. A tiny town on the St.Lawrence River bordering Canada</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 23:30:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>My god, these are absolutely amazing!! You may have inspired me to continue my grandmothers passion, with a little twist . Wow . I will be showing these to people !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 01:51:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Morristown, New York. A tiny little town on the St. Lawrence River bordering Canada.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 02:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am not sure, honestly ! She was from Morristown, NY. Her name was Janet. Could very well be my grandmother :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 02:36:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your life must really be in ruins if you can be so negative at this. Hope it gets better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-25 19:53:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is extremely helpful. I am definitely "engaged to wait." I have to respond to calls within two minutes, and drive there immediately if the call necessitates . I'm actually not even allowed to be further than 5 miles away at any given time. What will happen if I file a complaint with the dol? Will the company be aware ? There is only one other person in this position , and they are salaried, so it would be very obvious it was me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-25 20:08:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>So.. just so I'm clear... you're telling me that I can potentially receive back pay for each day that I was engaged to wait on call for the past two years and they did not pay me the full amount??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-25 20:16:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would you recommend contacting an employment lawyer prior to filing the complaint ? This is going to be a potentially huge amount of money they owe me. I'm hoping an employment lawyer would be willing to take me on with nothing upfront.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 01:13:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, helpful stranger! By my calculations, not considering overtime and a minimum of 8 unpaid hours a night (closer to 12 in reality) they owe me at least $50,000. I've contacted the dol, hopefully I will hear back on Monday. Prior to filing a complaint, Id like to get confirmation that I meet their standard of being engaged to wait. Since you seem like a wealth of knowledge, I'll ask.. currently I am paid the extra on call hours (two per night) as a "bonus" on my paycheck and not overtime pay. Is this legal?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 01:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>What I am saying is, I do not receive overtime pay for any of these hours either . I am hourly, my on call time is paid as an additional two hours per night, but just at my regular rate. It is listed as a bonus on my pay stubs and not as hours worked. Also, I am expected to be able to answer calls within the same timeframe even if it is 3am, so why would that time not be considered engaged to wait as well ? Thank you again for responding! Your answers have been wonderfully helpful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 03:30:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my god.. I had that same good charlotte wrist band. I wore it every day . Thankfully there is no photo evidence. The smell still haunts me though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-08 19:15:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idk, my senior prank (2010, upstate ny) was pretty amazing. Tl;dr: school took away our senior trip to the beach, we had our own beach day on the school's front lawn. Photos: https://imgur.com/gallery/S1KbB A little backstory: this is a very, very small school. My graduating class was 24 kids. Because of this small number, it was tradition for seniors to do a senior trip, which was usually a trip to , a cruise, or something equally fun. The year I graduated, the new administration decided that the seniors were no longer allowed to visit anywhere with a beach, because it wasn't educational. You fundraise for this trip from grade 7 to the end of your senior year, so naturally we were all very upset when all of a sudden we aren't allowed to do what we've been working for looking forward to and for years. So, to enact our revenge, on the last day of school we decided to have a beach day. On the front lawn of the school. In be middle of the night we laid tarps down, brought in roughly ten truckloads of sand, and dumped it in the lawn. We brought inflatable pools, beach toys, fake palm trees, a volleyball net- the whole nine. The following day, we all showed up early in our bathing suits and had a beach party on the lawn before skipping school. It was an inspiring amount of teamwork and coordination for a group of people that didn't get along on a normal day. Shockingly, no one got in any trouble. The elementary school kids were made to clean it up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>White girl's wedding starter pack</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 00:55:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Woman lies about being in labor to avoid speeding ticket. It doesn't work.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 02:21:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 02:28:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha, before I saw this I posted one about white girl weddings, and it has none of these things! Ironically enough, scrolling down the sub, my post is directly underneath yours right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to make a stoner cry :</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 23:34:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-11 16:28:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah this was posted in a group I'm in, I just thought r/trees might appreciate it . That notification bar hurt me to look at as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>On my local Facebook garage sale site..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 01:44:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 06:35:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably should have edited that out.. oops</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 20:17:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not from here so I refuse to use the butchered Spanish pronunciation. I just say BV instead</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 20:17:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! The town has boomed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 20:33:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol, well there's still only one stop light, but we are in desperate need of a few more at this point . I've been here two years now and like 20 new businesses have sprung up in that time. I don't think the barbecue restaurant exists anymore. If you like the outdoors, mountain adventures, hot springs, sunshine 300 days out of the year then this is the place to be!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-16 17:38:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>R/unexpected</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 22:00:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>National pupper day! Groot in all of his majesty</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 03:01:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Browsing CL for jobs today..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 23:10:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 23:13:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, phonebatterylevelbot! I'll get my charger.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yeah, okay, let me know how that works out for you when your tiny cut turns into a massive infection and you die of sepsis.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 19:35:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Please keep one hand on the dog at all times</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-20 16:04:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-20 21:38:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to think the same, until I actually saw someone I knew personally on one of those ads. Never got up the courage to ask her how her picture ended up there, but it was definitely her. She had very distinctive tattoos. And great tits.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-20 21:48:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to think these "Fuck hot horny locals" ads were bullshit... until I actually saw someone I knew personally on one of those ads. Never got up the courage to ask her how her picture ended up there, but it was definitely her. She had very distinctive tattoos. And great tits. I'm sure the majority of them are fake, but this one was very real. Now I always double check to see if I know the person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-20 22:53:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is exactly why I never brought it up. Figured it was something sketchy like that, and I would not appreciate an acquaintance coming up to me saying "hey, I saw your tits on the internet! Looking good! How'd they end up there?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 00:17:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is so infuriating. I'm sorry that happened! And I'm glad you were able to have it taken down. I assumed something exactly like this happened to this poor girl, which is why I never brought it up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Christine does not have time for your nonsense, QVC</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 21:08:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 21:56:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello fellow Vertex-er! I hope you had a good time! Sad we won't be returning next year. I thought they provided a goddamn magical experience that exceeded my expectations. I live here and work for the landowners. The townspeople suck. The promoters and landowners did everything they could to bring it back this year but just couldn't jive with the restrictions the town put on, so they did the responsible thing and cancelled it for next year. Because Madison House knows how to put on a successful festival (see- Electric Forest) unlike these jibronis.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[NSV] Almost time to retire my size 12 jeans I bought only two months ago!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 21:27:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://i.imgur.com/tZGzaMI.jpg Feeling pretty proud of myself at the moment!! Down from 180ish to 165 this morning. Wish I would have measured myself to know how many inches I've lost. Keto is lifeeeee</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 00:01:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I should! It really does help to stay motivated</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 00:02:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Our stats are pretty similar! You'll get there, I still have a ton more to go but your kind words Help keep me going :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 00:03:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I am trying !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 00:03:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 00:04:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, even if I'm disappointed in the scale, I'm happy when I look in the mirror and that's what matters !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 01:21:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't include my height, which may make a difference to you . I'm 5'5. I've been doing lazy keto for about two and half months. So not very long at all. I think I've lost about all I will with diet alone so I just started going to the gym as of yesterday. Writing this from the locker room now in fact! You got this :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 02:51:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks and I wish this was my bedroom! It's a hotel room.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 02:52:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perhaps I'll post one at my goal weight, but I've still got a lot more to go! But these jeans were tight when I bought them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 02:54:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just reread my comment and it sounds super patronizing. Definitely didn't mean it that way, keep up the good work sister friend :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 02:58:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im about 5'5</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 20:38:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, but I absolutely disagree with you on this one. If you are not sure of what you want to do careerwise, do not go to college. Reading over her comments, she says she wants to go to community college, for art. Community college is a great option for a lot of things, but unfortunately, not art. Its a harsh reality butt It's just the way it is. She is getting kicked out of her home in a matter of months. She needs to focus on getting a stable income and a roof over her head. ASAP. If she goes to college and decides it's not for her, fails, she will not get another opportunity to receive that financial aid. OP, you can do this. You are not a failure for not going to college right out of high school. This dangerous mentality needs to change. This is how our generation became the most in debt generation in history. With the lowest job prospects. P.S. Think about trade school! My fianc #233; took an 8 week class and a year later is making 90k a year. I graduated college, it took 4 and a half years because I changed majors. (Because I went right out of high school with no idea what I really wanted to do) I make 35k a year later. My degree is in business. I am one of the lucky ones because I only owe about 5k for my education, but I can't help but know I would be much better off had I waited to attend college. Rant over.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 23:27:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's something I feel very passionate about because it has personally affected myself and many of my peers. I'm 24, so the negative consequences are really starting to become apparent to many of my friends. Their degrees are useless or unfinished, and the debt they have is very real. You did not say she was a failure, but this is a real issue. All throughout high school this was my exact thought. "I will be a failure if I do not graduate college, because that is what successful people do." And the teachers, counselors, parents, pretty much echoed that. It is a dangerous mentality, and way too much pressure to put on young children.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Today, at age 24, I got measured for a bra for the first time ever...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 16:20:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've always worn a 36C, and thought it fit me. Today when I was measured, I learned I'm actually a 34DDD??!! When she told me the size I pretty much laughed at her and said no way .. and then I tried it on and holy shit. A revelation. No more armpit boobs, nipple pop outs, and It looks 1000x better. I'm standing straighter. How have I been so wrong for so long??!!! I could have hugged this lady. Has anyone else had this experience?? My user name is merely a coincidence. ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 16:32:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just wish I would have done it sooner! I'd probably have better posture today</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 16:56:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like you could be writing a story about my office. I have an Agatha, who has gone much further and done some cruel and unspeakable things to women in the company. We had a female employee who shared with someone that she was gang raped at a Christian camp, took it to trial, and lost. Someone told Agatha, and she proceeded to tell every male in the office "Stay away from X or she will accuse you of rape." I've never lost respect for someone so quickly. (Yes I told my male boss, nothing was done, they are so fucking lucky they didn't get sued.) Women can be so cruel. Most of the time we are civil and polite, but we regularly get into verbal arguments, because she can just be so unreasonable. She comes from a conservative background and has never left the small town where we are, meanwhile I am younger and from across the country.The male bosses know how she is and continually side with me but don't do anything about it . She has been there since the company started and does play an important role. Hopefully your situation does not become this frustrating!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 16:58:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Victoria's Secret.. I suppose I'm basic but she was wonderfully helpful!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 17:01:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Legitimate question that I am asking myself. Bra shopping is an expensive, terrible experience. Most people never bother getting measured, myself included, for many reasons. I have had the same bras for years because they are so expensive and buying new ones is such a chore. I bought two yesterday and it cost me $130. Meanwhile your weight and hormones fluctuate constantly so your size changes over time. Most people also don't know what a correct bra fit is. Apparently I am one of those people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 17:03:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I am still in shock myself! I would have never tried on a cup size that large without someone telling me to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 18:14:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like Victoria's Secret gets shit on all the time on Reddit, but I had an awesome experience. She brought me about 15 sizes and styles, and gave me honest feedback on every single one. And did the same for the other customers there at the same time. She really wanted everyone to have the correct size bra. Maybe I just got someone particularly awesome . Or maybe getting rid of their clothing line and focusing on their core competency (bras, lingerie) has made them step up their game as a whole? Idk. I'm happy tho!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 18:15:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Copy/pasted from another comment below: I feel like Victoria's Secret gets shit on all the time on Reddit, but I had an awesome experience. She brought me about 15 sizes and styles, and gave me honest feedback on every single one. And did the same for the other customers there at the same time. She really wanted everyone to have the correct size bra. Maybe I just got someone particularly awesome . Or maybe getting rid of their clothing line and focusing on their core competency (bras, lingerie) has made them step up their game as a whole? Idk. I'm happy tho!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Purchased this for the novelty, but it is the best chap stick I've ever used! Proof that weed makes everything better.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 20:46:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 22:41:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Easy. Say "hey babe, I want to buy you some nice new bras!" And then take her to a lingerie store. Intimacy, Victoria's Secret, wherever. She will likely be all over it, but be forewarned you're about to spend at least $100 if she wants more than one. Then just be honest with her. Tell her you read a thread on Reddit that told you that many women are wearing the wrong size and she should get measured because you care about her comfort. It's sweet, she will appreciate it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 02:08:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, but I am a pretty heavy smoker.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 02:18:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely way more than 20 uses. I've had this for like 4 months now and use it multiple times a day because CO is dry as fackkk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 06:29:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was $5.. totally worth it. You can get some really potent things from the dispensaries here. First legal state after all..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thanks Mailman! You are good frendo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-07 17:55:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Badass gets pulled over doing well over the speed limit (xpost r/thathappened)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 21:31:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guy gets pulled over going well over the speed limit so cop can ask about his engine. (Xpost to r/iamverybadass)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 21:34:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 04:41:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's amazing! We played there for hours and drank way too many mystery shots. And then ate at this very Cheba Hut. From what I remember it was an excellent time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 04:41:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's amazing! We played there for hours and drank way too many mystery shots. And then ate at this very Cheba Hut. From what I remember it was an excellent time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-01 21:35:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, location is Colorado.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-01 21:48:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>My issue here is not actually the damages. My issue is with the landlord falsely stating the lease was violated and terminated, when the premises was left voluntarily as a courtesy to them, because they wanted to move in themselves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-01 21:50:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>My issue here is not actually the damages. My issue is with the landlord falsely stating the lease was violated and terminated, when the premises was left early voluntarily as a courtesy to them, because they wanted to move in themselves. It was completely surrendered a week early, meaning there is 7 days of rent that should cover a portion of the damages.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-01 21:54:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it is a normal termination of the lease, are we entitled to the seven days of prepaid rent?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hmmm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 20:36:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>350 pounds, unemployed, extremely proud of her new "Born Freak" chest tattoo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-06 01:14:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://i.imgur.com/7SIkMOq.png</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Misleading Makeup</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 18:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-29 02:26:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. I really liked this primer and was really confused when it became empty so quickly. I mean, yes it is a cheap brand.. but holy shit .. I've loved my other products from them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 05:00:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't see trashy here. This is something that an old midwestern geezer with suspenders, square glasses, and a tattered Vietnam Veteran's hat would choose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 06:26:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>We just voted to allow a municipal internet service in my town ! (Buena Vista, CO) I hope it ends up being something like this, although my internet is a bit cheaper for great speeds. (34$ mo/ Century Link) I don't see that price lasting though. The rate lock for life is amazing. Fingers crossed !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 22:26:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Office kitties are the best! More places need to have them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 22:36:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>College - Charges $40,00 for a piece of paper. Doesn't even proofread it before submitting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 22:43:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah. I did not see the original post. I stand by my statement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 06:34:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>So funny, The church near my house just put this up on their sign, and I've been meaning to pull over and take a pic for this sub. They have enough room to on their sign to add "Confirm" and "Ignore." Truly brilliant marketing. I think I'll go pray now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A fake police car and dummy to deter speeding on the base of independence pass in Twin Lakes, CO</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 01:03:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 19:46:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chillupa out and dab wit me homie ayyy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-11 06:20:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>It would be a vastly superior format. Books are split into chapters. There are clear beginning and end points for episodes. Much more time to get to know the characters and see them develop, as we do in the books.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mountain Floofs</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 22:40:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"What a time to be alive"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 19:31:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 04:54:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I'm intrigued. Did she go the obvious route and make it one of the table legs or is there a better way I'm not thinking of ? Any chance you've got a pic?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Watch out everyone! He's got the balls to hit copy and paste. Fuck you.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 01:29:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Watching a video and trying to adjust the volume...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 21:41:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-25 00:38:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have one almost exactly like this. I hate it. The Percs are impossible to clean, even with formula 420.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DJ Jesus in the hizzy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-25 00:41:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-25 06:21:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>All of the pit bulls I have met have been incredibly sweet. Nothing makes me more upset than Breed Specific legislation banning these perfect lil muffins.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dressing to impress for your kid's first day of kindergarten..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 17:52:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 17:55:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I grew up on the Canadian Border, in New York of all places, and this shit is exceedingly common. Lots of poor uneducated people in these parts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 18:18:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, jokes aside, in history class (Northern NY) we were absolutely taught that the civil war was about "states' rights" and not slavery. If we gave an answer of slavery, we were told it was wrong. So it's not surprising to see that people believe this. Anyone else taught like this? I graduated hs in 2010.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 18:22:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol, I agree. I was not the original poster of this. My friend, who's children attend this school, sent it to me and I thought it belonged here. One could also argue that teaching your young daughter to take photos to online shame people who are dressed inappropriately is also trashy. But if we didn't this sub wouldn't exist  #175;\_( #12484;)_/ #175;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 23:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>My husky sits outside all day when it's 15 degreees. My husky sits outside all day when it's 50 degrees. My husky is currently sitting outside when it's 84 degrees. My husky just likes to be outside.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 21:08:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol, it is Fort Hood. My friend's family just relocated there from South Carolina last week, so I doubt it is the same person. Small world!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 21:56:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could instantly tell you were in upstate New York from the first picture, and then I saw your license plate. Finished product looks great! I'm not sure what the obsession was with paneling and drop ceilings in the 60s/70s but I swear every house up there (including the one I grew up in) has it. Depending on how far upstate you are, you probably got it for a steal! Houses like this are on the market for like $12,000 all over St Lawrence County. Do you mind me asking how much you paid and costs to renovate?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 20:34:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Buckle up folks, cause this story is a wild ride. A friend of mine did way too much acid, and then did not sleep for three weeks. Like, at all. On this weekend we were all volunteering to put on a haunted house in an old nursing home. They placed my friend in a room that was set up like an auditorium, with a bunch of dummies and people in masks staring at a tv screen with just static playing. In between customers of the haunted house everyone was hanging out, drinking and generally having a good time. We notice friend is missing. She is still sitting in the dark staged room, with her mask still on staring at the static tv, in a trance. Took a few minutes to snap her out of it, weird but now we have more customers so we need to get back to the haunted house. In the next lull, we hear stomping noises on the second floor of the house, where no one is supposed to be. Friend is pacing around up there, talking to herself. Everyone is thoroughly creeped out at this point. She then proceeded to steal a puppy and disappear with it. Panic ensues. No one knew she took it. She comes back and at this point the haunted house is over. It was put on by my employers (hotel) and in exchange for volunteering they gave us all rooms for the night. I was getting my room key when she comes up to the desk screaming, in front of a large crowd, "I NEED THE KEY! I NEED THE KEY FOR MR. KEY OR HE IS GOING TO FIND ME. IVE BEEN LOOKING EVERYWHERE FOR MR KEY AND HES NOT HERE. " Turns out she had picked up a random note off of the ground written by someone with the last name Key, and hallucinated that it was real, and was wandering around the hotel knocking on people's room doors. At this point I'm obviously concerned, so I called her mother. She flips out, tells me I'm a terrible friend, gets into her car, and speeds away. We thought this was the end. Fast forward to the next day. My coworkers are concerned and a bit scared, and I assured them she wouldn't be coming back for day two of the haunted house. Boy was I wrong. I am working front desk. She walks through the front door. I tell her she's not allowed to be here and she needs to go outside and wait, and I will come talk to her when I can take a break. I take my break, go outside, she is nowhere to be found. I assume that she has gone home. Hours later, she comes back yet again. She hadn't been home. She had somehow snuck onto a boat tour and was riding around for free for a few hours. I tell her again that she can't be here, and I'm really concerned for her wellbeing, trying to remain as calm as possible. She absolutely flips her lid and starts hysterically screaming at me that I'm a piece of shit and the worst friend ever, in front of all my coworkers, children, and haunted house attendees. She was practically foaming at the mouth until she got back into her car and sped away, narrowly missing a pedestrian. She went into an inpatient program for a few weeks, and she has never been the same. It was honestly terrifying to watch. Lack of sleep will seriously fuck with you. Don't do drugs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 21:31:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good color choice in flooring. Medium colored and distressed will help camouflage the large piles of white hair that appear daily.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 20:31:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to have a professor that would deduct 15 points from your paper if it was not stapled at a 90 degree angle. The automatic library staplers would not staple at a 90 degree angle. This professor was an asshole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 05:24:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey thanks man! I tried to click the flier to enter and the link appears to be broken. I'm on mobile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 20:51:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>As someone living in CO, why the hell would you want to go hike somewhere with that many people?? There are endless trails, alpine lakes, and waterfalls here. Is there something especially cool/unique about hanging lake that I am missing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 21:08:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have so much rage for those who allow their off leash dog to bombard my leashed dog. "Oh he's friendly!" Okay sure but you don't know if my dog is, and you've just trapped him into a corner -_-</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 01:00:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm in Buena Vista. Drove to silverthorne the other day, absolutely gorgeous. They seem to be at their peak right now in the high country. It would be the perfect time to drive independence pass. Edit: spelling</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Considering purchasing a mattress off of Amazon..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 20:27:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>The prices seem too good to be true. Less than half of the cost of traditional retailers. Has anyone had experience doing this? Do you love/hate your mattress? Which one did you choose? Any recommendations? I'm looking for something on the softer side..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 20:43:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't believe their mattresses are available in retail stores. And I'm in a pretty rural area.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 21:09:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you ! What brand did you purchase? I've been looking at the Zinus models.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 21:11:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, however they come super compressed in a bag, I don't see how I'm supposed to return it in said bag if I don't like it . There's no way it's going to be easily put back in .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 21:12:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>What brand did you go for? Is it super firm? I've been reading all sorts of mixed reviews</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-24 07:25:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>This happened to me at Red Rocks. SO INFURIATING</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Every workplace should have an office kitty. Here's ours taking a snooze in the flowerpot.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 00:20:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 16:39:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kitty lives above the office, his humans travel frequently so he hangs out with us during the day .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>For when all of your charger blocks magically disappear, or you are staying in a hotel and forgot yours, most tvs have USB ports that will charge your phone.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 21:28:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>No middle ground, no option to ignore. The new Reddit app, folks.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 21:46:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 23:09:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! Internet modems and cable boxes almost always have them as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>V V V Goodboye Otis finds his hoomans after 3 years!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 23:58:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 06:57:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this just a universal thing? Today I bought pumpkins and decorated my house for fall . Must be instinct now that I have reached my mid twenties. It's motherfucking decorative gourd season bitches.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 04:54:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let's not forget Oscar from the office! Just a normal dude who happens to be gay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A couple more weeks left to head to the top of independence pass! Took this yesterday .</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 20:02:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 16:39:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Upstate NY here, so definitely a border state but we feel it too . His last concert streamed on CTV was amazing. So emotional, I teared up watching the stream.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 20:59:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol, I went on a princess cruise last December. We were some of the very few people in our 20s. Most people were definitely seniors, but we didn't mind ! Almost all of them were in bed by like 8pm, meaning no lines and empty pools galore. We were about the only people in the nightclub, aside from the 70ish year old lady getting freakin down on the dance floor in her floral jumpsuit. We overheard quite a few people discussing how they'd been on the ship for 6 consecutive months. Apparently if you cruise often, the discounts compound to the point where it's cheaper than a retirement home. But with better food, facilities, and day trips to amazing islands. 10/10 would do again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 21:21:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did a ten day cruise from Miami to Cura #231;ao, Aruba, and Bonaire. Absolutely amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>*punches through wall* How name your Business</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 18:04:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 23:19:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy fuck where did you go to school ? I'm pretty sure we had the same finance professor.. There were many times in that school where I wanted to rage quit. Edit : just read through the comments and we did not attend the same school . We just had a similarly assholish finance professor. For the record I did pretty well in that class, despite putting nowhere near 50 hours a week in , and having a full time job and other classes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 20:01:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a precious blep.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 22:53:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hotels will be much more lenient about smoking weed in a room. Usually they don't even care unless it's bothering other guests. Weed smell is really easy to get out a room. An open window and a spritz of air freshener will usually do it. Cigarette smell is an absolute nightmare to get out of a hotel room . Every item needs to be taken out and steam cleaned, every inch of the room needs to be scrubbed, and then we close off the room for at least a day and use an ozone machine. That doesn't always work and the process sometimes needs to be repeated. The fine most hotels charge for smoking cigs in a room is totally justified. Source: hotel manager</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MINION HATRED INTENSIFIES</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 20:05:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 04:39:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Clearly you've never been to Ontario. That's probably not an exaggeration.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 03:37:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought this looked familiar! I live in Buena Vista and also have huskies. Haven't done Princeton yet, but I have done Huron and we ran into so many other huskies! https://imgur.com/gallery/VigXP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 01:59:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure why this is on here. This is hilarious and accurate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Husky Zoomies</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 17:27:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>STAND UP YOU IDIOTS</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 20:18:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 20:24:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shut up, Libtard! You owe your freedom to this brave minion. Go back to your safe space!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Zoomies ending in a ferocious attack</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 20:29:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hOuSe LiOn MaUlS hUmAn iN vIcIoUs ATTACK</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 20:32:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 18:27:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah lol this is my single male friends house and baby kitty. It's definitely a bit ghetto</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Attack of the ferocious house lion</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 18:34:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 20:27:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/iamverysmart</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What the fuck, Pinterest</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 21:11:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 17:58:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>My company is looking to provide this option to us as an alternative or addition to high deductible insurance. Everything basic is covered and the doctor even does house calls. I hope it happens, I haven't seen a better option. My boss, with two young kids is looking at like 2000 a month for a 14,000 a year deductible plan. I'm 25 so lucky to be covered by my mothers insurance for one more year. My fianc #233; gets his high deductible insurance covered by his company with supplemental insurance from Aflac because it's a high risk job. It's going to be expensive when I go on his insurance plan next year. Ugh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 05:54:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aside from "put it on the credit card" which is disturbing, it's a list of things someone can make more money off of than peddling these shitty products.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 20:19:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree, however I don't think any of the new detective characters have been successful at replacing Stabler. It was such a weird exit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Remember the time I followed you home from work after you told me no? I did it because I'm such a nice guy that no means yes.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 22:33:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 22:34:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whoops - Reposted because I forgot to blur out the name.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 22:44:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was my sister, and not myself . But ironically enough, this guy was actually fired from this job for picking up a girl and carrying her while she was yelling at him to stop. Cameras showed it clear as day. Niceguys are weirdly similar in their approaches..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 23:51:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh well. His last name and photo are blurred. I'm sure there are many creepy rogers in this world.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 03:05:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>If only someone would have said that to your mother.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 03:43:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really hate how Facebook automatically adds me to these groups now. Why don't I get a chance to approve or deny them? I don't want to be a part of your fucking scentsy party or essential oil bash, and I most definitely don't want to see all your dumbass posts in my newsfeed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 22:03:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have the same fear. On my first 14er hike I was terrified to hold them at the summit. I was terrified to even stand up without anything anchoring me. Also afraid of heights. But we made it! https://i.imgur.com/iLwqNrB.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 23:01:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tragically Hip. If you ever want to see an amazing concert, look up their final concert, which was broadcast to the entire Canadian nation. I watched it on youtube, but I'm so sad I missed it live. It was after the lead singer, Gord Downie, was diagnosed with terminal brain cancer and you can feel the emotions in the room.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 23:05:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait a minute, what did I miss? Did someone shoot Drake in the school hallway, paralyzing him from the waist down?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 00:10:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not liking the popular thing everyone else likes on principle. Absolutely nobody fucking cares if you've never seen an episode of game of thrones. I swear I see this posted on Facebook at least once a day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 00:17:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your hobbies. Rich people hobbies: collecting sports cars, sailing/yachting, collecting country club memberships, jetsetting all over the world to ski Normal people hobbies: biking, hiking, trying to drown the mind numbing dullness of life with alcohol, fishing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 00:59:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Smoking weed doesn't make me interesting, but it does make other people less boring.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 16:36:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Science disagrees with you. ](https://www.google.com/amp/amp.timeinc.net/fortune/2017/09/26/your-dog-loves-you-study) Doggos really do love us!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 01:18:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seriously ? Call your friend when they are going through something is a life pro tip? Who needs this told to them ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This vacation rental I cleaned today had a note telling to put ALL of the pillows on this bed, since I did not last time. 14 full size pillows!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 01:26:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 15:43:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a king size bed, the pillows take up all of it. There are three pillows stacked on each side. Two regular pillows in front of each stack. Four of the large striped decorative pillows, (one is hidden from view) one furry one, and one green one .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 22:27:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've actually bought about ten pairs of boots at the promotional $10 price point. I always just cancel as soon as I receive them. I've been doing this for a few years now. They seem to charge the next $40 at a random time, even though it's supposed to be on the fifth of the month. They've always just refunded me when I called to cancel. Only once have I had an issue where they continued to charge my card after I cancelled. I issued a chargeback through Capitol One and they gave it right back to me. Slightly shady company but I'm yet to find a better deal. $10 to pick from their pretty massive style collection , which includes all wide calf options, has always drawn me back in. Edit to add: I've bought so many pairs because justfab pairs are relatively cheap quality and never last longer than one winter season. I'm a cheap person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 23:31:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is actually how I ended up on Reddit. I would click on those click bait stories, only to go through five pages of annoying ass ads and incomplete answers to find the original thread. And then I never left.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 04:42:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I downvoted you because your thumbnail image gave me cancer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Did anyone make a Spotify playlist of the recent askreddit thread of the 10/10 albums by underrated artists?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 16:35:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looking for someone to do the work for me. The thread in question: https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/7cv2f0/whats_a_1010_album_from_the_last_15_years_by_a/?st=JACMUNOG amp;sh=dd4ca8a6. Thanks for the help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 21:31:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have two huskies. I vacuum once every three days at least. Daily during shedding season. 6 days is pushing it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 19:19:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Donate it to him please! OP can save it for next year. If he's been asking for the same truck for 17 years, I really doubt he will be asking for anything different next year! You rock!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any tips for making tomato sauce from canned crushed tomatoes less watery?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 03:26:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I make tomato sauce from canned crushed tomatoes pretty often. I get more out of my money and its without the sugar and weird added ingredients of premade. It tastes delicious. My only issue is that it tends to be watery. I always end up dumping liquid off my plate before eating. Here's what I usually do: -brown some type of meat (usually ground beef, turkey, or sausage. -add onions, tons of garlic and other random veggies. (Carrots, zucchini, whatever I have) -once everything is browned I add the crushed tomatoes, sometimes a can of premade pesto, and herbs and spices. -let it simmer for at least an hour. Sometimes longer Any tips to make it less watery?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 09:26:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cigarettes and coffee.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Weirdo Bleps</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 18:59:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So regal</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 19:18:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thupermodel</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 19:49:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Working gold mechanical watch pendant, purchased by my grandmother on her trip to Spain in 1962 and given to me 5 years ago.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 20:00:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Groot taking a break from guarding the galaxy to take in the scenery</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 18:12:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 19:11:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>The one in the back looks like he's about to give me a stern talking to about my life choices</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just scored two giant mature plants in heavy ceramic pots for $10! Now what are they and how to I keep them alive?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 22:28:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/a/nQ7Zf</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 01:58:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stupid question - which is the dracaena ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 20:26:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi internet stranger! I feel compelled to tell you that this too shall pass. I found myself in this exact situation three years ago. I had never in my life failed a class before, told all of my family I was graduating, job lined up, etc. And then due to my own stupidity, I failed a class. One I took because it was supposed to be an easy A. And it was easy. I just couldn't be bothered to attend class because I didn't feel it was important or necessary. I felt like such a complete and utter failure. I never even told my extended family. Only my immediate friends and family knew.. So then I was jobless, still living at my parents home at 23. It was an incredibly humbling experience for someone voted "Most likely to succeed." But I wasn't about to be a failure AND a liar. So I sucked it up, took out a $2000 loan and retook the last class I needed. I truly feel like failing that class was the kick in the ass I needed. I wanted to prove to everyone that I wasn't a failure. So I applied for more jobs, all around the country since I was no longer tied to this job offer in my hometown (which was a great job but I know I would have been unhappy).. And I managed to land my dream job! So now, I'm 1800 miles away from my hometown, I manage a brand new hotel, am engaged to the love of my life, and we even bought our first home together! What I'm saying is- don't wallow in it. And don't feel like you even need to tell everyone in your life. In a few months it will not matter. It's really not as bad as it seems, just a small bump in the road. Keep trucking on. You'll be okay!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 00:25:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dear god those chunky, skunk stripe highlights are the absolute worst, and still incredibly common in my small home town .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cat.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 21:56:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 18:18:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had a medical bill of $2800 go into collections. It was there for probably 5 months before I paid it off in full with interest. I even got a summons in court for it so they could garnish my wages. It did show on my credit report before I paid it, but now that it has been paid off it seems to have disappeared. I have a 778 credit score.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 01:56:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you start any new birth control? Mine grew 2 cup sizes after getting a hormonal iud. All of my curves were amplified and I lost about 10 pounds. My bum got bigger too and my waist stayed about the same. Hormones are weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 21:51:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think, technically, they would be Chaps. Fancy denim chaps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 17:10:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can we mark this post nsfw? A whole lotta (nice) ass just appeared on my computer screen at work .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 00:25:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just mesmerized by the little fuckers . Minion love for life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 21:06:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>They made more room. Facebook ads are so intrusive it's made me never use it . The ads in the middle of videos drive me nuts, and Facebook is all videos now. I do use Messenger. Which now has ads in my list of messages . It's insane.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 21:38:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think this would be more fitting in r/ATBGE . She looks very put together and not trashy imo. Also her body is banging.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 21:49:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vastly underrated show. Canceled way too soon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 19:30:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't understand. I thought people were offended that atheists didn't say "Merry Christmas." (Even though everybody does) Now we're not allowed to celebrate Christmas without offending Jesus? Make up your mind so I can be a heathen in peace.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 19:43:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's probably been absolutely obsessing over telling you and is understandably crushed with your reaction. You just confirmed her worst fears and insecurities. Honestly I really feel for this girl. She was really brave for telling you, and did the right thing by not having sex with you. This will probably make her even more terrified to tell future partners. The worst part about herpes is the stigma. The actual symptoms are negligible for most people. You just made this stigma worse for her. But if really you don't see a future with her, and if it's really for the reasons you mentioned, then you aren't wrong. If it's just because of the herpes and she is an otherwise wonderful person, we enter into a grey area. It's not her fault at all, she deserves love, and you're allowed to say no. Please make sure and tell her she's brave for telling you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 19:57:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a terrible thing to say. He's absolutely allowed to not date her. But I don't think someone who disclosed prior to sex is going to forcibly give it to him. And she described her mother as a sociopath, not herself. She said she felt trapped because she was scared to tell anyone. She was really brave to tell him, she's clearly trying to do the right thing. Giving it to someone without prior knowledge is a horrible thing to do, and is exactly what happened to her. I doubt she would inflict this on someone else. Also he wouldn't be "trapped" if he did decide to keep dating her and contracted the disease, just like she wasn't. People agree to risk these things all the times for partners they love. The worst thing about herpes is the stigma, most people are asymptomatic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 20:07:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I just hope you aren't listening to the insane people saying she will try and give it to you on purpose and to run far far away. I know they say honesty is the best policy, but I wouldn't mention to her that herpes is the catalyst making you end the relationship. Tell her to focus on her other issues. Encourage her to be open and upfront with future partners. I'm guessing you were the first person she told after her ex, and her mental state is probably fragile. I definitely agree she could benefit from therapy. It's a lot of baggage to carry around. Perhaps when she has worked through her issues the two of you can give it another try.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 20:26:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Things, and people especially, are not black and white. She did the right thing by telling him, and she is brave for doing it. She is projecting her insecure feelings about her condition onto him and guilting him. This is wrong, but does not make her a bad person. And is she just supposed to walk up to people and be like, "Hey! I have herpes! Better stay away!" She did it before they had sex or things got too serious. People like you are the reason she was so scared to tell him, and will be scared to tell future partners . You really are a judgyhoofbag.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 20:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're a very mature person! You did the right thing. Keep doing you !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 21:32:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Standard std panels don't test for herpes. Because of its prevalence and relative harmlessness. Unless he specifically asked to be tested for herpes, it wouldn't have made a difference. You could both have it and be asymptomatic and blissfully unaware.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 19:32:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you Billy Fucillo? I didn't think obnoxiously yelling "YUUUUUGEEEE" was a thing outside of northern New York</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 20:16:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is unfortunate he exists outside of ny. Those commercials are the worst.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 06:48:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I audibly gasped when they started going the other way . Very satisfying minus the early ending.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cuddle Buddies</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 09:15:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 21:03:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Find a friend who hunts. My fianc #233; hunts so we have a pretty endless supply of super lean ground meats (deer, elk, wild turkey) It's very tasty when cooked properly !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 21:08:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>My guess is this is a hand painted item. I buy these exact mugs from Dollar tree to paint and give as gifts. And now I know what I will be doing next.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 18:12:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know in sitcoms where the fat husband is trying to go on a diet and the too hot for him wife cooks him "healthy" food that looks godawful? This is what your chicken looks like.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 18:15:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmao this is so petty. I can't afford to travel, so no one else should be able to. Get a travel rewards credit card buddy. That's how most people are paying for those expensive plane tickets.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 19:19:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty sure I do from reading this story. This is the stuff of nightmares.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 21:02:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Routine: condition only with Shea Moisture curl conditioner. Flip upside down and scrunch with old t shirt right when I get out of the shower. Scrunch in a small amount of herbal essences curl gel. Scrunch in larger amount of suave curling mousse. Absorb into hair by scrunching upside down with old t shirt. Diffuse on low setting, right side up til about 40% dry. Flip upside down, spray rusk w8less hair spray and diffuse until about 80% dry. Scrunch out any crunch as soon as it finishes drying naturally. Sounds like a lot but really the entire routine only takes me ten minutes max. My curls used to be much tighter when living in a humid climate. After moving to dry Colorado, I had to discover a new routine as I thought my curls would be flat and sad forever. I recently got a hair cut too which helped immensely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 23:13:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh yeah and if the dog gets too old to control it's bowel movements, just quit your job and throw the whole damn dog away. /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 22:22:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very true. I have insurance, and I just put off going to the doctor for 6 weeks for chronic recurring hives. Finally gave in today after they appeared on the inside of my mouth because I was worried about anaphylaxis. The initial visit where I saw a doctor for five minutes is going to cost me $200. Prescription is going to cost me at least $50. They referred me to an allergist who is going to cost me a lot, I am sure. In 2016 I got appendicitis. We had met our deductible that year because my mother had a hysterectomy (which cost her about $7500) . The cost to me after insurance was $3800. The hospital billing department made an error and sent this to collection and I got sued to garnish my wages. I've since paid it off but still absolutely ridiculous. Fuck me I guess for not wanting to die. My insurance is through my mother and I will lose it in a few months when I turn 26. I'll go on my husbands health insurance presumably when this happens. His company pays for his high deductible health plan for him only. I'm guessing it'll cost us about $400 a month to put me on there. Oh, and when he actually used his insurance recently, it cost him $3000 out of pocket to go to the er And have a few tests done. He found out he will have to have his gall bladder removed ultimately. They recommended doing it as soon as possible. But it's going to cost at least $6000 and we're just not ready to pay that right now. Fuck America.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 18:00:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd hate to see what her house looks like. She seems quite used to ignoring the dog feces on the floor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 01:41:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I also smoke a small amount every night, 2-3 single hits from a bong. I feel as if it's the only thing stopping me from going to a therapist and getting anxiety meds. Honestly I don't see how it is any different from that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 05:07:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That will allow you to tell if the meat is bad. It will not prevent it from going bad in the first place by alerting you if the temp goes above freezing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 16:48:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just replying at the fact that your school is "tiny" with only 160 in your class... My graduating class was 24. This was an average size for our school. 420 total kids from pre-k to seniors.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 16:53:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay for the record after The Obama school lunch program was introduced our school lunches became significantly shittier. We went from lots of different fresh options to pizza every other day. Because pizza was a vegetable. Also ridiculously small portions and no snacks. Oh and they required you to take both a fruit and a vegetable, which I understand, however 90% of those items were just thrown away increasing food waste and costs to the school.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 17:06:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sure the administration is partly to blame. But the increased amounts they had to spend on fruits and vegetables, which almost always ended up in the trash, and the lost revenue from snacks being sold certainly didn't help anyone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MoonMoon does a cuddle</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 19:04:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 19:13:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I'm really glad I know this exists. Instant sub.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 02:26:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my favorite features of my f150 is a lock code on the outside. Never have to worry about locking the keys in the car and I can leave it running and lock it .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>As a rule, precut veggies are much more expensive, but these veggie trays are almost always on sale at my Kroger. $2.50!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 01:42:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 03:08:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Colorado. Definitely not the cheapest state by any means.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 03:09:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Normally they are that much, this was $9 originally. But they are seemingly always crazy marked down. I often get the really large ones for $5 that were originally $15.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 03:49:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine is a City Market.  #65532;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 06:05:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair enough, but the packaging is clear so it's pretty easy to tell if they are going to be bad or not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 06:37:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>God you're so right. I won't eat these raw, but I can cook them into something. I love cherry tomatoes from the garden or some decent grocery varieties. Exploding bites of terrible. I don't know why they are so bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 01:30:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah nudity on Reddit is not the same as creepily asking a stranger for nudes. LOL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 19:43:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Social media. Or a terrible coworker who doesn't shut up about their vacation plans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 18:19:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/madlads</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 19:03:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something about Chuck Tingle not being as weird as him when he's up playing video games at 3am lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 19:12:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Happybara</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 21:10:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm only 45 minutes away from this wolf sanctuary and I am yet to visit. I really want to come pet some wolves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 21:55:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cutthroat Kitchen is also entertaining, as long as you aren't looking for recipes and cooking tips.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Woman gets kicked off of plane for screaming at the mother and baby she was seated next to (video)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 21:17:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Moonmoon and friends</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 18:15:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 21:15:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another question: Do you have a personal vendetta against mailboxes? Mine gets destroyed every year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 21:19:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. My hometown is Alexandria Bay (NY) AKA : A-Bay so this very much confused me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is that a frying pan full of skittles?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 20:42:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 20:54:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>The burner isn #8217;t even on...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 22:44:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get that it #8217;s supposed to be making fun of these exact posts, But the person who posted it did so completely unironically. I suppose that is the real face palm.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hmmm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 17:29:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 01:41:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can order subway online, FYI. Online ordering is bomb.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 04:59:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I once read an askreddit thread about meeting celebrities irl. Many people hinted that Brittany Spears is.. not all there.. Her father has conservatorship over her which is generally only done in pretty extreme circumstances. It was really interesting and slightly depressing to read this about someone who was such an icon growing up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Where to find cute mismatched bridesmaids dresses?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 19:21:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m having such a hard time finding cute mismatched bridesmaids dresses! I want my girls to be able to pick something out that they will wear again that isn #8217;t overly expensive. I like a variety of colors, lengths, styles, patterns, etc but would still like them to look like they sort of belong together. I figure the best way to do this is to order them from the same designer/shop. Anyone know of a shop I could find such a thing? I #8217;ve been looking at some different Etsy sellers but nothing has jumped out at me. Here is an album of inspiration. My dress is at the bottom. https://imgur.com/a/8i2gC Thanks everyone!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 21:16:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Loving the ASOS options so far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Picked up my dress this week and I #8217;m still in love with it!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 01:17:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 01:56:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you !! I have not had it altered at all. Didn #8217;t even think about a bustle. But I #8217;ll surely add one because I don #8217;t want to be tripping over it all night .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My business is no different than someone starting a construction company.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 15:55:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 02:54:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I manage a hotel and have my share of gross stories. But this one made me laugh. The room was relatively clean. They clearly had a lot of fun. https://i.imgur.com/Yty9T5C.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wasn #8217;t sure whether to post this here or on r/trees..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 16:45:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 17:40:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I am being honest with myself I #8217;d probably smoke it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 17:58:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Valid point, but I #8217;d be willing to bet every stoner has smoked plenty of taint-ed weed . This is a new one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 22:24:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yet another reason to say  #8220;Don #8217;t do heroin, kids #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 23:04:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friend sent this to me, so I didn #8217;t know the origin. But I do live in Colorado, and my second thought after seeing this was I bet this was from somewhere around here . My first thought was this is fucking gross. I #8217;m so happy to know that Colorado Big Game Trophy Wook Hunters exists.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 23:33:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you in a legal state? If not, you can #8217;t be positive that your dude #8217;s source did not carry it over the border in that sweet meat pocket .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 08:21:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine says  #8220;I don #8217;t care, do whatever you want! #8221; And then I tell him what I want to do, and he hates it. Mostly just the bridesmaids dresses which I didn #8217;t think he #8217;d even have an opinion on. I must have looked at thousands. But we seem to be much more on the same page lately.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Four Free sets of Address Labels, Today Only at Shutterfly!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 18:41:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Use the promo code GETFOUR . I just got mine and saved $40 bucks, so I figured I'd share the love with Weddit. You'll still need to pay shipping ($5.96) but so worth it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 01:33:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am October 2018 as well! Being able to make your own dress sounds so cool! It #8217;s definitely a different perspective when you de with it daily. I feel as if I am much less organized than many of my clients.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 19:54:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve read a lot of  #8220;What #8217;s your biggest wedding regret? #8221; Threads on here and the number one answer is always  #8220;I wish I would have splurged for the expensive photographer. #8221; You will be looking at these photos for the rest of your life! I say go with your gut. Option two!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 20:28:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg meow wolf looks so cool, this is an awesome idea ! As a guest I would be all about this, even having to pay for myself . Side note- they are currently building a second Meow Wolf in Denver which will be open in 2020. Can #8217;t wait to go check it out!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 20:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m doing brick oven pizza and a taco bar for my reception! My reception is at a brand new rather upscale hotel. The regular wedding menu is super fancy. But since I work there, the chef is customizing the menu for us, and we want tacos and pizza lol . There #8217;s even been talk of a nacho cheese fountain.. Every guest we #8217;ve told so far is super excited about it. I #8217;m excited about it too. I say go for it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 22:21:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>My only living grandmother will likely not be attending. She lives in NYC and we have never been close, and she treats my mother terribly. The wedding is in the Rockies and despite being cleared by her doctors, she says she can #8217;t travel alone. Whatever. I honestly wouldn #8217;t even care but my beloved paternal grandmother passed away last year. She had a huge part in raising me and I #8217;m devastated she wont see me get married. The fact that my other grandmother just isn #8217;t willing to come just makes it even more hurtful. My paternal grandmother would have absolutely been there no matter what :( I learned at my grandmothers funeral last year that before she passed, she created quilts for each of her remaining unmarried grandkids to be given to us at our weddings, so there will be a piece of her there. My great aunt has also promised to be there (paternal grandmas sister) but I #8217;m still just so sad about the whole thing. Writing this post made me tear up. I miss my grandma so much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 03:23:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m so sorry for your loss. It #8217;s so hard .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 23:14:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I #8217;m starting to annoy my friends so I #8217;d love the link!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 01:30:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>What venues did you look at? I #8217;m a Colorado bride as well! Mine is in Buena Vista, where I live. I also work in the industry and am always curious who our competition is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 19:17:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was about 10 years old I was digging in the freezer looking for something to eat. Way in the back of the fridge I find a box of toaster strudels.. fucking score!!! Open it up, and its an ounce of weed. 10 year old me was very confused and disappointed. To this day I still rag on my father for this.. like come on Dad, hide it in a bag of Lima beans or something. Not the toaster strudels!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 20:32:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know you #8217;re being sarcastic but I actually know this girl and she really does have both of those things.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 06:24:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>34f here. I #8217;m so worried about my dress. Right now it #8217;s too small on my chest even tho the stylist ordered a size up to accommodate. Hoping a seamstress can work wonders.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 01:00:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m so sorry this happened to you. You #8217;re a strong person. Your father should be in prison. I know being a scrutinized as a victim is not an easy thing, but he deserves to rot in prison. You should never have to see him again. I hope you reported him. And your family is just as bad for covering it up. Please skip those family gatherings. Fuck those people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 19:17:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Date Twins! I also have two huskies. So I love these a lot! I #8217;ve been thinking about marrying them at the ceremony, but am worried about husky yelling and general mischief. This is such a cute way to include them. Dog tax! They were holding paws last night  #128557; https://i.imgur.com/l1AfFEg.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 19:23:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>We #8217;re going to go to Tomorrowland in the French Alps! I #8217;m so ridiculously excited. FH and I have never been to Europe. We plan to tour around as much as possible after the festival and be gone 2-3 weeks. The wedding is in October, but we won #8217;t go on the honeymoon until March 2019. Worth the wait!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>PSA: Book the extra hotel night before the wedding.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 20:20:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello my lovely wedditors! I am the manager of an upscale boutique hotel. We host a ton of weddings and brides. Often multiple brides in a single weekend. This is a problem I encounter constantly, so I wanted to make this post as a psa (and maybe a tiny bit of a rant) We really appreciate you choosing to spend your special day with us, and understand the importance and gravity. You've worked so hard to get the scheduling and details perfect, and the last thing we want to do is stress you out. If your day of schedule requires you to be able to check in 8 hours before scheduled check in time (3-4pm usually) to be able to get ready (or check out 5 hours late to finish getting ready) you NEED to book the extra hotel day. So many things are out of the hotel's control when it comes to getting the honeymoon suite or similar rooms ready. Many weekends we have one bride on Friday, and another on Saturday. Both are requesting early check ins and late check outs. It is literally impossible for the hotel to accommodate both requests. We will work as hard as humanly possible to accommodate your request, but we need to consider every paying guest. There is simply no way to guarantee that the guests staying the night before won't trash the room and refuse to check out until 1pm. Please, just book the extra night. You will save yourself so much stress and uncertainty the day of. You can even ask the hotel to pay for a half day stay if you don't need the room all night. If you have not done this, please know that there is just no way the hotel can guarantee for you to get in early Saturday morning. It may happen, but the ONLY way to be sure is by booking the night before. I promise you will not regret it. The staff is doing their best, and we really do care that it is your wedding day! The same goes if you are just a wedding guest that needs to get ready before the wedding. The entire wedding often requests early check in, and there is just no way to get every room done early. I know this is often cost prohibitive. So, if you can't swing the second night, you should have a backup plan. I suggest finding a friend who is staying two nights. Thanks for reading! Sincerely, A bride to be and sympathetic hotel worker</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 20:32:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg girl, YES. Constantly. I wrote this after getting a 1 star review from a bride. She showed up and demanded that we let her check out at 2pm so she could get ready, saying another staff member told her it was okay . (no we didn #8217;t but whatever) she booked one night, Friday night. After some back and forth, we allowed her a 2pm checkout. This is a huge stretch for us because our checkin time is 3pm, and the brides getting ready room is always a disaster to clean. 230 pm rolls around and she still hasn #8217;t left. I knock on the door and politely as pie, ask her to please check out as soon as possible. She slammed the door in my face and checked out after 3. According to her review, this incident ruined her wedding. This is an extreme example, but it #8217;s a very common situation. We had another bride coming in that night, who was lovely and very understanding of the delay. Most brides are wonderful. We really do love hosting weddings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 20:33:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>You made the right decision!!! The hotel staff sincerely appreciates you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 20:35:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>If your ceremony/reception is being held at the hotel you will receive preferential treatment. We also greatly prioritize room moves, since you did book two nights. Our general policy for room moves is to allow the person to stay in their first room until the second room is ready to allow for a seamless transition. If you need to leave for the day, just pack up your stuff and the hotel will move it for you. Most places have this policy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 20:37:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are handling this the best way possible!! Your plan seems great, and the hotel will be happy to work with you. You have a backup plan, and seem to be very understanding of the situation. The staff will be very appreciative.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 20:45:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>They will almost certainly move it for you. We book up ridiculously fast on high season weekends, so I alwayyysss suggest two nights to my brides, and for their guests. A heads up would have been smart on their end. Two night stays work out better for both parties.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 20:51:01</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Well I paid for a day, this is ridiculous! #8221; NOOO. No. You paid for a night. Not a 24 hour period. How would you feel if we came into your room at 6am demanding you leave now so other guests can check in?! My daily struggle .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 21:41:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s nothing too crazy and If you check out at a normal time and/or leave a nice tip do not worry. Usually just champagne bottles, flower bits, glitter, dishes, hair everywhere, furniture rearranged, lots of extra trash..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 21:57:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely. Photographers often move furniture, or the bridal party sets up different getting ready spots.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 22:38:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Theoretically yes, but the owner is generally not a fan of responding to any reviews, much to my dismay. The review is, of course, completely one sided and worded to make us look like the bad guys. And she made sure to post it on 7 different sites. We shall see . It just came in this morning and I #8217;m off today.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 23:49:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>99% of our reviews are great, so they generally don #8217;t warrant a response. We usually respond on the case of inaccurate information being presented, but don #8217;t want to be confrontational. It #8217;s not a bad approach.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 02:27:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>These people are everywhere, and it #8217;s not just weddings. A few days ago I let someone know their room was ready three hours early, as per their request. They responded  #8220;well I really thought it would have been sooner. #8221; What more do you want from us?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 18:07:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>if you miss your flight you don #8217;t have to buy a new one. they just put you on standby for the next flight.. Source: I #8217;m a dummy that has missed flights</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 20:39:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can ask, and they might be able to accommodate. But there is just simply no way to guarantee an early check in. An hour before is usually doable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When FH thinks he #8217;s funny</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 18:23:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 18:37:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>He #8217;s more photogenic than I am !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 18:37:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Done: photographer hired, venue(s) picked, catering set up, room block done, lodging done, wedding website done, my dress picked, bridesmaids dress picked, talking to officiants right now, save the dates sent (destination for most people) florist/day of coordinator hired, officiant hired Left to do: hire dj, pick out suits, dress alterations, cake, invitations, rent chairs for ceremony... I #8217;m sure I #8217;m forgetting things but I #8217;m happy to see that my done list is now bigger than my to do list . How are things going for you??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 19:03:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The shooter used to work with my fianc #233;. I #8217;ve had lunch with him. They work on the road so my fianc #233; shared a hotel room with him at one point . This is fucking terrifying. He is definitely schizophrenic. Thought that Taylor Swift was stealing his ideas and writing them into her music. Legitimately stalked her. At one point he hopped the fence at the White House because he wanted to kill Trump. He was incredibly unstable and the fact that he was allowed to buy and keep his guns is so fucked up. I am both shocked and not surprised to read this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 19:07:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know the shooter unfortunately. He is definitely schizophrenic and should have never been allowed to keep his guns. Last year he hopped the fence at the White House because he sincerely believed it was his mission to kill trump. He #8217;s been stalking Taylor Swift and thinks she taps into his phones and steals his ideas. She has a restraining order against him because he used to stand outside of his apartment with an engagement ring he bought from her. The company used to give regular drug testing and he always passed, dude is fucking crazy. He has had his guns, legally, for years . This is definitely a mental health issue and a gun issue</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 19:09:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve also met the shooter. He has serious problems and I can #8217;t say I #8217;m shocked or surprised to read something like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 19:16:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve met him more recently and he absolutely has mental health issues. Dude is schizophrenic and incredibly unstable. Tried to jump the whitehouse fence last year to kill trump, thinks the government and Taylor swift are tapping his phones and stealing his ideas to save the world . My fianc #233; used to have to share a hotel room with him (they worked on the road) and listen to his ramblings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 19:25:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>He hopped the fence at the White House last year because he thought it was his mission to kill Trump. He had no business having guns and this is absolutely a failing of the system. He is definitely schizophrenic. I knew him .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 21:03:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>The police have already been in contact with my fianc #233; #8217;s employers who have informed them. Secret service contacted them last year after the White House incident. He worked for them for about a year until he quit to go stalk Taylor Swift full time. I #8217;m not making that up. He went from ha ha crazy to holy fuck crazy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ROMPERS ARE DANGEROUS</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 18:34:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 19:00:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fianc #233; and I randomly chose our wedding date one day. It worked with our work schedules and the fact we wanted a fall wedding. 10/6/18 . We didn #8217;t tell anyone immediately. Two days later I get a phone call that my beloved grandmother has passed. We fly home for the funeral . I #8217;m devastated, obviously. I want nothing more than my grandmother to still be here and a part of my wedding. Relatives ask us our wedding date at the funeral, we tell them. Turns out the date we picked is my late grandparents anniversary. We had no idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 22:29:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Upvote for palindromantic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 03:39:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>My question too! Looks like a particular Etsy seller I #8217;ve had my eye on for my wedding ring ... Very pretty</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Watch out ladies, this  #8220;nice guy #8221; is about to get ruthless</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 22:26:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>VeryBadass Nice Guy  #8482; puts us all in our place</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 23:04:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 00:08:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh I posted it there too lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 04:37:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>My two huskies who love swimming will only get in the kiddie pool without water in it. Will not get in with any bit of water. It #8217;s so weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 20:13:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg I feel this so hard. My employers are opening up a restaurant and testing out the kitchen and bakery. Just yesterday, there were fresh hot beignets, fresh sourdough bread loaves, fresh sub sandwiches, grilled cheeses, 3 pizzas, all free and amazing . So dangerous.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;ll gladly leave</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 04:26:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Absolutelynotme_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 20:40:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 03:42:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a great idea. Totally stealing. If you still have the doc, I #8217;d love a link to see your formatting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 01:33:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>There were a few bests for me . One was Lance Hawkrider. The other was Sepiroth. Like the final fantasy character. I know that because he was wearing a t shirt when he came in. No last name(or no first name?), on his government Id. This was at a military marriage retreat, meaning there was a Mrs. Sepiroth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Getting engagement photos done today, my florist just sent me this photo of the real flower crown she made me to sample for the wedding!! So excited to put it on my head  #128525;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 18:38:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Our photographer was such a champ. We hiked for two miles at 11,000 foot elevation to get to this spot.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 18:11:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 19:40:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! It #8217;s a trail off of independence pass, near twin lakes. One of my favorite places . There Were wildflowers everywhere! I #8217;m trying so hard not to harass my photographer for more photos ,</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 02:45:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had the honor of fulfilling this one : https://www.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/4ywm1n/happy_to_oblige_sir_dont_test_my_customer_service/?st=JJQENF6A amp;sh=1d918a4d</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 03:05:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amazon! It was like $10 https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07D9GBVG4?ref=yo_pop_ma_swf</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 07:32:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>We planned it together as a gift! He works on the road a lot, and wasn #8217;t super excited about the engagement shoot ( until we were there!) but he was excited about this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Amputees of reddit, what were the circumstances of losing your limb? How did this changed your life?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 16:42:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Full body pants</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 01:42:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me #128695;irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 05:58:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 21:19:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my bridesmaids just dropped on me a few days ago that she doesn #8217;t want to come to the wedding if I invite another good friend of mine. The two in question are former best friends who recently began fighting. I mean, obviously I like one more since she #8217;s a bridesmaid, but I still want the other there. LIKE COME ON ITS MY DAY PLAY NICE FOR ONE DAY FUCK . Luckily, one of my other bridesmaids talked her down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Roses are red, pick up the phone</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 00:20:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 01:59:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was in high school we often had parties where we played quarters. (Same as beer pong, but you play with quarters instead of pong balls) The quarters would always get lost and people would pull out more. In the morning when we were hungover and cleaning we usually found enough to buy a gram of weed to share. Good times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>To buck it or fuck it bucket it ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 02:08:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>My wedding is in 70 days and I still do not have a dj or officiant . For no charge, I am able to use the venue #8217;s sound system. The sound engineer is also volunteering his services to run the equipment, set up, and tear down. The ONLY dj in the area I can find wants to charge me $700 for the day. This seems insane to me!! I #8217;m not saying it #8217;s a worthless service, but I #8217;m basically paying him $100 an hour to push play on his laptop ffs. Does this seem like an unreasonable quote to you guys?? Is it such a horrible idea to just give my sound engineer like $150 to play dj for the night with a playlist?? He is a friend but has no experience. I #8217;m really nervous about making playlists for some reason! As far as an officiant, my fianc #233; has always envisioned one of his childhood friends marrying us. Unfortunately this friend couldn #8217;t commit. Now, he says he can #8217;t see any other friends doing it. But the officiant wants $300. We aren #8217;t religious and it seems like we could just print off a speech on the inter webs and have one of our charismatic friends do it. There are no requirements for officiants in my state. I #8217;d probably have both of these vendors paid already, but neither accepts credit cards and I don #8217;t even own checks lol. Who doesn #8217;t take credit cards these days !! The only benefit to this hugely expensive endeavor has been the number of miles We #8217;ve accumulated. (and I guess being married to the love of my life, and seeing everyone i love in the same room for probably the only time ever will be pretty cool) How did weddings you #8217;ve attended with no professional dj or officiant go ? m so SOO close to throwing both in the fuck it bucket. I need advice! Talk me down!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 02:22:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, id definitely make baseline playlist for him- I #8217;m not trusting enough to just set him free lol, even tho he is a friend. Have you started your playlist already? I #8217;ve always been weirdly self conscious about my music choices so I #8217;m a bit nervous. I #8217;m much less worried about the officiant component.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 02:39:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I definitely see the value in keeping the evening moving, but we are skipping most of the traditional stuff anyway.. I #8217;ve just always been weirdly self conscious about my music choices? Like I hate being the one to play music during parties and in the car because I think everyone will hate it. It #8217;s probably silly but I am so nervous!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 03:32:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is an incredibly helpful perspective. I think the biggest thing I am struggling with is the lack of choice in my area. If I were getting multiple quotes that I could compare, reviews, etc, then it would be a lot easier to justify spending the $700 to know I #8217;m getting someone good. But I can only find this one dude! I #8217;ve tried fb marketplace, google, etc and no luck .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 03:34:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not doing any of those things. But you make a very good point and music and the overall party atmosphere is important to me. Did your $890 include the equipment, or was it just the dj service? I am struggling with the lack of choice in my area. I have only Been able to find this one dude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 01:18:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have mixed feelings about this. And I think we might have the same last name! My go to response when people comment on how pale I am is to tell them  #8220;I #8217;m so white it #8217;s my last name #8221; and I #8217;m kinda sad I can #8217;t use that joke anymore lol. I #8217;m also moving from W to G (are you me?) and I wanna give our kids the front of alphabet advantage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 01:47:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>So rude!! Also an event manager here. I #8217;m never scared to tell the dj that the open bar is not for him and the bride most certainly didn #8217;t include him in her final count.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 03:23:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Etnies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 20:26:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a beautiful Derp.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 08:21:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>There #8217;s no official registration for service animals. As a business, you are only only allowed to ask two questions.  #8220;Is your dog a service animal? What tasks has the dog been trained to perform? #8221; You are right on support animals. They are currently allowed on airplanes, but not protected under the ada like service animals.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I mailed my invitations three days ago with instructions to RSVP on our knot wedding website. Today, the knot's website is down?!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 20:25:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it just me or is everyone's the knot wedding website having issues?!?! Why Today?!?! AHHHHHHHHhhhHHHHhhhHHHHHH</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 20:30:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay it's back up working again. Exiting panic mode now. Someone's trying to give me a heart attack today.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 20:39:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no! Is yours back up again too?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 01:31:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>This sub has taught me that finding an adorable and affordable wedding dress is very possible. Etsy, preownedweddingdresses.com, thrift stores are all your friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 01:36:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you feel like sharing your dress? I #8217;d love to see, but only if you #8217;re comfortable. I #8217;m sure it looks beautiful on you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 02:15:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got my bridesmaids dresses and engagement dress from Lulus for under 60 each and have been super happy with both!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 04:24:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Middle school dance classics Get Low- lil John Ignition remix - r kelly Hey ya- OutKast Lose control - Missy Elliot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 04:28:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was a beautiful dress but I #8217;m so happy that you are getting what you want!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 06:44:29</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Don #8217;t look at me with that tone of voice. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 06:58:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Several years ago, the company I work for hired a young girl . She was clearly troubled, and not a great employee. After missing some work, she confided in her supervisor that she was gang raped at church camp and had taken it to trial, and lost. Her supervisor then proceeded to tell the office manager. Upon hearing this, the office manager told every male employee in the company to  #8220;Stay away from X or she will accuse you of rape. #8221; I have never lost respect for someone so quickly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 17:48:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus Christ fuck that lady* office manager is female, which almost makes it worse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 19:23:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm obsessed with this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Accessory help? Is this too much floral? I #8217;ll also have a bouquet</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 18:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 18:04:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The shoes have already been purchased. And the flower crown is a definite. the photo is from the trial I did . I really love the shawl but am worried it will be too much floral. I haven #8217;t bought it yet. Thoughts? Thank you weddit!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 19:40:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you might be right! I think I will look for a simpler, sheer shawl.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 21:14:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Posh mark! They are vera wang shoes, never worn, they were $28 on posh mark and I think $60 originally.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 23:31:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fall and no theme</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 20:36:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I despise the r/frugal wedding circle jerk. According to that sub, anyone who spends more than $1000 on theirs is a vapid materialistic shrew, and definitely will cheat on their husband. (They also seem to think that only women want weddings and no man has ever cared to have one) I agree it's not smart to take on a large amount of debt for your wedding, but it's like they think it's impossible that anyone can afford things they want. They assume everyone who has a wedding with a decent budget with be in debt forever, never afford a down payment on a house, etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 00:19:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>The bridesmaid and groomsmen outfits. My original plan was to let my bridesmaids pick mismatched, patterned dresses. FH was not having that. Insisted that I pick matching solid color dresses. My suggestion for the groomsmen was to keep them casual, button up and whatever dress pants they already owned. Nope - FH wants them in matching suits. The other thing was doing a first look. I work in the wedding industry, and always suggest my couples do them so they can enjoy cocktail hour. But, it's very important to FH that the first time he sees me is when I walk down the aisle. This one surprised me and made my heart happy! We are doing a two hour cocktail hour with lawn games and open bar so we can get all our photos and enjoy time with our guests.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 00:22:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg. Mine too. He's even gone so far as researching fountains to purchase and give to the venue, because they do not have one. We are having a taco bar tho, so I kinda want it too! Queso is bomb!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 02:14:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I lost it at cold lentils. R/frugal is utterly obsessed with lentils</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 01:33:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m allergic to regular condoms. Still used them. They make non latex ones.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 02:02:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait.. so you #8217;re telling me that since my work email is logged onto the gmail app on my personal phone, my employers have the ability to wipe my entire phone remotely? How is this possible?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dog lost after fatal Jeep rollover is reunited with owner after three weeks. [video]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 05:15:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Finally finished my biggest diy- Ceremony backdrop!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 15:20:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ceremony backdrop for my wedding, made out of a set of elk antler sheds my fianc #233; found</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 15:44:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 16:23:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! My fianc #233; found the set of elk antler sheds, which I think makes it extra special!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 17:43:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I did not crochet the doilies. I bought them off of Etsy and attached them to wrapped wooden hoops. I was initially inspired by a post from another wedditor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 22:58:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Correct- disclaimer - I did not crochet the doilies myself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 22:58:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, I #8217;m not that talented! I bought them from Etsy and attached them to wrapped wooden hoops</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>