<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7801</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I need to stay away for ~ 2 months. Recommend me a tier 2/3 city to stay</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 07:06:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because of few personal issues I would like to stay away from my family and current city. I work remote. My requirements are 1. Ready accomodation like the ones I can find in Hyderabad and Chennai\- Executve Men's Hostel where food/laundry/internet access is taken care of 2. Access to Airport \(reasonably near\), though not a high priority 3. Preferably in Southern India \(Orissa is okay\) The following are my current choices 1. Trichy 2. Coimbatore 3. Palakkad 4. Gokarna 5. Bhubaneswar I am leaning towards Coimbatore and Bhubaneswar. Any other place that you can suggest? EDIT: Are executive men's hostels available in Bhubaneswar? I did a bit of googling and in Coimbatore they seem to be available. I've been to Bhubaneswar couple of times and would be totally good for it. EDIT 2 : I want to run away from hustle and bustle of city life and still be connected to the world. Coimbatore seems to be a good choice. I've been to Mysore couple of times and I feel that IT crowd has screwed it up. Can any of you ping someone from Bhubaneswar to provide insight on the city? EDIT 3: Thanks for all your suggestions guys. I've made my decision to move to Bhubaneswar. I am planing to leave for it tomorrow. One of the reasons for my decision is Puri, Konark and Satapada that are nearby. I absolutely adore these places. A beach that's very nearby, easy access to weed and Chilka Lake made my decision. If I like, I might even nest and lay eggs there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 07:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not even India. Try again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 08:19:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. I like the sound of it. Can you speak of my first requirement in Pondy?  gt; Executve Men's Hostel where food/laundry/internet access is taken care of</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 08:21:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. Internet connection and easy and quick access to nearby cities and preferably Airport is a requirement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 11:02:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright. Coimbatore is on the top of the list. I just hope someone can comment on Bhubaneswar. I need to make this decision by tomorrow evening</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 11:46:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I am dammed eager to know about Bhubaneswar. Are you from Odissa or familiar with the city? In general,I am a hard guy, used to rough life. I've never complained about summers while most of my friends and family members do. So you say executive Men's hostels are a thing in BBS? I did see couple of ads on magicbricks. But they never mention availability of internet. Anyway, I will call them up and talk to them directly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 12:23:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I made my decision to go to Bhubaneswar. A good beach at Puri, Chilka Lake at Satapada and easy access to weed made my decision. Will be traveling tomorrow evening.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 12:41:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for your recommendation. This time around I've made decision to go Bhubaneswar. I am in process of booking my ticket for tomorrow or the day after. As I mentioned, a beach to relax near by at Puri and a beautiful Chilka lake at Satapada and easy access to weed has made my decision.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 12:41:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for your recommendation. This time around I've made decision to go Bhubaneswar. I am in process of booking my ticket for tomorrow or the day after. As I mentioned, a beach to relax near by at Puri and a beautiful Chilka lake at Satapada and easy access to weed has made my decision.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 13:13:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I might need some help. I will PM you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 13:59:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am okay with the budget. But I've already chosen to go Bhubaneswar the day after tomorrow; I am going to book my tickets tomorrow on Tatkal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 15:06:46</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;not everyone hates women That's what you chose to read into it. I am just careful about them. And you've written a lot of stuff. Noice. Good day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How the fuck do you subscribe?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 06:48:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where is the fucking button that I can click and subscribe? Do I have to use RES, turn off the theme and uncheck sub theme and THEN find the fucking button? If you really like Shri Ram, show me where the button is!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 07:00:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shriram hates you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Falling ...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 07:13:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 07:17:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I need to use RES right? The browser I use will not allow any extensions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 09:38:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>No I am not. Will you take me as your sishya and turn me into Brian Laura of Bakchodi?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Joke for Karma] Boss wants to have sex with secretary</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 10:56:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>A boss said to his secretary "I want to have sex with you. I will make it very fast. I'll throw $1000 on the floor; by the time you bend down to pick it, I'll be done." --- The rest of the joke is in the comment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 10:57:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>#Boss wants to have sex with secretary A boss said to his secretary "I want to have sex with you. I will make it very fast. I'll throw $1000 on the floor; by the time you bend down to pick it, I'll be done." She thought for a moment, then called her boyfriend and told him the story. Her boyfriend then said "Ask him for $2000, pick up the money very fast; he won't even have enough time to undress himself." So she agrees. Half an hour goes by, and the boyfriend decides to call his girlfriend. He asks, "What happened?" She responds, "The bastard used COINS! I'm still picking and he is still fucking!" --- Upvote and liberate me from 'low karma account'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 11:05:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>#Two terrorists having discussion in a bar. The bartender asks them what their discussion was about. Terrorist 1: We're planning to kill 14,000 people and a donkey. Bartender: Why a donkey? Terrorist 2: See? I told you no one would care about the 14,000 people. --- Upvote and liberate me from 'low karma account'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 11:07:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>#Where are you going to get the Lawyer? An Engineer dies and goes to hell. He's hot and miserable, so he decides to take action. The A/C has been busted for a long time, so he fixes it. Things cool down quickly. The moving walkway motor jammed, so he un jams it. People can get from place to place more easily. The TV was grainy and unclear, so he fixes the connection to the Satellite dish and now they get hundreds of high def channels. One day, God decides to look down on Hell to see how his grand design is working out and notices that everyone is happy and enjoying umbrella drinks. He asks the Devil what's going on? The Devil replies, "Things are great down here since you sent us that engineer." "What?? An engineer? I didn't send you one of those, that must have been a mistake. Send him back up right this minute." The Devil responds, "No way! We are going to keep our engineer. We like this guy." God demands, "If you don't send him to me immediately, I'll sue!" The Devil laughs. "Where are you going to get a lawyer?" --- Upvote and liberate me from 'low karma account'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 11:11:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>#A new priest at his first mass was so nervous he could hardly speak. After mass he asked the bishop how he had done. The bishop replied, 'When I am worried about getting nervous on the pulpit, I put a glass of vodka next to the water glass. If I start to get nervous, I take a sip.' So next Sunday he took the bishop's advice. At the beginning of the sermon, he got nervous and took a drink. He proceeded to talk up a storm. Upon his return to his office after the mass, he found the following note on the door: 1. Sip the vodka, don't gulp. 2. There are 10 commandments, not 12. 3. There are 12 disciples, not 10. 4. Jesus was consecrated, not constipated. 5. Jacob wagered his donkey, he did not bet his ass. 6. We do not refer to Jesus Christ as the late J.C. 7. The Father, Son, and Holy Ghost are not referred to as Big Daddy, Junior and the spook. 8. David slew Goliath; he did not kick the shit out of him. 9. When David was hit by a rock and was knocked off his donkey, don't say he was stoned off his ass. 10. We do not refer to the cross as the 'Big T.' 11. When Jesus broke the bread at the last supper he said, 'Take this and eat it for it is my body.' He did not say 'Eat me'. 12. The Virgin Mary is not called 'Mary with the Cherry.' 13. The recommended grace before a meal is not: Rub-A-Dub-Dub thanks for the grub, Yeah God. 14. Next Sunday there will be a taffy pulling contest at St. Peter's not a peter pulling contest at St. Taffy's. --- Upvote and liberate me from 'low karma account'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 11:14:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>#Is Google a boy or a girl ? Google is a Girl because it won't let you complete the whole sentence and starts guessing, suggesting and you ask only one question, but get hundreds of irrelevant answers in seconds... Additionally Google constantly wants to know your location --- Upvote and liberate me from 'low karma account'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 11:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>#People go through 3 phases A family is at the dinner table. The son asks the father,  #8220;Dad, how many kinds of boobs are there? #8221; The father, surprised, answers,  #8220;Well, son, a woman goes through three phases. In her 20s, a woman #8217;s breasts are like melons, round and firm. In her 30s and 40s, they are like pears, still nice, hanging a bit. After 50, they are like onions. #8221;  #8220;Onions? #8221; the son asks.  #8220;Yes. You see them and they make you cry. #8221; This infuriated his wife and daughter. The daughter asks,  #8220;Mom, how many different kinds of willies are there? #8221; The mother smiles and says,  #8220;Well, dear, a man goes through three phases also. In his 20s, his willy is like an oak tree, mighty and hard. In his 30s and 40s, it #8217;s like a birch, flexible but reliable. After his 50s, it #8217;s like a Christmas tree. #8221;  #8220;A Christmas tree? #8221; the daughter asks. Yes, dead from the root up and the balls are just for decoration. --- Upvote and liberate me from 'low karma account'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Going over the edge</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 15:38:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 05:01:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don't have to worry about spreading MGTOW. Women will do that job everywhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The way the clocks align to make the time</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 05:10:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>She always bounces back</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 05:26:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mera Bharat Mahan</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 06:24:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is the qty I use per joint. Is it too low?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 11:35:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 11:37:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not used to making joints. Usually smoke in Chillum which unfortunately broke. So, is the amount I usually use (may be little less too) per session. Puts me in a high for ~4 hours, though I usually smoke before going to bed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Recommend me smoking method (Pipe/Chillum/Bong)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 11:50:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been smoking using a Chillum (clay) which unfortunately broke. I am not adept of making joints and I suck at it. Looking for alternative ways. I searched through the sub and found few recommendations by earlier folks 1. Recommendation for 8-inch chillum / 12-inch glass bong [here](https://np.reddit.com/r/IndianEnts/comments/8majcd/can_anyone_help_me_with_ordering_a_nice_simple/) 2. Another [positive review](https://np.reddit.com/r/IndianEnts/comments/5pbzfo/if_you_smoke_in_a_small_bong_change_asap_pic/) on larger bong 3. Another one has good things to say about a [glass pipe](https://np.reddit.com/r/IndianEnts/comments/65aawa/how_come_no_one_in_india_uses_glass_pipes/). Though one of them says it's harsh on his throat. May I know what's special about glass that could give sore throat that say clay chillum wound't? My preferences are 1. Preferably portable 2. Not too expensive (~ 700 max ) 3. Reasonably easy to clean. Chillum, Pipe and portable bongs seems to fit my requirement. Can any of you that are more experienced give me recommendation. And possibly some cons that I may have to be aware of such a recommendation. Also I've seen little goa mentioned a lot. So can any of you provide links of your recommendation from [littegoa](http://www.littlegoa.com/pages/bongs/pgid-1176870.aspx)? EDIT: I just saw a [video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0sfk70FV3gA) comparing smaller bongs with a big one. According to this reviewer, (a) Small bongs have a con that you can't take big gulps of smoke at one go (is that a rif?) (b) Larger bong smoke is a lot harsher, though not sure why. Also, I am not quite sure what this contraption called a bong. From wikipedia, I gather the following  gt;To get fresh air into the bong and harvest the last remaining smoke, a hole known as the "carburator", simply "hole", somewhere on the lower part of the bong above water level, is first kept covered during the smoking process, then opened to allow the smoke to be drawn into the respiratory system. So in short, you close the "carburator" hole when weed is burning and open it when inhaling. This process will hold the smoke until you inhale. Is my understanding correct?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Watch me dance!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 12:03:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 12:33:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am just happy that there is no one to nag me. You seek your answers elsewhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 12:43:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like to know more about anonymous support systems. Something like first aid for mental health / depression/border line suicidal. Few years ago I was low and visited a psychiatrist (or shrink) and that guy made me depressed and borderline suicidal. When I was at the most difficult of my life, asshole blamed me and made my situation worse. And I had to pay for the ordeal. Man! There is no fucking thread to hang on. The thin like men will have to walk and there is an abyss on either side to devour you. Support systems are practically non-existent,</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 12:47:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey thanks for the answer. Yes, I had to discover to cut the paper size. I made another [post requesting for recommendations](https://www.reddit.com/r/IndianEnts/comments/8x0g74/recommend_me_smoking_method_pipechillumbong/) for pipes and bongs. I am kind of newbie so looking for guidance on selection. Well, infact, I didn't even know what a bong is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 13:05:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is what I gather from [wikipedia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gravity_bong). Nah man I don't think that's appetizing to my eyes. Can you please check my other [post](https://www.reddit.com/r/IndianEnts/comments/8x0g74/recommend_me_smoking_method_pipechillumbong/) requesting for recommendations?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 14:00:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>God that's a lot of information. Newbie here. Will take sometime to process and understand many of the terms. I just saw some video that recommended a glass bong. Yes, I've just now come to know vapourizer goodness but at the moment, it's off the budget. Anyway, the chillum I was using was gifted to me at the place where I purchased my weed. It looked quite ornate and beautiful. Apart from aesthetics, it was a bit cumbersome to smoke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 14:04:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow that's a beauty. I think I am going to place the order. Regarding cleaning, I guess any alcohol can be used right? Commonly available iso-propyl alcohol can be used right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 14:38:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whew! Never thought I could find one on Amazon. I thought they would be illegal to sell and littlegoa guys must be doing some trick to sell online. Anyway the amazon product you've recommended has few reviews at the bottom and that got be a bit concerned  gt;The black color comes from the insides being coated with some paint. I had to burn it off completely before using it. Its transparent now, but atleast its not toxic. Thanks for pointing it out.  gt;And get a mesh screen to fit at the bottom of the bowl so that you don't get any stray ashy bits into your mouth when taking a hit. Does a regular cheese cloth do? Or is it one of the accessories that I can find? Too many questions!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 14:41:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, I just found a video [review of a portable bong](https://youtu.be/t4cjczCI0QU?t=606) (along with time offset). This one actually looks really fun. I mean freaking FUN! I'd like to hear what you would think of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 14:43:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, I just found a video [review of a portable bong](https://youtu.be/t4cjczCI0QU?t=606) (along with time offset). This one actually looks really fun. I mean freaking FUN! I'd like to hear what you would think of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 05:35:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a repost. Posted just a day ago [here](https://np.reddit.com/r/SweatyPalms/comments/8wq7if/balls_of_steel/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>View from top of Lakhta Center (under construction), Saint Petersberg</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 05:38:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 06:11:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's my weed + some keef as an additive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 06:20:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seesh! This sub is scary.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 06:22:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Repost. You can find the [previous post](https://np.reddit.com/r/SweatyPalms/comments/8x6pdc/hitting_a_dart_with_a_golf_club/) few links down</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 06:27:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I am forcibly put there, I'd shit even if I am on white pants.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 06:30:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boy don't ask for sources. Breaks the rules!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Now you try this!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 08:35:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Now it's your turn</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 08:46:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Help in selecting a Bong (Metier 8-inch Glass Ice Bong)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 09:43:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am a newbie started using weed recently, mostly out of health recommendation from friends. It is helping with my sleep and mood/depression. I've used few Benzos on recommendation of doctors but it has gotten worse over a period of time. And specially horrible withdrawal symptoms. Last two weeks since I started using were good. Really really good. The first time I smoked, I slept like a baby. So seems to be working really good. I hope we legalize weed so that more research could be carried out for it's potential benefits; and importantly accessibility and improvements of quality. Anyway, I'd like to make my smoking more pleasant and I am looking forward to buying a small bong to begin with. This [video review](https://youtu.be/t4cjczCI0QU?t=606) of large/small sized bongs made me want to try a smaller one. Also I don't know what this device called bong so this [video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4VG03oq1Mxg) makes the function of Bong clear. I am thinking of purchasing ["Metier 8-inch Glass Ice Bong"](https://www.amazon.in/Metier-8-inch-Glass-Bong-Black/dp/B01AUUSXMG/). Does anyone have an opinion on this? Also, I don't understand many of the terms used by folks on this sub. What's a shooter in a bong? (google tells me its something to do with the pipe that connects to the 'cup' that holds weed. Don't know it's use). Another term used is **percolator**. I am not sure what is this and what to do with it. There is some information on [this](https://herb.co/marijuana/news/what-are-percolators-and-how-do-they-help/) page but it just looks like pipe. I don't know whats the difference between shooter and percolator. So, help with the terms and opinion on portable bong I found on Amazon. EDIT: I found a good [guide on what is a Percolator](http://stonerpros.com/bong-perc-guide/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 10:06:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is an[ overwhelming evidence from Genetics](http://humanorigins.si.edu/evidence/genetics) that we evolved from great apes that are common ancestors to Chimpanzees and Homo sapiens. For example, ~ ~~99~~% 98% of DNA of Humans are similar to chimps. Chimps have 48 chromosomes and humans have 46. It so happens that [two of the chimps chromosomes](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chimpanzee_genome_project#Starting_the_chimpanzee_genome_project) have fused in Humans and we've found where and how. There were also evidence that early humans were able to mate with a kind of chimps. I've read this a long ago and don't have source to cite at the moment. Also, we all of us humans have come from Africa. There is a genetic evidence for it too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 11:48:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey thanks for your very helpful series of posts on edibles. Where I stay now, I don' have oven with me but a Pan. According to your instructions, I should do the following 1. Moist the weed 2. Put the weed on hot pan and until I can sense the smell of weed (not sure what this is though!) 3. Cool it down and add coconut oil. Organic compounds dissolve is oils/solvents right? I think I could use other oil as well? 4. Filter out the residue and collect the oil. Use this oil for cooking purpose I have another question. Can't we put weed in hot oil and then cool it down and filter it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 12:02:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>After searching, I've found an [older post](https://np.reddit.com/r/IndianEnts/comments/4so68s/how_to_properly_make_cannabis_edibles_for/) on how to decarb in just a saucepan without oven. I think I can follow these instructions. According to these instructions, I will need to heat weed in oil for 30-45 minutes until I see bubbles coming. Then drain the oil and use for cooking. Am I correct in my understanding?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 13:19:18</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;when it engages in its pseudo philosophy it #8217;s usually lacking What? Example please?  gt; It #8217;s all about the interpretation of experiments and thats never treated rationally just experimentally Whew! I can't make sense of what you say anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 13:47:04</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Most of the mysteries of quantum mechanics and special relativity and the speed of light Special relativity and speed of light don't have any mysteries; they have been experimentally proved beyond any doubt. Quantum mechanics appear mysterious for those that don't work in Quantum mechanics. Well quantum mechanics is actually completely experimental i.e. how particles are behaving at sub atomic level; the only problem is trying to come up with an explanation that makes experimental results understandable. The current theory is quite robust beyond a resonable doubt unless you are talking beyond weak forces.  gt;How does purposeless matter produced something as purposeful as mind? That's a VERY big question. Yes, science doesn't have an answer. If science don't have it, it's NOT debatable that none have it. I think I'll leave it. Doesn't look like there could be any fruitful discussion. Peace!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>/r/AskMen want nothing to do with women that call themselves Feminists. And /r/AskFeminists loose their mind.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 10:39:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here is the [archived thread](http://archive.is/AcRBD). Few excerpts from the thread are pasted below. If reddit overlords want to start banning subs, they've got lot of banning to do. Anyway feminists are going apeshit [here](http://archive.is/Hh5Lf). Always use archive.is links guys! --- Having feminist core values is fine and most men, even mras and anti feminists will (mostly) agree with them. But as soon as a woman uses the label as a self descriptor and sees that as part of her identity I instantly will nope the fuck outa there like my hair was on fire. It means something totally different, it means you're likely searching for conflict and injustice in everything and take yourself far too seriously to have open and fun communication. --- If "patriarchy" and "Mansplaining" are in your everyday vocabulary I nope the hell out of there. Unattractive. --- Most people are, by the definition of  #8220;feminist #8221;, feminist I.e. support gender equality in the eyes of the law and in all things reasonable where gender could possibly play a role. People who  #8220;proudly announce they are feminist #8221; are usually a whole different animal. They are typically not for gender equality at all and, in my experience, are trying to speak a revenge fantasy into existence. They don #8217;t love equality, they hate men. --- Equality in the law? Sure. Social equality? Sure. Equal/Fair Pay? Yes. No more sexual harassment? Definitely. Patriarchy/men is the root of all the world's problems? Nah. Saying you are for gender equality, but performing the opposite in word and action? Nah. Using your sex/gender to wholly invalidate someone else's opinion on sex/gender? Nah. Feminism holding a monopoly on treating women with respect? Nah. Being a feminist as a necessary label for being a humanist? Nah. I don't think there's necessarily anything wrong with being a feminist. I do have some concern when you feel the need to shout it to the world, as if it's some oppressed ideology in the liberal first-world countries (where most of them reside ironically). Look, I'm just trying to eat my sandwich and figure out the rest of my short stressful complicated meaningless life. I don't need someone blathering in my ear about how the angle between my pelvis and knees is somehow reinforcing female oppression. --- If they are proudly announcing it, it means they play the identity politics game. They are people I would not want to be involved with as friendship or relationship. --- Generally people who find it that necessary to announce their beliefs on anything, completely out of context are bad news. I put some mums in the same category. They have a kid and every sentence out of their mouths begins with  #8220;as a mother #8221;. I have no problem with mother #8217;s, but when it #8217;s your sole identity then I lose the desire to listen. --- Annoying. Telling me you #8217;re a feminist doesn #8217;t do anything. It doesn #8217;t make me aware, it doesn #8217;t offer any understanding of your views. It #8217;s like they #8217;re doing it because it #8217;s the trendy thing to be not because it actually matters to them. Your actions will show me you #8217;re a feminist, you don #8217;t have to tell me every other sentence. The whole point of a movement is to educate people on the cause, not point out you #8217;re a part of it. --- I think feminism is anti-male. I don't really care if random people do it, but someone I would be a little wary with someone I know or someone I want to know because I'm not interested in feminist activism or feminist man-shaming nagging being a regular part of my life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 10:48:36</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;In the spirit of full disclosure my personal opinion is that there should be fewer posts of higher quality of a good balance of topics, with a low tolerance for repetitive posts (within the same 24 hours) and confusing or dreadfully inciting posts. As for what makes a  #8216;good post #8217; my opinion is I'd agree. I think we should partition the sub and reroute all the memes etc to say another sub MGTOWMemes and /r/WhereAreAllTheGoodMen , or other subs. I also think we should have tagging/flairing system to indicate the type of post (Personal Story/Divorce/Dodged the bullet/ etc).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>There was a post on a woman who cheated on boyfriend to sleep with her rapist to 'get back the power' While we find it bizarre, /r/Bluepill thinks that's "natural" ! WTF</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 11:11:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometime ago, there was a post : [Whore thinks she was raped when she was just cheating on her boyfriend](https://np.reddit.com/r/MGTOW/comments/8vg9qv/whore_thinks_she_was_raped_when_she_was_just/). And this shocked the sensitive sensibilities of our dear /r/TheBluePill ers and they go on to tell their own tales that are identical. WTF is wrong with this gender. A woman willingly sleeping with her so called 'rapist' is a way of taking back the power from him? This is #NUTS! ###NUTS!! #####NUTS ######NUTS ######FUCKING ***NUTS*** Bluepill [drama here](http://archive.is/KCMCR)  gt;I've known a few survivors who thought or fantasized about getting a Do-Over, of sorts. I don't have numbers but I'm going to guess few actually make it happen but it's no doubt interesting to read from someone who did. ... This comment is messing with my head. Baby don't do this to me  gt;I did. It was a strange thing for me: like, I was angry and hurt at what had happened (the tl;dr of that is "no vaginal penetration because I hate it and vaginismus", and there was vaginal penetration. I froze and don't remember much because I was in a lot of pain), but as this person was my friend, I was not yet ready to call it "rape", despite it clearly being so.  gt;**Trying to sleep with him again was "proving" to myself that it was consensual.** ... And this one gave me schizophrenia. She's cooked up a complicated story and a reason **why it makes sense** to sleep with the guy who raped. Bitch, there is a much simpler and straight reason : He is your rapist who slept with you while you didn't want to. I don't expect you go back and sleep with him again.  gt;People can more easily understand a black-and-white scenario (punching someone in the face is assault), then moving to a grayer area (is boxing assault? No, because of consent. But breaking the rules of boxing is assault, even in a boxing match, because broken consent). As for the redo, I've found that talking about "revenge" plots is a stepping stone: people get that if you got beat up by someone, you might want to fight them again to "win" against them. If someone hurts you, sometimes you want to "re-do" that encounter, so you can feel like you undid the hurt. Maybe those tactics appeal to you or could be helpful in finding a way that makes sense for you to talk about it when you want to. I just don't know what to make of this at all. How is it possible that they are human. How is it possible that they have almost the same size of brain as men have and still come up with twisted reasons and answers for to justify something that's so obviously they say they are harmed by it. I'd probably give them a pass if it's say 20% of a man's brain.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 11:22:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are useful in their own way. We could either tag/flair them. Or those that want to post can create another sub mgtow memes and post there. We call it a sister sub and include it in our side bar. I just note that there exists a sub /r/MGTOWmemes where we could direct that traffic there. Also there is another sub /r/WhereAreAllTheGoodMen with a lot of overlap of posts on memes/tinder stories. We could redirect those post there. We can have /r/WhereAreAllTheGoodMen as our sister sub and listed in the bar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 11:22:36</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;They are useful in their own way. We could either tag/flair them. Or those that want to post can create another sub mgtow memes and post there. We call it a sister sub and include it in our side bar.  gt;I just note that there exists a sub /r/MGTOWmemes where we could direct that traffic there.  gt;Also there is another sub /r/WhereAreAllTheGoodMen with a lot of overlap of posts on memes/tinder stories. We could redirect those post there. We can have /r/WhereAreAllTheGoodMen as our sister sub and listed in the bar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 11:26:11</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; where a rape victim will reenact a rape scene to deal with it You don't say! Are you kidding? If you've got stabbed and have PTSD. Are you going to enact the stabbing again to get out of it. I DON'T WANT TO LIVE ANYMORE. SOMEBODY KILL ME.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 11:27:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're doing good. I'd help you if you are on the wheel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 11:29:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd say NO to any censorship apart from adherence to the rules which I think are just fine. Only violence inciting posts should be moderated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 11:31:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, I get you. Think of it this way - making changes to the functioning of the sub and NOT becoming authoritarian. For example filters by flair is also a change. And anyway OP's suggestion that some debates to be removed was overwhelmingly downvoted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 11:44:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. But they should be directed to /r/WhereAreAllTheGoodMen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 11:53:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know at the moment. But I can know how to do it. It's a CSS/JavaScript. Shouldn't be difficult at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 12:01:06</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; True. But not dangerous. Haven't you heard of [Black Widows](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WEgol8UstaY)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 12:53:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be a moderation nightmare. This exactly is one of the reasons why I recommended high volume 'meme' posts can be redirected to /r/MGTOWmemes. That sub could use some volume and it will also reduce the burden on your moderation. Look, there are other subs that also has similar content and they have their moderators. Let them take that burden. That will free our sub. I'd be okay if subscription count take a hit though in this process.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 13:03:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't moderate either. Can you check for this feature when you read through moderation guide 1. Every post MUST have a flair/tag. We will not accept posts that don't have a tag 2. Now the user creates a post with a flair 3. All posts that have a tag "MGTOW Meme" will immediately be removed and poster will receive a message "Please post it to /r/MGTOWmemes" Similarly, if you check out posts of /r/WhereAreAllTheGoodMen , there is a significant number of posts that have a "regular" format of the headline. We could craft a regular expression that will detect that template and redirect to post on that sub. I am nearly sure that this tool should be available as a moderator. Else, we could craft a custom bot for the sub and deploy. I could do that - no problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 13:11:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only one problem though. Stefan Molyneux talks a lot. He likes to hear his own voice. I'd like to listen to his guests as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 13:12:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>No problem. Let's do it on our time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 04:35:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would doubt the mental capacity of anyone who says they are for equality. Inequality is the medium through which the progress of society express itself. When you want to run faster than the motherfucker to the left of you, you are wanting to create an inequality with him that is advantages to you. Standardised testing is a barometer of how unequal students are on the measure tested. Of what use is a test where everyone scores equal? Shut this crap here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 04:47:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who else thinks that this sub can get scary</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Feminism summarized very well</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 06:46:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 06:59:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/Gifsthatendtoosoon. What happened next? I WANT THE STORY!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 16:08:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, why bother about [partition of integers](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Partition_\(number_theory\)).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 18:43:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>USE archive.is links. DON'T directly link to threads in other subs for god's sake!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 19:32:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus in which world is the title "X-post from r/india" is name of any food?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 22:21:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>It wasn't locked when I made the previous comment. Guys from here must have followed the link and that might have forced them to lock. This will be construed as brigading and it qualifies the sub to be quarantined. If we have enough of such direct links posted we are on the radar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 22:53:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why the hell anyone feel the need to announce their gender online? You claim you are a woman and I can't verify that. Why make that useless information public? Why the fuck won't start talking about what you want to talk instead of asking if women are allowed to talk? Didn't you know that no one would know if you have a vagaina unless you said you have it? Drama bitch here. Nothing to see here. Not that I am willing to see anything if something is shown given a billion+ videos I could watch on a random porn site right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 23:00:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would hurt you more if I want to. Drama bitches aren't worth anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 10:34:03</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; shalyachikitsa Lungi here and learning hindi. I didn't understand only this word.  #2311; #2360; #2325; #2366;  #2357; #2367; #2359; #2351;  #2325; #2381; #2351; #2366;  #2361; #2376; ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 10:37:22</DATE>
    <TEXT> #2361; #2350;  #2325; #2367; #2360; #2367;  #2325; #2375;  #2360; #2366; #2341;  #2348; #2376; #2336; #2325; #2375;  #2350; #2342; #2367; #2352; #2366;  #2319; #2357; #2306;  #2349; #2366; #2306; #2327;  #2346; #2367; #2325; #2375;  #2342; #2379; #2360; #2381; #2340; #2368;  #2348; #2344; #2340; #2375; #2361; #2376; Lungi here. Is my sentence correct?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 10:44:59</DATE>
    <TEXT> #2361; #2350;  #2351; #2379; #2327; #2367;  #2325; #2379;  #2346; #2360; #2306; #2342;  #2344; #2361; #2368; #2306;  #2325; #2352; #2340; #2375;  #2361; #2376;.  #2319; #2325; #2342; #2350;  #2327; #2369; #2306; #2337; #2366;  #2332; #2376; #2360; #2366;  #2342; #2368; #2326; #2340; #2366;  #2361; #2376; #2404;  #2348; #2366; #2340;  #2349; #2368;  #2313; #2360; #2368;  #2340; #2352; #2361;  #2325; #2352; #2340; #2366;  #2361; #2376;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 11:02:21</DATE>
    <TEXT> #2350; #2375; #2352; #2368;  #2326; #2381; #2351; #2366; #2354;  #2350; #2375; #2306;  #2343; #2352; #2350;  #2324; #2352;  #2352; #2366; #2332; #2344; #2368; #2340; #2367;  #2342; #2379; #2344; #2379; #2306;  #2325; #2379;  #2309; #2354; #2327;  #2352; #2326; #2344; #2366;  #2330; #2366; #2361; #2367; #2319;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 11:05:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the time you need to make yourselves knowledgeable about different types of rapes. --- Raping Without Touching: Here is a short list of some of the most common forms of non-tactile rape which is perpetrated by ALL men and which is suffered by ALL women every day of their lives (no exceptions). Verbal rape (type 1) - if he speaks to her. Smile rape (type 1) - if he smiles at her. Smile rape (type 2) - if she smiles at him (he #8217;s cute) and he refuses to smile back at her - you guessed it, that #8217;s rape. Thought rape (type 1) if he imagines raping her, then that #8217;s rape. Thought rape (type 2) If he imagines having consensual sex with her, that #8217;s also rape because she didn #8217;t consent to him thinking about having consensual sex with her. Denial rape - if he is in a relationship with her and refuses to have sex with her, that is also rape. Thought rape (type 3) if he imagines that someone else might have consensual sex with her (see thought rape by proxy). Verbal rape (type 2) - if he talks to someone else about her - yeah, that #8217;s rape too. Eye rape (type 1) - if he looks at her with the intention to make her feel uncomfortable. Eye rape (type 2) - if he looks at her without any intentions at all and she interprets it as bad intentions. Oh man, that is so rape! Eye rape (type 3) - if he glances at her briefly with indifference and she takes offense - honestly, didn #8217;t you know that was rape? Eye rape (type 4) - if he is looking at something beside her and she interprets it as his attempt to look at her. Of course, that #8217;s rape. Eye rape (type 5) - if she stares at him because she thinks he #8217;s cute, and he refuses to return eye contact - that #8217;s just so rapey. Non-verbal rape (type 1) - if he deliberately refuses to talk to her because he want #8217;s to give her the cold shoulder. Yup, rape. Non-verbal rape (type 2) - if he fails to talk to her (and he #8217;s cute) because he doesn #8217;t notice her because she #8217;s not his type. Double rape! Non-ocular eye rape - when a blind man unknowingly points his head in her general direction giving the impression that he might be looking at her (if he could see) #8230;RAPE!!!!!! Olfactory rape (type 1) - if he does not wear deodorant - yup, rape. Olfactory rape (type 2) - if he wears cologne and she doesn #8217;t like it - rape again. Olfactory rape (type 3) - if he #8217;s cute and she wears perfume and he refuses to say something nice to her about how she smells. Triple rape. Refusing to give up your seat on a crowded bus rape - the mother of all rapes! Thought rape (type 4) - when a cute guy refuses to think about her because he is not in physical proximity to her and he is busy hitting on another women. Do I even need to remind you that that #8217;s rape? and the worst one of all: Rape Via Ignorance - when a man who is not in her physical presence, doesn #8217;t know her, has never even heard of her (and may even be in a different country), refuses to think about her as  #8220;a whole person #8221; worthy of having a relationship with despite never having met her - that #8217;s rape - and worst of all, you #8217;re probably doing it Right Now to thousands of women you don #8217;t even know! You shitlord!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 12:05:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is just script though. Can't talk with any degree of fluency. I'll need to think of a sentence in english and then do a mental lookup for words, try to assemble them with the grammar of my mother tongue and expect it to come out correctly. Too much effort at this age! Whew!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 12:06:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh it is Shalya-Chikitsa.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 12:12:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh! I would love to watch another round of meltdown of ekta kapoor on twitter. I am going to message him and hope he does it again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 12:13:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. That's an nice encouragement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 12:32:57</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; But lungis need to know their place Alright. I am out of here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Question about addiction to weed</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 13:03:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Though I have read online a lot that weed is not as addictive (physical) as Tobacco and other opiates, I have reasons to be cautious and a bit scared. So I would like to know your practical opinion about how addictive can weed get, how to manage the dose so that I don't get addicted etc. A little background. I am a newbie trying out smoking weed on advice of few of my friends in US for my lack of sleep, depression, mood swings. I was under treatment with two different psychiatrists and they have given me with various SSRIs/SNRI drugs. However they had adverse affects on quality of my life and performance at work. Finally the medication became untenable and I stopped taking medication. And that was a nightmare. Withdrawal symptoms were extremely severe. I had to visit the doc again to help me off the medication. It took me 2-3 months to become sane again. In this context, I have had my friends in US to give weed a try. So here I am. And I have reasons to be really scared to travel down the path of drug dependence again. However, I've noticed a remarkable difference between the communities that are on benzos (like me) and those that smoke pot. The later group are extremely chill, usually very happy and quite content. I mean, you can watch any random video of any guy who is smoking pot you would see them extremely happy and joyful. If you don't understand what I am saying, just go on any forum that are discussing the side affects of clonazepam, withdrawal effects, general quality of life - they are all miserable. So that's sounds good. Now, I smoke 2-3 times a week and use little over 1.5 g per session. I smoke only at night after meal when I do. If I were to be addicted, I don't know what my recourse is. Possession of cannabis is illegal. I don't know if I can approach doctors for help. I don't know if and when I do approach, would law enforcement get involved. Damm! I really wish I have some expert medico guiding me. I'd pay dam handsome money to him to help me through this, watch me over, walk me through baby steps. So my question is where is my support? As of now, my family members are happy to see me doing well for last 3 weeks. According to them, it's at least few years that they have seen me this well. My moter-mouth mother infact told couple of her friends in the neighborhood that I am smoking weed. That's another headache I don't know where would it lead to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 13:39:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what I didn't do. I went off the meds cold turkey and then had to go to the doc again to reduce the dose gradually. But my question is can I get addicted to weed? Suppose I run into a problem that requires medical attention can I/should I disclose that I smoke weed. Would there be any repercussions if I do. Today I am fine. Suppose few weeks later I have some issues with my mental health/sleep/mood swings can I approach doctor. Would I have to reveal my practice of smoking weed? Look here is my situation in nutshell: I have problems with quality of my life and two years of medication with good psychiatrists didn't yield much help. Now I am smoking weed and I am on my own. I am scared of it. I want to be 'guided'. I hope I am able to convey. It's a kind of helplessness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 13:46:32</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; And benzo's gt; gt; gt; gt; gt;weed for anxiety. Oh is it. Thinking back, yes it did relive me for a while. But then, the doctor increased the dose slightly. Slowly I my mind became extremely cloudy and couldn't function well in office environment. I had to call it quits to keep my job. As of now, weed seems to be doing well. My family members are quire appreciative of how I am.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 13:48:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks a lot. To me, and to my family members this is indeed a welcome change. I just wished I had a doctor to oversee me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 13:51:45</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; My question is that in smoking whatever lil pot you smoked. Did it help? Oh yeah! It's a miracle drug for me. The first night I smoked, I slept like a baby. The next morning I woke up with such freshness that cried with joy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 14:03:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks man! That helps. Another question. If I were to be given an anesthetic for any surgery would the weed consumption affect it? I mean, will I have problems having an anesthetic when needed?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 14:12:20</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; What you are doing is looking for a physician/ psychologist / expert to give you assurance. Now that i read about your past medicine use it think this is normal and i think it is kind off mental block. You are just looking for hope. Yes that exactly is right. It's very similar to walking on a slacky rope and no safety net staring right into the abyss. What worried me is there are some posters here using drugs (benzos) that nearly destroyed me recreationally. There was a post on Heroin usage as well. That added lot of anxiety. I just hope I will be okay. I just want to live well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 03:51:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could get doxxed if you are the only guy who is living around your neighbourhood that has MGTOW lifestyle. I strongly believe you should not draw any unwanted attention towards you. MGTOW will grow at its own pace and don't worry about that. Women and feminists are the greatest drivers to MGTOW.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 03:58:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool. Just a caution.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 04:05:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not that way. I mean people can notice someone in the neighbourhood that is living a MGTOW lifestyle and if he is the only one around then they may have reasons to come to conclusion that this guy is the one. May be if there more than one they may not. Aside, I will tell you what would be fun. When you turn on WiFi you see bunch of SSID that are all MGTOW.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 06:48:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Put in all the parameters in this [function](http://patentimages.storage.googleapis.com/WO2005010218A1/imgf000014_0001.png). Positive value is a good indication that the woman is good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This rock</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 07:11:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This rock (x-post from /r/OddlyErotic)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 07:22:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 07:29:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright. Ban me. I am not going to visit this sub anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 08:19:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey,I think you are referring to me. I am the guy who stopped taking medications all of a sudden. I'd like to explain my end of the story. Many folks here are lot more knowledgeable than I. They have reasons to acquire that knowledge. A typical joe on the street like me is just happy to drink cough syrup and experience cough subside. Or take Gelusil and have a relief in stomach. No one would look into the chemical composition of those tablets (one exception I found was one of my uncle though). Anyway, I was being treated with a certain dosage of clonozopam and lately there was an increase in dosage. That made me extremely drowsy, stone headed and unable to be functional. I've got a job to keep and I don't have the luxury to battle side effects ad nauseam for months to no end. And there are deadlines and deliveries to catch up with. On one day, I knew if I did take the meds, I would screw something up, miss the deadline, put the project in jeopardy, put team members at risk and possibly get fired subsequently. So I had to stop. And what came after that was monstrous. TBH, folks here are probably are more confident than I believe they should be in benzo drugs. I believe there is lot of variation in how individual is affected by the medication that is not captured adequately by medical profession **as yet**; perhaps things would change as time goes by. But look at the what I have to endure - endless experimentation, acute tolerance for drugs that are ***known*** to have quite scary consequences and a life to live. You could express your anger calling me a bastard. But I don't really know what else I could do. It really isn't a straight line. Have taking drugs been better than not taking them, yes absolutely. But they fall short of giving a reasonable quality of functional life. Anyway, I am really looking forward to having a great life with weed. It's been good so far. Actually very good so far. What I am missing is a prescription from a well educated doctor. Oh boy! you've no idea how empowered you'd feel by a prescription from a doctor and a pharmacy that would sell you the cure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 09:21:17</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; All in all, it one of the safest drugs you can use so you should not be scared to use it, Thank you. That does give me an enormous confidence. I really appreciate your response. I'd post my queries in following weeks and I'd be honored with your guidance. I cannot stress how much I am dependent on the support and advice I receive online. To give you a sense, two weeks ago, my father said -"I hope you know what you are using" and I put up a very confident face and gave an emphatic yes. But you folks know I am just stumbling in dark trying to find my way around. Thanks again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 09:26:00</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;So 4 of us were chilling in a drive smoking a few joints and listening to music when suddenly a cop car stops So you want to drive back home high on weed? And you don't think that's a problem? Jesus!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 09:41:04</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Here's my PUA handbook for free. Save your money, travel the world or your hobbies, DGAF about the opinions of parasites and snake oil salesmen, break most rules, if you want to, talk to women about mundane and boring things, and you'll be surprised that the women are coming to you and asking you out. Then fuck or walk, no one cares but you. I'd recommend walk. I'd pay you $19.95 for this free advice on patreon just to rub it in face of Mr.PUA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 10:33:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am that guy. I write about my struggles and the effort [here](https://np.reddit.com/r/IndianEnts/comments/8y8rrg/question_about_addiction_to_weed/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 12:10:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look, I might sound preachy but do listen. I ain't your enemy. You could harm yourselves if you choose to. But when you drive under influence, you are putting others at risk. Please don't do that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Falling down ...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 05:24:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Koreans are doing something WTF with mud. No idea what!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 05:42:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Good morning view</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 05:53:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bait and Switch</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 05:55:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bait and Switch</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 05:56:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How did this happen?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 06:07:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Erotica, environment friendly version</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 06:32:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:55:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of them has [123 cats](https://youtu.be/GdMIUYqochI?t=554)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 09:53:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey check out my [post here](https://www.reddit.com/r/IndianEnts/comments/8y8rrg/question_about_addiction_to_weed/). See the struggles I had to endure and how careful I am. DON'T self medicate. That too drugs like Ketamine that is employed as a secondary anesthetic by an experienced medic. 1. You don't know what dosage to adminster 2. You don't know how to handle any side affects 3. You don't know the quality of drug you are getting 4. You don't know how to use it over a period of time. Since you say you suffer from depression one time use isn't what you are looking for. 5. You don't know if this WILL actually treat your depression, the primary problem. You might catch secondary problems in addition to the primary problem that you have. 6. It will be HARD on people that love you. When you get sick they are the people that you will be depending on for support and you are taxing them in doing so. If you are completely independent and don't involve other people in your health and sickness you have right to use or abuse your body the way you choose. Otherwise, please consider including your people in your quest for treatment. Okay, let me try it something else. I've had similar problems and I have had two Psychiatrists treat me. They have primarily used benzodiazepine drugs for treatment. Do note that these are the drugs that have been clinically tested, in legitimate use medically for years all over the world and have been deemed safe for administration by a specialist. Are we good till now? I've used such kind of drugs prescribed by a specialist, purchased at pharmacy, with support of my family and people around me. And that includes partially my professional team mates as well. **Still**, fucking ***still***, it didn't help me. I've had problem with dosages with an expert (one of the best in my city) prescribing them. It interfered with the quality of life and eventually my professional life as well until I had to call it quits. No, I am not blaming my doctor at all; he did as much as he could and I'd still recommend him that need his help. Please learn to respect doctors and their expertise. So you, probably a novice, handling a drug which probably isn't meant for your condition (i.e. depression), think that you could treat yourselves and get out of it unscathed? Look, I've seen other people on this sub that are lot more knowledgeable, probably academically trained that MAY be are more qualified to use the drugs responsibly. Just because they happen to post their experiences, don't think you could do the same.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 10:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Guys stay away from this one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 10:32:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>You a medico? Kindly let people know self medication is dangerous. And importantly this guy claims depression and isn't a recreational user; he needs continuous treatment. Guide him correctly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hoop Skills</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 10:42:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 11:56:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are violating no sourcing rule. I strongly encourage you to delete your comment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 12:39:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, I am not sure if I understand what you are saying. I've just viewed some videos on psychedelic experiences of some prominent figures. It does look and sound promising. OP is looking for treatment for depression. I nor anyone on this forum can take responsibility for handling drugs that he doesn't understand. If you do know, it's ***you*** know. I am not sure if your experience is transferable via informal and non-precise information that we can share here. I am just worrying out loud. And I do believe I have reasons to be worried.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 12:46:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. Did you read my post in full? Do you understand that I have best interests of OP. If you pick my brain, you'd know that I'd have your best interests as well. Question: Why did you feel the need to downvote my carefully thought out response to OP? Am I giving him a harmful suggestion? Am I distracting him from his need? Did you for any reason think that my response will take away any value from his life? Or did you think that your suggestion as I quote below  gt;remember, dont take anaesthetic dosages. take enough within 10 minutes till you feel yourself dying or slipping away is lot safer than mine? Tell me why did you downvote?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 13:37:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know man. I think my doc is a very reasonable person and I think he helped me as much as he could. He treated me for ~ 1.5 years and it lead to scary drug dependency. I am finally out of using benzos and trying my luck with cannabis. So far it's going well. My family members tell me that I am doing very well and are happy about it. I would just be happy if some doctor oversees my cannabis usage. I don't know how much to take - too less or too much. Would there be any side effects - what can I do? Should I change my diet? I'd just need a prescription from doctor. That'd help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 13:43:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also if you are a doctor or have access to a good one, I'd like to know if I am doing right. It's just scary to treat yourselves with only help from an anonymous forum where people may or may not know things that should know. Or any doctor that can offer treatment minus use of benzodiazepines or cannabis. I'd pay well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 14:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never thought I'd actually go and upvote a thread in TwoX. You made me do it. You sneaky bastard, take an upvote.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 14:56:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>archive for win</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 04:21:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>How about I don't know what the hell do I know what other person has in her head, what the other person want do do, can do and willing to do. So guarding my ass is something I can do while trusting others what they might/could do is something I have no control over. I don't know about you but people in my neck of woods don't go with a sealed^TM sticker pasted on their foreheads written "Trustworthy". And attempt to discover who is and who isn't is itself not safe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 04:25:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>What you are saying is "paranoid". If women have that much to fear, they'd remain closed doors and NOT on Tinder advertising themselves to be available to meet strangers on internet at their places and be physically intimate. I don't see any of that "paranoid" on these dating sites. Where are they? eh!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 04:32:54</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; discriminate against women in the workplace and prevent them from getting career opportunities. Her career opportunities should be her concern; not mine, not your's not other men and not anyone else. Why should the entire world be obliged to help this woman for her career advancement? Not my woman, not my career, not in my interest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 04:35:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>In real life there is no way to know which of these "some women" you have as your peer. It's in a man's best interest to assume "some women" is equivalent to "every woman". A man is entitled to take measures to save his own ass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 04:41:49</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; The truth is, believe me or not, you don't have to be a mindreader to learn flags.  gt;  gt; It isn't impossible. It is a **skill**, that with effort is learned. You aren't getting my point. You are assuming that this skill that you are referring to is **precise** like a mathematical formula. Now you'd say there are nuances. And I'd say these nuances **could** become a problem and there is no insurance against those problems.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 04:48:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen you use this word "discrimination" with abandon. Tell me, if I see a problem exclusively from a gender, why shouldn't I discriminate ? Yes go ahead and throw that gender discrimination lawsuit. It's like a rock and a hardplace. I'd rather defend the lawsuit (and it's very easy to do for the situation at hand)and keep my job rather than have false sexual assault and face economic death penalty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 05:05:16</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; gt; His policy protects him and the company #8217;s interests from any potential lie.  gt;  gt; So a small risk is worth a discrimination suit? That makes no sense. Given in this specific situation, go ahead and file a discrimination suit. And see how quickly it gets kicked out of the window. It's lot easier and cheaper to field possible discrimination suits than sexual harassment claims. In case of later, the entire social media plays mob justice even when there is an acquittal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>NASA has just confirmed this man's balls are visible from space #65279;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 05:13:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Collection of excerpts from a thread on #MeToo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 06:00:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Recently there was a thread on TwoX by a woman who felt that she was at a loosing end because her boss refused to be with her behind close doors for fear or being metoo'ed. The post is [here](https://archive.fo/GdArQ). Of all the comments in that post, there were a few that have personal experiences/anecdotes that might indicate the direction we are headed to. And I am really beginning to think gender segregation isn't that bad after all. Each of us have our own "spaces" (hate to use that word!) in which we know and understand how to communicate to the other. Here are the [excerpts](https://imgur.com/a/aVXeb7w)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 06:08:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've responded to you in the same vein as your comment. The problem is how you are viewing the situation as. You are boxing it in 'discrimination' while it isn't so. You are trying to see discrimination whereever you can and be enraged about it. Good luck with that and high blood pressure that accompanies what that rage. The boss is trying to take measures that he can to keep himself out of a potential risk. You might have had a different approach to deal with it; but that's **your** approach. You can't demand everyone else take measures as you would. To answer the other question if there were situations in which I'am constantly reading in news that few (just a ***few***) black people have tried to stab white men when there are behind closed doors, then I'd perfectly avoid them being close doors. Well, you'd re-label it as discrimination and raise an 'outrage'. Btw, I am brown, not that it matters to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 06:14:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>No problem. You are talking as if women already don't discriminate. Look, see how men are protecting themselves. This MeToo movement isn't that a big one as yet. Really very few incidences that are reported. But chances of that happening and cost of that risk being extremely high, most of men, including me simply want women off our radar. If harassment women face, as you say is actually true to the extent you say it happens, I'd see more women protecting themselves just like men are doing. Instead, I see them on Tinder ready to meet strangers on internet and get intimate with them. Instead I see them turn in numbers whenever there is a frat party and free drinks. I'd think you are just exaggerating the extent of harassment OR women care much less than men of the said harassment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 06:15:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright. File a lawsuit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 06:20:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bye baby</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 06:25:55</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; read below link https://www.bbc.com/news/health-43753073 You seriously want to self medicate for your depression based on BBC news article? Or may be many other articles that you probably will bring up. You think you understand how to cure yourselves? Sigh!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just get a Dog!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 06:45:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Last evening I had some weird experience smoking weed</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 09:02:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Tldr**: **Had slightly more weed than I regularly have and this gave me initial extreme high that's not very pleasant but the rest of the night was well and woke up fresh as a kitten**. This is the [quantity of weed](https://i.imgur.com/ki7Hbca.jpg) I've used for yesterday evening dose. This looks like it's slightly more than what I've been having in last two weeks. Experience was, let's say not exactly pleasant, in comparison to alcohol. I'd like to know if this is something you can identify with? Within 2 minutes, it hit very high. It's like someone possessed me completely and I seem to be powerless. Next, Extreme hunger. Never experienced that kind of strong hunger. Reading the posts here, I make sure that I have food with me (infact it's my regular dinner). But this time around, the hunger is so extreme that I didn't want to touch food. I don't know how can I explain it. I just lied down on a mat. I've started experiencing strange temperature differences around my body - it's simultaneously pleasantly cool and pleasantly warm. But I didn't feel like my body is in my control anymore. If someone could chop my hand I don't feel it would have hurt me. Next, I with my eyes closed, I felt that my head is on a spindle and I am downward spiral in a whirlpool. This state continued for ~ 10 minutes. I could barely get up after that and still stumbling heavily, I was back at my desk. At this moment, I have just enough control over my limbs and have my dinner. Like every other time, food always tastes lot better when I am high on weed. Drinking water is also a such a pleasure , tastes so goddamed good and fills with satisfaction. Watched a movie for ~ half hour. This time around it's like watching in multi-dimensional space. I'd go into the skin of the character currently on the screen and feel them, understand their dialogues as if they were mine, adorn their mood and react to the other characters themselves. At times, I was all of those characters and all of the crowd on the street. I could feel the cold breeze glaze past the face of the heroine when she's standing on the culvert waiting for someone. This is quite an experience. And I feel like I've watched myself going through these detached, standing apart. And then I walked down the stairs really carefully, stumbling all the way down to my room. I went into a deep sleep. Woke up to a pleasant sound of my alarm at 4:30 AM completely fresh. But, honestly, I really didn't enjoy the top high I've experienced. Is there anyway I could reduce this or avoid? Also any suggestions on controlling the quantity would help. EDIT 1: 1. Regarding the weed be spiked, I am sure that it isn't. I've collected it directly on the farm. 2. And just saying that it is spiked isn't informative. Can you add more details on the substances that weed is usually contaminated with? 3. I've already had a sample of weed sent to my colleague's chem lab to test for amphetamines, opiods. I'd get a report within 3-4 days unless he needs Raman spectroscopy done which could delay the results slightly depending on availability of equipment. EDIT 2: Not many people have responded. Man, most of the posts here are showing off the pics of their loot for the day as if that's a pinnacle of achievement. Not many write about the actual experiences one has with weed so that we could compare. Anyway, few months ago [someone has posted about their experiences](https://np.reddit.com/r/IndianEnts/comments/83v1ea/serious_has_anyone_ever_had_a_panic_attack/) that are similar to mine and I can identify with. I am sick of the responses "oh this is spiked".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 09:47:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. I am sure it isn't spiked. I collected this directly from the grower.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 09:49:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm. Did you see any suggestion here or elsewhere that men should make out with dogs? Curious. OTOH, I have seen women that are into knotting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 10:02:06</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; or example, take 6-10 drags from a J and just give it a couple minutes to kick in Well, with me, 3 medium deep drags are all it takes. If you check my comment history, I am using it for medication for sleeplessness, mood swings and borderline depression (not yet!). Previous medication by Psychiatrist sent me on path to benzo addiction and I struggled to wean it off. So, I am very worried about anything I take. Also, I am not under medical supervision for smoking weed. That's why I am checking out with others how their experiences were. Given that I am confident on my product (I've collected directly from farm in bulk), are my experiences commensurate with the ones of Psychonauts community? Or is it at odds with it? If so, what are the measures I need to take. So these are the questions I have. I've been using for ~ 3+ weeks and is doing me good as of now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 10:03:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>C'mon man. Chill. It's a beautiful dog that has lot of love to give. Give yourselves a big smile. Isn't it lovely!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 10:19:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also I keep hearing about spiked a lot around here. I've had my friends in the US caution me about it because of which I had to hunt a lot to get to a farm where I could directly buy. What exactly is (or are) the substance(s) that usually weed is spiked with? If there are two different substances A and B with which weed could be spiked, then are you saying irrespective of what A and B are the effects they induce are identical? I'd like to hear more about what do you mean by "spiked" instead of just that word. I mean, details. I have access to chemistry nuts who could get it tested for me in their ultra-sophisticated labs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 10:20:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dogs are tools? GET OFF MY LAWN! I don't want to see on my street again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 10:34:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you explain more? I've asked[ this question](https://old.reddit.com/r/IndianEnts/comments/8yzyn6/last_evening_i_had_some_weird_experience_smoking/e2f2zqu/) to other commenter</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 10:47:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm. So you know the experience between pure weed and a spiked one? Suppose I'd smoked pure one how different would my experience been? Also, just saying the word 'spiked' isn't really giving me any additional information. It'd be helpful if you could give me more details - possible contaminants etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 12:34:49</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; You don't find safe people over night. You work your way from safer to safer to safer until you start to find people who are safe--- and learn how to be safe person for other people to be around as well. I might be willing to go through all this process to 'start finding people who are safe' if I am looking for a partner. Do you,for a moment think that in work environment you will get opportunity to do this kind of exploration? If I am looking for a partner, I'd do my study, vet the person thoroughly before I choose to allow within my boundaries. In work environment, you are obliged to work with people whoever that are thrown at you. You live with that 5-6 years of progress. I am not even interested in seeing those societal progression meters. I just want to get work done and live my life away from any chaos. Nah! leave me alone. I am fine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 12:54:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, I was going through some of the posts of other ent subs and [I found this thread that has something to say about THC and anesthetics](https://np.reddit.com/r/eldertrees/comments/8ucaqn/im_currently_in_disagreement_with_my_doctor_and/). You might find it interesting. Here are few excerpts  gt;It is well known that marijuana reacts poorly with general anesthesia preventing the anesthesia from working properly. You could wake up mid surgery, which is very dangerous. Especially if the anesthetics are still having a lingering affect, it could be confusing, traumatic or dangerous. ...  gt;Definitely, cannabis can impact anesthesia, even as just a metabolite. That being said, I think it really depends on what sort of anesthesia they are using. When I was knocked out for my wisdom teeth removal, they only asked me to refrain from smoking weed the day before and for a few days after. When I had my appendix out, there wasn't really time for me to go a few weeks without smoking. They ended up pushing my surgery back about a day to give more time for the THC to be out of my system, and the anesthesiologist mentioned that between the THC and my Reynaud's Sydrome, she was using a different cocktail than usual for an appendectomy. ...  gt;I had an anesthesiologist tell me I would be fine as long as I wasn't currently under the influence. They asked me about a bunch of different drugs as well but I think it's pretty logical that Crystal meth would mess with an anesthetic. My doctor gave me the "cannabis might effect it so better safe then sorry" speech so I would think 2 weeks is a bit extreme but don't smoke the day of.  gt;I'm a crane operator though so what the fuck do I know. ...  gt;**I woke up during spinal surgery, I now have PTSD. Trust me buddy you do not want this in any way.** ...  gt;Also, THC is fat soluble so itll stay in your fatty tissue and some organs to be slowly metabolized.  gt;Listen to your doctor and dont smoke for the few weeks before surgery. Dont mess with general anesthesia because when things go wrong it gets really bad.  gt;Take those few weeks as a T break man! ...  gt;I recently had minor surgery so I quit smoking for 24 hours (their recommendation). They gave me proprofol (the sleeping drug that Michael Jackson died from) and it knocked me out. Afterwards my wife drove me home.  gt;When I got home I took a hit on a reefer for the pain, and man it was horrible - a big mistake. I figured most of the proprofol had worn off, but nope, I almost passed out.  gt;I used to be skeptical like you, but sometimes the doctors are right about drug interactions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>IMPORTANT: How smoking Cannabis interfere with anesthetics when you require surgery</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 13:01:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello All, As I was going through many of the posts here, I did notice certain kind of recklessness in substance usage. Here is [thread that discusses how continuous usage of Cannabis can mess up anesthesia](https://np.reddit.com/r/eldertrees/comments/8ucaqn/im_currently_in_disagreement_with_my_doctor_and/) when you need surgery. Imagine a situation where you meet with an accident and require surgery immediately. The following are few excerpts of the thread I mentioned how it could affect you. **Be Cautious** brothers!  gt;It is well known that marijuana reacts poorly with general anesthesia preventing the anesthesia from working properly. You could wake up mid surgery, which is very dangerous. Especially if the anesthetics are still having a lingering affect, it could be confusing, traumatic or dangerous. ...  gt;Definitely, cannabis can impact anesthesia, even as just a metabolite. That being said, I think it really depends on what sort of anesthesia they are using. When I was knocked out for my wisdom teeth removal, they only asked me to refrain from smoking weed the day before and for a few days after. When I had my appendix out, there wasn't really time for me to go a few weeks without smoking. They ended up pushing my surgery back about a day to give more time for the THC to be out of my system, and the anesthesiologist mentioned that between the THC and my Reynaud's Sydrome, she was using a different cocktail than usual for an appendectomy. ...  gt;I had an anesthesiologist tell me I would be fine as long as I wasn't currently under the influence. They asked me about a bunch of different drugs as well but I think it's pretty logical that Crystal meth would mess with an anesthetic. My doctor gave me the "cannabis might effect it so better safe then sorry" speech so I would think 2 weeks is a bit extreme but don't smoke the day of.  gt;I'm a crane operator though so what the fuck do I know. ...  gt;**I woke up during spinal surgery, I now have PTSD. Trust me buddy you do not want this in any way.** ...  gt;Also, THC is fat soluble so itll stay in your fatty tissue and some organs to be slowly metabolized.  gt;Listen to your doctor and dont smoke for the few weeks before surgery. Dont mess with general anesthesia because when things go wrong it gets really bad.  gt;Take those few weeks as a T break man! ...  gt;I recently had minor surgery so I quit smoking for 24 hours (their recommendation). They gave me proprofol (the sleeping drug that Michael Jackson died from) and it knocked me out. Afterwards my wife drove me home.  gt;When I got home I took a hit on a reefer for the pain, and man it was horrible - a big mistake. I figured most of the proprofol had worn off, but nope, I almost passed out.  gt;I used to be skeptical like you, but sometimes the doctors are right about drug interactions. Also you could read this : [Is Smoking Cannabis Before or After Surgery Safe?](https://www.leafly.com/news/health/smoking-marijuana-before-or-after-surgery)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 15:25:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey do you mix weed with alcohol? I see advices all around not to mix weed with other substances.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 17:43:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need to talk to me next morning. Am over the top now. Just want to buzz now. Women will fuck you up. Later</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Chilling out</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 02:12:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 06:42:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh yeah. I will ignore the divorce rape of my cousin(s), my neighbors, my friends, my coworkers and their destruction piece by piece live in front of my eyes AND read a blog (a fucking blog, an opinion piece) and that too by a woman and go 'geez I should tie myself up right now!". Noice! (read that in british accent) You do sound like a woman. You sure would advocate marriage. It would benefit you it if it works and also if it doesn't. And advice from a woman advocating marriage is .. how should i put it .. - "A conflict of interest". Nah! I just want sex. That'll do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 06:51:07</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; But I also have a hard time with assuming all women are vicious gold diggers How do you know which one isn't. They don't go about with stickers on their foreheads "Certified Golddigger^TM". And by the time you discover it's too late, under the bus, getting crushed. It's better to assume worst in women and then discover that your precious little one isn't THAN assume everyone is a little precious and get fucked in the end.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 07:02:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you get triggered? Did you cry?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 06:53:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>He just read a page in her book</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 08:20:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometimes I find it strange and unbelievable that people here celebrate a piece of flower that they managed to purchase in some corner of the city. And other stranger things are messages if anyone else in their city is on this forsaken sub. I am a newbie, never been a significant smoker nor drinker NEVER once thought I would (oh gosh!) smoke pot. I've managed to buy in bulk right on the edge of a farm that would keep me going for months to no end. It's a marijuana nation out there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 08:39:46</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; remember we fought one time and she started hitting her stomach. Then, a month later, we found she had a miscarriage WTF! There is a complete online guide on how you should prepare yourselves for divorce so that you come out of it unscathed or with minimal damages. Not an American. I'll let other people guide you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 10:51:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't use tobacco at all. I have never come across a recommendation to use tobacco. Am I missing something?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 11:01:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The problem is I don't see any reports - well written and detailed on this sub to be able to compare and contrast with what a canonical experience should be. All I see is boys going over the top for just being able to procure weed underground and proudly displaying their loot. So, I've gone through other subs and experiences and found that my experience is actually quite a norm. It also happens that these experiences can differ wildly from individual to individual. For example one non-scientific inference that I can draw is weed 'accentuates the mood' that you are currently in. If you are introspective, man, it takes you to deep into your life, back into far past, pick up episodes and show you what you are naked, strip away from any cover or niceties. Not very unlike the descriptions you find when you take DMT. Well, I was doing this exploration because the 'quick answer' the weed is bad doesn't hold with me. I purchased it directly on the farm. Also you don't really have descriptions of experiences that you can compare your's.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 11:06:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh yes, I do experience problems with smooth burn. I've just thought that's how it is supposed to be and lit up again. Until a week ago, I used to smoke in a Chillum which anyway doesn't burn continuously. So in summary, tobacco aids in getting a 'professional' burn. If I am okay not having that experience, it should be fine right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 11:16:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, I've a quick question on buying a bong which I am doing right now. Would you recommend a glass or an acrylic one. Small or the long one? I am looking at [this](https://www.amazon.in/Stoner-Baba-Glass-Bong-Combo/dp/B079P8JQL3/) and [this](https://www.amazon.in/Metier-Acrylic-Bong-Combo-Black/dp/B01L3TJII6/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 11:22:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks a lot. You are a saver!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Help me pick one of the 12-inch glass bongs and few questions</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 14:43:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>After careful research and bit of study, I've found that MANY experienced people recommend (a) A Glass Bong (b) 12-inch or longer I've shortlisted the following on Amazon. I did go through littlegoa's product list but there is no information/ reviews of the product that can help me make a decision (apart from different colors, designs and prices). I'd request if you could help me pick one of them 1. [Moksha 12inch Tall Blue Honeycomb Waterpipe Bong. Solid Built Heavy Glass](https://www.amazon.in/Moksha-12inch-Honeycomb-Waterpipe-Bong/dp/B017WEFJG6/) 2. [Stoner Baba 12 Inch Glass Bong. - Ice Chamber.](https://www.amazon.in/Stoner-Baba-Inch-Glass-Bong/dp/B079P7T7DD/) 3. [Metier Glass Tall 4 Arm Tree Percolator Ice Bong](https://www.amazon.in/dp/B01ESY4WFW/) 4. [Stoner baba 12 inch bong](https://www.amazon.in/Stoner-Baba-Inch-Glass-Bong/dp/B079P7T7DD/) Few questions : 1. What accessories should I look for? 2. As far as I understand, shooter (the pipe that holds the weed (?) )is replaceable. Can I purchase shooters separately from different vendors? I understand there are standard sizes that are agreeable across all bong manufacturers 3. Do these bongs come with hole (Carb hole, I guess). I'd prefer to to use carb hole than pulling out the stem Mild humor: Check out the [comment](https://i.imgur.com/g8MeE8n.png) of Q amp;A on [this](https://www.amazon.in/Stoner-Baba-Inch-Glass-Bong/dp/B079P7T7DD/) page EDIT: I've finally purchased [12" 40 MM Percolator Green Color Leaf Sticker Glass Bong](http://www.littlegoa.com/products/bongs-glass-bong-12-inch-glass-bongs/little-goa/12-40-mm-percolator-green-color-leaf-sticker-glass-bong/pid-13072316.aspx) from Littegoa on advice of /u/mdamkhan. Unfortunately littlegoa doesn't have Visa payment setup. They accept only PayTM (sigh!) as the only online payment method. I've chosen COD that costs additional 120 bucks for shipping.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 15:46:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am guessing that there will be many underground testing centers will spring up. Or may be neighbouring country will allow testing. Or they can fly to my country where everything is on sale for few dollars. That would still be lot cheaper than 18 years of child support and alimony.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 15:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which one? As I have already mentioned, all I see is fashionable glassware with colors and designs. I have no way of knowing anything more. If you can recommend one and a small description why I'd buy right away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 16:09:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright boss! Any recommendation of a 12 inch bong? A link would be helpful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 16:58:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you been using this model? If so for how long? What advantages do I have if I purchase from littlegoa? Any advantages when ordering any accessories?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Double the loops and double the joy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 03:10:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Next level Hula Hooping</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 03:23:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 03:30:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>This one is [better](https://i.imgur.com/zR4rYf4.gifv)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 03:42:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably. Didn't think that way though. It doesn't look like I broke any rules. Did I?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 04:07:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. I didn't know there was such a sub. Thanks that's a great find. I found the pic on imgur. I posted it to GirlsInaGif and then here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 04:34:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Christopher, you are goddamed right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 04:52:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chris, if I want to mess with you, what would you do?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 05:30:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am having slight difficulty with vocab here. To be clear 1. Bowl : is it the round bottomed flask? Are they all detachable from the long glass column? I don't see the purpose though. **OR** is it the cup that holds herb? I think later makes sense 2. Downstem : This is a hollow pipe that has "herb cup" at one end and dips into the water in round bottomed flask at the other end. So there does exist a notion that this could be replaced 3. There is one [product](https://www.amazon.in/Stoner-Baba-Inch-Glass-Bong/dp/B079P7T7DD/) that does seem to have a [carb hole](https://i.imgur.com/MTVkvWN.jpg) Other poster also made a recommendation from Littlegoa while also suggesting not to make a purchase from Amazon. Anyway, I am down to [this](https://www.amazon.in/Stoner-Baba-Inch-Glass-Bong/dp/B079P7T7DD/)(Stoner Baba 12 Inch Glass Bong with Ice Chamber) and [this](http://www.littlegoa.com/products/bongs-glass-bong-12-inch-glass-bongs/little-goa/12-40-mm-percolator-green-color-leaf-sticker-glass-bong/pid-13072316.aspx) (12" 40 MM Percolator Green Color Leaf Sticker Glass Bong from ***Littegoa***). What would be your recommendation? Thanks. Really appreciate your help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 06:10:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would have shown her a complete market out there in exchange for free sex. Of course, as long as you don't call me a pimp.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Multi-tasking on steroids</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 06:30:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 08:53:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for your recommendation. /u/Doctor_Blunt agrees with your choice. BTW, are you affiliated to littlegoa in anyway? No, not that I mind, I'd just like to know if it so. Others and I might want to pick your brain sometime.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 08:55:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. I've posted there, infact a better one. That sub seems to be extremely picky what they approve.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 09:01:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just found that littlegoa has whatsapp as a customer support number. I will ask wide variety of questions just until they get sick of me and then place the order. Will update the post with all that information. Also purchasing from littlegoa provides me with direct customer support and a source of compatible supplies. I think that's valuable in itself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 09:36:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you are looking for [/r/FFNBPS](/r/FFNBPS)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 09:37:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you are looking for [/r/FFNBPS](/r/FFNBPS)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Teen made up story of being raped in bathroom, airport police say</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 10:25:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Multitasking on steroids</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 10:34:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 13:35:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>So? What's the relevance to the sub?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 13:46:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Quick question. How many people actually use these for smoking other than weed? I'd guess very less. Doesn't that ring a bell with authorities?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 13:52:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Angry boy! Have a check on your blood pressure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 14:01:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here by I certify you as Serial Mansplainer^TM. Here is [your seal](https://media.gettyimages.com/photos/certified-blue-round-seal-picture-id187736895?s=170667a amp;w=1007). May you live long and prosper. Amen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 14:09:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>He is deluded that she stopped him from suicide. To her he is more useful alive as long as she can suck him completely dry. After that, he is again on the road to committing suicide.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 14:46:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Best wishes. Sincerely hope you have a great life with your family. On behalf of others, I'd just advice to stay cautious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 14:56:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy cow! Did I have to live to see this? Fuck. These are the same medicines that fucked me over for ~ 2 years. And look what I see here - someone who is euphoric to have consumed the drug. General unasked advice. Be very careful with that thing in your hand. If you ever get used to it and want to withdraw, you'd wish you were dead. That's how strong withdrawal symptoms are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 15:19:27</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; it was a big hussle going to a doctor and getting a prescription for it . He obliged and gave ne a strip with no prescription . You've got this drug without prescription? I am almost sure you wouldn't be able to do this again, at least in Hyd. Most of the pharmacies will make a photocopy of prescription from a doctor that **they** recognize near that locality. If you try to purchase from a pharmacy that's far away, they might not outright reject but they will make sure to remind you that you should purchase from a place that's near your clinic that you are consulting. There were couple of deaths reported consuming similar benzos. That's the reason for tightening up and for good. EDIT: Not sure why the downvotes are. The prescription part is true to my knowledge and experience. And also, completely based on my experience, this drug has a potential to screw up your life big time if you fall into the trap of 'feeling good'. It will raise your tolerance and before you know you are hooked. May god have mercy on you weening from it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 15:21:43</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I get too panicked and anxious and cant do any critical thinking in that gun point kinda situatiion . Even if i try to think , my brain just stuts off . I couldnt properly communicate and solve questions which i would have easily solved in a jiffy provided a normal environment. Boy, you do have my sympathies. And I am your friend, even if you find me disparaging. I understand what you are saying but I don't have any solution at the moment. Let me give it a thought and may be consult few others and get back to you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 15:27:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not that I know about those reported deaths first hand; I've just overheard. Anyways, I think I someone like me should also do a verbal diarrhea to balance some adventure on this sub. Look you do know quite a lot and you could experiment. OP or I are anywhere close to that. We need caution. That's all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 18:09:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the [post](https://np.reddit.com/r/IndianEnts/comments/8z801q/platinum_bubba_kush_kinda_day/). Honestly, the sub seems to be taken over by teenagers. There are another one or two guys that behave like unplugged hand grenades ready to blow up at drop of hat and resort to abusive language needlessly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 18:30:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>/u/Urban_Aghori , this is a piece of shit here. This is the [nonsense](https://i.imgur.com/k5aBo00.png) he is talking And Mr /u/ditwatnoew it appears that you did lot of good work and some charity too. Can you tone your language to also be good and charitable. For one, doesn't look good and second, I can't fucking understand and third, abusive language involving mommy and dicks is ... how can I put it .. "puberty blues". And anyway, this is an internet forum. Have no idea what can anyone do to you on internet to go on a rage this way. Your real life must be hard. Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What fireworks look like from the air.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 02:24:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 02:28:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; You talking to me, tough guy? So you do recognize yourself. I'd appreciate that remarkable self awareness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 02:33:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Use archive.is to post excerpts from other threads!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 06:51:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometime ago, I found a 100 page guide (I think it's a PDF) on how to plan a divorce over a period of ~ 1 to 1.5 years very carefully. I am not a resident of US so I didn't bookmark it or save a copy. It does look pretty comprehensive and rigorous. May be others can chime in and point you in right direction. Always help your friends!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 06:57:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perhaps. It does sound like it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 07:01:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>He could honeytrap her into cheating. It's so easy with women these days. Just let them see an ***opportunity*** knocking down the doors, they'd just open it. Women are suckers for many shiny things. It's very easy to bait them into doing many things.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 07:08:23</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; get ANOTHER weathly buddy Its a lot easier than that. It only need to be wealthy presenting guy, possibly a scam artist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 07:19:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometimes, Ends justify means All is fair in love and war To protect yourselves, sometimes you'll need to kill your opponent Well, what can I say. After having burnt badly, if I were to be asked what would I have done to not get burnt, then I'd have all arrows in my quiver, legal, borderline legal, illegal and beyond. I'd put all cards on the table.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Questions on Spiked/contaminated weed</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 08:27:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>**TLDR**: My objective is to understand what the spiking is all about, finding ways to detect it within reason, as effectively as you can and as cheaply as one can. The idea is **NOT for the end users** to make use of these tips/suggestions. The idea is users can request/demand/ask **their dealers to do this tests before accepting the product for retail sale**. This way, they could sell pure wee and spiked weed to the differentiated audience if he chooses to do so. I am just trying to help **folks here who are regularly worried** if the product they are purchasing is as they expect. Here is the[ weed](https://i.imgur.com/hn2ZnaE.jpg) I use. I bought this directly on a farm - 8 large flowers dried, grounded and stored in a dry container. I've had few folks here comment that the weed is spiked (or contaminated). I see this word being thrown about frequently. But never did anyone provide ANY details on what substance(s)/additives/contaminants could be used. Just that they didn't like the color of the substance is an enough reason to immediately cast the herb/flower as spiked. So I've had a sample given to one of my friends who is a PhD scholar working on Organic/Bio Chem at one of the national institutes to do tests (if they aren't expensive). Though I am not a chemist myself, I did love the subject while I was an undergrad and did lot of on-hands work in synthesis, separation (using distillation/TLC/Column Chromatography), identification (physical characteristics, spectroscopy - IR/UV/NMR/Raman) etc. Of course, experimental science has grown 100x folds since the last time I lay my hands on chemicals. Okay, I got preliminary report from my friend. The sample does have few trace contaminants which are fertilizers (Phosphates/Nitrates and Urea) all of which are water soluble. The sample does not contain any opioids. The tests consist of first separating water soluble and solvent soluble (di-ethyl ether) and using specific diagnostic chemical for presence of salts/acids. For opioids there are specific reagents one can use to test. When I meet him sometime this weekend,I can get a list of reagents that he has used. Now, for the question time. 1. When the flower is plucked from the plant it remains greenish for ~ 7 days. After that it turns brown. EVERY green leaf or anything that contains chlorophyll will die when plucked out of the plant. The residue is brown or yellow. So when you want to dry weed flower and preserve it for longer duration, it WILL be brown in color. 2. Suppose someone on this sub tells you that your weed is spiked - what is your recourse? Are you (a) Going back to your dealer and exchange it for something different? (b) Will you change up your dealer? (c) Curse your bad luck and smoke it anyway? (d) Throw it away?. I really want to know what you are going to do. 3. For those that claim something is spiked - where does your knowledge come from that you could say it with confidence just by looking at the picture? Now if you do say it indeed is spiked, can you provide more details on what contaminants could have been used? Just saying 'spiked' doesn't add any value. 4. Suppose someone purchases dried and stored weed. Do you still expect it to be glow-stick green in color? If it isn't are you going to say it's spiked? Did you consider purchasing product for long term storage,probably in bulk and not bother about if you are going to score tonight or not? 5. If folks here are SO concerned about contaminated product, why aren't mitigation strategies not being talked about? EDIT 1: Two reagents that my friend mentioned over the phone to test opioids and I remember are Marquis, Cobalt thiocyanate. I am sure these can be purchased in retail. EDIT 2: Here is a [decent quora](http://archive.is/C3Qkw) post on spiked weed. Few excerpts that are interesting  gt;If the dealer says he/she doesn't have time to give you a sample, delete the number of that conman/ conwoman ...  gt;When it comes to weed, 99.9% of weed sold in metros is stored , or rather not stored but kept in moist gunny bags in slummy areas with no quality control. This weed is sold until the gunny bags are empty ...  gt;This weed may be spiked with pesticides(**so that it doesn't mould**), strange white powder like substances that look like fake trichromes(use a magnifying glass) ...  gt;here in india it could also be mixed up with weed that is just old and, as we call it, water-pressed and packed, which means a huge bale was compressed hydraulically so that it takes up less space, this is usually done when moist and when it happens it causes mould to grow on the buds. ...  gt;Spiked marijuana is a myth. Spiked in this context means "To add another drug to contaminate" while such spiked marijuana exists, it's either spiked by the dealer for his own use and/or by the user before smoking it. The reasons for this are simple, weed is one of the cheapest drugs and cutting it with another drug is not as cost effective as is cutting other drugs such as cocaine or diamorphine. ...  gt;Myth. It #8217;s too expensive to spike weed and then sell it as weed. You need to be aware of contaminants such as molds and pesticides though. A lab does these tests as most issues other than a bad case of mold can #8217;t be readily detected with out lab equipment. EDIT 3: There is another [post on quora](http://archive.is/4KJia) which talks about **rat poison, glue and ink**. I'd find out how to do cheap chemical tests to detect these chemicals and post it separately. I've already mentioned two chemical reagents that can be used to detect opiates. I guess I will also be able to provide information on testing for amphetamines. EDIT 4: Thanks to user /u/DhuliGod, here is an [article that talks about the same topic of the discussion (https://www.spliffpoliticsco.com/single-post/2017/09/14/Moldy-Marijuana-aka-Spiked-weed)  gt;When weed in India is transported, the reason you often wind up with buds that are flat, or almost look like they were pressed flat to pack together, it #8217;s because they were. A hydraulic press is used to compress the marijuana to a much smaller volume, which is then packed into a bag. But if it still has water content (which it almost always does), this is a certain way to get mold and fungus, as a compressed bud has even less airflow and there #8217;s nowhere for the water to escape.  gt;Your dealer is just probably an idiot like the rest of them, and has no idea what #8217;s good weed and what isn #8217;t. It #8217;s the result of poor knowledge and needing to get rid of the illegal substance  #8211; ASAP. There #8217;s no time to sit around and wait for it to dry unless you know the importance that this lends to the marijuana consumption process. The dealer is an idiot, the farmer is also an idiot, and two idiots don #8217;t make a genius  #8211; far from it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 08:38:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>ok boy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 10:03:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it could be poppy gum, a kind of resin that the bud secrets. So, this is no longer weed but straight up an opioid. Now, the problem I have with this is you could sell opioids at a much higher rate at smaller quantities and is more profitable. Something does't seem to clearly add up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 10:10:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds about right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 10:28:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now, the question is chemically I can detect presence of at least one of the classes of opioids. Can you visually identify such contamination OR via smell. I think smell could be a good indicator. Any idea how to identify via smell?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 10:40:03</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I do get my weed for long term (3-4 weeks) storage and it is glow-stick green right up until the last bowl. If you say 4 weeks is not enough 'long-term' then I don't know what to tell you. Maybe I can say that I don't treat weed like wine, that is, I don't think it becomes better with age. Even if it does, I don't care. I'm not about to score a pound and risk a felony. And I wouldn't recommend it to anyone either Good to know. I didn't know that. I purposefully dried them in sunlight before grinding. Next time I won't do that. The guy on the farm advised me to dry before smoking. Thanks for your answers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 12:00:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oops I think I did not make the objective of my post clear. My objective is to empower the end users to demand dealers to perform the tests cheaply before they accept the product from their uber dealers/growers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 12:02:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've added a new TLDR to the post text. Do check it when you are free.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 12:20:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let's see! If someone wants to try, he know how to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scary Figure inside this cabbage</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 13:12:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 13:58:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because I didn't impregnate her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 14:07:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Post this to /r/CringeAnarchy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[NSFW] Cambridge economics professor using art to combine feminism with economics</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 14:35:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 14:57:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy cow there is a sub for sexdolls? I've just subbed it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 15:05:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Guys have you seen this [news piece by ABC](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-cN8sJz50Ng)?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Men will be Men!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 15:23:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Loading up the truck.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 15:37:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>People who are falsely accused of sexual abuse, how did the accuse impact your life? (/r/AskReddit thread)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 03:38:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 03:41:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Doesn't exactly go with rule #3. I thought [the thread](https://np.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/906ilu/people_who_are_falsely_accused_of_sexual_abuse/) on /r/AskReddit about false accusation of sexual abuse is relevant here. Remove if it doesnt fit here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>King Mackerel chasing its prey.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 04:10:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is a cave in Afghanistan</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 04:15:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 04:16:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here is the [source](https://imgur.com/gallery/RHrydDk). This guy went on a vacation to Afghanistan and made a post. It's an interesting read.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 04:52:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>okay! Seems I am too mild for you folks. Cheers!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 06:02:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like your excellent research. Do you have anymore samples? I'd recommend you to Harvard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 09:49:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are oddly terrifying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Demonic tree</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 12:18:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Smooth clay-making</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 13:45:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Carrot Knight</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 06:46:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Brick by Brick</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 08:47:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 11:03:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bought in bulk ~ 300 gms on a farm. After drying, removing seeds and grinding, I have ~ 235 gms. This will suffice me for next 4-5 months or even more.  gt;I just wanna know how you got in touch with the plug. There are obvious places in India in South, East, and of course North where you have large congregations of sadhus and places where festivals that involve weed are common. There are a few places in south and I traveled there. I took ~ 5 days before I finally found the village where it's grown. Heck, the entire mountain ranges have them growing wildly - not even being cultivated. I discovered the later when I was returning back with my product. This information should be sufficient for you to find the place. Now, transporting them back to your city safely can be a concern. I don't know other states but A.P and Telangana can be a bit difficult - law enforcement is on work day and night. You will need to plan it a bit carefully depending on your situation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 11:09:22</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Don't take more than 7-10 pills a week as it will cause tolerance.  gt;  gt; YES side effects are real and deadly. Longterm side effects mostly. Thanks for that foot note. Request you not to forget mentioning it anytime.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 11:43:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is from Cage of Death in Australia. Few more pics [here](https://imgur.com/a/khvNJ)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 12:05:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Up in North, I don't think you will have much problem. Just don't stand apart in the crowd. And if you want to do it, do it alone all by yourselves. That's way safer. Also, one problem I can see is opium additives. Down south, opium doesn't grow - the climate isn't conducive. Anyway, this is only if you are buying from a dealer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 15:19:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>okay. I don't know anything about that. I was just paraphrasing someone else's comment on this on other thread.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This Black Wolf (x-post from /r/NatureIsMetal)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 15:24:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 04:17:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>That concerns me a lot. Why are this guy's lungs in bad shape? I haven't heard this before. Does smoking weed damage the lungs to that extent? Or is he smoking cigarettes as well? What if I smoke once in two days and that too small quantity ~ 1/5 the of a regular Kings size gold flake per two days. Should that be a problem? Yesterday I have got my glass bong and I would be smoking using that. Would that still be a problem? I wonder why isn't this discussed more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 04:25:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey OP I am a bit concerned that you have problems with your lungs. Perhaps you should see a doctor without further delay and make sure you have a remedy. But why did you at all have this problem? What were your smoking habits? How often, frequency and how much were you smoking? Are you smoking just the weed or even tobacco? And how were you smoking - ciggies, pipe, bong, chillum? I have started smoking weed recently for health reasons. And am worried sick if I could get into different problems. My usage of weed is approximately 1/5 of regular king size cigarette, one for two days and smoking through a glass bong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 09:09:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you please keep us updated with your treatment and also the result of your visit to the doctor. Do let us all know any precautions or the ill effects of cannabis.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 02:20:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. I access this site using tor over vpn. You expect me to join a WhatsApp group? And what benefit does it bring? Nah. Leave me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 08:54:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure. Make a once a life time journey to meet this highnesses. Book your tickets right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 08:55:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Coming close. I use utmost precaution because this isn't the only site I visit when I am on vpn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 11:04:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>This one has a pussy boys. This is the standard signature of a bitch's writing. I mean a useless, meaningless, totally unnecessary lol at the end of a 3 word sentence is hallmark of a bitch's creativity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 11:16:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>You've written a goddamed essay. Guys is this worth reading?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 11:26:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am usually quite sympathetic to those that put lot of time to write such long posts. Couldn't read past the first paragraph. Lady, seek help somewhere else. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 01:47:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is bhang same as weed? Do they sell weed in that shop?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 15:04:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it just a shop or a restaurant attached to it? I always wanted to be able to sit in a nice restaurant, with slow and soft music, enjoy good food and smoke weed. Seeing that Orissa is quite charitable with consuming weed, are there any restaurants that allow smoking weed? Does Orissa has, what do I say, weed culture?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 05:20:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't you guys use archive.is? Why link to the thread directly?  gt; And precisely because I had bad experiences with ~~men~~ **women**, I can't really have compassion for ~~MGTOWs, incels~~ **women** and various other ~~terpers~~ **feminist shills** FTFY  gt;Because despite my problems, I didn't adopt any ideology or set of ideas that claim that men are hard wired to be evil bastards and abuse women. I don't generalize men So because you don't generalize you get to tell the world that they shouldn't generalize? Generalization and specialization are two primary ways of learning to live with the world. You generalize over a class of problems and specialize to a specific problem. You are free to not do so just as others are free to do so. According to you men should simply say I've had bad experiences with Tanya,Gloria,Phebe and Lilly but I've not had experiences with 3.5 bill women. Really? Suppose I've had another bad experience with Debby, you expect me to try morgan on my wallet? And I should oblige you? Suppose I see a general pattern with all of the women above, are you telling me that I MUST not notice that and ignore it? Most AI/ML algorithms that have changed the face of internet rely on past experiences to adapt to new experiences - that's exactly what ***intelligence*** in AI is all about. So are you saying that men shouldn't be allowed to do what algorithms can do? Are you saying that depending on our experiences in past aren't we allowed to make decisions in the future?  gt;Because despite my problems, I didn't adopt any ideology or set of ideas that claim that men are hard wired to be evil bastards and abuse women. I don't generalize men Okay, and I would like to know why? If you are consistently loosing,giving you a heartache why aren't you trying to protect yourselves from the harm you say you are enduring? You may have an explanation for it but let me offer you mine. You (in general women) don't loose as much as men loose in a relationship. If you feel you are loosing a lot more in a relationship than being single, the **rational** choice would be NOT to ***once again*** seek a relationship. In the same vein if you are getting more being in a relationship than without, it's rational to seek one. Unless you want to plead insanity, tell me that you are consistently loosing badly in relationships but still seek them. And now think what would people that are sane an rational would do? --- Next, I 'll bite your shaming language. Now you'd say if I am constantly being hurt, the problem is me. Alright that may be true. Are you the one to educate me how I should change/adapt myself so that I could see more success? First, you don't know me and I like it that way. Next, I don't know if you are a person capable of providing such an education that would help me in my situation. And importantly I have no reason to seek help from people on internet and that too why I don't feel I need any of the help that you offer. Shame is such a powerful motivator, especially for men, that you have made us immune to it. --- There is a difference between reddit and platforms such as youtube and facebook. The later pushes you the content algorithmically based on your online habits. On reddit, you seek the content you want to. Folks that are on MGTOW or any other sub have external reasons to seek that sub. Reddit does provide you recommendations but you need to actively seek them for specific purpose. And specially MGTOW has no proselytization agenda - no adverts nothing. And members of those sub actively seek anonymity and infact even unwilling to meet each other in real life (go check threads that want meetups - they are ruthlessly downvoted and heavily criticized). What I am saying is the reasons of existence of MGTOW sub are external to the sub. If you think they are "indoctrinated", then it happened outside the sub. Yes, you could say it reinforces, yes it does. So? Do you have any idea how difficult it is to forego biological wiring? Walking away from opposite sex that we are biologically programmed to live with? Have you any idea what kind of traumatic experience would require such a reaction? --- So an anonymous group, guarding their privacy zealously and hiding behind anonymity, share their mutual experiences and advocate to guard themselves is causing you problem? Of course you will see hate. Why won't you hate something that caused so much of trauma. Well, women did have a hate movement themselves that's public, receive public funds and is honorable to be part of and you call it feminism. Yes, you don't see it has a hate movement; well, I'll let you keep that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 06:58:18</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I had back surgery about 2 months ago and have slowly been getting back into shape Hope you are doing well now. I've had back problems as well though lot milder. I am not American and my diet is quite different. I'll tell what helped me FWIW 1. One heavy meal consist of boiled sprouts of various cereals/legumes : [Bean Sprouts](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mung_bean#Bean_sprouts) + [Kidney Beans](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kidney_bean) + [Black Eyed Pea](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Black-eyed_pea)+ [Chick Pea](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chickpea)+ [Green Pea](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pea)+ [Pigeon Pea](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pigeon_pea). I'd either have it in the afternoon or early in the evening. Also they are very tasty. 2. Stop smoking cigarettes and also alcohol. Instead, I'd smoke weed. It's lot safer than any others out there. I am a vegetarian and had to research a lot to increase my protein intake. I had to design my own recipes to reduce carbs (regular Indian diet has lot of them). Let me know if you want any veggie recipes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 06:59:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Guys don't fucking cross post. [Use archive.is](https://archive.fo/dT8D1)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 07:03:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Talking talking talking about problems will NOT solve problems. Unlike women we don't feel the problem is addressed in anyway just because we've talked for hours about it. Why the fuck you want to waste time taking about it when it doesn't help a bit. You could better spend time in actually trying to find a solution.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bluebills have brigaded this thread. Incredibly satisfying to witness the 'triggering'. Keep it coming babes!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 07:47:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 07:53:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are going nuts [here](https://archive.fo/gRwRw). Obligatory: always use archive.is links. Fun to watch. For a sub that claims to be a satire, well, what's lacking is satire. They come to this sub, which THEY KNOW it would trigger them and go fucking nuts and loose sleep over it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 08:00:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I'd also recommend Keto diet. I've seen many of my friends see improve with the diet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 08:11:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tired of sniffing your own butt like your cats do, here you are seeking exotic olfactory delights in a road that's tangential to your's. You are welcome anytime.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 08:46:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. Look at the comment that's highlighted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 09:24:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>C'mon man. Its a comment by /u/mengoingtowin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 09:29:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>And the comment received gold. Now if you can't find that thread I think I have failed you in a big way. I'd have to smoke pot tonight to drown in that sadness. If you do find it, I will still smoke pot and celebrate it. So, pot it is!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 11:05:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. This will be my last message here. Before I begin, I don't endorse abusive behavior by any one in any context. Let me get that out of the way. Lady you seem to be barking up the wrong tree. I really, genuinely haven't understood more than half of your post. I've only realized you are talking about redpill sub guys. You've got confused by mgtow and redpill subs? Nothing can be as divergent as those two groups. I don't want to be abused by a woman neither do I want to abuse her and never did when I was in relationshit(s). Manipulating people is never a good idea; it will eventually backfire with magnitude many times over. I've never visited that sub never posted there. Why are you even telling me about them? I'd say again, mgtow #8800;theredpill. You don't usually see cross over of people posting in these subs. If you want, I've got a simple python script that will dump data that you can verify intersection of posters is negligible. You are welcome to conflate both of them if that makes you happy.  gt;You "fixed" it the **wrong way**. I make a clear distinction between men in general on [...] You have your ways of fixing and I have mine. Feel free to think you know the right way. You know, I am sick of women that think they know the best and try to fix men and irritate them bit by bit, one day at a time until it all blows away.  gt;On top of it, how do you view women who say "i had bad experiences with men, so I'm gonna generalize men" ??? Because that is precisely what you are doing. Look, if that's what will keep you safe you should do it. If you have to generalize men and view them as predators, keep them away from out of the ring you draw, you **should** do it. I'd totally encourage that. You are important. Your safety is important. Your well being is important. Give no fucks about political correctness or what others think or feel. You don't want to throw yourselves under bus on altar of being agreeable to people around you.  gt;I don't know why is it that you think men lose more in relationships than women You don't know why I think? WTF. Show me equivalent set of women that want to shun relationshits all together ***because*** of legal issues, divorce rapes and loss of money and retirement and importantly children. Is there a sub for that? I can show in, in your county within a 1 km radius plenty of divorced women that are ready to hop on to next relationship on tinder. You want to take that challenge? I travel to US quite frequently, I'd meet you in person and show you that it is so. I'll pay out of my pocket. There is one event : Divorce. One of the parties are ready for new love of their lives and the other party nopes the fuck out of relationshits. Infer what you want to.  gt;ut that pattern stems from **patriarchy**. NOPE. Not going to touch that one with 10 feet pole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 11:15:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>DON'T link to the sub directly. Kindly use archive.is or waybackmachine. Anyway, your link is incorrect. I possible, delete this post and make a new post with the same title and use [this archive link](https://archive.fo/qGIzz).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Man takes acid and shrooms,realizes that his partner was cheating all along and dumps her</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 11:16:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 11:17:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>As if I care.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 11:20:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Too late for me though. I think I've lost my children to the devil. Hmmmm.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 11:25:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>May be it depends on the method of smoking. Yes, I've had problems with smooth burn when I make joints (I am very bad at rolling them, though). But I've lived with that inconvenience. I've purchased a good bong and I never had problem with quality of burn at all. I'd just say, if you can, don't use tobacco.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 12:19:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Li #42817;e i give a  #7711;uc #42817;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 12:29:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've only t #7811;o things to say 1.  #7811;o #7747;en shoul #7691; be  #7747;ore care #7711;ul in selecting a responsible partner. They shoul #7691; have  #7811;itnesse #7691; the responsible behavior o #7711; their partner  #7811;ith their o #7811;n eyes, an #7691; consistently over a perio #7691; o #7711; ti #7747;e. They shoul #7691; have their brothers/ #7711;athers/uncles vouch  #7711;or that person be #7711;ore they go babies  #7811;ith the  #7747;an. Use the  #7747;en in your li #7711;e that you can trust by biology to select the  #7747;an  #7811;ho you  #7811;ill  #7747;ate  #7811;ith. 2. I' #7691; hunt that bastar #7691;  #7811;ho isn't there  #7711;or that chil #7691;ren, beat hi #7747; up to pulp, pull  #7747;oney o #7711; out is butt chee #42817;s an #7691; give it to  #7747;other. No #7811; (1) is i #7747;portant.  #7691;on't give  #7747;e victi #7747; bla #7747;ing bullshit that goes on in stupi #7691;  #7711;e #7747;inist circles. You shoul #7691; learn  #7711;ro #7747; the  #7747;ista #42817;es o #7711; the victi #7747; i #7711; you  #7691;on't  #7811;ant to en #7691; up li #42817;e one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 13:09:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kindly use archive.is for linking to threads on other subs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 13:37:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is no test, shit test or not that I  #7811;on't clear. Lay  #7691;o #7811;n the rules o #7711; the ga #7747;e, I  #7811;ill beat you at it. I #7711; letters are your proble #7747;, change it up.  #7747;a #42817;e ne #7811; rules.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 14:02:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the place where there will be lot of women and few men. High value men will have absolutely no problem in getting the chick they desire. They don't have to go to these places.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 14:15:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>She wanted 1.5 micro grams of attention. While others are content with 1.5 micro grams of LSD.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 16:09:42</DATE>
    <TEXT> #7747;y  #7691;ear princess yo #361; as #42817;e #7691;  #7747;e a q #803; #775; #803; #775; #361;estion. I can't let  #7747;o #7691; the  #7691;ae #7747;on is bet #7811;een  #361;s. I've  #361;se #7691; one  #7711;ro #7747;  #7747;y bag o #7711; tric #42817;s to reach yo #361;.  #7711;inally  #7811;e are together. No  #7747;o #7691; can co #7747;e bet #7811;een  #361;s. It's ti #7747;e  #7711;or  #361;s to hol #7691; han #7691;s together an #7691;  #7811;al #42817;  #7691;o #7811;n into s #361;nset an #7691; live happily ever a #7711;ter. PS: Other chil #7691;ren on this s #361;b, no #7811; yo #361; sho #361;l #7691; close yo #361;r eyes an #7691; go to be #7691;.  #7811;hat happens no #7811; is  #7691;e #7711;initely not PG 13</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 04:49:15</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; And the giant point you're trying to make that weed smoke is magically less harmful than cig smoke is your delusion and I hope you get out of it. Well, that seems to be the news all around ENT forums/subs. The consensus seems to be smoking Cannabis is significantly less harmful than smoking tobacco. I know nothing about it, haven't done any research (I don't think I have expertise to be able to do it) and I rely on other people that do. All ears - do tell me about it. Just a conjecture that the quantity of weed one smokes is significantly less than the quantity of tobacco one smokes on average. Does that make weed safer? For example amount of weed I smoke ~ 1/5 of the quantity of 1 king size cigarette and **once per day**. That's a lot less of one herb than the other. Does this make weed safer? Do reply. Appreciate your response.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 10:13:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>[.](https://i.imgur.com/6N75NGi.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 10:26:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are an asshole troll. But still, let me give you an answer. After my devil wife fucked me in divorce, taking away all that I have and dumping multiple debts on my head, I slogged for ~ 4 years to clear all of them living in a miserable one room house that is kitchen+bedroom+drawing room. And I've saved enough money that will sustain me for the next ~ 3 years. I am quitting my job the end of this month, renting a small house near to a beach and take up some serious hobby that I am going to pursue it for the next ~ 2 years. Again, you are an asshole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 10:34:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck you asshole. Try living in one room with a stove (no oven), few cooking vessels and cook your goddammed meals (breakfast/lunch/dinner) all by yourselves, saving one penny a day. Do that and dare to come here and make a post with that title.  gt; I #8217;m sorry that person treated you that way. That #8217;s not fair or okay. No one need your fake dressed up sorries asshole. And no one got any meat on the table with 3^rd party sorries like your's. Unnecessary, useless virtue signalling and usually crooked people feel the need to do that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 11:15:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are the hero we need. Scam the shit out of them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>These leaves (x-post from /r/oddlysatisfying)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 12:55:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 14:24:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here is the [post](https://np.reddit.com/r/oddlysatisfying/comments/925x1d/the_gradient_on_these_leaves/) from on /r/oddlysatisfying. One of the comments say it is  gt;Oxalis palmifrons</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 14:45:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a cunt, no doubt. Bitch sent me these [messages](https://i.imgur.com/Tw3mYhq.png) an few more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 09:10:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Surrogacy can be a choice. If you don't mind walking down few semi-legal/borderline legal alleys, and some adventure, I can direct you a way. You will need to plan for it for ~ 1.5 years very carefully and then you will be able to take home your baby sans any woman. I've seen people do it. PM me if you want to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 10:32:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>In this case, I think it's a bit harsh and unjustified criticism. You've got women that you were protecting until you got killed. What option do they have? Kill themselves or submit to conquerors. Now committing suicide is such an extreme step, fuck my head explodes thinking about it. It takes a great amount of courage and probably some insanity to want to kill yourselves. Consider people that you've known personally or through acquaintances or a popular figure that has committed suicide - and then look at the reasons, the magnitude of insurmountable grief that made them choose that road to death. I am not sure if living under a different ***management*** can be so grief inducing that people want to kill themselves. Before civilized democracies, the ruler and conqueror were both equal opportunity assholes. That said, I do agree that women in general have absolutely no loyalty. Fuck they aren't loyal to you in a marriage when they depend on you for their shelter/food/clothing/luxuries and so on. They treat living off you as an entitlement and an early retirement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Where is it?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 12:06:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 13:01:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Guys use archive.is. And importantly don't fucking brigade the other thread. Just don't link to threads directly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 13:14:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perhaps. But it bothers me that we are faulting people for not killing themselves for reasons that is not a personal trauma.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 13:24:01</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I'd say it's more that defying gender roles. And why should I defy my gender role? Is there pot of gold waiting at the end if I do that? And who are you to tell me that I should defy it? Or tell anyone to should defy them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 13:31:13</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Toxic masculinity [...] blah blah blah First you denigrate my gender. And then you give a dressed up explanation in "nice" words as a cover to hide your blatant misandrist attitude. And then you expect us to take you seriously and talk to you respectfully. No man who's worth the man he is will ever give a cursory look at the dirt that you call feminism until you wipe that "toxic masculinity" off your bloody dictionary. Anyway, here is a [thread](http://archive.is/AcRBD) on /r/AskMen what they think of women that claim to be feminists. I think this time, feminists might have to actually become lesbians out of lack of choice. Such a nice job you've done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 13:48:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's pretty badass!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 14:06:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, the last time I've heard, men cause massive destructive hurricanes and give them feminine names.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 14:09:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy, I fell for it. Removing the post</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 14:10:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boy looks like it's trolling. There is no http://lipstickformen.com/ site.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>And then, it goes in</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 02:40:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's big, it's black, and you can sit on it (x-post from /r/OddlyErotic)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 02:53:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 02:56:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/OddlyErotic has many posts that I think fit here. Do take a look. Also I discovered new sub r/PareidoliaGoneWild. Yay!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 03:16:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the thing. A website like reddit doesn't manipulate you with their algorithmic content. You CHOOSE to visit this sub because you wanted to. And the reason you wanted to is because you were looking for such content elsewhere and you hit upon this. OR you are a cunt from /r/TheBluePill looking for content to get triggered and then whine about it on their sub.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Asian Dating sites are a fucking scam - a video by two awesome bloggers on bikes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 03:59:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>These are two awesome channels - [AdvChina](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCwNPa8fSXzzAZuT9859GVhg) and [serpentza](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCl7mAGnY4jh4Ps8rhhh8XZg). These two guys go on their bikes around the vast country that is China and talk about things they find interesting in mundane lives of chinese people. Also the culture you find it on the ground. It's just great watching two men hit the road on their bikes and roll smooth like superbikeman. I'd like other MGTOW youtubers to take a page from these two vloggers to make their content more interesting. Anyway, on [this episode](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WtMF5YtCw8M), they talk about how Chinese dating sites are a scam. Quite interesting revelations. MGTOW Tax: Two little girls that learnt bullying from their single mother and a boy like -"[nah! I am gonna fuck outa here](https://i.imgur.com/K18Ftxz.gifv)" EDIT: Forgot to add the link to the video. Now it's there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 04:00:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>And leaves you with satisfaction.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 04:23:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>C'mon man! We don't have to look everything through 'lenses'. He's got a good channel and happy to watch his videos. It ends there. I don't have to know anything about his personal life. He could be a cuck but his vlogs still are interesting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 04:25:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>What nonsense is this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 04:31:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Son, get some help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Balance!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 04:56:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ever see a baby rhino yawn?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 05:48:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 06:06:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't listen to anyone here. They are all lying. You should get on a dating app and find all about it. Now!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 06:12:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could buy a roomba. There are multiple gadgets that could complete the house.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 06:17:34</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; They want to control and terrorize women, not get a sexual release This is the narrative feminists have put forward ripe from their heads even before interviewing an actual rapist. I don't buy that a bit. I am yet to find a comprehensive report by a good psychologist (not a indoctrinated leftie) who've done actual interviews with rapists and their account of why did they do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 06:20:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>You'd be surprised. They don't ask because it isn't politically correct to do so. Even your boyfriend would have wanted to ask it but didn't. Don't go and pose this question to him - he'll deny thinking that way because he knows you will sulk if he tells you the truth. And of course you will deny him the sex.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sex robots 'will make make women interchangeable with technology', campaigners warn</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 06:21:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 06:27:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't get me wrong, I love sex dolls and trying to get one shipped to my country using (ahem!) less than savory ways becuause they are not legal. I am just posting it here to document the crazies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 06:33:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look I told you and you didn't like it - exactly as expected.  gt;I don #8217;t want you stalking me ya know Nah! I am done with women. Not interested.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 09:00:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have absolutely no idea what you ha e written. No I can understand the individual words but what do they amount to together beats the hell out of me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 09:07:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>So what you are saying is...investing in cat food stocks is a good idea?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 09:08:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you haven't responded, you could have been inscrutable black magic fuckery. Now you ruined it all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 09:15:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool that's what it looks like when you dry it in sun. I did the same - I bought greens and sun dried it and it turns brown. Don't let others passing judgements just based on pic dishearten you. Anyway I think posting pics is silly unless there is a good context. Your pic is quite interesting because it's a retail store. It's a fucking retail store man!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 09:51:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow! There is one dude who is like arm chair expert on desi ganja vomiting out his opinion of weed looking at a pic and here you, shows all of the fucks a wholesale market! Kudos. Well done boy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 10:06:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that you in the pic? Or do you own the bike in the pic? Who took the pic?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The way this building camouflages with the sky</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 10:35:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 10:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this what how the world looked like when I was coming out?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can #8217;t get enough: Europe #8217;s first sex-doll brothel set to open third venue</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 11:30:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Mixing Tylenol and Alcohol even in small amounts can kill you.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 13:21:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 14:32:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>The video was sped up at least 2x-3x. I don't think this would be sweaty palms at normal speed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>That's a fine wine ma'm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 06:28:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Vaping by a freeway</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 08:45:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 08:48:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>By op, you don't mean it's me right? Anyway, do you have the post you are referring to? Should I delete this post?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 11:10:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have issues with the term 'disorder'. Something out of the norm or out of order should be called 'disorder'. It's better to identify sane and sensible women, if they exist as having 'rational personality disorder' or 'Sense Struck'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 11:33:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why don't you post a link here for us all to enjoy. Share with me in private if you don't want to. Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Slug!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 12:17:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cute Otter</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 12:20:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 12:36:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>DON'T fucking link to threads on other subs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Friendly PSA : Guys don't link threads to other subs diectly</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 12:45:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>As said in the title, kindly don't link to threads in other subs. The following are the alternatives 1. Use [archive.is](http://www.archive.is). This used to be the best one until recently. For some reason, since last few days it started showing a large OC watermark. The work around is to use "old" reddit link i.e prefix "old." (that's old and a period) to link that you want to archive. For example the url https://www.reddit.com/r/Tinder/comments/92yyax/daddys_little_girl/ becomes https://old.reddit.com/r/Tinder/comments/92yyax/daddys_little_girl/. Notice the old prefix added to the URL.Now use this link to on Use [archive.is](http://www.archive.is) website 2. [Use Way Back Machine](https://archive.org/web/). On this page there is a form on which you can submit the url to archive. If you are using Firefox browser, [you've got an extension](https://addons.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/addon/wayback-machine_new/) that will do it for you at a click of a button. 3. Post an image/screen shot 4. Finally, which I don't recommend, use non participation mode link. For example https://www.reddit.com/r/Tinder/comments/92yyax/daddys_little_girl/ becomes https://np.reddit.com/r/Tinder/comments/92yyax/daddys_little_girl/. Notice the np prefix to the URL EDIT: As to why we should do it, you need to understand the concept of brigading. This happens when a post of sub A is linked /crossposted to sub B, folks of sub B will **launch a raid on sub A** and start commenting and skewing the voting pattern. Brigading is against the reddit rules. If evidence of brigading is there, it is one of the grounds to shut the sub down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 12:48:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because it will be construed as brigading, which is against the reddit rules. If there is an evidence of brigading, it becomes the ground to ban the sub. I've made [another post](https://www.reddit.com/r/MGTOW/comments/93313i/friendly_psa_guys_dont_link_threads_to_other_subs/) to help you use other tools for posting link. If possible, kindly delete this repost again with archived link.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 13:27:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh is it? I usually do it when I see direct linking. Let me assure you that I am completely blind to the poster and you aren't targeted. I just wish moderators enforce it. Let me page them /u/DangZagnut or /u/ss_camaro can you see if we can have this rule publicized and may be see how it can be enforced. Of course if you think it's important enough, which I do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 13:34:59</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I did find it disturbing that they were monitoring this sub Not sure what do you mean though. Mods are there to monitor the sub. At least on this sub you do enjoy lot more freedom than many others. You can make a post on your bullying and threats and I am sure it would be dealt with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>HMB while I kick ..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 14:01:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Secret Facebook Groups for Shocking DNA Tests</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 14:15:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 14:18:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Few weeks ago there was a news article on DNA tests being banned without consent of mothers. And I commented that underground testing networks would spring up to fill the need for testing. Though this article doesn't exactly reflect that, it does look like we'd have them sooner than later.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 14:24:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it possible we provide some hints before posting [like the one](https://i.imgur.com/02zzLur.png) /r/MensRights do? Actually if there are hooks into submission API (either JavaScript or Python reddit API i.e. either on the browser or on the host), we could enforce it well and have much more fine grained control. I could look into it if you think it's desired.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 14:27:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>The you would enjoy /r/UpvotedBecauseBoobs. [This](https://www.reddit.com/r/UpvotedBecauseBoobs/comments/8kka5v/walk_along_with_me/) is one of my favorites</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 14:31:43</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Men used to send their wives to doctors to get fucked every week for "hysteria" What? Really, what? Did I read it correct?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 14:36:12</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Yea look it up Where do I look up? You've made an explosive statement keep me hanging on here. It's unfair. I protest!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 14:55:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright, I found a better source [here](https://lithub.com/hysteria-witches-and-the-wandering-uterus-a-brief-history/). I don't know why you are outraged. What the fuck did men or medicine know about complete functioning of uterus. Did women knew how their internal lady bits function. It's just the case of what they thought the right thing in their time of day. You could complain if they did today.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 15:02:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>What ulterior motive does a husband that sent his wife to a doctor to treat her hysteria has?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 15:13:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are writing too much before illuminating your point.  gt;A combination of perversion and submission to authority. Who is pervert here? The husband that willingly is sending his wife to the doctor OR the doctor himself for designing such a cure? You mean wife is submitting to the authority of man/doctor? You don't seem to have a grip on historical events and progression of it. That to think, to have freedom were the qualities that are very important to societal condition AND there being an acceptance of it is relatively **new**. Now, tell me why are you talking about aristocracy of 17-18 th centuries. Talk about freedom of speech of a cave woman who is subjugated by the best the man is. Yes go ahead and talk about her rights, her freedom, her vagaina and uterus. I'd like to hear what you've got to say. Are you an outrage machine?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 15:22:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, when you have edited your post, it's good etiquette to separate the initial comment and later additions. That way when I see your comment next time, I'd know there is an additional content. First, I think we are talking about the condition of 'hysteria' in women and doctors. So can we complete that discussion? You didn't answer the question  gt;What ulterior motive does a husband that sent his wife to a doctor to treat her hysteria has? and before you answered you made an additional statement  gt;A combination of perversion and submission to authority. Who is pervert here? Doctor OR Husband? And finally how did you manage to find a segway into pyramids and biblical history from condition of women? Can you, for love of god, talk one thing at a time before you blast out in hundred different directions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 15:28:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am sorry boy. I give up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>German tank holds the beer while it races towards the enemy lines (not really HMB)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 04:45:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 05:05:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>No matter what you think you are good at, there is always an asian guy who will beat you at it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 05:24:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only modern tank I like is a Fish tank; except of course if its a gif.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Perfect camouflage</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 05:44:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 08:04:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meh! Pales in comparision to usual gifs posted here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL about Blanche Dumas, a french courtesan with 3 legs,4 breasts and two fully developed and sensitive vagainas. She is known to have entertained men with both of her vagainas.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 09:52:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 10:24:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that your sex doll? Good job. Here we prefer more professional ones, like the ones you get to see on /r/Sexdolls</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 11:00:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Googling the name "Blanche Dumas" will bring lots of articles (few look like duplicates/copies). Among them is a book [Anatomical Anomalies](https://books.google.com/books?id=CrU7BAAAQBAJ amp;pg=PA38 amp;lpg=PA38 amp;dq=Blanche+Dumas amp;source=bl amp;ots=1_k9C9fzNK amp;sig=7WjsMRkbxeZpSKElY9bKYpIKUJo amp;hl=en amp;sa=X amp;redir_esc=y#v=onepage amp;q=Blanche Dumas amp;f=false) that makes mention of this lady. If you are interested or have morbid curiosity like I have, do check out other pages of the same book.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This dragon pipe is really cool!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 02:55:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This dragon pipe is really cool!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 02:56:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A user on imgur quits job and travels entire Africa on his Scooter</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 03:00:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 03:03:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>This [user on imgur](https://imgur.com/user/theostacy) really seems amazing. Apparently he gave couple of watermelons to a family and here is the[ pic he took of the kid enjoying eating it](https://i.imgur.com/INCnc9y.jpg). It felt so good seeing the pic. So good. **Fucking Sooo good.**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ummm.. Watermelon</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 03:14:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 03:19:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Liking an African kid enjoying fruit = SJW?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 03:35:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, now I get it. I loved it so much. Posted it to /r/wholesomepics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 03:49:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus what are you doing. Wamen are alwayz bootiful. #bootieAtAllAges</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 04:40:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the [imgur post](https://imgur.com/GkTPYsx) from which I took the gif and it says the IG account of this poster is [this](https://www.instagram.com/p/BhNDGkjn4hz/?utm_source=ig_share_sheet amp;igshid=wymgejc0g5sb). As you can see, many people are wanting to buy (including me).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Greater Kudu, a Woodland Antelope Native to Africa (x-post from /r/NatureIsFuckingLit)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 05:34:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 12:26:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are there different pipes to smoke tobacco and weed? This comes as a surprise to me. Can you guide me or elaborate?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Inside a sex robot factory: The frighteningly realistic 'breed' of A.I-equipped androids</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 13:02:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 00:38:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>May be [this](https://www.reddit.com/r/india/comments/5ydjjf/ask_how_to_get_cannabis_indica_oil_in_india/) post can help you OP. It mentions the [website](https://buyhempoilindia.com/). Or if you have some contacts in US, they could buy the CBD oil and transfer it to some other innocuous oil bottle and ship it to you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 00:47:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck that man. /r/india is so negative that it really hurts hard. I've stopped going there for more than an year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 01:13:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh boy! Welcome. So good to see you back. You have no idea how much people really loved you. Here is a post someone made on /r/MensRights: [A user on /r/MGTOW got fired from his job and finds out that no employer will hire him because of a PO filed by his wife. He makes a good bye post around a month ago. I am crying uncontrollably.](https://np.reddit.com/r/MensRights/comments/86zztr/a_user_on_rmgtow_got_fired_from_his_job_and_finds/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 07:28:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I recently bought a Bong ~ 1.3k. Quick delivery and product is as good as they said it is. So far so good. One more person on this sub recommended the product and he has good things to say about Littlegoa. Here is the post where I was recommended to buy from Littlegoa. May be you can ping mdamkhan and ask your way around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 09:00:18</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Subhash usually has at least ~7 varieties in that one gully, most of it coming from the south. Sheeeit!! I've discovered a gold mine down south. Now I am fearful that it would get unwanted attention. Why don't you folks find something around your place. I protest!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 12:21:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>There goes the farm where I bought weed at.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 10:03:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't tell anything just by a picture. And I don't believe anyone who says they can. You be the judge. To be it looks just fine. Why, it looks good. This is how the weed looked before I sun dried it. Frankly, I find this displays of "score" pretty lame. Yeah, I can understand the feeling of achievement given the conditions and constraints but, c'mon folks if you think weed is part of your life, you'd have means to purchase them in bulk and have it ready at your finger tips. Btw, your series on edibles is great. I think I am ready to to try them. Will request your inputs may be in a day or two.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 10:07:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow man! Just wow! You, indeed are a weed connoisseur. That's quite a lot. What do you plan to do with it? Holy shit! half a kilo will get me going for an year or may be more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Woman tries to smuggle cocaine and ketamine in noodles packets, nabbed by NCB</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 10:10:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 10:12:46</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;She was travelling in a semi-sleeper bus. She was apprehended while alighting from the bus and was found to be in possession of 200 grams of cocaine and 100 grams of ketamine. Fuck they are now checking private buses? They've gone mad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 10:58:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I am falling in love with you. I read your posts, try to understand what you are doing, ask questions, try to imitate what you are doing. Boy, I am not gay and hope you aren't either. We should sit one evening and smoke our lungs out while munching on food I make. I am an excellent, top notch cook.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 11:01:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just a caution. Don't repeat that. It's too dangerous. Once you are on police record, your professional opportunities will shrink down to naught. I've seen that happening.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 11:23:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know why people snitch. What does the seller gain by snitching on his customer?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"The Pence rule is sexist and disadvantages women and the men who espouse it should be removed from their positions"[+4]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 11:44:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 11:53:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>So what do you want to know about who hurt? An address, a phone number, a picture, identification card, or identification marks on her? Tell me what you want to know, I will tell you all. A simple question though. What are you going to do after I give yo the information?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Octopus launch!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 13:15:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 03:15:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agree! I'v seen this happen to my little cousin(s) and my wonderful niece. I actually got into a fist fight with a heavy drunken asshole once at a train station. Fortunately people around me restrained him. Seriously there are creepy assholes who think every woman walking down the street is a doll for them to enjoy as they please. Though I'd say I will defend and protect my family members but I won't extend the same to strangers; let them have their family members look out for them. Not my family, not my people, not my problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 03:36:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>True that. There is something as being a just a good person, just for yourselves, as a part of your identity. Not to show it to others, not to get approval brownie points from others, just for yourselves about yourselves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 06:36:04</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;But every time I think about not being in a relationship I think about dying alone Boy, you think you wouldn't die alone if you are in a relationshit? If you are alone, at least you'd have money if you need to 'buy' some help. Else, you'd spend all your money on a piece of shit in expectations of companionshit (which will be promised but won't be delivered), family and children (which will be promised but will be taken away when you are sucked dry), grow old happily (you will grow old, no money with a wife that hates you for miscellaneous reasons that are traced back to events seven or ten years ago). No. I am a liar. Anyone who tells you anything here is also a liar. DON'T trust anyone of us here. You are the exceptional one. Every one here had a bad luck or we are all assholes that deserved what we experienced. Experience it by yourselves. Go ahead and get married. We are waiting here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Marriage explained simply!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 06:44:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bike!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 06:52:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 09:32:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell me what you are taking. I'd avoid that shit like I am in mortal danger.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 11:15:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>They've debunked wage gap with that video unwittingly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 11:37:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shoutout to /r/SexDolls</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 11:41:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait until men realize the actual cash women need is only likes and virtual thumbsup. They would strip for free, put out their ass on display for free. Don't you guys know /r/gonewild and other subs where women strip and pose for for validation, for **FREE**.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lighthouse stairs.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 12:01:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 12:28:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excellent choice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Surprise!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 12:34:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 12:39:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you mail me those seeds at my cost?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 12:55:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lo here I am. And there are many others. Just do your thing. If you smoke weed, hit me up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Harpya(1979, 9 min) a film by french director Raoul Servais</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 13:00:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>A city dweller, out for an evening stroll, hears a woman's cries for help and rescues her from an assailant who is trying to drown her in a public fountain. However, when our mild-mannered hero pulls her from the water, she proves to be not a woman but a harpy - with a woman's face and breasts and the body of bird of prey. He takes her home and treats her like a human, but she is true to her nature, mercilessly and ravenously taking command of the household, dispatching his pet, and trying to make sure he can't leave. When he does manage, by a clever ruse, to get out of the flat and enjoy a snack, things don't go as he'd hoped https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0261725/ And here is the [video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6ytotfJSLp8). Whenever you think of relationshit, first masturbate and then watch this video.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 13:22:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tumi bangla?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 13:25:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Joint porn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 13:33:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kid, don't drink or smoke (especially weed) until you are out of your teens,  gt; 21+ years. There is significant literature indicating permanent psychological and physical damage if you engage in those activities while you are still developing. Keep your head down. Eat good and healthy food. Learn cooking from your mother the best way as you can. Completely ignore women. Prepare well for JEE or something competitive at a national level well. Best wishes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 13:34:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, your name sounded as if you are a Bong/Bengali.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>6 Reasons to buy Sex dolls</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 13:41:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 13:41:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/SexDolls</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 13:47:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am an IIT grad. So if you are into something of that sort, I'd be glad to help you out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 13:59:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. I've never paid for any porn or pics. I can only hope other men not pay for it. But if they want to, well, it's a market.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The original Ent says Hi (x-post from /r/Pareidolia)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 14:17:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 18:13:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I relax. And do consulting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Trends on MGTOW being talked about elsewhere on reddit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 03:51:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is a new thread on a sub that supposedly meant for discussion among feminits and MRAs on "MGTOW is now beating 'how to get a girlfriend'" in google trends. Here is the[ link to archived version of the thread](https://archive.fo/HQvL2) There is one comment that triggered the mod and removed it. You'd be surprised how innocuous that removed comment is  gt;My personal experience is the girl who works at subway will refuse to date the dude who also works there. Women refuse to date down and are rarely willing to date on equal terms when it comes to a job and or social status. A dude will marry his secretary but most women in my experience would refuse to do that. I also notice a massive dislike among white collar women for blue collar men even if they earn good money which in my experience leads to some weird results. Anyway, I don't really feel good about this. I'd like this sub to be a secret, invisible to everyone but readily discoverable for those that seek it. Ideally I want zero visibility outside the sub. Obligatory MGTOW Tax : [Harpie](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6ytotfJSLp8). Also, always use image/[archive.is](http://archive.is/)/[waybackmachine](https://archive.org/)/Plugin for internet archive : [Firefox](https://addons.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/addon/wayback-machine_new/) and [Chrome](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/save-to-the-wayback-machi/eebpioaailbjojmdbmlpomfgijnlcemk?hl=en) to link to threads in other subs. EDIT: Just saw this [video of a guy](https://i.imgur.com/o5RCmRQ.mp4) who made drums out of pipes and playing them. Neat!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 04:14:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really? That many? I thought it's just a small niche that the rest of the world doesn't even know. Or is it MGTOW got into focus because of that lone Canadian incel ?(that guy was decent looking though)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 04:32:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would you like to have some fries with that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Discussions on Ketamine and LSD elsewhere on reddit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 05:27:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ocassionally there are posts on Ketamine and LSD. Here are two threads I found discussions about it. 1. [Ketamine is for horses, they said](https://old.reddit.com/r/WTF/comments/94j62a/ketamine_is_for_horses_they_said/) 2. Casual [discussion](https://old.reddit.com/r/NatureIsFuckingLit/comments/933i9r/water_droplets_on_a_dragonfly/) on LSD on /r/NatureIsFuckingLit Hope you get something out of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>