<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject5409</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why is Dark Seer not picked anymore?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-04 14:26:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>He is a flexible hero that fits into most lineups, just haven't seen him around... thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Workshop Tools crashing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-10 10:28:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>As soon as it finishes loading the asset browser, it crashes. I was really excited about making a map, too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is your favorite combination of 5 heroes and explain the reasoning behind it</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-11 13:11:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>My personal fav would be AA, Zeus, NP, Silencer, and Blood Cyka. My reasoning is the global damage will give BS vision and lightning speed to reach any target, and if Silencer gets scepter, this strat becomes even better. What do you think? Please share your ideas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Embrace the nostalgia!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-14 07:42:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Toilet Paper: under or over?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-07 00:34:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is Ness top tier? Look at these buffs.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-15 21:05:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the most awkward moment you have witnessed in a classroom?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-13 18:43:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Saw this interesting gizmo on the road today, any idea what it is?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-06 00:08:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why is there no way to prematurely end a match?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-02 01:12:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>The pros have this option, and the mechanics make sense. I don't see why we do not have this option available to all players. In Smite, there is a majority vote after 10 minutes, and it makes the whole gaming experience a lot better. There isn't even much frustration because not much time is wasted. Something like this is what Dota needs, in order to minimize wasting the losing team's time. Maybe start a vote at the 20 minute mark, and allow votes every 5 minutes. The majority of the team would have to agree. If a team feels like they have no chance, why draw it out? Food for thought. Also, if you are going to downvote, at least give a reason for it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL The first meal on the moon was bacon squares, peaches, sugar cookie cubes, pineapple grapefruit drink and coffee</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-09 21:40:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If time were slowed down for you, what mistakes would you still make?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-30 15:13:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If you could summarize your college experience in three words, what would those words be?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-19 23:39:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are Gamer Glasses actually effective at reducing eye damage?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-03 03:03:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are Gamer Glasses actually effective at reducing eye strain?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-03 06:28:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Graduates of Reddit, which is more difficult: school or your job?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-10 00:11:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Workshop still keeps crashing instantly upon loading interface, with no report</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-17 17:48:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is this subreddit a paradox?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 02:07:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Should trash be dumped into space?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 20:30:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Should trash be dumped into space?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 21:41:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When holding in a huge fart on a flight</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-14 19:30:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What process would be a lot worse if went from automated to human?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-30 01:30:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If your life was a game, what would the README file say?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-15 20:41:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is your life's "How-to-play"?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Test</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-09 20:13:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>printf("hi");</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Parents of reddit, what's the most interesting thing your kid said?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-04 22:58:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just got a new mini fridge. Should I remove the styrofoam wrapped around the metal here? http://m.imgur.com/tqjjRVg</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-11 00:38:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What was the best As-Seen-On-TV product?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-13 04:07:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Test</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-28 02:15:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>[word](www.google.com)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found this furry fellow in my apartment</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-14 23:04:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-26 18:58:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never tell the mods.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-27 17:32:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exponentially increasing cyclomatic complexity is a natural occurrence when developing in any situation. This in turn will increase the chance of bugs proportional to that complexity. You can take all the time in the world to develop a piece of software, but you'll still find bugs in your code. It's a natural part of development. The real challenge is minimizing bugs, and that becomes easier when you learn to use the right tools for what you are trying to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-27 19:12:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really wish they'd stop trying to milk the nostalgia / money out of old fans and just release new content already. I mean there are still a lot of Nintendo fans out there I think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-27 20:05:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there a subreddit with funny bugs like this? I love this kind of stuff</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-27 22:13:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love Splatoon, and that's the problem. There's not enough of titles like Splatoon out there. They are trying to get every last drop out of older titles and rehashing when they should be focusing on releasing new content. I mean who wouldn't want a new Metroid Prime type game for the WiiU?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-28 02:29:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>try this: https://www.assetstore.unity3d.com/en/#!/content/21288 You can't go wrong with toon shader especially with your low poly design here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-28 03:42:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you, this is what I needed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-28 05:14:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>2meta2furious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-28 05:24:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>To find the best birds, you've gotta shake up the earth a little bit. How neat is that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is Storm Spirit back?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-29 04:35:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>his Aghanims is sick, benefits from the 1% magic damage buff, and Bloodthorne would be awesome on him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-01 21:04:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>The things people will do for gold...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-02 01:00:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wanna solve this like Top Men</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-02 01:11:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/shittyaskscience</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Who needs shoes in a public restroom anyway?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-02 01:56:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-02 04:28:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's going old-fashioned Nintendo, back when they used to be in the [love hotel](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nintendo) business</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-02 20:37:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>2meta2furious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-06 01:06:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was snatching punani part of your plan?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-06 01:22:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, Donkeh!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-06 08:18:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>br0</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-10 03:56:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>let me get back to you on that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-11 05:41:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't like sand. It's coarse, rough, and it gets everywhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-16 14:13:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. There is no "programming gene" 2. The best way to learn is to dive into your interests. My interest is game development. I just started developing a game in Unity and now love coding and making games. You will make mistakes, but also learn a lot in the process. Hate reading? Just go with the hands-on approach and dive into something you're interested in. Github, coding challenges, anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-16 14:52:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>The key is to learn things one step at a time. If you try to learn too many things in one day, it will most definitely seem like no light at the end of the tunnel. Arrays are simple enough to start. Think about a grocery program to help you shop. I need a list of items to buy. How can I "write down my list"? Array is just a list of stuff. Use an array to store those items as strings, objects, whatever suites your program. Hope that example is easy enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-16 18:39:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Glad to help! I started with Visual Basic like you when I was in high school. Honestly I hated it and didn't want to pursue programming. It was only when I found something I was interested in that I wanted to learn how to code. Find your interests, pursue them, and learning to code will become natural. Take it one step at a time and learn what you need to achieve your goals.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-17 06:14:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>A delightful mix of pure elegance and simplicity</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-17 07:07:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>"One win, coming up." RIP my sides.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-17 20:42:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Defend the payload!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-17 22:55:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>k/d top notch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-18 19:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>hahah me too thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-19 03:17:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>the only time I've seen /r/splatoon leaking. Squidkids, [unite!] (http://imgur.com/JqYTmjn)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-19 05:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>How long did it take to get this far?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-19 18:36:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>*pushes up glasses*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-19 19:57:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Enhance! Enhance! Enhance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-19 20:05:21</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; they are not consumed. Would make for an interesting deny mechanic lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-20 04:43:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unity is a powerful tool for both beginners and professionals. Highly recommend it especially if you're into 3d game development.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-20 06:20:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This](https://unity3d.com/learn/tutorials/projects/roll-ball-tutorial) would be my first step. Follow through the entire thing to get a basic understanding of how Unity works. It's one of the best tutorials out there for Unity beginners. Hope this helps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-20 08:16:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shhh... no tears, only memes now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-20 17:08:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow this comment really clears a lot of stuff up for me. Action is louder than words I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-20 23:28:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love and gravity are both forces of attraction. Is gravity actually love? At the center of the black hole, Cooper expresses his love for Murph. The love acts as a massive force of attraction, thus creating the overwhelming gravity of a black hole. You can find me at /r/shittyaskscience</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-21 08:14:31</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; we need to build a YUGE splash wall FTFY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-21 16:31:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Makes me kind of want to start a new game as "The Trump" and exclusively use splash walls</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-23 23:36:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha oh man here we go</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-24 20:14:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>My Gameboy Color. Went to visit cousins up north, realized it was missing on the way back to the airport. Man that sucked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-25 05:30:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>hahah</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-25 05:57:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>hahah thanks and you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-25 06:02:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>1 year in this situation. She's making progress, but slowly. Had to basically say straight up I'm not attracted to her. She took it fairly well and is now doing regular cardio and eating right. You've got to be honest or else you won't get what you want in life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 00:02:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>hahah me too thanks and you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 01:35:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, like you need to counter Treant</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 20:31:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Freshman Computer Scientist here, can confirm I am an expert. I can now Java anything. In all seriousness though, I agree with you. What makes you knowledgeable on a subject is experience, which most college students don't have much of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 05:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>B T F O T F O</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 20:06:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone have a playlist for rap-vgmusic mashups like this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Chrono Trigger: Wind Scene mashup with Jay Z</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-01 03:04:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-01 06:17:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make Toss a debuff. Wouldn't be complex at all and would be nullified by buying back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-01 06:36:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make Toss a debuff. Problem solved!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-01 06:38:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>This would not be a bug if Valve simply made Toss a debuff. Edit: nevermind, it seems like the bug resides in not being able to buyback while disabled!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-01 23:00:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>dang</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-01 23:48:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least harsh truths can inspire positive lifestyle changes. Source: I've got as much muscle as a potato</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-02 17:27:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't find a picture of it, but my favorite has to be a Lego helicopter with the rescue hook underneath. Would fly that thing around the house trying to "rescue" everything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-03 20:16:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've got just the [thing](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xVMEthpONd0)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-06 18:37:41</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; 'oh so you have slanty eyes, how come?' Not sure that one would go well, I'd argue that's even worse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any tips for a Lucio noob?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-07 07:30:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>He seems fun, just looking for ways to get better with him. On a related note, where can I find competitive Overwatch discussion and data? Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-07 15:19:52</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Stunning Hah</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-07 17:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>"You're with the trees, aren't you?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-08 17:32:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or McCree</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-08 21:34:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha me too thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-09 00:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something something kid fall in and gorilla shot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-09 22:47:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was honestly expecting it to be top comment lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 05:26:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am simple man. Am Overwatch, Am upvote.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 05:50:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Thresher shark](https://www.reddit.com/r/gifs/comments/4ndncw/shark_hunts_with_giant_weaponized_tail/d430y5f)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 05:53:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thresher shark</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 05:54:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thresher shark</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 05:54:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>thresher shark commonly known as the thresher shark</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 17:23:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go to the Overwatch wiki and learn her inside and out. It helps to have exact numbers when you are playing any hero. Test different maps to find the best spots for her. Learn when to use her based on the maps or teams.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-11 21:46:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>XD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-14 02:55:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>"It'll work" -every engineer ever</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-14 03:00:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>It bugs me. Source: am Software Engineer ^^^haha ^^^get ^^^it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-14 03:07:25</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Hey there, buddy. I'm an engineer. That means I solve problems. Not problems like "what is beauty?", because that would fall within the purview of your conundrums of philosophy... I solve practical problems. For instance, how am I gonna stop some big, mean mother hubbard from tearing me a structurally superfluous new behind? The answer... use a gun. And if that don't work, use more gun. Like this heavy-caliber, tripod-mounted little ol' number designed by me, built by me, and you'd best hope... not pointed at you. #65279;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-14 03:31:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why do so many of them have tusks and fangs? Purist Thunderwrath looks totally badass though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-15 04:24:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Choo Choo! All aboard the Dingus train.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-15 21:21:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>And here I am, still a gold virgin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-15 21:24:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not with that attitude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-15 21:26:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nape vaysh /\V</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-15 21:27:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gold me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-15 21:28:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>DUNKEH!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-15 21:29:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>DUNKEH!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-15 21:30:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>ONIONS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-15 23:24:31</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I had slept with a mutual friend Not saying the dude is justified, but this part hurts a lot. I've been there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-16 21:03:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Donkey, two things okay? Shut...UP!**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-16 23:31:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>DIDN'T MAKE SENSE NOT TO LIVE FOR FUN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-17 08:36:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha... nothing like that X</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-17 08:37:59</DATE>
    <TEXT> #960; = Pi so it's Pi-rates.... HAH^ah^ah ^^^cough ^^^^^it ^^^^^is ^^^^^even ^^^^^less ^^^^^funny ^^^^^when ^^^^^explained ^^^^^like ^^^^^this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-18 06:37:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hi there.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 01:27:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 01:27:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 04:52:11</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; This is pretty much /r/relationships. That was the first comment on my post in r/personalfinance lol. We haven't had a conversation about it in person, and she just heard about it from a talk with her mom tonight. I want to discuss it with her this weekend. We have no joint finances, but I don't want to get pulled into a shitty financial situation here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 22:57:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what I hate about that clickbait title. Misleading information often gets more attention unfortunately...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 23:00:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>and Italy...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 02:40:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is this even downvoted? I thought it was pretty clear as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 06:44:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>hahaha I love Gintama, and this makes me love the show even more</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 07:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn't even get that. Where's my consolation prize? Source: 5'6" checking in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 08:51:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 08:55:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep, 22 y/o male. Only way to get bigger is to get buff! ...or fat but that would put me at about 0/10</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 21:07:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>he as in you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-22 16:27:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Versus... FIGHTING POLYGON TEAM</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-22 17:39:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's so shiny</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-23 15:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>B T F O T F O</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-24 17:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>It all makes sense now...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-24 19:19:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>ctrl-f "vore": 0 results Really? Guess I'm the only one then.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-24 19:27:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess you could say ( #8226;_ #8226;) Reinhardt encountered (  #8226;_ #8226;) gt; #8976; #9632;- #9632; a RogueVector ( #8976; #9632;_ #9632;) ^^^^YEEEAAHH</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-24 21:19:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>didn't know DVa was that big</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-24 21:38:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>The inconsistent ordering here really bugs me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-25 20:02:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd probably try it at least. Unless it has their cheese in it. That stuff is not cheese. Same goes for gay sex.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-27 05:57:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>My code compiles with only 10 errors the first time. Also, I don't comment anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 05:49:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This scene](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h1BQPV-iCkU) from Wall-E illustrates this concept pretty well I think. The ultimate in laziness as achieved by automation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 19:30:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can't kill the metal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 23:23:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very elegant, morbid warning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 23:29:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's very similar to a situation like [this](https://thumbs.gfycat.com/SoreImmediateEgg-mobile.mp4). Adrenaline takes over, and you are in a daze.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-30 10:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, like Riki Aghs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-30 10:42:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was very disappoint in hero choice for that one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-02 17:00:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whers me shert</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-02 17:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is why I play Mei. The devil's worst enemy is herself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-03 18:16:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically we're all in an [echo chamber](http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=echo%20chamber)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-03 22:20:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>H O T E L M A R I O O T E L M A R I O</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-07 21:20:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly I'd be fine with the current right click as it is now plus invulnerability during the charge time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-07 22:39:27</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128514; #128514; #128514; #128514; #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-07 22:53:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Correct, and you'll need it anywhere you'll use random numbers such as here: # [ $[ $RANDOM % 6 ] == 0 ]  amp; amp; rm -rf / || echo  #8220;You live #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-07 23:32:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well it's not exactly as easy as it seems. You'll need to use a root kit to access those numbers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-07 23:49:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd consult Yahoo Answers for advice, my expertise on hacking ends here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 11:54:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dadude - Dudestorm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 12:31:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>How does /r/dota2 sneak into every Reddit post?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-11 14:24:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just get the game and your questions will be answered</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-13 02:16:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>that one is actually Five Shots Rubbing Alcohol On A Sunday Night Liver Bomb</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-13 16:23:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Pizza Boys** are in **higher** demand than **musicians**.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-13 22:01:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>...and tabled.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-15 20:22:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>stay safe penwing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-15 20:56:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Aw, yeah! Turn up my jam! Right /u/Demetirus ? ... turns out he's a metal kind of guy"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>UI could use an upgrade</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-20 03:59:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seriously, it looks extremely outdated and unprofessional. Why the futuristic tech design for the main menu? Isn't this a game about ancient deities? The in-game menu looks like it got stuck in the alpha phase and never made it past that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-20 15:44:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean it's not only the design, but the icons look [scrappy](http://i62.tinypic.com/ra88z5.jpg) as well. For reference, here's the Dota 2 [item menu](http://107.170.126.251/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/shop-crop.jpg). The smite icons don't have any shading or fitting color schemes. I mean [come on](http://imgur.com/a/8NZQR) don't kid yourself. Inefficient use of space there. The text description unnecessarily takes up a lot of space. It could be a mouse-over and the item cost should just be underneath the icon. You would be able to view a lot more with such a simple change.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-20 16:02:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's not entirely true. It gives a greater sense of immersion when your game's UI is consistent with the overall theme.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-20 16:41:24</DATE>
    <TEXT> #3900;  #12388;  #9685;_ #9685;  #3901; #12388; SERVERS TAKE MY ENERGY  #3900;  #12388;  #9685;_ #9685;  #3901; #12388;  #3900;  #12388;  #9685;_ #9685;  #3901; #12388; SERVERS TAKE MY ENERGY  #3900;  #12388;  #9685;_ #9685;  #3901; #12388;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-20 17:44:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-23 15:26:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/titlegore</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-25 16:18:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Call Mech OP, pls nerf</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-28 17:06:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>No thread</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-28 17:27:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>pics or it didn't happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-28 19:49:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>He might just have the best personality in the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-31 17:14:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Torb needs a sprinkler next to him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 00:22:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>something something no more footsteps</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 15:19:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Minor text fix</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-05 21:20:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>*furiously taking notes*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-09 05:07:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>So what your saying is the crazy bullshit is stalled, man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-09 17:17:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha thanks, and you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-10 16:36:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Vietnam War flashbacks*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-10 18:47:23</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; He'll be so sick when he's a 100%IVenusaur FTFY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-11 00:32:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's asleep. Give him another 4 hours for a wholesome rest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 16:25:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks Ken M</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 16:57:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>How did this comment trigger so many nerds?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 20:15:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's also a fact that PC gaming is always superior for many reasons when it comes to multiplatform gaming.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 21:41:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean the bait was so obvious though, damn I think I'm just getting old.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-17 13:49:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>--" #19981; #20877;"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-17 14:06:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>nope. proud to be OCD-free.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-18 12:28:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>You forgot to capitalize the 'e' in egg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-19 19:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>might be a stretch, but was it Two Guys?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-29 21:47:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stop triggering me! get out normie get out REEEE!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-02 01:53:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Especially if you are **Psychic** type.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-03 20:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess they don't believe in !=</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-07 22:09:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>About the indie side questing: How do you balance your indie deving and family time? Just curious, as I plan to go basically this exact route upon finishing college.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-08 04:47:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does that actually work?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-12 21:29:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice b8, m8</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-12 22:08:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I miss God. What a great hero concept.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-13 20:37:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>were you confident you would make it inside?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-14 00:39:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol why is this even downvoted</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-14 21:00:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why would it only work with lure? Incense makes way more sense considering you benefit from walking while using incense. Hope they realize this mistake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-15 02:59:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess I expect too much from Niantic. Their speciality *is* minor text fixes after all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-16 07:34:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rip in pepperoni</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-16 22:39:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pastor says hogs were created to become bacon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-16 22:47:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>and the STUPIDITY continues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-19 03:48:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-20 01:14:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>W</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-23 20:59:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>boy's SOUL cmon Frank</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-23 21:49:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too, thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-25 21:11:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-25 21:11:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-26 15:27:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>while(yoggSpellMana  lt; manaFromSpellsCast) { spell = RndSpell(); yogg.Use(spell); yoggSpellMana += spell.cost; }</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-27 03:33:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-30 19:56:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>then grab a band-aid</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-07 13:32:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ideally the width comes from muscle, not fat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-12 03:32:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like. big. posteriors.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 21:19:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had a threeway with her and /u/Hack1137</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-19 02:10:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>username checks out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-19 19:27:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Slaking would be ok if not so damn lazy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-20 04:12:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You tried.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 19:27:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not really... they've been rehashing and re-releasing the same games almost exclusively. Sure there's titles like Splatoon and Bayonetta, but we need them to have more 3rd party titles. Switch looks to be headed in that direction and will broaden Nintendo's target audience for sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 19:32:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know you're joking, but it seems more aimed towards portability such that you can just bring it to a friend's place and play together.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 19:32:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Speak for yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 20:56:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>At the same time though, that distrust severely limits their library. It's one of the main reasons they've fallen behind in popularity and I'm glad to see that they are allowing a more open market.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 21:15:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's got a [point](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0108255/). PG Rated. Also, I apologize to whoever is just now learning that this movie exists.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 22:38:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; capped to 800mb/per day  gt; average speed of 100kbps My sides.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-22 04:07:56</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Splatoon isn't an "adult game", I'm sorry ...[what?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XemNst4UFF4) I agree with some of the stuff you said like with Paper Mario and Switch being geared towards the millennial generation, but you should check out how Splatoon is currently an eSport, albeit not as large as others. Just because it's fun for kids and easy to pick up (same as Melee) doesn't mean it can't be competitive and considered an adult game as well when you take into account the eSports community behind the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-23 20:40:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometimes skill helps, but usually not too much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-25 01:09:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am still playing it every now and then on the DS. Which by the way was an amazing port with fun minigames, thieving rabbits, multiplayer, and... you can *actually* unlock Luigi haha... anyone else tricked by that as a kid?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-25 01:10:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Echoes was great too. Amazing atmosphere and music.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-28 21:18:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>*G amp;W Judge 9*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-29 20:20:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Always.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-29 20:47:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's the boy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anyone else a Nintendo bag-holder?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-30 01:48:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean surely the Switch will bring it back to Pokemon Go hype levels... *nervous laugh*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-30 02:12:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let's just say I jumped onto the hype train right before it crashed. Also, it was and still is my only stock I've bought independently. (NTDOY)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-30 19:01:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Godspeed, /u/fuckthislifeee</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-30 19:13:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>He should try having a more zen attitude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-30 22:31:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>He clearly said he didn't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wish I was this good at riding the bull market</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-01 23:50:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-01 23:56:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>s a v a g e a v a g e</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 19:57:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spy sapping my... entire team!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How will the release of Sombra change the meta?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 20:30:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which heroes will be countered or combo well with her? What do you think about invisibility being in the game now?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 21:28:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Given: upvotes - downvotes = points  amp; upvotes + downvotes = votes We can find the # of upvotes and downvotes using only points and votes. 1. upvotes = votes - downvotes 2. (votes - downvotes) - downvotes = points 3. (votes - downvotes) = points + downvotes 4. votes = points + 2*downvotes 5. (votes - points) = 2*downvotes 6. (votes - points)/2 = downvotes Edit: Haha, oh man here come the downvotes. You guys realize that "50 points/7483 votes" is actually an impossible combination right? Try to prove me wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 21:56:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Interestingly enough, that vote total and point value is actually impossible because you end up with half-votes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anyone else hear this sound in your head when looking at posts on here?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 22:00:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-06 21:26:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>No more Splatfests, but the game is still very active and fun. No guarantees on that Splat2n release date, so go for it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-08 22:00:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>***ENHANCE***</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 01:02:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The way their heads split matches their campaign. Hilary's mouth and mind are separated, signifying differences in what she says and what she thinks. Trump's head is split in half, signifying his mind is broken.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 01:43:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>had to read the comments to get it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 01:59:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unreal Tournament 2004 ONS-Torlan. I'd lose because that was my jam back in the day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-10 05:33:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are who you choose to be...  gt; Superman</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-10 08:13:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're all Iron Giants on this blessed day</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-10 17:42:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Be a hound!*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 06:52:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>(dank)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-13 07:52:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>***boil em mash em stick em in a stew***</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-13 07:54:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me 2 thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-17 21:18:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Classic graduate financial status.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-23 03:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>So what you're trying to say is...Ditto</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-28 15:35:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder how long the squirrel lives in the heron...and what it might be thinking?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-28 23:44:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>REEEEEEEEE STOP TRIGGERING ME, NORMIEEEE! ^^^^lol ^^^^reading ^^^^these ^^^^comments ^^^^is ^^^^fun</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-28 23:52:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha sort by controversial for the Youtube tier comments.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 18:46:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>#***Where there's smoke...***</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 21:27:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Certified Googler is the official position name. At least to coders. ^^^Shhh ^^^don't ^^^tell ^^^anyone ^^^else ^^^our ^^^secrets.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 03:32:25</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; You spelled Sombra Wrong Does not contribute to discussion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 11:22:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry about that!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 21:17:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>unexpected Pack Pride on reddit. **Go Pack!**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 21:20:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>What if your mom is a duck, /u/Duckcest ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 23:19:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then it's probably the former. Find better friends is my suggestion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DotADeMoN has admirers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-03 06:25:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-03 10:55:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was looking for this comment. Dude looks like Trump's dad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-03 11:00:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really? No one is going to talk about how cute this guy is?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Game Of Thrones in Bossa Nova</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-04 10:55:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-04 11:41:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-06 09:00:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>#***UP***</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-06 22:08:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know... I have always thought the color blue when applied to animals was misplaced and looked just grey. I think I understand why they are called blue now, they actually look blue!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-06 23:49:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pastor says chewing on condoms prevents pregnancy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 20:25:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should see a doctor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-08 17:12:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rockin, rockin and rollin...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-08 17:13:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're kinda pitchy...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-08 22:37:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stat distribution. You can't have Strength, Constitution, Dexterity, Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma all maxed out. Otherwise, playerbase would be boring and not diverse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Two Years</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-09 22:20:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-11 02:18:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>And now it's taking pure damage as it walks around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-14 03:39:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>GOOD point</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My Budget Gaming Box ~$600</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-14 04:02:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-14 06:07:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's basically [this](https://pcpartpicker.com/guide/vpMnTW/entry-level-gaming-build)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-14 06:16:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, but it is upgrade-able.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-16 17:05:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>a VERY sad photo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-16 18:57:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>And the people bowed and prayed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-16 20:29:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your cat looks slightly possessed by Satan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-18 01:01:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favorite subreddit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-18 01:04:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/outside</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-19 17:51:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'M READY TO ACTIVATE SHIT-POST SEQUENCE.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 23:47:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also height.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 18:39:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>....for a price.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 18:42:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>"""We need Tank"""</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-24 01:55:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 00:29:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>If</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 04:36:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I laugh out actually at this loud.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 04:14:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Peasant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 20:22:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>REEEEEEEEEEEEE^al ^nice ^explanation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 20:32:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>ITT: People claiming that these cart escalators are everywhere. Am I the only one here who hasn't seen one of these before?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 02:01:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>HAhaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-05 15:57:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>So...what does she watch?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-05 16:00:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wife and I like our references with supplemental memes. Keeps the redditing nice and fresh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-06 19:13:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mercy would be able to capitalize off the other heroes' movement much better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-06 19:28:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have answers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 15:05:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Call up his ex!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 17:05:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Came here to say this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-08 04:19:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're good dogs Br #252;nt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-08 18:58:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>hAHaH</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you wake up, how do you get ready for the day?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-08 22:19:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 02:43:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>ayy lmao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 04:43:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>So far [this](https://www.reddit.com/r/starwarsspeculation/comments/3w421j/snoke_as_force_sensitive_kaminoan/) does seem like a possibility.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 17:51:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha I get it! Sex!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 17:56:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>At the bottom is [this](http://i.imgur.com/d64Dg1K.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 19:46:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>The floor is actually its body</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 23:00:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 23:27:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Worked for me every year except Sophomore year of college. That's where they weed students out. After that year, I continued this trend however.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 06:09:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Genuinely curious, how is [this](http://www.revitcity.com/object_docs/14808.jpg) not better than that? Isn't there a lot of unused space between the corner drawer and the regular ones in the design OP posted?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 06:17:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's interesting how he starts off defending the efficiency of the corner drawer, then quickly changes his argument to be about practicality. *munches on popcorn*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 06:23:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would definitely buy this if someone made these.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 06:33:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why not just prevent things from falling off the lazy Susan? [Someone else](https://www.reddit.com/r/interestingasfuck/comments/5n0ro7/corner_drawer/dc87kkl/) suggested this in the comments. Seems like the perfect solution to the lazy susan vs corner drawer debate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-16 20:44:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now that's a SPICY meme.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 05:38:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chance of extreme consequences vs. low reward (Reddit karma). What am I missing here?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 05:50:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>#</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 05:55:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>The real joke is in the ^overused ^^comment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 23:52:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry about that!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-19 00:04:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>SEE YA LAYDER</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-19 00:47:01</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Dude eats it hard. Hey he might have enjoyed it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 07:53:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hang on now, he hasn't even married yet!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 07:53:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>If this gets 1000 upvotes I won't bamboozle anyone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 18:25:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>!!!JC niart nmad eht wollof si od ot dah uoy llA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 18:38:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-21 00:00:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 05:03:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; family lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 05:05:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sleep tight pupper</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 05:06:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>F</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 23:38:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Doubt he has "everything". some things can't be bought.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 01:12:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok, so I should downvote then. Got it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 01:13:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>me too thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 01:25:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally any other land mammal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 01:31:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Confetti when shredded to pieces.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 02:41:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Neither. They want to capitalize off of the sequel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 23:05:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>SPICY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 23:28:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>So are you a C++ wiz now or what??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-01 15:51:21</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Crazy stuff. Man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-01 23:24:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is not normal at all. Go see a doctor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-01 23:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honkeys be hatin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 17:47:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yosh!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 17:40:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-05 07:18:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're welcome!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-05 21:26:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>shut fuck up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 05:36:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. Do read what he asks, as he usually makes at least one of the short answer questions about the reading. Most important is to take notes of the lectures. He sometimes directly tells you certain things are free game for the exam. Great professor and I hope you enjoy his class!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 14:15:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Waluigi number waaaahn!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 20:15:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't tell them apart.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 20:17:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait...doesnt that mean you've already visited it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-08 13:55:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>same...it's like he's preparing his dogs to chase someone down lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-09 20:12:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>A little bit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 21:20:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>2META2FURIOUS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-11 20:18:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-11 22:29:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>very good, haha yes!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 13:37:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sort by controversial for the insulting comments.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 19:36:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hell yeah he is!! #Musk4PresidentAfterTrumpIsImpeached</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 19:39:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>-Even if it is copied beforehand</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 17:14:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Grand Dad is a Great Game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-19 21:59:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gotta stock up on my Rad-X, give me a sec</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 01:15:22</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; spaghetti place Bruh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 01:15:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>The cheese rises!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 14:25:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can confirm. Once channeled the power of the sun as an energy blast in a dream. 10/10 would blast again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 14:32:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good composition, but electric guitar sound could be better. Overall, I like it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 14:36:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>- Genghis Khan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 21:47:45</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; At 300 meters Per second?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 03:38:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's the mixing. I think some slight pitch correction on the lead could really make a difference here. It just seems slightly off, but once you do that, it would sound much better. Hope this helps! Edit: to be more specific the lead part around 1:30 is the part I think could be improved</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 14:43:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jajajaja noob</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-24 00:24:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>breh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-24 00:29:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>You thought it was a Jojo reference, but it was me, DIO!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-24 05:57:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>phenomenal ult zen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-25 17:54:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>thresher shark</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 03:03:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rabbes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 21:39:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jazz version: https://youtu.be/Y6tF6aEK1W4</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 01:54:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://i.imgur.com/wcKAZcH.gif</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-01 14:11:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>#LEAD ME TO THE LAND, THAT YOU UNDERSTAND#</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 02:10:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah... Am I missing something here??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-05 22:22:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been hurt too much by these false promises. Not upvoting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 00:13:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey don't be so harsh on yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 00:25:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm obsessed with the Moana soundtrack</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 01:01:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably went on to not be a pimple-faced fat dude so that he isn't recognizable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 01:02:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>^^^^and ^^^^vore ^^^^fetishes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 01:04:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>#M E D I O C R E# #B O I S#</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-11 21:26:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>now *that's* a proper roast.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-14 13:19:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Username checks out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-14 16:10:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>SysAdmin porn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 05:20:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go to an animal shelter. Get pics with kittens and puppies. Also, be casual and not desperate sounding. You're welcome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 05:24:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can confirm. Was one of few guys not desperate in online dating. Got girl(s). (I'm 5'6" btw)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 05:32:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's no need to be upset, Brunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-17 13:40:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well it is when opportunity meets preparation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 17:54:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 00:08:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 22:33:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's why I keep necessities away from my son. Don't want to taint the boy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 23:34:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you just assume his gender?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 22:46:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>So that must be what it's like to die alone and afraid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 23:01:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Came here to say this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-30 06:41:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>that manikin is my spirit animal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 00:55:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not all carrots are orange. Some are purple. The reason orange ones are most common is because of Dutch independence. Not even kidding.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 01:11:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Got some stank I want to spraaaay....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 15:41:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Best phone I've ever had was an Android. Galaxy Note 4 since 2013, still going strong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 03:17:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean what else is the gif about?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-04 04:11:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>she may be a murderer, but her spelling is on point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-08 17:10:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>brutal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-08 17:10:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>brutal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 06:42:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 19:08:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>REE^ee^^ee</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-10 05:13:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe not, but it's just easier to use the fracture tool in blender. ^^^at ^^^least ^^^that's ^^^how ^^^I ^^^did ^^^it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 00:35:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reading that manga gave me chills. It wasn't particularly scary, but that feeling of dread was what made it so intriguing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 00:36:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>this is my hole...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 14:04:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's almost as if Reddit consists of different age groups, of which some post childish and unfunny things.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 22:57:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems like something from Portal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is it possible to live off of just brain food?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 00:34:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 03:30:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Small if false.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 05:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>ajsdavslkme me big boyasdiubfoi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-13 17:36:28</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Orisa What a babe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 15:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Except for a lot of people. Relatively speaking console-wise, yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 14:21:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because this is Reddit. Believe it! ^^^/s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 05:25:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am one with the payload and the payload is with me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 06:09:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>My money's on you getting lazy over time and giving up. It's tiring. Prove me wrong and I'd like to see your ideas!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 18:24:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Big if true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-20 23:59:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Joined United Airlines</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 06:22:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you ever heard the tragedy of Darth Shitpost the Redditor?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 21:43:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. She sounds like a crazy. Teach her respect or get out. Unless you're into abuse...I mean hey everyone has their kinks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 21:48:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>WTF. Dodged a bullet there, bro.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 22:55:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically Crocs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 06:25:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>More like "Trump does not understand simple concepts."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 10:05:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my god, the Battle Frontier made Emerald AMAZING, easily my favorite "3rd" version of the Pokemon games. I'm a sucker for nostalgia though, which would probably put Silver first, but Emerald is a *strong* second.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 21:49:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>For whatever reason, it always seemed like they intentionally would put the hardest question first on exams. Idk why, maybe it's the initial stress of starting the exam. Anyway, glad I'm done with college.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 01:46:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hang in there. Sounds like you've got a solid plan. Study hard and try not to get distracted by the girls too much. I know my gpa took a hit after I started dating in college.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 02:49:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same, though not always a great long term prospect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 05:54:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>assertFalse(true);</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 05:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>united airlines</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 18:05:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was in the Ruins of Alph in Pokemon Silver. Was going for that 100% pokedex after beating Red. Save file corrupted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 19:01:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or "sometimes in order to reach your goals, you've got to cheat a little bit" lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 23:59:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>ITT: Redditors who were beaten as a child and do not feel empathy towards OP because they're too edgy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 00:29:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>So are we trusting Ronnie the Rapper to be our authority on what's cool?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 05:08:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Sebulba buffer overflows your pod*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 05:11:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>foreach(arm in arms) { equipLightsaber(arm); } I'll deal with this jedi slime *myself*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 06:52:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Too white for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 07:25:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Microsoft what now? ^^^^RIP ^^^^Edge</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 10:01:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>*after talking to It* "Alright alright I've heard enough. Now I'm getting depressed."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 17:55:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>SCATTAH</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 05:36:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>whars the salade</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 06:33:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Russian?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 07:05:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was assuming I was straight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 07:36:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>How does knowing you're handsome make you less handsome?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 22:47:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Them Hyenas doing that Deer a HECKIN bad time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 23:15:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>What?? Where do you live? Mall food is not cheap here...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-28 18:59:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or just put kernels in a bowl like that guy said.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 00:02:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think he does...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 00:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>or replace peach with party... amateurs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 07:02:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>ew, please don't do that. What's the point of even asking that at a job interview?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 14:09:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's making me irrationally angry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 01:17:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you're late for work but your bro got your back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 03:09:14</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Very yellow white flash!  gt;A violent wrench grips mass, rips light, tears limbs like rags</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 03:13:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Yes](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S3fTw_D3l10). Story about a war photographer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 03:17:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a verse from "Taro" by the band Alt-J. Great song.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 07:13:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're fat. That's what she's trying to say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 07:00:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Doot doot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 07:01:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>But replaced One with Doot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 18:41:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's all the touchy SJWs. I thought it was funny.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 18:25:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't woooaoont a pickle..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-08 17:57:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Downvoted b/c of edit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-08 18:27:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It clearly says Husk with stick and teeth. He then opens it with the machete.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 00:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sleeping with its mom? Its arms must be broken.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 06:42:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean ideally if you wanted $100, you'd price it a bit higher than that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 08:11:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah if we're talking about Craigslist, people can and will haggle. That's how it works. I don't know what platforms you might be talking about, but you can't avoid negotiations in some of them, so it's better to price higher. Being picky and waiting for the right seller to come by not only wastes time, but it may never happen. If you don't want people haggling your price down, just use something like Amazon seller. Hard price that can't be negotiated and it's easy and free.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 12:04:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep it's the Note 7 that exploded</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 12:21:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Small price to pay to keep m'lady from escaping</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 01:22:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, who could forget the delectable appetizer garbae.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 02:09:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Logically, what he did makes perfect sense. I'd be proud of him!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 02:36:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>well with that logic, he should have treated them as [words](http://www.makelinux.net/books/lkd2/ch19lev1sec2)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 03:45:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>-disable_teammate_help 1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-12 12:40:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just Hit the gym, Delete your lawyer, and Facebook up. It's that easy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 04:55:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 04:55:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>^^choo ^^^choooo ^^^^:(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 06:50:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ever played the game Splatoon? The main story is basically you have to restore power to the city with this giant eel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 20:21:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nowhere to go but down!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-19 20:23:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>You. Front of the bus, now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-19 20:25:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can totally relate to that statement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-19 20:27:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>He be rollin down the street</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 00:49:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Life, [uh](https://media.giphy.com/media/A3L5BeHxAXLWM/giphy.gif), finds a way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-21 19:23:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>...and?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 07:53:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>wtf is wrong with that cat's mouth? looks photo shopped</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 16:27:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me2tanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 18:00:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's an actual person btw</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 18:38:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Should also have experience with * Ember * AngularJS * React * jquery * .NET * Angular 2 * Angular 4 * SQL * MONGO DB * Cobol * Scala * Visual Basic * Salesforce</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-26 15:56:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/wholesomememes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 13:16:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>4u</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-01 06:59:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your the worst kind of person their is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 02:46:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>^^^^^^:(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 02:53:02</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128549; #128549; #128549;ouch #128547;LAD #128547;now #127865; THAT'S #128134; #128076;what #128405; #128073;I #128064; #128064;call #128586;EDGY #128298; #128298; #128298; #128298; #128298;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 06:18:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you're tired of babysitting, so you just let the kids play until they get exhausted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 20:24:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>"But Dad, I don't like cleaning chimneys! They smell bad and it's gross." Don't let them guilt trip you like this. Gotta pay the bills somehow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 00:49:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Eyes burn with stinging sweat..."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 00:53:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bout to drop the next hit single "Trap King"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 08:15:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let me get them digits breh. In all honesty though you look great. Congrats!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 11:04:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>CYA LAYDER</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 13:13:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah wtf OP where do you work?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 18:14:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>It seems that in your anger...you super soaked her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 15:50:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>holy prophet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-18 04:25:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a small pupper</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-18 16:15:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pastor says ideas should be run by him first, before we allow them to be heard by others.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-30 08:00:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 02:00:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which way out though?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 17:43:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sen... SEN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 23:08:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never trust a fart... Not even your own</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 02:36:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Despite the constant negative covfefe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 18:10:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's basically Skyrim but with with Guns</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 07:37:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>DOLT.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 15:22:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don't *swing* it like you used to, man...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 17:40:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well Tamatoa hasn't always been this *glam*...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 18:17:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blasphemy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 18:18:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>print("Henlo you STINKY bird");</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 18:22:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>hahaha *throws football up and catches it*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 20:05:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think she just doesn't like cleaning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>US Citizen moving to Finland</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 22:26:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Considering moving to Finland as a Software Engineer. What are some thing I should know before pursuing this? Is it difficult to make this kind of move? I don't speak Finnish btw. Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 08:11:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's always at its best. I mean c'mon, it's a shitpost by our president on Twitter. How does that get old?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 04:58:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess he's saying it's too much trouble to get them all? Personally, I thought it was worth it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 18:46:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am all cows on this blessed day  #128591;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 23:06:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>You Only Get One Vote</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 00:29:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Saw them in greensboro, nc. They were amazing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 12:21:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>[PUT,POST,GET,DELETE] http://www.poop.com/on/her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-05 20:14:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I kind of get it... the music seems so generic and catch-all oriented that it can make you feel a bit isolated. A lot of pop music uses vocal processing to make weird noises mostly unintelligible, so I can see what he's saying. That being said, do most people still like it? Well, it wouldn't be pop^^ular music otherwise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 08:34:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>me_irl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 20:40:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looking at this post and it's comments probably halved my lifespan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 17:50:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>We will do nothing because we have no power.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 17:55:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>ghost.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 23:28:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>So for the shattering effect... Did you just use Blenders fracture tool?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-11 02:24:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh nice! Dang, I need to really start using UE. I have been working on a game that involves destruction similar to yours, with that shatter effect made using Blender's fracture. I should get around to finishing that... anyway congrats on the game guys! Incredible that you can balance a full-time job with this side-hobby to release a full game!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 00:14:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>ITT: people who don't get older jokes..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 23:38:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>rip</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 17:58:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never says she doesn't know what a Lynel looks like, only asks to show her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 20:16:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I named my son Sparky before we had him get struck by lightning, why not the bison?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 21:29:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like a Turd.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 21:45:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 22:51:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here come dat b-</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 07:03:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>My son likes the ravioli flavored kibble. GOOD product.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-25 15:17:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly any soda + rum is great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 11:00:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>The ultimate closure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 22:50:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always upvote sym deathball</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 22:54:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually this isn't the camera panning, it's steadily increasing the field of view. Idk why this would happen though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 00:23:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm hella stupid, lemme read this. Edit: I cant believe I read that whole thing. I need an adult.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 15:59:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Certain things appear in rainy weather</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 05:11:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>But muh fEelz breh, I'm sPeCial</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 18:29:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>C U M U L O N I M B U S B O Y E</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 18:31:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could also add Guy to that list in A. ^^^and ^^^maybe ^^^B</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 18:44:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be fair, being DevOp is probably a buff overall.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 18:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I *always* upvote Drake and Josh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 19:31:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The collision handling resolves his position to be underneath the terrain, causing him to fall until otherwise. Looks like he went prone, which can cause collision resolution issues. Possibly could be due to some change of state when exiting the vehicle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 04:49:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omae wa mou shindeiru.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 05:24:04</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128169;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 07:44:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anything else is grounds for perma ban on this blessed server.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 02:36:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 06:15:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like it, but would have probably made the brass more prominent to give a more intense feel. That's just my personal preference though, we all have different tastes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 03:18:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>###YOU'LL FLOAT TOO###</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 00:19:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something is probably seriously off about your resume. You should get a professional to help you build one or just look at examples online.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 18:45:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Black Mirror anyone?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 19:05:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im a Muggin irl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 22:47:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's my guess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-02 01:23:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll need a scalpel to tear your chest apart. Now here's some drugs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-02 23:56:39</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Nutella smoothie bowl Uhhhh wat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 03:46:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Follow the rule of ones instead. One responsibility per module. Makes testing and refactoring a lot easier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 00:48:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this comment chain really going to cover all Korok locations? I hope so, because I need some help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 23:55:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not even compliance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 01:37:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>This. Dude is probably paid by hour. Chances are knows its a joke but will gladly do that than actual work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 01:42:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>He would, but his arms are broken. -Mom</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 06:03:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>DS Lite was probably one of my favorite consoles. It was easy to flash and had so many great games. The buttons and form factor are so smooth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 07:43:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>The CEO's big sala^^^d ry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 21:50:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>And here I was thinking a comment like that would be the top comment..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 21:53:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey cheer up, you can always throw Siri and Google Voice in the mix. AI partyyy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 21:54:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>You had me at good ass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 23:41:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's been a while, but you can try getting the Cardboard app and access YouTube from that. Should allow you to find those 360 videos and plenty of other stuff. Edit: it's called "360 Video Channel" and you can get it through the Cardboard app.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-07 19:09:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mom definitely looks cooler.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-07 19:12:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm seeing the glimmering yellows as symbols of hope in searching through the dark canvas...interesting piece! +1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 23:16:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blasphemy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 23:23:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ideally it actually should be self documenting though. Who will actually maintain comments and / or documentation? Write the code so that someone totally unfamiliar with your project could figure it out. Practice proper naming conventions and you shouldn't need anything else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 23:34:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gym up, Delete Lawyer, Hit the Facebook</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 03:22:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some are not as fortunate as to have expendable money outside of paying bills. That being said, if you can, invest while time is on your side!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 03:26:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fairy revival into death is my favorite part about this gif</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 03:03:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Mandy, why aren't you upvoting my memes?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 18:27:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Post it now!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 00:22:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dolt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 02:51:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Speak for yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 04:27:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mama Mia Mama Miaaaa! Mama Mia give him a raise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 05:44:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>All this needs is sunglasses panning down onto dude's face as he walks out. Maybe a "Thug Life" caption too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 17:15:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Polite Men with Audience</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 17:21:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>"It was that damn red shell outta nowhere!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 20:03:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol at "educated guess". I'm gonna take a guess here: you're projecting your own insecurities.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 20:07:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be fair, his face looks like dog poo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 20:59:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel personally attacked with the second row.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 21:25:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Game of Pwns</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 22:51:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>...but that wasn't an album.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 23:41:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love GameMaker, and learning C# and Javascript was really fun when I was making games in Unity. It's good to know how to build practical applications, but game development is how I started and I wouldn't have it any other way. Bugs are typically way more interesting and fun to fix in game development as well. One time I had a bug in my script for player movement, but I liked the behavior better than what I was going for, so I just kept it! One of the few times a bug literally became a feature.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 05:04:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol I knew someone would point this out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 16:44:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Be afraid. The technology for that is already here!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 16:44:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dolt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 19:09:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Owning so many companies probably doesn't leave you with much family time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 19:18:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Downvoted because that doesn't align with my views.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 05:12:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fellow Charlotte resident here. Just got off the Lynx, first time too. Was a fun way to go to uptown at night and had some delicious ramen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 08:28:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ever had a Man Slamwich?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 08:45:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Downvoted. This kind of degeneracy is what's killing the Reddit community.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 15:16:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sake! Sake! Sake! *Shatters arcade machine with palm*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 19:25:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Polite and informative. Am I still on Reddit?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 19:30:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why not do it? They're in Russia. What else to do other than hack servers and down power lines?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 20:38:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hope you find it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 03:01:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was Futo Buta! Wouldn't say it's like authentic ramen, but it's more of a fusion thing. Very delicious though and it's right next to the Bland Station.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 05:13:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, I'll check it out! Always looking for good asian restaurants in Charlotte.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 06:09:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>some might even go as far as [this] (https://en.rocketnews24.com/2013/09/03/limb-lengthening-surgery-becoming-increasingly-popular-in-korea-despite-inherent-dangers/) to escape manlet status. gotta have that $$$ though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 18:56:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the great thing about Open Source though. You can just improve upon the software how you see fit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 23:43:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why would I play this game over Call of Duty: World At War? What is the difference?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 03:15:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm 100% serious. Game looks like a cheap rehash.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 03:28:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure how well it would work, but [Wine](https://appdb.winehq.org/objectManager.php?sClass=version amp;iId=29690) may be worth a shot?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 03:36:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who is this kid? looks like a mix of all races.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 05:05:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol... thanks for this actually. Would've had no idea where it was from with just ST.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 18:25:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or as some might say "idiotic".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 18:27:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Concurrently, there may be a few people who have watched Rick and Morty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 23:50:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>underrated comment. ^^because ^^ya ^^know, ^^HAL ^^Laboratory... ^^^ehh ^^^nvm ^^^no ^^^one ^^^will ^^^get ^^^the ^^^joke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 06:16:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>To shreds you say?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 22:48:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yikes! Not sure why you are so heavily downvoted... but you are absolutely right. Not to downplay how cool it looks, but yes we've had this technology built into game engines such as Unity and Unreal Engine for years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 22:52:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>out of what profits... millions of dollars? EA won't care at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 00:11:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. The market will buy their product, a few people won't make a difference.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 08:43:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Musk for President 2020! He probably doesnt know shit about politics, but then again neither does Trump. At least someone who has the goal of making the planet a better place would be in charge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 09:01:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not gonna lie, it made me a bit nauseous. Maybe tone it down a bit?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 10:45:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, giving the player an option like that is always a good idea. I do love the art! Did you create the assets? If so, what tools did you use to make them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 11:02:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>baybee!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 12:17:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very cool! Good that you 2 seem to understand the development scope very well. Keeping the scope realistic while making the game as fun as possible can be hard. Good luck to ya!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 01:23:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>link to that comment? I want to downvote it too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 06:21:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! Now I've done my part!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 07:11:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>stay fresh!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 23:53:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>second one looks like a terrorist attack, yikes!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 23:53:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>and teardrops.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 00:02:45</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Welcome inconsistent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 06:07:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>O</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 23:37:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>How dare you oppose our impossibly ignorant group-think!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 00:11:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>unless yer a Wizard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 00:14:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>A surprise to be sure, but a welcome one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 00:16:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Won't you come?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 23:19:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>The creation of the universe tends to make people very angry, and is widely regarded as a bad move.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 23:25:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>don't be jelly, guy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 23:47:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know I did, and now I have to change my pants.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 00:02:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oddly specific.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 09:26:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's barbaric as shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 20:34:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Foreign Pig -written by Reddit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 04:55:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Comment section saltier than the Atlantic Ocean.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 05:02:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why does Java really suck?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 14:34:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean honestly is this subreddit funny?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 14:37:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>you almost had it, take your time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 16:48:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's chump change for them. Why not do it? Must be satisfying to rustle some jimmies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 06:07:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>In all honesty, I am very disappointed that this game won't sell very well unless EA cleans up their act. Was looking forward to this game for years... Edit: well fuck me for expressing my opinion, right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 13:20:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know right? Doesn't this easily give away that he's a damn troll? Also, his comment is apparently tasty Reddit bait. I guess it's easy to troll here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 13:34:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Relaxation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 14:14:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Add to that the immense disappoinment with the release. Shits nauseating. If only Reddit was more vocal about things that actually mattered.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 08:49:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why even buy when Android is superior in every way?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 08:52:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean... Isn't it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 08:57:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's actually quite simple though. If you want cheap then shop Walmart. Nothing wrong with that, some can't afford more. If you want quality, look elsewhere, shop around online.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 09:08:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Username...doesn't check out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 16:19:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Up to interpretation I guess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 16:20:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are you fighting to make work? Just curious, as I've never had any problems with Android.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 23:33:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was amazing. Still doesn't check out. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 04:08:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always knew that my IQ was at least double that of my peers who hadn't watched the show. Now look at me, living the high life with my Hulu subscription in my 1 bedroom apartment. No, you aren't welcome to my abode lest your IQ is within 3 points of my own, preferably lower.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 04:20:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Impressive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 06:54:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>including the blush?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 07:45:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cuphead is another example. WAY better with a controller.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 20:09:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you ever feel nauseated playing the game? I find that whenever there is a disconnect between real life movement and the virtual reality world, it can trigger nausea for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 20:21:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think he'd rather not cause his brother to quit playing altogether..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 23:15:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>good on you to put the options there. I noticed that when I played a Vive vs. a Cardboard, it was way less nauseating, and I think it was mainly because the movement is 1-to-1 irl vs in-game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 19:38:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>According to your username...He's a master of karate and friendship for everyone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 04:32:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll bring the Surstr #246;mming as ammunition.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 08:32:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>One might even say you feel apathetic about this drawing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 04:57:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>###WAHHH###</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 03:21:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>As opposed to our East Coast rappers spitting cold fire.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 04:54:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's something philosophical about this, but maybe I'm just rolling my dice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 07:02:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/oddlysatisfying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 01:44:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>!isbot perrycohen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 01:49:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>!isbot subject5409</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 02:07:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>he actually went into a coughing fit and died shortly after.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 04:26:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>All-in on TVIX while the price is hot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 04:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>**and** VIX</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 04:43:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have faith in Chinese Amazon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 23:31:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>that's enough Reddit for today.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 23:34:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/dashcamgifs = 40,827 readers /r/gifs = 15,460,343 readers yeah..not gonna happen, bud.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 01:47:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>eh, it's been bottom barrel jerking for a while too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 01:48:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is actually amazing. Such a shame...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 01:51:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>You cannot penetrate the incredibly dense skulls of the /r/gaming circlejerkers with logic. Just give up, dude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 01:53:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>makes me kinda want to unsubscribe to this subreddit tbh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 01:55:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>They fixed the issue. It's easy to get heroes. It's not Pay2Win, actually it never even was. Everything is unlocked in a reasonable amount of time through gameplay. Also, why is this the ONE game that doesn't get a pass with the loot purchases? It's been a thing for years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 04:31:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Upvoted because 'pooping', checked for 'pooping', wasn't reason other people upvoted, left disappointed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 04:34:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>They fixed the issue. It's easy to get heroes. It's not Pay2Win, actually it never even was. Everything is unlocked in a reasonable amount of time through gameplay. Also, why is this the ONE game that doesn't get a pass with the loot purchases? It's been a thing for years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 09:07:55</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; fight these devs for what we want you realize the devs have absolutely NO say in how the game is designed, right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 04:38:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>5'6 guy checking in. Great thing about this height is that you don't have to bend down to kiss your girl because most are about that tall. Also, hugs are convenient and easy. I love being the same height as my girlfriend. I have to admit, there is something hot about her wearing heels and being a few inches taller than me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 04:44:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol. only reason I'd want to be taller is to give her a better view when we do piggy back rides.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 06:11:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I heard they were even recently impeached! DAE celebrate this every day?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 02:51:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't ever talk trash about Cory in the House. It's a beautiful story with complex characters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 00:06:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because 5 is pronounced "ha" so it's basically "hahaha"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 04:58:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>zzzzz...ah ravioli....zzzzz....ah mamamiaa....zzzzzzzz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 05:16:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>it honestly isn't even Pay-2-Win, so who cares either way. you can unlock everything anyway in a reasonable amount of time. Edit: to those downvoting, I bet 2 things: 1: You haven't even played the release 2: You have no counter argument, and are just a drone of Reddit's anti EA hivemind</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 05:55:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>It may be steep for the unlockable heroes loot boxes, but I personally have found that Star Cards are only so helpful. Sure you can get the best Star Cards for a hero and have a slight edge, but it doesn't break the game by any means. You can still get hero Star Cards from the 4,000 loot as well, just not as likely. The heroes don't require much time to unlock. You could have them all within roughly a week after EA drastically lowered them. The game does have a lot of free content already out of the box: great maps, fair/balanced multiplayer with a lot of class content, and a ton of single-player content. I do admit the campaign was weak, but the other stuff is not only fun, but rewarding because you can rack up a lot of credits just through the single-player challenges. I don't buy into the sense of pride and accomplishment b.s. PR that EA tried to push, I just see the game as objectively fun and rewarding. That being said, what I don't want to see are season passes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 06:12:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Response to point 1: There's a difference between vicariously experiencing a game by other's video footage or opinions, and actually playing it. Personally, I decided to block the bias out until I tried it, and then look at what other people thought. I've noticed that a lot of the issues people bring up are really non-issues and blown out of proportion, like the credits thing for instance. Response to point 2: I assume you are referring to the Crystal system they pulled? The loot boxes would be no different than they are now, just purchasable through those Crystals. The game is definitely not based around lootboxes, and more-so about racking up credits through gameplay, which you can then use to do a variety of things. Player level has significance with regards to the Star Card upgrade thresholds, but not much else. Admittedly, I would have liked to see more things unlock through that player level, but like I said earlier it's more about the credits unlocked over time and the challenges you complete, which unlock your weapons and other cool stuff. Something people commonly overlook about this game is that completing single-player and multi-player challenges gives you an *enormous* amount of credits, such that you really can't complain about the credits unlocked through multiplayer being too low.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 06:33:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well from my personal experience, having more lootboxes isn't going to put you at a significant edge over the competition so I don't really understand how this game could be parsed as pay-to-play. That being said, I'm not a fan of season passes, so it would be nice if we got rid of those "chunks" of content. I think what they need to do is akin to what Overwatch did, which is only cosmetics for crates/loot, that way no one can complain about unfairness. I bet if you ask anyone else that has played the game for a decent amount of time, they will tell you that lootboxes aren't the way to progress, it's earning credits through gameplay which can't be bought, and you can earn a lot of them very quickly through single-player and multi-player Challenges. I understand it's not just about this game, and it's more like this was the straw that broke the camel's back, but I have to admit that it's pretty disappointing that it had to happen to this game when many others got a pass. Especially given that the loot / hero system isn't really unfair (aside from the ridiculous initial hero cost that they then fixed), just misunderstood and blown out of proportion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 08:39:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Regarding your first question, yes you get star cards from loot, however you can just unlock the star cards you want through Crafting parts, which is a common drop of the loot. So if you want a certain star card, you don't have to open much loot actually. Regarding your second question, no it is definitely not integral to power scaling. The game rewards skill, teamwork, and positioning over just having those star card upgrades. They give you a slight edge, but it's not enough to make it not fun if you had no star cards and are playing against someone who had maxed star cards. Also, about the story thing, they just released another Arc for free! Here's hoping EA continues to keep the DLC out of the game, they've been doing well to serve the players and their complaints so far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 22:48:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>nah .ogg is where it's at</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 01:31:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>You almost defected from the hivemind, but we knew you would come back. They always do...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 03:30:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's ironic how this comment is controversial.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 02:50:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>lil bat nuggets. just need some BBQ sauce.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 03:15:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>got some bad news about the demographic of Reddit, bud.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 07:19:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're up!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 06:18:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I can break these cuffs."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>As a Java developer learning web development</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 08:37:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 08:46:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has a Stanley Parable vibe. I like it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 09:10:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>or just filter "princess", "feminist", "marriage", "married" in the bio and swipe left. Should be frequent enough to work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 12:28:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>good to know both. It's just that js is very fickle in **var**ious ways. Also having classes be classes and not weird function-y classes makes for more understandable code. (at least to me)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 23:54:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>honestly I found this to be the best advice. Saw the most improvement when we both lived better and healthier lives. Sometime it's just simple things like your diet that can change both your moods.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 23:57:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>implies extra baggage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 23:59:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>we'd port over Java, but that hasn't turned out too well in the past. *cough* JSP *cough*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 23:17:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>RIP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 23:23:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>not a mentor, but [this](https://www.udemy.com/the-complete-nodejs-developer-course-2/) could be a cheap way to get a learning session. As far as actual coding, just try to make a prototype of what you want and go from there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 06:29:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will aggressively extrapolate inaccurate assumptions about your family if I want to!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 11:06:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>WTF</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 00:35:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>OH, NOOO!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 00:44:45</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Or how about we draw all the things, and just remove the ones that aren't Elephants?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 00:47:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well it worked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 00:48:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>mine is your facial structure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 00:55:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>for real. Also, I'd feel conflicted between wanting to buy something to support her and letting her study uninterrupted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 01:53:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. Don't doggedly stick to habits that degenerate your health. Doesn't need to be switch to vegetarian, just eat healthier foods. Diet and exercise were big factors in ours. As a plus, both of us look better and more attractive to each other too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 05:11:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have exceeded your daily request quota for this API. To request more than 25,000 map loads per day, you must use an API key and enable billing: https://developers.google.com/maps/documentation/javascript/get-api-key</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 15:58:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Plot twist: the party is actually an enemy Stand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 13:23:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Finally got out of the gaming chair, there's the One Weird Trick to losing weight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 01:07:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>is that Natalie Dormer?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 02:19:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know what they say: sest lah vii!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 02:26:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hue hue, le fine upboat to you my good sir. To le top with you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 02:27:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Edit:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 06:16:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>DAE hate when people comment jokes in /r/jokes? Time for le pitchforks to come out!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 06:21:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol it's the new /r/incel based on the comments in that subreddit. How sad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 06:26:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Speak for yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 06:33:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>N A K E D B O I</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 06:44:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>How much experience did you have before reaching that salary? Starting out at ~65k as a developer in NC and wondering if I should try working elsewhere for higher pay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 07:26:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>me too thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 08:03:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then drop it right back onto the ground.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 09:21:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>WiiU connection has always been fine for me, but then again I live in a small apartment. I think what really shattered sales for the Switch was not the console itself but the games released for it. That being said, I don't see why I'd buy Splatoon 2 having already owned the first one. Seems like not much was changed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 15:12:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>The ending is a twist, but it has a nice Swing to it. Also, that class name is causing Internal Pain</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 04:48:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Works as a riddle too. What remains stationary no matter how far you throw it? An envelope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 05:12:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>His body runs at 100% efficiency, no worries</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 05:13:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not a problem for me. Small apartment residency ftw!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 07:58:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where did the squirrel even come from? It seemed to appear out of the ceiling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 21:09:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right? OP where did you go to highschool?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 20:20:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know, this is what I **don't** get about the Switch. Why would anyone do this? Their advertisement about taking your Switch everywhere didn't really resonate...aren't you supposed to enjoy the outdoors if you are outdoors?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 08:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Flatiron? I'm considering that boot camp.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 18:35:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because a Python library is the authority on all time keeping and semantics...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 00:02:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was primarily in response to the side comment about Monday being the first day, supporting the original post / discussion. The inconsistency of the library has not escaped me. Sorry about the rant. sleep deprived so I really shouldn't be on Reddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 21:37:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah Tesseract is pretty shit. I use it at work for my current project. It's only right like 70% of the time. That's after optimizations, btw.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 09:29:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that was the peak of this subreddit. Each bad UI post was amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 19:45:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why do you say this? Considering jumping into web application development full-time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 07:53:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like once you understand each bit is a power of 2, representing decimal numbers isn't that hard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 18:42:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Being an Android user (previously an iPhone user), I have to ask: why would I ever use an iPhone? Seems limited in functionality by design and way less customizable, unless you can root it. Also their phones battery life is terrible compared to Android.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 19:29:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfortunately, you're probably right. I think over time it has just devolved from a revolutionary device (the first iPod/iPhone) down to a status symbol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 03:21:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>What was this post?? It's deleted with almost 10k!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 17:08:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spending a week in Kauai this April. Is this a dangerous move? Don't want to be ballistic missled while trying to enjoy the vacation of a lifetime.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 03:32:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>But then they also risk losing a percentage of their user base entirely. Not sure it would be worth it...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 01:05:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>???</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 14:55:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 18:32:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cory what are you doing in my house?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 18:37:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mfw Reddit can't spot the fucking troll.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 18:40:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>KenM? Is that you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 06:48:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>This should have been the slogan, not MAGA.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 23:56:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>TRX to the moon! ....or Sun! ^^hah ^^get ^^it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 23:58:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hah Litecoin...nice meme, friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 00:19:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>portfolio: 2/15 PSI, 5/15 FDN, 1/15 ITA, 3/15 FBT, 4/15 IHI thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 19:37:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>So weird... The intro to that song played in my head when I saw the image.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 19:44:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>How much? He's already rich.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 00:50:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like the little bro got his hands on the account.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 01:18:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe it's just basically buying a ticket to buy or sell at a certain price, and it has an expiration date. That might be way off though, personally I've never traded options.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 01:33:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should invest in off-brand Chinese such as Baby-Beenies and Vurbees. Diversify, brother.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 00:51:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Makes me feel some kind of way seeing millionaires and nillionaires in the same sub. Almost tried day-trading options, but knew I'd end up as the latter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 01:08:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>about 5'6" myself, I'm with you. Market should be low enough for me to climb aboard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 18:00:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blockchain delivers both. Happy?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 02:10:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your subtly is legendary.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 02:15:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Came here  #128071; #128166;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 17:11:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>RONALD WEASLEY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 08:54:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>They've gone up the ventilation shaft.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 08:56:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>rat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 09:00:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>damn bots taking our jobs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 09:08:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>maybe I misunderstand it, but it seems like a good time to buy...? If there's a crash, should be a high payout.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 09:11:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Truly in the spirit of wsb, where no effort is made to do your own work/research. Good show!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 19:17:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>The answers aren't jokes for the most part, but I did laugh when I read "gatordile" after "serious question".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 19:22:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like there's 3 kinds of people in this situation: those who recognize and explain why it's a caiman, those who try to explain why they think it's either a crocodile or alligator, and people like this guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 19:27:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>But...but...it's so easy to access such food. How do I break out of the capitalistic slaughterhouse industry? Soybeans for life?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 20:59:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>One could argue entertainment makes the world a better place. I found the story entertaining, as did many others.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 19:51:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ruin the joke, with your bones the cat will choke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 12:18:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Buying puts on crippling depression.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 23:23:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>You said male power even though it's female power. She even had female power, you just assumed male power. That's a sign of male power.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 23:33:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>No.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 00:01:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm referring to male power.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 04:10:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Merely trying to sort out the shitcoins from the others, that's what I'm trying to do. The more legitimate support a coin/service gets, the more I invest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 10:11:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>or worst.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 07:12:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>So is understanding mortality a prerequisite to be entitled a free life, despite also having the capacity to feel pain?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 23:50:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>The overwhelming misinformation about this game in general is incredible actually. They still haven't brought micro transactions into the game btw. Even if they did to begin with, it's not a big advantage to have the best cards unlocked...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 23:55:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the part I can't believe people still refuse to believe. It's actually not that hard to unlock a lot of content very quickly. This is a classic example of hivemind and telephone simultaneously. Like, someone even thought the game had a season pass. There are no season passes for this game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 06:29:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have to wonder why people aren't as up in arms about games like Hearthstone where the advantage is very obvious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 00:04:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>The real programmer is always in stack overflow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 05:32:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>and baybeh said... ***Dance, Magic Dance***</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 07:07:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>In other words "I got mine, so you future generations can fuck right off."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 07:09:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>On our way to becoming the next China. Buckle up, America is about to get SMOGGY. Can't wait to drive to work in code Purple conditions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 07:31:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>looks like it could be Zeus's finger, the red part is the fingernail.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 19:40:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate that this is relatable. Do you happen to work in fintech?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 23:20:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>become an admin or mod.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 18:50:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol asking why results in controversial vote and no actual answer. Stay classy, Reddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 04:55:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also, no shit of course nearly all posts here are disturbing. This being one of the more mild ones actually. Stupid tag.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 18:24:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Soup is the fool's fig leaf.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 23:27:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>"So it would seem..."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 23:44:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>All it needs is a gong sound effect for her ult and we're good to go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 17:09:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah it's almost as if the caste system is unfair and that pisses people off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 19:04:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maine Coons are very nice cats, I'm sure you will love having her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 23:36:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Precisely the opposite. You can easily refactor method and variable names with even the most basic IDE. However, rewriting comments because of changes is a life changing experience, and not in a good way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 23:39:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I disagree. If you calculate parts of the equation separately, naming all variables accordingly, it becomes unnecessary for any comments. Maintenance on comments is way more tedious than maintenance on variable/method/class names.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 23:42:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well he's not *my* Python programmer, I didn't vote for him!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 23:49:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Count me in, too! Fuck comments and the potential nightmare of maintenance it brings. Descriptive names all day. Stay mad, haters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 23:55:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meh. That's what TDD is for. Your tests should be built as you walk through the functionality and requirements. Also should be descriptive AND they provide you with repeatable regression and unit testing. Cucumber or similar tools should describe and generate scenarios, unit tests should test individual classes and methods.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 01:27:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Code changes, sometimes frequently. No one wants to maintain comments. I'd rather leave that planning phase on the whiteboard than in my codebase.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 17:44:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>No he was accelerating, just into the pit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 23:57:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>5' 6" here. Feels good to not have to experience face to face rejection with the magic of the internet. If she's not interested, I just don't get a reply! Found my girlfriend and soon to be wife through online dating, couldn't be happier, and without the inferiority complex BS.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 21:08:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Error: NullPointerException</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 23:33:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>END METHOD.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 19:50:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it means at least one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 23:18:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>My sweet sweet Java Server Pages, how I have not missed you. Also, doesn't React basically encourage the two to be combined?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 23:37:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>What Front-end you using?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 23:43:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>"-coughs-" -Abe Lincoln</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 00:41:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>$$$</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 19:07:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did we just become best friends?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 19:48:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ravioli's gale is the only one I grabbed in Master Mode, too useful to not have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 19:50:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only one I cared about in Master Mode. Yeah it's a challenge without any of them, but seriously it's just tedious to not get that one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 19:52:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Immediately fight Gannon and expect to win? That's a bold strategy, cotton.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 05:49:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>it is Meme, friend</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 03:39:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>yikes those look ugly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 18:31:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's time to face the facts. Some of us are getting older. The longer I browse Reddit the more I realize the community is mostly people younger than I am, sometimes much younger.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 18:34:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're looking at a shift in generational memes. Based off the title, the kid probably doesn't even know the source.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 04:53:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>you're not a very good friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 16:50:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are they doing in Europe differently than here?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 17:07:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>And do what? Comments like this make me laugh. It's not like you'll be able to change the government's mind. Our country is too big for any of us to matter, and good luck getting the majority of people to care.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 17:43:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Canada here I come!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 19:20:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm in cardiac arrest, couldn't handle the voltage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 22:13:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can almost hear the heavy breathing from here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 00:13:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is the trade-off really that great though? Can my poop tell me whether I've got cancer?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 21:13:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't change your diet drastically, practice gradual change in diet and excercise and it makes the change easier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 17:52:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>does our vote really matter?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 23:31:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.amazon.com/Electroplankton-Nintendo-DS/dp/B000CI8EXA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 03:47:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>WALUIGI NUMBER WAHHHN I'd not worry about him being added. There's no real reason they would.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 04:06:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's probably just thinking "Eh, I've had a good run, might as well read this to see how I might die."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 01:51:03</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; "You and I have *very* different opinions on what is pretty." Doesn't contribute to conversation, so I downvoted it. Maybe that helps you understand how Reddit works.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 01:56:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ever played Banjo Kazooie: Nuts and Bolts? Might be able to learn from that game too as it is very similar looking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 02:08:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yikes, not sure why heavily downvoted, that's pretty cute. Hey maybe he knew you liked coffee and so it made sense for him to make this. I'd be interested in *why* he decided to make that for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 02:31:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>it doesn't really lead to meaningful discussion. maybe if you said why you thought so it would be a more interesting conversation, but it's kinda like someone just commenting "I don't agree." Doesn't add much. whatever though, this is just Reddit so idc either way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 21:12:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean the shoppers of Walmart may have inspired some Yo Mama jokes tbh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 06:51:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yikes, such negativity with this game! idk if anyone actually watched the video but it seems to be interesting enough with the unique customization system. OP, congrats on releasing a complete game. Game development can be draining, especially if it's a long hobby project.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 07:04:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>pastor says tits are the fools fig leaf.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 22:09:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't want to set the world on [fire](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n9D6GNzpmkM)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 22:11:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I don't want to set the world on fire..."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 22:26:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>General Grevious. You're shorter than I expected.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 23:06:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey he had some great points, but I felt the same way before watching it anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 00:51:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really want to move there...beautiful city.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 06:36:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there an anime about trading?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 18:06:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love looking at a game with realistic graphics that suddenly spurs into some ridiculous shit-show because of a bug.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 00:22:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, didn't realize a nice looking building with some plants could spark so much controversial opinion! Lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 00:33:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Except when security policy doesn't allow it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 15:55:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>^Like ^Reddit?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 15:55:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Pope is Woke, bruh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 15:58:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait. Who am I?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 22:51:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Putting on my solar panel hat now. (TVIX)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 23:37:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the American way, good work son.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 23:42:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>C L A S S I C J E R R Y</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 01:37:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>please stop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 03:03:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tryna get that Costco pussy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 17:02:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Laughing all the way to the bank. And btw, it's safe to say all social media data isn't private. This isn't just for Facebook.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 17:04:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>How? Genuinely curious...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 17:14:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Out of all the content about the Facebook data scandal, this comment is the most enlightening. I wouldn't be surprised if they implemented such designs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 17:19:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are many flavors of Linux and Unix that do not. Here's a [few]( https://www.google.com/amp/s/fossbytes.com/secure-linux-distros-privacy-anonymity/amp/) that may be of interest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 17:50:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>You cannot purchase a phone that has the Linux or Unix distro you want by default, but you can root and install it yourself. Also, if you really care about privacy more than anything else, you get the most basic flip phone that you only use to call or text. Or you can just not use a phone, and find some open source VoIp service that you trust and carry a device that has that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 18:04:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>[These](https://www.makeuseof.com/tag/linux-smartphone-operating-systems/) may be worth checking out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 05:29:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>until it falls onto someone and fries them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 05:31:14</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; analysist I'm not a spelling expert, but I'm pretty sure that's spelled wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 05:38:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>*sees picture* *heavy breathing / sweating*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 09:22:11</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; meat doubt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 09:22:50</DATE>
    <TEXT> #127345;oneless  #127345;icken  #127345;ings</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 19:04:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Y I K E S</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 22:48:57</DATE>
    <TEXT> #127345;oasting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 22:51:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha... subtle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 23:02:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>you've got to be prepared for the worst when you make that decision to have a child. Talking about financially, emotionally, and mentally.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 23:07:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! Quinoa Burgers are simply AMAZING. Took a chance on one at a vegan restaurant. Was pretty skeptical, but my god it was good and by far the healthiest burger I've had, better tasting than other veggie burgers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 03:28:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the real answer. So many companies buying into Ripple every week.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 04:27:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>More likely, Ripple.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 04:28:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Invest in the ones that are the most solid. Some survive some don't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 14:50:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol the only reason all coins are dropping is because they are still tied to the price of btc at this point. Look up the charts. Read the news. You'll notice positive news for other coins doesn't affect price simply because it's still tied to the biggest crypto which is Bitcoin. Give it time, and they will have their own trends.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 02:59:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think this, it's in international news. Hence "read the news". Also, the reason for banks and other systems of transaction isn't the value of the coin. It's the service that Ripple provides. International payment without the middle man. You'd be smart to buy the coin now, but many will not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 03:09:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your hands are so weak you can't even hold your phone...lol. Market swings like these always shake out the weak ones. You have to accept some will win, others will lose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 03:25:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine when it's prime. Buy when it dies. That's the strat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 17:08:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Haven't you eaten enough?" "Stop triggering me!!!" *Eats entire apple pie*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 17:11:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rip.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 17:16:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tally Ho!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 23:53:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/pcmasterrace</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 02:50:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>parties are over-rated anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 06:00:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is my lightbulb. It was made for my mouth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 18:33:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Might be something other than text in the div.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 02:30:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Settlement  amp; Clearing. It's absolutely ridiculous how our system works today, takes days to settle and clear transactions...also DTCC charges outrageous prices to process it all too. Blockchain would allow us to bypass that garbage. This is basically what Ripple is trying to fix, but more focused on international payment. Edit: also Stellar is working towards this, basically a decentralized version of Ripple.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 15:40:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep, I've got my eye on the yield curve... Not looking great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 15:41:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can confirm. I've been more green than red on bear days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 22:57:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'mma FIRIN' MAH LAZAR.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 23:26:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Music helps depression, it's that simple.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 23:15:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 04:20:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>do we? Sometimes I can't tell if I am making bank compared to other salaries I've heard of... $65k is the average entry level salary in my area with ~$1000 per month for rent. Should I just move to Cali and make mad bank after a few years of experience? I know it's HCOL there, but don't they pay significantly higher even taking that into account?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 23:52:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>And eventually: "ah whatever just let them run a casino or something"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 02:39:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Xbox Live is 15 years old. I guess time flies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 18:07:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same height as most women. Perfect for hugs, kisses, and staring deep into each other's eyes since you don't have to awkwardly lean down. Honestly I wouldn't want to be taller. I got plenty of girls just fine and now settled down with an amazing one. Oh yeah and same height makes for great sex, all positions are just so easy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 08:13:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it would be cool to have the player's model only visible for a short amount of time when they shoot, but when in range of an enemy bullet radius, linger for slightly longer. Or vice-versa. Messing with durations of visibility would be interesting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 17:32:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hurts because true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 14:28:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also impossible if you understand what dropping a table means.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 06:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dark Blade: Knights of Darkness can't see a damned thing in this game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 10:24:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>hmmm... it's almost as if we'd want this to be a system of decentralized ledgers. How would we make sure that all the ledgers are in sync and playing fair though? I know! We can have each transaction "chained" to the next, with linked encryption. To make sure the system is secure, we'd need to 'solve' for the correct key so all ledgers can agree on any additions to the chain. I guess we could call each addition a "block"...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 22:30:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like it. We'll call this system the Chainblock! Also, to give people incentive to solve the keys we can reward them with Coinbits, a currency to be used with that system.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 21:29:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>-Xavier, Renegade Angel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 16:39:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>HN?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 02:12:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean... interior cameras though? Getting some 1984 vibes here. Exterior ones on corners of the house would certainly seem to be enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 02:28:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>My [boi](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LfWGYW4uZVg), this meme is what all true Warriors strive for.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 02:30:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just wonder what *Zeus* is up to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 04:48:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bobby stop lookin' at those Chinese Cartoons, it ain't right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 23:23:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>It totally is. Hateno is the European themed village and Kakariko is the Japanese themed village.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 05:02:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well here's the problem...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 05:39:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>The frog is boiled.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 02:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>ZA WARUDO! tick ^tock ^^tick ^^^tock</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 19:45:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like I need to nurture it, so it's Karma can grow big and strong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 19:51:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>###FLEENTSTONES?###</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 19:57:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's satire considering someone else posted a Japanese village looking like Hateno, when it actually looked like Kakariko.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 20:31:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice. Did your grandpa retire there?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 22:25:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfortunate, but true. Is any country run by ethics other than smaller ones like Switzerland?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 22:33:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yikes! way to burn a bridge in record time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 22:42:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was mainly referencing their guinea pig companion [law](https://www.techly.com.au/2016/03/14/in-switzerland-its-illegal-to-own-just-one-guinea-pig-due-to-loneliness/).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 22:00:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe companies like Tesla are the gateway to such a future. Investing in tomorrow instead of today to ensure a cleaner long term future.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 22:05:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's where I went recently! Got to see a variety of fish and a sea turtle. Also, we were very lucky to do this because the historic storm had just happened two days before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 02:28:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Considering living there, are taxes really that bad over there?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 14:27:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah we were at the Hanalei Bay Resort, basically located right before the road was totally flooded/blocked by debris further up the island. People were getting rescued by jet ski and helicopter over there. Passed by quite a few people coming from Hanalei on Puu Poa beach carrying all their essentials.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 15:30:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Escapes by grabbing onto a taxi*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 18:20:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah on the rainy days we just tried to make our way down to the southern part of the island, incredibly different weather, all sunshine. Lihue was right in the middle, and you'd see rainbows frequently.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 11:54:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>M o o d</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 13:30:55</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Graviton Surge is ready.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 14:57:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wasm is coming.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 03:08:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 23:54:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scandinavian thing. They don't like socializing very much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 02:29:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can relate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 14:14:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boolean is an object, therefore null is also an option. You've got yourself 3 types of grill.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 06:20:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>considering the context of that jojo quote, it's actually very fitting!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 18:42:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>through its digestive system.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 01:35:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think any of us will need to worry about that happening. Except maybe Warren Buffet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 16:27:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol @ the high levels of sodium in the comments.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:09:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>where in NC? Looking for good outdoor adventures.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 20:55:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same. He/She sure is beautiful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 08:25:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>future? more like present.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 17:15:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're either a raging leprechaun if you are mad or you are overcompensating for your height in some way. The state of a short man is boolean.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 17:25:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like overcompensation, manlet. Deal with it and accept the label society puts on you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 18:01:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>You got me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 19:38:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a preconception. People assume the little guy to be sensitive about his masculinity without giving it a second thought, despite no actual proof that it was the case.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 20:17:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>AND 100% REASON TO REMEMBER THE NAME</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 03:55:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>#######filtered content</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 10:38:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Millennials are killing the theft industry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 14:23:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>more like /r/expectedfactorial</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 16:11:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Except that would likely give too many false positives. "I'm not attached to my company." "Here's a link to that charger attachment."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 17:08:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Potion seller, I am going to battle and need your strongest potions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 20:47:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where in Cali? This is awesome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 00:38:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll bet Pepsi is way cheaper to buy in bulk simply because the demand is lower.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 22:32:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haters gonna say it's fake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 16:24:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some languages are easier to fuck up than others though. It's way too easy to write garbage JS code versus some other languages.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 16:25:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>No matter what hand color / language, you'll cause some sort of controversy these days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 18:12:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is where I'm torn... Work on personal projects to show I can actually build something by myself, but flop the technical interview? Or ace the technical interview but have no side projects completed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 04:29:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude looks like Frodo. Thanks for saving the ocean!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 04:50:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wtf. Reminds me of brentalfloss and his parody of that song.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 00:16:24</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; 0 Friends /r/meirl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 04:24:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice concept. It's fresh enough to be interesting yet not too different as to be hard to approach. I like the idea of tricks giving you some ammo. Combos seem to be a big part of this game, maybe also some kind of buff when doing a trick to make it more intense, like a weapon modifier of some sort?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 04:25:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pre-ordered it already. jk, haven't found a way to do it yet. OP how do I give you money?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 18:06:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>When on Master mode, I did something similar to kill tough enemies, but instead using the Monster Hammer to boop them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 17:54:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>bRO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 21:55:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/outside</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 23:37:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Applets main flaw was security, if I'm not mistaken? Also isn't WASM basically going to allow applets to happen again?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 04:37:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>do you even understand what that subreddit is about?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 03:45:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>This. This is the real acronym now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 04:50:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kauai, what a beautiful island. Hope to return someday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 00:46:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spent 3 racks on a new boat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 03:50:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>all 900 of them. blot out the sun with your leafy companions and rein terror on Ganon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 22:52:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>My potions would kill you, traveler.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 04:27:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>M-M-M-Monster Kill^..kill^^..kill</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 03:46:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Ok I'm driving over, should get there in about 10 min"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 18:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>definitely don't break his arms.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 19:51:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>[what she was thinking](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PB4Nby2Ai-g)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 20:21:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sell it as some kind of Business Value, and just about any proposal would work. Throw in words like investment and efficiency, depending on the idea. Just make sure to do some research too. Discuss ideas 1-on-1 with coworkers to get their actual thoughts on an idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 05:58:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Comments are 90% innacurate and 10% apologies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 06:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Interesting. Thanks Sun and Netscape!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 01:41:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>tfw when 2 kool 4 debugger mode.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 06:15:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not gonna lie, it's tough to keep up with all these front-end libraries and frameworks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 04:00:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Couldn't have said it better. I'm a sucker for adventure. Recently started watching One Piece to fill that adventure void after finishing DiU. Stadust Crusaders holds a special place in my heart.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 04:48:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh man, you wouldn't think that with the expansion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 06:12:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Walk through a wall</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 06:15:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Serious question: does LeetCode actually help?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 02:27:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>probably my favorite subreddit. It's a shame that the name of the subreddit doesn't really give an indication what it's about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 18:28:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>create empty child r/me_irl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 23:40:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's just a bunch of Luddites who hope advancements in technology fail. Also, if you read in more detail, it wasn't proven impractical, and he may still have it officially tested.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 00:24:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't speak for others, but I did my part in trying to avoid the Trumptastrophe by voting Hillary. Didn't feel good, but I knew at least she would be better than him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 23:10:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Happens with plenty other IDEs as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 00:10:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Gang Starts a Dumpster Fire</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 00:11:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm on Gucci?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 23:26:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Recipe: "Microwave until Go od"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 16:42:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>As s ** #214;** ** #214;** n as they're d ** #214;** ne. Patience, br ** #214;** ther.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:29:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or...Botox for short!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 02:18:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah that's what I'm wondering. was the ground one just an Alpha timer and they just forgot to take it out? kinda tacky this way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:24:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>We live in a society</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:35:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yer a wizard, Harry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 18:28:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is getting out of hand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 18:32:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>great when paired with this celestial [tune](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KF32DRg9opA)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 05:16:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>for 7 pieces, Chess is [solved](http://tb7.chessok.com/about-site) ...though requiring 100TB of data.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 03:10:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh Oh OH.. TIME TO ACCELERATE!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Oldie but Goodie [Crysis]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 05:49:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Crysis] Oldie but Goodie</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 06:03:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 23:39:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>guy here. read as "woman"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 00:36:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>honestly having things work the way they do in BoTW would make for a pretty simple engine. They focus on most objects in the game being truly their own entity, allowing for any possibility of interaction as a side-effect without the extra work. Although I'm sure there would be some challenges when it comes to optimization, as to keep the game running at a stable fps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 00:30:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>public boolean isOk() { isOk(); return true; }</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 01:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>huh...maybe I should make more call-outs if stuff like this happens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 23:24:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ded irl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 02:21:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>###Childhood is a joke!###</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 02:16:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>gotta love java.lang.reflect :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>JoJo DiU - Another One</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 05:11:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 05:19:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Another One  #12300;Bites The Dust #12301;](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PFve94hl0QM)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 14:48:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see 'vocal minority' as a fallacy because you could say that about any group size and it doesn't prove anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 00:19:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Java is great because its like C# without the big licensing expenses involved (Windows products vs. Unix). So you'll find a lot of large companies looking for Java devs. That being said, I prefer C# as a language.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:35:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know you can get .NET/Core to work on Unix, but I've heard in practice it's a real hassle, and just easier to use Java. I haven't much experience with it, but I know both C# and Java will be around for quite some time, with massive investments made into those languages by many companies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 04:52:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brawl engine but Melee physics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 06:47:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>who needs callback functions when you can just Sleep forever?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 23:38:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bitches love "non-distracting-background-extra"s. I'd go for it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 16:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Babe, you mean ZA WARUDO to me. ^WRRYYYYY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 16:38:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well for starters you could try being nicer to people. Also, username checks out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 18:58:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>good bot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 03:17:09</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;**evil nuclear ball of deadly radiation** ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 04:15:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope, just a Civic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 13:16:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Bison."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 13:24:51</DATE>
    <TEXT> #129300;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 14:03:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I figured it was just * #931;* 1000 \* 2\^(n-1) where n starts at 0</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 00:32:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Biggly Wiggly Depresso</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>