<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject1512</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MY REACTION DURING EPISODE 11...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 03:08:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://gfycat.com/WhiteHighlevelBluebottle When June was taking FOREVER to pack the essentials in the duffel bag and then took even longer to admire her pregnant self in the mirror and fantasize about the  #8216;before #8217; life. Like, I understand the Waterford house is a mirrorless house of horrors and you #8217;re in a walking nightmare but LET #8217;S MOVE.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 03:10:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>BUT HOW CUTE WAS THAT WOLF?! I mean, I know he/she was plotting to potentially murder June and her baby and leave their bloody remains in the snow, but all that aside....the wolf had the cutest little face ever and was very fluffy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 12:56:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>What fjord cruise did you take? I #8217;m going in October and thought they all stopped running around that time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Spoilers S2E13] My face during all of Emily #8217;s scenes...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 03:04:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Quartier Petit-Champlain in Quebec City, Canada. The entire place was a snowy, romantic dream.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 00:27:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Quartier Petit-Champlain in Quebec City, Canada. The entire place was like a romantic, snowy dream.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 01:44:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 03:56:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is fantastic, thank you for the information I will definitely be looking into it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Quartier Petit-Champlain in Quebec City, Canada. The entire place was a romantic, snowy dream.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 23:00:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Quartier Petit-Champlain in Quebec City, Canada. The entire place was a snowy, romantic dream.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 03:07:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Last year I had just ended a 7 year relationship with my loving boyfriend, as I realized we were not compatible. The breakup was devastating  amp; thought I #8217;d never emotionally survive. In the year that passed, I #8217;ve turned 30, gotten a promotion,  amp; head to Miami in a week for a girls #8217; trip. I am happy.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 02:52:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 03:05:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m sorry to hear about your divorce. And you will! I #8217;m surprised to be sitting here because I #8217;m in the exact spot I was a year ago when I was sobbing my eyes out, pretty much certain I would never be okay again. It #8217;s crazy what a year can do. I still have my moments where I miss him dearly (more so, our incredible bond, memories and friendship that we had while we were together) but I do not regret my choice and know that it was for the absolute best. I hope your year is as reflective as mine was.  #128151;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 04:33:12</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8234;https://giphy.com/gifs/wife-eazy-tomica-8GbvxxFHJDBa8?tc=1 via @giphy #8236;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:16:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stay strong and remember that even though the hardest part is upon you, you WILL get through this.  #128153;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:16:46</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128151; #128151; #128151;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:18:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stay strong and stay busy. What you #8217;re feeling right now will soon be a distant memory. It will still hurt at times but you #8217;ll feel a new layer of strength. You #8217;ve got this.  #128153;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:21:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it #8217;s meant to, it will! I #8217;m a year out and there are times I #8217;m triggered by a memory we had together and it can feel temporarily debilitating. However, something that helped me when I was going back  amp; forth on whether or not to end things was to just ask myself  #8220;does this feel right, and can I do this forever? #8221; Before my head or my heart could answer, my gut would always tell me the truth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 15:49:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have no plans! Please send me things to do! We #8217;re all 30, enjoy the club scene on occasion but also mostly laid back and don #8217;t mind margaritas and beers in a laid back outdoor bar. We #8217;re staying in the middle of south beach and also are all about day drinking lol so I #8217;d love to hear of any fun spots!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 16:53:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was so much back  amp; forth for me, it was unreal. I actually found myself searching  #8220;should I break up with my boyfriend of 7 years #8221; articles to see if other women had been through the same thing. (which I don #8217;t recommend, because every article is basically saying  #8216;if you have a nice guy, don #8217;t let him go! #8217;) I didn #8217;t realize then that people who are in happy, fulfilling relationships aren #8217;t taking time to search the Internet for advice on whether or not to break up. In the hopes of not making this too long, we were together from ages 22-29, and in that time we grew a LOT. I felt like I had a huge list of things I wanted to see/accomplish, and wanted to live as full a life as I could, while he became more focused on laying down roots, settling into life and eventually having a family. We had always been very different people, but it seemed like we were slowly losing our common ground. Also, I found myself going on more adventures and traveling more with my friends, (and he was always very supportive of this but had no interest in coming along) and when I #8217;d get back I #8217;d tell him a million stories of funny memories and things that happened. I used to love doing that and he would always listen intently and we #8217;d laugh together, but there was one point when I realized  #8220;hey...I don #8217;t want to come home and tell him all the cool stuff I did, I want him to WANT to do this cool stuff with me. #8221; (Over the years we had many talks and went back and forth about trying to do things that the other enjoyed, but at the end of the day, being very different in terms of interests and what we wanted out of life was something that became difficult to get around and ignore.) I think it really ended with me having to decide who I loved more, him or myself. And while it was extremely difficult and something I never want to go through again, I chose myself. Just remember: if you #8217;re going back and forth on it, that may be your sign. Even though I don #8217;t recommend searching the Internet cause you #8217;ll just find a bunch of stories of how  #8220;leaving the nice guy is a terrible idea #8221;, [this article ](https://www.manrepeller.com/2017/03/should-i-break-up-with-my-boyfriend.html) was the only one I found that mirrored exactly what I was going through. I read it several times (and still go back to read it from time to time). It has helped a lot. Good luck.  #128151;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 19:43:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>THIS IS THE BEST. I #8217;ve highlighted it and am gonna send this to my girlfriends for our guide for the time that we #8217;re there. Thank you so much for giving me that info cause I literally knew nothing about Miami other than that it #8217;s hot AF in the summer lol. I #8217;m so excited and will def be trying the Cuban food!  #129303;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 02:44:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was one of the hardest things to get through, because after 7 years people just assume these feelings are the natural  #8216;give and take #8217; of long term relationships, or that one of us is getting  #8216;cold feet #8217;. It was so much more than that and it #8217;s hard to have your feelings validated. Good luck and I hope that what you #8217;re working through has a positive result.  #128153;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 12:51:24</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128153; #128153;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 19:00:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was AMAZING. I #8217;m still recovering!  #128514; We only had one heavy day of rain that messed up some of our activities that were scheduled, but it was very temporary. We #8217;re already talking about how we need to go back lol. Thank you so much for your insight!  #127796;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When my  #8216;always regular #8217; period decides to randomly come 10 DAYS EARLY. GO AWAY, WHY ARE YOU HERE?!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 03:45:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Quartier Petit-Champlain in Quebec City - one of my favorite photos I #8217;ve ever taken. I got lucky that it was a frigid weekday and the tourists hadn #8217;t arrived yet.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 14:23:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 17:18:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was about 6 degrees every day, and dropped below 0 at night!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 17:19:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d love to go during summer, just to see the differences. The winter was pretty magical, though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 18:11:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>We went specifically for the winter carnival, but actually ended up doing more sight seeing than participating! It was still such a fun time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 18:16:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>It depends how used to cold temps you are...I #8217;m from Maine so I was pretty prepared, although I won #8217;t lie, at night it got absolutely freezing. As long as you #8217;re bundled up (I wore lots of layers and water proof boots, fleece leggings and wool socks) you #8217;ll be fine to walk around. We arrived during a blizzard which made things even more picturesque, despite the fact that it was so cold. I think Christmas would be perfect! It will be busy, but everything will be covered in snow and sparkling with lights. We spent the week sight-seeing by day, and dipping in and out of little cafes and pubs for warm beverages at night.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 18:17:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I couldn #8217;t believe I got so lucky that there was nobody on this street! It made for the perfect shot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Quartier Petit-Champlain in Quebec City. I got lucky with this photo...it was a Wednesday night  amp; the tourists hadn #8217;t arrived yet!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 18:19:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 18:36:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it helped that there was a massive blizzard pretty much all day which drove some people home. I #8217;m actually a tourist too (but from Maine, so I #8217;m your neighbor  #128579;) and I was surprised that I was able to walk around that night without bumping into many people!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;m pretty terrible at cooking but I am proud of this one...gnocchi with bacon cream sauce!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 23:45:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Gnocchi with bacon cream sauce...I #8217;m still working on my cooking skills but I #8217;m proud of this one.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 01:21:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:25:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>The gnocchi isn #8217;t.  #128584; but everything else is!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:28:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ingredients: 1 lb gnocchi Water enough to fill a large pot 3/4 full 4 strips smoked bacon chopped 2 cloves garlic pressed or minced 2 egg yolks beaten well 1/4 cup milk or cream 1/4 cup freshly grated parmesan cheese 1/4 cup chicken broth 1/2 tbsp cornstarch Salt and pepper to taste Chopped parsley and more parmesan to garnish Directions: 1. Bring water, salted heavily, to a boil in a large pot. 2. In a medium mixing bowl, mix together egg yolks, milk and cheese with a fork or whisk. Set aside. 3. In a large high sided saute pan over medium high heat, cook chopped bacon to desired crispness. At this point, you could remove or keep the rendered bacon fat, it's entirely up to you. Once done, turn heat to low and add garlic. Stir well, making sure garlic doesn't burn. ***4. Add gnocchi to the water and cook for 2-3 minutes, or as package describes. 5. While gnocchi is cooking, add the egg mixture to the bacon in the skillet (heat still on low, or turned off) and whisk well. In a small bowl, whisk the chicken broth into the cornstarch, then add to the sauce, whisking well to incorporate. 6. Drain gnocchi, then add to skillet and toss well with sauce. 7. Serve immediately with parsley and parmesan as garnish ***I actually had to use  #8216;skillet gnocchi #8217; (it was all they had left at the store) so I cooked it in a separate fry pan and then added it to the mixture at the end!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:28:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Posted above  #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 21:39:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 22:49:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow thank you very much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #8220;Wake up early! #8221; they said.  #8220;Seize the day! #8221; they said. I #8217;m going back to bed.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 13:43:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 13:52:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s a chia banana smoothie WITH a little strawberry included, don #8217;t add insult to injury here.  #128514; #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 14:49:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please, have one in my honor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 14:50:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sticky AF.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 14:55:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol I can #8217;t tell whether this is dripping in sarcasm or not and I like it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 15:47:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #8220;Wake up early! #8221; They said.  #8220;Seize the day! #8221; They said. I #8217;m going back to bed.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 15:49:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:03:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s a chia banana boost smoothie! I was trying to be healthy and chose this over a breakfast sandwich. Clearly a rookie mistake.  #128514; #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:05:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean I #8217;m a boxer and I do need to lose 10 lbs to make weight so, you might be on to something.  #129335; #127999; #8205; #9792; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:07:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>If only Wham would have started singing immediately after I dropped this, and I could have just danced my way on into work.  #128557;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:29:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Disney World castle and coordinates!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:30:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>So true, although the side of my car wasn #8217;t so lucky.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:31:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually put it on top of my car to grab something, but the above has happened to me before lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:32:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! Love the chia smoothie! It was my first time having it for a while so it was doubly devastating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:32:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol I swear it #8217;s healthy  #128514; #128557;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:33:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:49:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t know! I #8217;m so awkward that this drink was literally my only hope.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:52:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Search no longer, I got you.  #128129; #127999; #8205; #9792; #65039;](https://www.lulus.com/products/josie-nude-lucite-studded-gladiator-sandals/480182.html)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:53:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha thank you! And yes luckily they #8217;re water resistant and I always keep spare sandals in my car.  #128584;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:53:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>SERIOUSLY. This was a luxurious treat that I just wasted.  #128580;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:54:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes it is, the Disney World castle  amp; coordinates.  #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:55:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually think you #8217;re right...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:56:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>IS THIS NOT WHY YOU ARE HERE?! What a movie, I may have to watch that again this weekend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:56:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol exactly  #128514; #128514; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:57:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! Luckily the smoothie remains washed right off!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>