<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject4247</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-02 00:12:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can remember a fair amount of things from when I was 2-4 years old, more than other people seem to at least. Anyways, when I was 3 years old, I was riding in the car with my parents and a Beatles song came on the radio, they started telling me about the Beatles. Among other things, they told me the Paul and Ringo were the only ones still alive, and then started recalling their own experiences of when they found out about John Lennon's assassination. Sometime that week, or that night, I had a dream about being outside a building of some sort, and I wasn't really there I could just hear what people were saying, one of the strangest dreams I can remember. From the varying conversations I managed to find out that John Lennon had been shot twice in the back (something my parents never mentioned). The next day I asked my parents about the "shot twice in the back" thing, and they said I must have overheard them talking about the incident another time. Well, lets fast-forward 6 years, when I'm in a 4th grade music class. Our teacher showed us a news report about John Lennon's death trying to make us understand how important this event was, and in the news report they showed his apartment. It was the exact same as my dream, 6 years prior. I have no idea how this happened, if I somehow saw a similar report when I was younger than 3 and didn't remember it, or what? Since then, I've had a couple of occurances in which I feel like I've already been to the place in a dream before, or insanely major Deja vu moments, but nothing about an event that happened before my lifetime. I am still baffled to this day about the whole matter. TL;DR : Had a dream about John Lennon's assassination when I was 3 years old, knew almost nothing about the incident, but 6 years later I found details in the dream were frighteningly accurate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Already in Production?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-27 06:28:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-29 05:24:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was like 90% true, hence memoir and not auto-biography. The Glass Castle didn't affect me much at all, A Farewell Arms was pretty depressing though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-29 05:39:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Considering I've never read any "Horror" books, and I've seen Night and The Glass Castle on here (disturbing as they're true) I'm making this decision. A Farewell to Arms, The Sun also Rises, and A Separate Peace all had really really fucked up endings/plot twists, or in The Sun also Rises case just general consistent depression.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-01-04 03:33:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>A Current events class (Nationwide-Worldwide)! There are so many students, and even teachers, that have absolutely no idea what is happening elsewhere in the world, and have no concern as they believe it doesn't directly effect them. More than half of my AP History class had no idea about the current conflict in Syria, the on-going struggle between Palestine and Israel, and in general what is really happening in the middle east. Also, just a general presentation on how to spot and avoid scams, and common scams, would be pretty useful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-01-20 06:36:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn't know "The Legend of Zelda: Collectors Edition" was worth much of anything, I actually got it with my Gamecube ;D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Good Ol' South Dakota</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-08 04:05:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-08 19:42:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is an older picture I took 3 years ago or so, don't worry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-19 02:36:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>When using the original X360USB Pro, you can power the drive directly through plugging the power cable into the 360 and powering it on, its a cheap alternative to the CK3s but frowned upon for various reasons.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-27 00:41:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since your SD card is bigger than 2GB, you need to use Homebrew. If you're on wii firmware 4.3, then just use Letterbomb to install homebrew. Once you have homebrew installed just go to the official Project M download page in the side bar, download the newest project M and the Project M Homebrew Launcher. There are loads of tutorials online for Letterbomb as well, but I'd be willing to help you if need be. Other than that you should be good to go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-27 21:21:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do not, but I would try redownloading P:M 3.2 and putting it on the SD card instead of updating through the wii (which it sounds like you did). In any case, I would just try downloading it again, sounds like there might be a file missing or corrupted or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-19 06:27:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey quick question I'm out of state this week, but I'm from western mass, are "walk-ins" welcome, like could me and a buddy possibly sign up next week? This seems really cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-25 03:22:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>This handwriting made my handwriting feel so inadequate that I have now decided to write with my left hand, as my right is not worthy enough to write on the same planet on which yours exists.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-01 03:09:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're correct, but I think he may mean why does he have to load the homebrew project M launcher for a retail brawl disc off an SD card, while Homebrew can also use usb for apps. If that's what he means, I have genuinely no idea why it doesn't work, but I think it might work wii Riivolution.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-01 03:47:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look into getting Project M through Riivolution, I'm pretty sure Riivolution is compatible with reading files from USBs, but Project M in general doesn't seem to play nicely with USBs, but its worth a shot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any suggestions on how to improve video quality?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-01 03:57:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here's the test video that i'm wondering how to improve the quality on!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WeblTS4t7IQ) This is just a test video to see how the video quality would come out using my method, the gameplay is just clips of two random recordings. So does anyone have any suggestions on improving Video quality; especially frame-wise, as I feel like it is skipping a little. The process i'm using consists of playing a match on wi-fi, saving the recording to the wii, transferring the save file to dolphin, and screen recording off of a HD-Textured Project M iso on Dolphin with Camtasia Studio. If anyone has any suggestions on how to improve video quality, such as a different screen-recorder or better program to record with, or any suggestions on reducing frame skipping when recording? Any advice/help would be greatly appreciated, thanks :D .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any suggestions on how to improve video quality?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-01 04:10:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here's the test video that i'm wondering how to improve the quality on!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WeblTS4t7IQ) This is just a test video to see how the video quality would come out using my method, the gameplay is just clips of two random recordings. So does anyone have any suggestions on improving Video quality; especially frame-wise, as I feel like it is skipping a little. The process i'm using consists of playing a match on wi-fi, saving the recording to the wii, transferring the save file to dolphin, and screen recording off of a HD-Textured Project M iso on Dolphin with Camtasia Studio. If anyone has any suggestions on how to improve video quality, such as a different screen-recorder or better program to record with, or any suggestions on reducing frame skipping when recording? Any advice/help would be greatly appreciated, thanks :D .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-01 06:05:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure I'd like to know to compare it to what I'm doing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-01 06:18:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya, I read about something like this when I was looking int methods, but the desyncing was a major problem, I didn't know there was an older dolphin version that tolerated it better, i'll have to look into that, thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-01 06:46:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha, it was fine, thanks :P</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Study: 1 in 25 Business Leaders May Be Psychopaths</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-23 23:49:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-24 00:08:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This Article](http://time.com/32647/which-professions-have-the-most-psychopaths-the-fewest/) Is what made me look further into it; there are some other interesting professions on the list as well :P .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is probably the fastest kill I've ever gotten.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-12 16:49:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-12 18:52:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>[It's like we're connected!](http://youtu.be/k9EBcNEKkcY?t=17s)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-12 19:06:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya, we are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-12 19:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>( #172; #8255; #172;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-13 01:13:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apparently there's like a crew of us or something lol, look at the comment by u/Gman_SSB .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-13 04:32:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its not in a video yet, I'll probably put it in a montage type thing I'm making.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-13 05:13:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Close enough!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-13 05:28:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saved the replay from my wii, transferred the save to dolphin, and recorded from Dolphin in HD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-14 02:17:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, I just found out about this through your comment lol. I have submitted the clip, hope it ends up on it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-03 22:19:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, this will work with a wireless wavebird controller, but I did read somewhere that it will only work with one wireless wavebird. If you try to plug in both, neither will work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-11 19:01:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>To quote you: have you ever played/seen a good Zelda? Like a really good one? [KDJ's Zelda is pretty amazing in Project M](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cLswTxGA7Ms)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Millions of bees swarm, close Del. highway ramp</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-21 05:10:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-29 18:32:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you forgive Steven Gerrard for slipping against Chelsea, which ended up costing Liverpool the EPL trophy this year?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-04 05:45:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is absolutely amazing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can't decide between i7-3770k, i5-3570k, i7-4790K, or i5-4690k.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-17 19:42:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've recently been considering upgrading my processor from my Intel Xeon W3550. This processor has been fine for me with the games I play, but struggles with recording, streaming and rendering. I now can't decide which of these processors to choose, I've ruled out the 4770k and 4670k as they are about the same prices as the 4790k and 4690k will be upon release. I'm mainly interested as to if spending the extra 100$ on the i7 route is worth it for what I am looking to do. I will also need a new motherboard, so suggestions would be appreciated. Any advice/help is greatly appreciated! Thank you very much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-17 21:47:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, you don't think a 4690k could adequately handle all of it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-17 21:52:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that's what i'm wondering, if i'm only gonna benefit in rendering is it really worth the spending the extra 100$?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-17 21:59:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright, thanks, that's pretty much what I needed to hear! Have any motherboard suggestions, i'm not looking to spend a lot on one, but don't want a cheap one dying on me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-18 02:58:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>sorry for late response, but ya my budget is more of a just bang for buck scenario, but not really looking to spend like half of what I'd be spending on the processor on the mobo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-18 03:31:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>$134 isn't too bad, any good options close to 99$ dollar range?(which looks like as low as they go :P).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-18 03:45:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright thanks! Sorry for the persistent questions, but now I have to ask, the cooler I am using right now/will be using is an H60, if I go with the $134 board will I be able to get anymore OC ability out of it than if I went with the 100$? thanks again :P</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is what MSN.com looks like for me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-26 17:13:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-03 22:56:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm on mobile, otherwise I would try to provide better advice, but does "Super Smash Bros. Melee" (aka the hackpack) show up under USB on Dios Mios? If it doesn't, your USB isn't configured correctly. If it does and you still have this problem, try using a different homebrew program like Wiiflow. Personally speaking, wiiflow worked for me, while diosmios did not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-03 23:00:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you "click" it through homebrew or the Wii menu?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-03 23:24:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>That probably just means the diosmios Wii channel is broken, I know the same thing happens with mine. Get the diosmios and wiiflow homebrew apps, and try loading 20xx through the homebrew channel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-03 23:41:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright, NP, once you get back tell if it works out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-09 18:43:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>To completely eliminate the need for the wiimote, after you instllall homebrew, you'll need to install either bootmii or priiloader. That allows you to bypass the wii-menu completely, and go straight to homebrew. And yes, you can still use the brawl disc, with the homebrew method. The easiest way to install homebrew is the letterbomb method, and there's dozens of videos on how to do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-09 21:04:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bootmii is more user friendly, and at least if I remember correctly, you are able to install it with the same installer that you install homebrew with. Bootmii will also autoload when you start your Wii with the SD card in, while priiloader requires you to hold the reset button after powering on. I use priiloader, due to the extra "hacking" availabilities it gives you, but for what you are trying to do, bootmii will be perfect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-09 21:11:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Launching bootmii? It sounds like you're trying to launch from the homebrew channel. Try turning your Wii off completely, and turning it on, does bootmii pop up? If not you may need to re-install it, or use priiloader (if the wii-post-2008 thing is true).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-09 22:56:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Glad you got it to work!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-10 02:31:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>For starters, the reason you've gone through two Brawl discs is because Brawl is a Dual-layered disc (while 99% of Wii games are single layer), and older Wii's have a hard time adjusting to the larger sized disc. Secondly, if the disc can't be read on the Wii, it can't be ripped. If you were to miraculously "find" the brawl.iso file on your computer, and have at least an 8gb empty USB thumb drive, your next order of business is to download a program called WBFS manager. WBFS manager will format the USB drive so that the Wii/usbloader can recognize it, and then will allow you to add the brawl.iso. This is at least how I do it, there is another way without formatting, but it didn't use to work that way back in the day lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-10 02:46:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I don't know about where you live, but around here Wii's on Craig's list/ local stores are only like $30. Or you could save up a big budget and build a computer that can handle netplay lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-10 06:45:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha, my system is also a launch day consle, but instead of not reading the disc it sounds like a lawnmower (and has since about a year after I had the console). The lawn-mower sound is what actually lead me to hacking my Wii in the first place, 6 years ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-10 06:47:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I'm glad I could help! Return the disc as soon as possible, before GameStop's policy kicks in! And I'm currently out of state, but I will definitely take up that pizza offer, hopefully in the not-so-distant future!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-11 19:57:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in the U.S, but I have had nothing but great experiences with DHL, although it might be because I only use them when dealing with wholesale. My packages were always in near-perfect condition, and would make it all the way from Hong Kong to Massachusetts in under 3 days. The delivery driver around here is a nice guy, and the thing they use to have you sign the packages is backlit, and isn't scratched to all hell the UPS one(probably because no one uses DHL lol), and they always deliver the package at a time of day when I'm actually there to pick it up. Just my experience though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-14 07:22:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>This happened to some of my friends as well, try the homebrew method, and if that doesn't work my friends got it to work through using Riivolution.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-14 08:28:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Specific SD cards have the error, from what I deduced. Riivolution fixed the problem for my friends though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-14 17:54:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Glad it works, but that is literally the most reckless fix I've ever read xD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-14 20:05:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, two things I would try would be: 1)Updating your Directx 11 (that's what I think its trying to tell you to do) 2) Or try changing your backend, in the graphics menu, to OpenGL (Since you have a NVIDIA card)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-14 21:03:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Glad I could help! And good luck, you'll love this game xD!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-14 21:35:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I use this](http://www.amazon.com/GC-Controller-Adapter-PC/dp/B0089NVTDM/ref=sr_1_2?ie=UTF8 amp;qid=1405366385 amp;sr=8-2 amp;keywords=usb+gamecube). Although when I bought it, it was only 11$. Some of my friends use Ps4 and 360 controllers too. If you already have a gamecube controller, and don't have any other usb controller, i'd get the adapter or a similar adapter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-14 22:53:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>A drivers disc comes with the adapter, after that its as easy as plugging and playing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-15 02:38:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>In the config menu, under Gamecube, do you have a standard controller in port 1?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-17 06:51:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>We see you when you're sleeping</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-17 06:52:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>( #172; #8255; #172;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Saved up for a PS4... but decided to get this instead.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-19 05:18:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-19 05:23:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Already have a R9 270, this was just a rather sweet upgrade from my older stuff ;D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-19 05:58:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Noooo xD, I was considering getting a PS4 for "exclusives" but decided against it and upgraded instead!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-19 07:57:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>The same reason I order a foot long at subway instead of a six inch. I was hungry. Edit: In all seriousness though, I do a fair amount of rendering, and use a lot of processor heavey programs that greatly benefit from hyperthreading.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-19 14:49:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I edit videos and use a fair amount of other processor intensive programs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-19 18:09:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I already have an SSD, and a 4770k is literally the same price as a 4790k</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-20 21:40:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I upgraded from some random dell 1366 motherboard and a Xeon w3550 processor. I use a lot of processor intensive programs that benefit greatly from hyperthreading, and I also do a fair amount of rendering. As far as my 270 goes I've never been dissatisfied with any of the games I play, the only really intensive one being Battlefield 4.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to Connect a Gamecube Controller to Dolphin without a USB adapter</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-28 23:01:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Before starting this guide I would like to say that I personally use the Mayflash adapter for playing on Dolphin, as I already owned one before I discovered this method and it is far more convenient. But if you don't want to spend the money on the adapter, or are just interested in this, this method does have its advantages. **How to Connect a Gamecube Controller to Dolphin without an adapter:** **Requirements:** * Windows 7, Vista, or XP (Windows 8 might work, but i'm not sure how to disable driver signing) * A Nintendo Wii with Homebrew Channel. * A gamecube Controller, I believe Wavebirds do work **Step 1 (Windows 7 and Vista only)** You will need to download [Driver Signature Enforcement Overrider 1.3b](http://www.ngohq.com/?page=dseo) Once the program is open, and you have agreed to the two statements, [you will see this screen](http://i.imgur.com/kSogVBu.jpg) You are going to want to  #8220;Enable Test Mode #8221;, hit next, and then restart your computer. Upon reboot, if performed correctly, [you should see this in the bottom right hand corner of your desktop](http://i.imgur.com/a638Bqd.png) **Step 2 Install PPJoy** **This is the most annoying part**, and is the part I couldn #8217;t get to work on my friend #8217;s Windows 8.1 computer. [Download this,](https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B4tiIt1c41d2YW5vbFFJZ1N1Z0E/edit?usp=sharing) and extract to a folder, you will need all of the files in this folder. Right click  #8220;ppjoysetup-0-8-4-6(5) #8221; and run as administrator, and then follow the installation. If any problems occur during installation, try running the install file in compatibility mode with a Windows XP service pack. Once PPJoy is installed we can move onto the next step. *If this doesn #8217;t work you may want to also look up guides on how to install PPJoy on a Windows 7/Vista Computer, as it is a rather annoying process, you may find a different method that works for you.* **Step 3: PadSend** The next step will be on your wii, you will need to open up the homebrew channel, and tap the home button on your wii remote in order to[ locate your Wii #8217;s IP Address](http://i.imgur.com/xMOAPgW.jpg). Write down your Wii #8217;s IP address in a notepad, and then return to the main menu of the homebrew channel. Now plug in whatever Gamecube controllers you are going to want to use on Dolphin. Leave your wii on the Homebrew channel and return to your computer. After this is done you can move back to your computer. If you #8217;re on Windows7 or Vista, you #8217;re going to right click the  #8220;PadSend Server (2) #8221; file and click properties. Go over to the Compatability tab, and make sure the settings [match this.](http://i.imgur.com/TlS5HYl.png) Once the settings are applied, run the  #8220;Padsend Server (2) #8221; file, It will open but will be in the [windows tray.](http://i.imgur.com/DMj4aoQ.jpg) Click on the Icon of the file, and then select the Wiiload Client, you might see a box that says  #8220;text #8221; just continue, [and you will see this box.](http://i.imgur.com/nt25EaD.png) Click yes, and paste in your Wii #8217;s IP from the notepad. If done correctly you should see a screen similar to this, [on your Nintendo wii screen.](http://i.imgur.com/JG3C8cy.jpg) The first time a controller is plugged into a port a [box like this should appear](http://i.imgur.com/OsWUtsX.jpg) And the PadSend Server, should now be displaying something similar to [this.](http://i.imgur.com/RNvl2Lb.png) Now in your Dolphin Gamecube Controller settings, the Controller [should match](http://i.imgur.com/rjpdqBd.png) the name of one of what is boxed in red in the previous picture. Then just map the controller like normal :) **Pros and Cons** Pros: This supports up to 4 controllers (while the Mayflash only supports 2) and this is essentially free(assuming that you already have a wii) Cons: Is nowhere near as convenient as the Mayflash, PPJoy can be a bitch to setup, and the program hasn #8217;t been updated in several years. **NOTES:** * To leave the application on your wii, Hold down L,R,Z,A,Y,START all at the same time. * [u/WhoresBlowMyMind](http://www.reddit.com/user/WhoresBlowMyMind) got this method working on Windows 8:  gt; If you wanna use this in your guide for all the Win8 people, here's what I did: Before doing anything, I disabled Driver signature reinforcement by going to settings in the charms bar, change PC settings, Update and recovery, and then Restart now under Advanced Startup. In the new menu, I went to Troubleshoot, Advanced Options, then Startup settings. Once my computer booted up, I pressed F7 at the window to disable Driver Signature Reinforcement. I did this once in the very beginning, and once after running PPJoy setup for the first time (Once initially, then once after the second Driver Disabling Restart). * This method can be used with up to 4 Gamecube Controllers, but they all have to be individually mapped. * If your wii IP isn #8217;t 192.168.x.x you may have to hex edit the Padsend and the .dol file * More information can be found about PADSEND and hex editing from the [official thread](http://gbatemp.net/threads/padsend-for-ds-wii-pc-application.295119/) but it hasn #8217;t been updated in a while. * If people have a lot of trouble with this guide, I do plan on making a video on how to set this up, and compare it to my USB Mayflash adapter, but from my preliminary tests I notice almost no input lag difference between the USB Mayflash and this method.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-28 23:24:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here's a condensed version of the guide with better formatting.](http://smashboards.com/threads/project-m-3-02-online-via-dolphin-netplay-full-setup-optimization-guide-redesigned.346700/page-13#post-17165357)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-28 23:54:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't gotten to test that as much as I would like, but from the limited tests I have done, I do not notice any lag.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 00:15:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got my Mayflash for 11$ way back when, but it actually [is currently $24 on amazon](http://www.amazon.com/GC-Controller-Adapter-PC/dp/B0089NVTDM/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 amp;qid=1406585410 amp;sr=8-1 amp;keywords=mayflash+gamecube). I personally don't notice any lag with this method, and that's after using it on and off for the past 4 months. One of the reasons I posted this guide now is due to the increase in price of the adapter :P</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 01:02:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Glad you got it working! Did you run into any problems with the setup or anything? Thats weird about the response time, I really didn't notice a difference between this method and my Mayflash, I just find my mayflash much more convenient.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 01:16:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright cool, i'll add it into the post. I don't think that would have anything to do with the lag, I'm also hardwired to the internet and have a kinda expensive modem/router so that might be why I don't notice any input lag.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 03:22:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe only installation, but I leave it on all the time, useful for other stuff as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 22:07:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try unchecking the boxes [here](http://i.imgur.com/RNvl2Lb.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My friend said that emulators only "Diminish" and "Take away" from the original experience... so I sent him this.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-03 19:34:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-03 19:48:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's very stable and works well with pretty much every game I've played on it. I bought the Gamecube controller-USB adapter, but Xbox,Ps3, and Ps4 controllers all work well too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-04 01:07:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>No HD mod was applied, just the standard game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-04 01:25:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya, I wouldn't recommend it though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-04 01:30:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you map the buttons correctly, yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-04 03:24:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably very well since you have an i5, dolphin is like 80-90% Processor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Paul George cheers himself up with new Ferrari (he can't even drive yet)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-06 05:53:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 20:35:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't worry too much about this, I average around 190 [but managed to get this](http://i.imgur.com/1aUor6D.png).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-10 22:41:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>According to you, God sent the shooter that killed 20 innocent children. If your interpretation of God is willing to kill 20 innocent children to "send a message", then what is your devil willing to do?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-11 05:13:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always look forward to these videos every weekend! Thanks for featuring some of my clips! Btw, I loved the build up to the 9 around 2:55!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-12 21:18:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I start school in a little over a week, and my major is actually Computer Security and Information Assurance, do you have any advice? How do you like your job?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Xbox One Will Soon Let You Play Pirated Movies  amp; TV Shows</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-14 02:56:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Toe dispute prompts arrest of beauty contestant</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-14 03:50:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-14 19:14:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you had it working before, and it is now connecting to the wrong IP, you need to [download this](http://www.mediafire.com/download/dgti1yzcjnk/Wiiload_1.1_Installer.exe). Then install the program, and when it asks for the IP address, put in the correct one. This is the only way I know of fixing this issue, and it is rather in-efficient, but it work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-14 19:33:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha alright, the Mayflash is definitely worth it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-15 04:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey a fellow Springfield redditor! The Tornado also came within a mile of my house, those were some crazy times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-16 21:35:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just get a 4gb and Hack your Wii, much easier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-18 07:57:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This guy](http://i.imgur.com/gMiiKUh.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-05 16:57:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I personally would say Mewtwo is currently the best character for a plethora of reasons. But, one of the unpopular opinions I have is that Zelda is probably in the top 5 best characters in the game; all of her moves are incredibly useful/strong, her dins fire allows for an almost Pit-styled projectile game, her recovery is relatively solid, and on top of all of that if the player is equally skilled with Sheik, down-b creates a whole new matchup for any opponent mid-fight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-08 02:41:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is very strange, try just to drag and drop all of the files outside into a folder?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-17 01:23:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you mean by "and my buttons are all messed up", as far as the c-stick thing goes, try shutting off your wii and unplugging your controller and trying again. If it still happens, I'm not really sure what the problem might potentially be a dolphin problem?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-24 01:23:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its not a virus.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL in 2010 the fastest supercomputer in the entire US Defense Department was made of 1,760 PlayStation 3s, 168 separate graphical processing units and 84 coordinating servers.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-06 19:56:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-06 20:25:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, if you'd like another source: "About the 33rd largest supercomputer in the world right now is the US Air Force Research Laboratory's (AFRL) newest system, which has a core made of 1,760 Sony PlayStation 3 (PS3) consoles. In addition to its large capacity, the so-called "Condor Cluster" is capable of performing 500 trillion floating point operations per second (TFLOPS), making it the fastest interactive computer in the entire US Defense Department." [Source](http://phys.org/news/2010-12-air-playstation-3s-supercomputer.html#jCp)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We currently have more users online than r/smashbros !</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-15 07:22:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-15 08:16:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>47</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-15 11:55:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're still awake? Get some sleep man you deserve it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-17 20:59:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I'm not sure how to feel anymore](http://i.imgur.com/FwHwLI1.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-22 19:54:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try a different gamecube port in your Wii</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-25 07:55:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>At first I was pretty much convinced the PDMT had nerfed what was arguably Tink's most useful move, but after getting used to the new nair I definitely feel as though it was an improvement over the old nair.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL The U.S. News and World Report gives the college preparatory SABIS International Charter School a "College Readiness" rating of 25.7/100.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-25 08:13:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-25 08:31:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, at least for me, I feel as if the new nair is better at helping to keep combos going by keeping the victim closer, whereas the old nair was more of a knock-back oriented move. The role of the move definitely changed from the old one, I just prefer the new role better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-01 19:49:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>It needs to be on the Wi-Fi set from the beginning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-07 21:41:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>if you haven't already fixed this, try setting the radius to 100 and the deadzone to 15.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-06 02:40:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a huge PM fan this is hard news to swallow. I seriously never want to hear any #oneunit thing from either side of the argument ever again, its a complete joke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-09 18:36:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Correct me if I'm wrong, but isn't the method of the Wii to HDMI adapter also laggy? I was under the impression that the adapter takes the analog signal that the Wii puts out and converts it to a digital signal, creating lag. I don't think the "Sewell" adapter itself naturally outputs a digital signal. I'm most likely wrong, considering the amount of effort it looks like you put into this post haha, but just slightly confused on that part.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-10 00:18:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand perfectly that the source says that it less than 2ms, it's not that I don't believe that the method is rather lagproof, I'm just trying to understand why.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-21 04:32:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually, on average humans can tell the difference all the way up to 150 fps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Welcome to Wat Do Wednesdays, where we have an in-depth discussion as to what each character in the screenshot should do in the given situation.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-25 19:46:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A true "0 - death" Captain Falcon Combo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-01 20:12:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A true "0 - death" Captain Falcon Combo (X-Post r/smashbros)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-01 20:13:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-02 08:58:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmao that's cause it is you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Welcome to Wat Do Wednesdays Ep2, where we have an in-depth discussion as to what the best course of action is to take given the situation in the Screenshot.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-04 23:02:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Welcome to Wat Do Wednesdays Ep3, where we have an in-depth discussion as to what the best course of action is to take in the given screenshot.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-12 00:29:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Welcome to Wat Do Wednesdays Ep4, where we have an in-depth discussion as to what the best course of action is to take in the given screenshot.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-19 01:30:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>EA's Origin is accused of purchasing 1 million fake likes for their Facebook page, a member of the Origin team shows up to disprove the accusations.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-23 22:17:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Welcome to Wat Do Wednesday Ep5, where we have an in-depth discussion about the best course of action for each character in the given screenshot.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-25 22:24:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-05 03:10:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>uwotm8</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why Super Smash Bros. Wii U Deserves to Dethrone Melee</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-09 18:33:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-09 22:56:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the article was so bad they pulled it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL after professional golfer Ben Hogan threw himself across his car to cover his wife during a head-on collision with a bus, the doctors told him he might never walk again, let alone play golf. He went on to win the US Open the following year.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-11 20:04:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-12 07:00:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>That wasn't the US open, that was the Los Angeles Open.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-12 11:40:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey Dingus where does that say US Open, learn to read before you start shit posting you ignorant dick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-12 18:15:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know what, I wasn't going to respond but you're just the kind of toxic person [I love to prove wrong.](http://i.imgur.com/ztZXjCd.png) So please, fucking read before you post something arrogant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>After the massive success of Ep6, Ep7 and Ep8, Wat Do Wednesday is back!Welcome to Wat Do Wednesdays Ep9, where we have an in-depth discussion as to what the best course of action is to take in the given screenshot.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-17 20:21:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-17 20:21:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>GIMR:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-17 20:21:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>NOT GIMR:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-18 01:46:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>shhhhhhhhhh.... There also may or may not be an Ep6,Ep7 or Ep8</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-22 03:12:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey on a completely unrelated note, are you that Level 1 from way back in the day?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Welcome to the special GFY edition of Wat Do Wednesday Ep10, where we have an in-depth discussion about the best course of action for each character in the given screenshot.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-22 22:18:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-22 22:21:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Captain Fabulous:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-22 22:21:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Diddy Kong Green:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-22 22:21:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Diddy Kong Yellow:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-22 22:21:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Diddy Kang Blue:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-09 17:48:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your budget is the biggest factor, but no matter what get an Intel CPU, aside from being the better choice for netplay, it is the far superior of the two processor competitors.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Project M at CEO 2015</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-27 07:55:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-04 07:55:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eyyyy I was the Mafioso this game! Really close game haha!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-04 16:25:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes unfortunately. The dead actually were the ones to convince Dominic to hang moonshine, because "Let's just get this game over with" - Dominic. If he had realized that he could have hung someone else and the game still would have most likely ended I don't think he would have been so apt to hang the GF.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Missing a tech against someone who is good at punishing.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-05 23:39:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-09 23:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where can I purchase this magnificent sticker/decal?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>eBay and PriceCharting seem to disagree in regards to the price of the game on the right. What do you think a fair asking price is?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-14 03:20:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-14 04:22:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that's good news! I have the memory card, manual and even the cable for the GBA. I actually got both of these games when I was younger, the Zelda Collector's Edition came with my Gamecube and I got Pokemon Box as a Birthday present I believe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-14 04:41:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright, thank you very much! I'll be on the lookout to see how some of the listings do that have everything I have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-25 06:37:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same here, glitch I'm guessing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 03:01:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you are trading from Omega Ruby, I will probably trade with you shortly as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 03:33:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I learned a lot!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 03:34:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I learned a lot!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 03:51:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I think with your last couple trades I figured out everything I needed!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 03:53:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks you to all of those who I got to trade, if I do this again ever I'll try to make sure I involve more people next time (sorry I was a noob to this haha).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-29 04:10:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>there a trade Embargo on Hoopa I believe, not allowing it to be traded until a certain date.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>All Competitive Gen1 Starter Pokemon! Shiny! (Hacked/Cloned)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-30 04:20:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>[SG] Shiny generation 1 Starters, all are holding their respective megastones. I have **30** of each Pokemon, and will trade each person who replies one of each. First come first serve. My friendcode is in my Flair! |[](/pokeball)|Species|M/F| Nature |Ability| IV Spread | Shiny | Moves| Pentagon | OT TID| |:-:|-|:-:|-|-|-|-|-|-|-| | [](/diveball) | Blastoise | M | Modest | Rain Dish | Perfect | Yes | Rapid Spin, Hydro Pump, Dark Pulse, Ice Beam | Yes | Salty 57295 | | [](/nestball) | Venusaur | M | Bold | Chlorophyll | Perfect | Yes | Giga Drain, Sludge Bomb, Leech Seed, Sleep Powder | Yes | Salty 57295 | | [](/pokeball) | Charizard | M | Timid |Solar Power |Perfect | Yes | Fire Blast, Solar Beam, Focus Blast, Dragon Pulse | Yes | Salty 57295 |</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-30 04:23:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>direct trade!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-30 08:00:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>lmfao you traded me the funniest pokemon out of everyone tonight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>All Competitive Gen 2 Starter Pokemon! Shiny! (Hacked/Cloned)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 01:27:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>[SG] Shiny level 100 competitive generation 2 Starters. I have **30** of each Pokemon, if you already have me added from a previous giveaway just trade me, if not use the GTS. |[](/pokeball)|Species|M/F| Nature |Ability| IV Spread | EV Spread | Shiny | Moves| Pentagon | OT TID| |:-:|-|:-:|-|-|-|-|-|-|-|-| | [](/lureball) | Feraligatr | M | Adamant | Sheer Force | 31,31,31,31,31,31 | 252 Atk, 2 Def, 4 SpD, 252 Spe | Yes | Crunch, Waterfall, Dragon Dance, Ice Punch | Yes | Mucho 19987| | [](/nestball) | Meganium | F | Calm | Overgrow| 6 IV | 252 HP, 4 Def, 252 SpD, 2 Spe | Yes | Synthesis, Toxic, Giga Drain, Leech Seed | Yes | Oddity 13589 | | [](/pokeball) | Typhlosion | M | Timid | Blaze | 31,30,30,31,31,31| 2 Def, 252 SpA, 2 SpD, 252 Spe | Yes | Flamethrower, Hidden Power(Ice), Focus Blast, Eruption | Yes | Gradetrain 18763 | ####Rules for GTS trade * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Starter. * Set GTS message as "SenpaiNoticeMe" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each *Edit*: Okay, I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 01:30:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I already have you added, I'l just give you one of each to save time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 01:35:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 01:36:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The three most American Pokemon: Snorlax, Mega Slowbro, and Vanilluxe! All competitive level 100 + Shiny! [Hacked/Clone]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-06 01:34:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>[SG] These are hands down the most American of Pokemon, in honor of Independence day I'm giving away these guys. I have **30** of each Pokemon, if you already have me added from a previous giveaway just trade me, if not use the GTS. |[](/pokeball)|Species|M/F| Nature |Ability| IV Spread | EV Spread | Shiny | Moves| Pentagon | OT TID| |:-:|-|:-:|-|-|-|-|-|-|-|-| | [](/heavyball) | Snorlax | F | Careful | Thick Fat | 31,31,31,31,31,31 | 252 HP, 4 Atk, 2 Def, 252 SpD | Yes | Curse, Giga Impact, Rest, Sleep Talk | Yes | Rain 18443| | [](/diveball) | Vanilluxe | M | Modest | Ice Body| 31,31,31,31,31,31 | 72 HP, 2 Def, 252 SpA, 184 Spe | Yes | Automize, Freeze-Dry, Flash Cannon, Blizzard | Yes | mkboards.com 34123 | | [](/lureball) | Slowbro | F | Bold | Own Tempo | 31,31,31,31,31,31| 252 HP, 2 Atk, 252 Def, 4 SpA | Yes | Calm Mind, Rest, Sleep Talk, Scald | Yes | Snow 20912 | ####Rules for GTS trade * Do not Deposit any Whismurs!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!1111!~! * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "SenpaiNoticeMe" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each * I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-06 01:38:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol its just a joke about us American's being lazy (Snorlax + Slowbro) and loving Ice cream (Vanilluxe).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-06 02:06:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for noticing haha! I just took the format from my last giveaway, which was with Starters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-06 03:26:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe I did? Or am I missing an ID in there, I know theres like an SIV or something like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-06 03:38:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha no problem, I made it kinda hard to see by bundling the OT and TID together into one slot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-27 08:12:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>This would be an amazing movie! So much potential!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Competitive level 100 + Shiny Latios and Latias! [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-31 02:13:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>[SG] Each is holding a Soul Dew. I have **30** of each Pokemon, if you already have me added from a previous giveaway just trade me, if not use the GTS. |[](/pokeball)|Species|M/F| Nature |Ability| IV Spread | EV Spread | Shiny | Moves| Pentagon | OT TID| |:-:|-|:-:|-|-|-|-|-|-|-|-| | [](/pokeball) | Latios | M | Timid | Levitate | 31,31,31,31,31,31 | 2 Def, 252 SpA, 4 SpD, 252 Spe | Yes | Recover, Psychic, Draco Meteor, Dragon Pulse | Yes | MeH 34452| | [](/pokeball) | Latias | F | Bold | Levitate | 31,31,31,31,31,31 | 240 HP, 252 Def, 16 SpD, 2 Spe | Yes | Recover, Dragon Pulse, Psychic, Calm Mind | Yes | Bidoof 23221 | ####Rules for GTS trade * Do not Deposit any Whismurs!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!1111!~! * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "SenpaiNoticeMe" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each * I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-31 05:28:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey sorry about that man, yours in particular for some reason I could just not find, I think because I have a lot of pokemon that people with Phione want. Whenever you see this PM me and we can sort something out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>30 level 100 Shiny Kyurems! (Hacked/Cloned)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-01 02:42:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>[SG] I was gonna give away 30 Kyurem Whites and 30 Kyurem Blacks aswell, but then I realized the GTS doesn't allow those to be traded. So, I have **30** of Kyurem, if you already have me added from a previous giveaway just trade me, if not use the GTS. |[](/pokeball)|Species|M/F| Nature |Ability| IV Spread | EV Spread | Shiny | Moves| Pentagon | OT TID| |:-:|-|:-:|-|-|-|-|-|-|-|-| | [](/diveball) | Kyurem | - | Timid | Pressure | 31,31,31,31,31,31 | I forgot to write them down lol | Yes | Ice Beam, Earth Power, Draco Meteor, Flash Cannon | Yes | Oi Matey 12231| ####Rules for GTS trade * Do not Deposit any Whismurs!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!1111!~! * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "SenpaiNoticeMe" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each * I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>subject4247's Reference</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-01 04:24:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>### |IGN| 3DS | Friend Code| Time Zone| |-----|-------|-----|-----| |Agent X | subject4247 | 4055-5370-6999 | [US EST / GMT -5] | | [](/medalyellow) | Giveaway | Quantity | | :-: | :-: | :-: | | 1 | [All Competitive Gen1 Starter Pokemon! Shiny! (Hacked/Cloned)](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3bl1wk/all_competitive_gen1_starter_pokemon_shiny/) | 90/90 | | 2 | [All Competitive Gen 2 Starter Pokemon! Shiny! (Hacked/Cloned)](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3boxg0/all_competitive_gen_2_starter_pokemon_shiny/) | 90/90 | | 3 | [The three most American Pokemon: Snorlax, Mega Slowbro, and Vanilluxe! All competitive level 100 + Shiny! Hacked/Cloned](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3c8s0p/the_three_most_american_pokemon_snorlax_mega/) | 90/90 | | 4 | [Competitive level 100 + Shiny Latios and Latias! [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3f88d0/competitive_level_100_shiny_latios_and_latias/) | 60/60 | | 5 | [30 level 100 Shiny Kyurems! (Hacked/Cloned)](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3fcw1x/30_level_100_shiny_kyurems_hackedcloned/) | 30/30 | | [](/medalbronze) | Giveaway | Quantity | | :-: | :-: | :-: | | 6 | [Shiny Semi-Pseudo Legendary Pokemon! Competitive + level 100! [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3fgai7/shiny_semipseudo_legendary_pokemon_competitive/) | 60/60 | | 7 | [Competitive level 100 Keldeo + Victini GTS Giveaway! [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3fj4hv/competitive_level_100_keldeo_victini_gts_giveaway/) | 60/60 | | 8 | [Meloetta + Shiny Genesect Direct Trade Giveaway! Level 100! [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3fkku0/meloetta_shiny_genesect_direct_trade_giveaway/) | 58/58 | | 9 | [To Celebrate my friend's new Pokemon Tattoo, I'm giving away Shaymin and Darkrai on the GTS! [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3fyn6l/to_celebrate_my_friends_new_pokemon_tattoo_im/) | 60/60 | | 10 | [Shiny Xerneas Giveaway! Competitive + Level 100 [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3r1cey/shiny_xerneas_giveaway_competitive_level_100/) | 30/30 | | 11 | [Giving away Shiny Yveltals until I fall asleep or my 3DS dies! [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3rv59o/giving_away_shiny_yveltals_until_i_fall_asleep_or/) | 30/30 | | 12 | [Direct Trade Thanksgiveaway [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3uf3up/direct_trade_thanksgiveaway_hackedcloned/) | 30/30 | | 13 | [Shiny Weavile + Shiny Lugia Giveaway! Level 100! Battle Ready![Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/4091fe/shiny_weavile_shiny_lugia_giveaway_level_100/) | 30/30 | | 14 | [Shiny Arceus! Level 100! [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/4ldg5t/shiny_arceus_level_100_hackedcloned/) | 60/60 | | 15 | [Manaphy + Shiny Jirachi Giveaway! [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/4lhlg9/manaphy_shiny_jirachi_giveaway_hackedcloned/) | 60/60 |</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shiny Semi-Pseudo Legendary Pokemon! Competitive + level 100! [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-02 00:38:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>[SG] I have **20** of each Pokemon, if you already have me added from a previous giveaway just trade me, if not use the GTS. #####Table-Title |[](/pokeball)|Species|M/F| Nature |Ability| IV Spread | EV Spread | Shiny | Moves| Pentagon | OT TID| |:-:|-|:-:|-|-|-|-|-|-|-|-| | [](/friendball) | ~~Lucario~~~ | ~~F~~ | ~~Timid~~ |~~Justified~~| ~~31,31,31,31,31,31~~ |~~4 Def, 252 SpA, 2 SpD, 252 Spe~~ | ~~Yes~~ | ~~Nasty Plot, Aura Sphere, Flash Cannon, Vacuum Wave~~ | ~~Yes~~ | ~~SGDQ 12295~~ | | [](/luxuryball) | ~~Haxorus~~ | ~~M~~| ~~Jolly~~ | ~~Mold Breaker (2)~~ | ~~31,31,31,31,31,31~~ | ~~252 Atk, 2 Def, 4 SpD, 252 Spe~~ | ~~Yes~~ | ~~Outrage, Earthquake, Poison Jab, Dragon Claw~~ | ~~Yes~~ | ~~Cant Even 22119~~ | | [](/duskball) | ~~Zoroark~~ | ~~M~~ | ~~Timid~~ | ~~Illusion (1)~~ | ~~31,31,31,31,31,31~~| ~~252 SpA, 2 Def, 4 SpD, 252 Spe~~ | ~~Yes~~ | ~~Night Daze, Focus Blast, Flamethrower, Trick~~ | ~~Yes~~ | ~~Super Mario 13375~~ | ####Rules for GTS trade * Do not Deposit any Whismurs!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!1111!~! * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "SenpaiNoticeMe" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each * I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-02 01:45:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trade me whenever you see this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-02 02:09:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only Haxorus is left!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Competitive level 100 Keldeo + Victini GTS Giveaway! [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-02 20:25:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>[SG] **THESE POKEMON HAVE HAD A RIBBON REMOVED TO MAKE THEM GTS TRADEABLE, THESE WILL NOT PASS AS LEGIT.** I have **30** of each Pokemon, if you already have me added from a previous giveaway just trade me, if not use the GTS. ####The Pokemon |[](/pokeball)|Species|M/F| Nature |Ability| IV Spread | EV Spread | Shiny | Moves| Pentagon | OT TID| |:-:|-|:-:|-|-|-|-|-|-|-|-| | [](/cherishball) |~~Victini~~ | - | ~~Adamant~~ | ~~Victory Star~~ | ~~31,31,31,31,31,31~~ | ~~252 Atk, 4 Def, 252 Spe~~ | ~~No~~ | ~~Brick Break, Zen Headbutt, V-create, Searing Shot~~ | ~~Yes~~ | ~~ #65328; #12473; #12463; #12521; #12483; #12503; 12014~~| | [](/cherishball) | ~~Keldeo~~ | - | ~~Timid~~ | ~~Justified~~ | ~~31,1,31,31,31,31~~ | ~~4 Def, 252 SpA, 252 Spe~~ | ~~No~~ | ~~Scald, Secret Sword, Icy Wind, Hydro Pump~~ | ~~Yes~~ | ~~ #65328; #12473; #12463; #12521; #12483; #12503; 12014~~ | ####Rules for GTS trade * Do not Deposit any WHISMURS OR ABRAS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!1111!~! * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "SenpaiNoticeMe" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each * I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-02 20:35:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>**GIVEAWAY IS OFFICIALLY RESUMED, SORRY FOR THE HALF HOUR WAIT EVERYONE** ` **UPDATE: ALL OUT**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Meloetta + Shiny Genesect Direct Trade Giveaway! Level 100! [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-03 03:54:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>[SG] I know these Pokemon are kinda hard to find now-a-days, and I figured I'd help some people out. I have **29** of each Pokemon, and will trade the fastest people who reply one of each. First come first serve. Just post your Friencode and your name, if you're not immediately available to trade, you will most likely be skipped. My friendcode is in my Flair! #####The Goods |[](/pokeball)|Species|M/F| Nature |Ability| IV Spread | EV Spread | Shiny | Moves| Pentagon | OT TID| |:-:|-|:-:|-|-|-|-|-|-|-|-| | [](/cherishball) | Genesect | - | Hasty | Download | 31,31,31,31,31,31 | 4 HP, 252 Atk, 252 Spe | Yes | Extreme Speed, Iron Head, Shift Gear, Blaze Kick | No |  #12360; #12356; #12364; #12363; #12435; 07133 | | [](/cherishball) | Meloetta | - | Timid | Serene Grace | 31,31,31,31,31,31 | 4 Def, 252 SpA, 252 Spe | No | Psychic, Hyper Voice, Focus Blast, Dazzling Gleam | No |  #12360; #12356; #12364; #12363; #12435; 07142 | **Edit, Once I trade you please reply to your comment confirming it. Makes sorting through comments a lot easier**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-03 04:09:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Enjoy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-03 04:09:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Enjoy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-03 04:09:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Enjoy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-03 07:08:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>My bad, I traded like 3 different people named Alex, PM me and i'll sort it out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-03 19:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya Hax$ would definitely be a much better candidate, considering he's already gone through it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-03 21:20:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guess My Favorite Pokemon, Win 30 Pokemon of your Choice!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 01:42:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>[cg] I figured I'd do one of these, they look like fun. If anyone can guess my favorite Pokemon, I'll add them and give them 30 Pokemon of their choice! Only 2 guesses per-person, and I will only reply to the winning guess! Have fun! **EDIT: FIRST HINT: IT IS PART OF AN EVOLUTIONARY LINE. ANOTHER HINT WILL FOLLOW IF NEEDED. EVERYONE GETS AN ADDITIONAL GUESS AFTER EACH HINT** **EDIT2: SECOND HINT: MASSIVE HINT, IT IS A WATER TYPE POKEMON, EVERYONE GETS ANOTHER HINT** **EDIT3: EVERYONE GETS ANOTHER GUESS BECAUSE THIS IS HILARIOUS**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 01:44:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll give out a hint if I deem it necessary haha. And if I give out a hint, everyone gets an additional guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 02:18:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still not right lmfao.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 02:20:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>**FIRST HINT IS LIVE:IT IS PART OF AN EVOLUTIONARY LINE. ANOTHER HINT WILL FOLLOW IF NEEDED. EVERYONE GETS AN ADDITIONAL GUESS AFTER EACH HINT**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 02:35:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>**SECOND HINT: MASSIVE HINT, IT IS A WATER TYPE POKEMON**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 02:47:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>**EVERYONE GETS ANOTHER GUESS BECAUSE THIS IS HILARIOUS**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 02:49:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>EYYYYYYY WINRAR! WE HAVE A WINNER!!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 02:50:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha dang, you were like 20 seconds too late.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 02:51:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope you like what it ended up being haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 02:53:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya just think about what 30 pokemon you want + any requested moves/items and post them here. I'll add you after I have them and we can trade.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 02:56:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya thats cool with me! Awesome move by you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 02:57:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey /u/Daeno has decided to split the giveaway with you! Think of 15 Pokemon you want + any items/moves or anything like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 03:14:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya dude, you can ask for whatever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 04:03:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay cool, I'll message you again when they're ready. Add me in the meantime.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 04:03:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay cool, I'll message you again when they're ready. Add me in the meantime.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 04:42:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>they're ready to go!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 04:42:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>they're good to go!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 04:57:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kk, im about to head out, but when I get back I'll be able to trade you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL of the Kerala red rain phenomenon, a blood rain (red rain) event that occurred from 25 July to 23 September 2001, when heavy downpours of red-coloured rain fell sporadically on the southern Indian state of Kerala.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 23:17:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 23:21:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You're Killing Me Sakurai</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 23:25:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I hate it when the house smells</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-05 23:31:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I hate it when the house smells</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-06 00:01:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-06 00:08:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya, that's honestly the funniest part haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>PSA Amazon Prime Subscribers can Watch all Four Episodes of Pokemon Origins for Free! (Link in the description)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-06 00:21:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Heres the Link!](http://www.amazon.com/File-1-Red/dp/B00Q7O050S/ref=sr_1_1?s=movies-tv amp;ie=UTF8 amp;qid=1438805589 amp;sr=1-1 amp;keywords=pokemon+origins)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-06 00:49:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya I hope they decide to make more one day!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-06 04:21:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>shhhhh.... I forgot lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-06 04:24:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome! Love the old styled Pikachu!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>To Celebrate my friend's new Pokemon Tattoo, I'm giving away Shaymin and Darkrai on the GTS! [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-06 05:40:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>[SG] **My friend got a classic Pikachu Tattoo (you can show him some love here to thank him for this awesome giveaway): [Picture of the Tattoo](https://www.reddit.com/r/pokemon/comments/3fydgi/just_captured_a_pikachu/)** **THESE POKEMON HAVE HAD A RIBBON REMOVED TO MAKE THEM GTS TRADEABLE, THESE WILL NOT PASS AS LEGIT.** I have **30** of each Pokemon, if you already have me added from a previous giveaway just trade me, if not use the GTS. Each Pokemon is holding a Life Orb. ####The Pokemon |[](/pokeball)|Species|M/F| Nature |Ability| IV Spread | EV Spread | Shiny | Moves| Pentagon | OT TID| |:-:|-|:-:|-|-|-|-|-|-|-|-| | [](/cherishball) |Shaymin | - | Timid | Natural Cure | 31,2,31,31,31,31 | 252 SpA, 4 SpD, 252 Spe | No | Psychic, Synthesis, Seed Flare, Air Slash | Yes |  #65328; #12473; #12463; #12521; #12483; #12503; 12014| | [](/cherishball) | Darkrai | - | Timid | Bad Dreams | 31,31,31,31,31,31 | 4 Def, 252 SpA, 252 Spe | No | Dark Void, Dream Eater, Dark Pulse, Phantom Force | Yes |  #65328; #12473; #12463; #12521; #12483; #12503; 02135 | ####Rules for GTS trade * Do not Deposit any WHISMURS OR ABRAS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!1111!~! * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "SenpaiNoticeMe" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each * I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-06 05:44:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I don't already have you added, use the GTS.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-06 09:38:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-23 21:19:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I Believe Whimsicott is actually the fastest Prankster user, but is countered hard by heatran and Aegislah, so Thundurus is chosen much more often.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-01 17:02:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Too late.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-06 22:38:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-18 00:12:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Its the most important meal of the day!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-18 00:13:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-20 02:56:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Going to school in rural Vermont has its advantages.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-26 21:26:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Less People are Supporting Gun Control</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-08 17:10:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-17 08:51:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guitar Hero Live on Wii U Dolomite Error code.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-29 03:23:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't have much to say other than I receive the Dolomite error code whenever I try to connect to Guitar Hero TV. I'm pretty sure it worked when I first got the game on Saturday, but hasn't worked since. I have tried literally every recommendation on the internet, from resetting my router, fully powering down my Wii U, clearing the cache, uninstalling and re-installing the update, and pretty much anything else posted on any forum. This is post is pretty much my last shot. Any help/advice would be very much appreciated. Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-29 19:10:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya, I'm most likely going to tweet their support, as nothing else has worked so far :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-30 01:45:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I am still having connectivity problems. I would love further assistance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-30 03:12:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have tried re-syncing the guitar and dongle, same error is still occurring. Here is my Speedtest with my ISP/region. I am in Vermont. http://www.speedtest.net/my-result/4788522127</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shiny Xerneas Giveaway! Competitive + Level 100 [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-01 02:56:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>[hcg] **HAPPY HALLOWEEN EVERYONE!** **THIS POKEMON HAS HAD A RIBBON REMOVED TO MAKE IT GTS TRADEABLE, THIS WILL NOT PASS AS LEGIT.** I have **30** of this Pokemon, if you already have me added from a previous giveaway just trade me, if not use the GTS. ####The Pokemon |[](/pokeball)|Species|M/F| Nature |Ability| IV Spread | EV Spread | Shiny | Moves| Pentagon | OT TID| |:-:|-|:-:|-|-|-|-|-|-|-|-| | [](/cherishball) | Xerneas | - | Modest | Fairy Aura | 31,31,31,31,31,31 | 184 HP, 28 Def, 252 SpA, 44 Spe | Yes | Geomancy, Focus Blast, Moonblast, Aromatherapy | Yes | X Y  amp; Z 10295| ####Rules for GTS trade * Do not Deposit any WHISMURS OR ABRAS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!1111!~! * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "SenpaiNoticeMe" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Giving away Shiny Yveltals until I fall asleep or my 3DS dies! [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 07:59:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>[hcg] **THIS POKEMON HAS HAD A RIBBON REMOVED TO MAKE IT GTS TRADEABLE, THIS WILL NOT PASS AS LEGIT.** I have **no set number** of this Pokemon (**read the title on the amount**), if you already have me added from a previous giveaway just trade me, if not use the GTS. ####The Pokemon |[](/pokeball)|Species|M/F| Nature |Ability| IV Spread | EV Spread | Shiny | Moves| Pentagon | OT TID| |:-:|-|:-:|-|-|-|-|-|-|-|-| | [](/cherishball) | Yveltal | - | Rash | Dark Aura | 31,31,31,31,31,31 | 132 HP, 28 Atk, 252 SpA, 96 Spe | Yes | Oblivion Wing, Sucker Punch, Dark Pulse, Foul Play | Yes | X Y  amp; Z 11055 | ####Rules for GTS trade * Do not Deposit any WHISMURS OR ABRAS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!1111!~! * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "SenpaiNoticeMe" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 08:44:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I have another Shiny Xerneas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 08:58:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Add me, I'm pretty sure the only Shiny Xerneas I have left are actual eventmons with the ribbon still on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 09:04:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>O, I'm very well aware haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 09:37:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey everyone, My 3DS just died. I think I got mostly everyone, sorry for those of you that put in 2nd requests that I didn't get to ( I was trying to get to as many people as possible).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guess the number between 1 - 10,000. Winner gets 100 Pokemon of their choice!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 20:41:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>[cg] ~~I'm going to preface this by saying this is more of an experiment on my end to see how long it will take for someone to guess the correct number, and I've never seen something like this done before. I have generated a random number using a program I wrote. Anyways onto the rules:~~ ####WINNING NUMBER HAS BEEN FOUND BY: u/muvers. On their 10th guess, and in under 30 minutes. ####Rules for the Contest * Everyday each person gets 10 guesses per day. (Midnight EST each person receives 10 more guesses) * Each guess must be an individual comment. * Number each of your guesses, even across multiple days. * The Number you are guessing must be **bold**. You can find how to do that in the sidebar. * I will not provide any hints, in order to keep true randomness. Even if you are 1 digit off, I will not tell you. * The winning guess will receive a comment + a PM from me to discuss further details, all other incorrect guesses will receive nothing. * Good Luck, and let the games begin **(  #865;~  #860; #662;  #865; #176;)**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 20:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>If a moderator would like, I can PM them the number to confirm that there is no bias.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 20:44:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make sure the number you are guessing is **bold**.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 20:47:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't worry about it, the odds of that happening for the correct number are very slim.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 21:06:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, I'm absolutely speechless. You got it in under half an hour. That was nuts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 21:09:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>You guessed the number, I'm still dumbfounded.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 21:12:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll be completely honest with you, I didn't expect anyone to win this quickly so I was going to make this contest, go finish my programming project and come back and check. So I won't be able to trade you the pokemon you want till either later tonight or tomorrow sometime, but PM a list+ any items/specific IVs etc... and we can setup a time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 21:18:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya I'm GMT-5 but I've got a pretty open schedule so whenever works for you I'l try to get to work for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-07 21:26:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am going to, purely to see if I can replicate the results or if this was a one time outlier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-10 14:04:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>No lmfao, never heard back from Activision Support either</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guess the number between 1 - 10,000. Winner gets 100 Pokemon of their choice!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-12 00:26:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>[cg] I'm going to preface this by saying this is more of an experiment on my end to see how long it will take for someone to guess the correct number, and I want to see if I can replicate the results of the last giveaway I did like this. I have generated a random number using a program I wrote. Anyways onto the rules: ####Rules for the Contest * Everyday each person gets 10 guesses per day. (Midnight EST each person receives 10 more guesses) * Each guess must be an individual comment. * Number each of your guesses, even across multiple days. * The Number you are guessing must be **bold**. You can find how to do that in the sidebar. * I will not provide any hints, in order to keep true randomness. Even if you are 1 digit off, I will not tell you. * The winning guess will receive a comment + a PM from me to discuss further details, all other incorrect guesses will receive nothing. * Good Luck, and let the games begin **(  #865;~  #860; #662;  #865; #176;)**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-12 02:34:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its a bold comment cotton, lets see if it pays off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-21 07:17:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>ayyyyy good job bro, you got it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-21 17:13:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you guys are still planning that 50/50 split I'd like it if you guys sent your requests in quantities of 25.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-21 17:58:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya, whenever is fine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-23 04:20:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Genned</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Direct Trade Thanksgiveaway [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-27 03:42:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>[hcg] Ayyylmao happy Thanksgiving everyone, here's a mew. I have **30** to giveaway, the Mew is level 5. Just post your Friendcode and your name, if you're not immediately available to trade, you will most likely be skipped. My friendcode is in my Flair! #####The Goods |[](/pokeball)|Species|M/F| Nature |Ability| IV Spread | EV Spread | Shiny | Moves| Pentagon | OT TID| |:-:|-|:-:|-|-|-|-|-|-|-|-| | [](/cherishball) | Mew | - | Careful | Synchronize | 31,31,31,31,31,31 | None | No | Pound | No | Fall2010 10160 | **Once I trade you please reply to your comment confirming it. Makes sorting through comments a lot easier**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-02 05:39:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to preface this by saying that you don't owe us fans any explanation, and you gave us a GAME that was responsible for some of the happiest, hypest, and funnest moments of the past few years of my life. But to go out with almost complete silence on the matter leaves a rather sour taste in the mouths of your thousands of fans, after they've been put and kept in the dark so many times before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-02 06:01:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to preface this by saying that you don't owe us fans any explanation, and you gave us a GAME that was responsible for some of the happiest, hypest, and funnest moments of the past few years of my life. But to go out with almost complete silence on the matter leaves a rather sour taste in the mouths of your thousands of fans, after they've been put and kept in the dark so many times before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>/r/smashcirclejerk has ceased development.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-02 06:53:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-02 06:56:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>While I wish this was a dank meme, it is not, this is legit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>380 days ago Project M was expunged altogether from Apex 2015, today it ceased development.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-02 08:32:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-02 21:31:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I need somewhere to post my old dank memes and this seems like the place.](http://i.imgur.com/frT8WHz.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-02 21:53:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry we can't give away any of the old already made stacks because further development is ceased :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-03 02:57:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very well written and somewhat informative, I think if you had commented something to this extent earlier on a lot of this debacle could have been avoided.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-03 04:35:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.reddit.com/r/smashcirclejerk/comments/32y7lm/after_the_massive_success_of_ep6_ep7_and_ep8_wat/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>After Flying for 40 Minutes, Someone Noticed a Plane Door Was Open</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-05 06:38:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shiny Weavile + Shiny Lugia Giveaway! Level 100! Battle Ready![Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-10 01:48:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>[hcg] **I'm gonna give away as many of these guys as I can withing the next hour and a half.** If you already have me added from a previous giveaway just trade me, if not use the GTS. Each Pokemon is holding a Life Orb. ####The Pokemon |[](/pokeball)|Species|M/F| Nature |Ability| IV Spread | EV Spread | Shiny | Moves| Pentagon | OT TID| |:-:|-|:-:|-|-|-|-|-|-|-|-| | [](/duskball) | Weavile | M | Jolly | Pickpocket | 31,31,31,31,31,31 | 252 Atk, 4 SpD, 252 Spe | Yes | Icicle Crash, Knock Off, Fake Out, Poison Jab | Yes | KSPNM 29074 | | [](/diveball) | Lugia | - | Timid | Pressure | 31,0,31,31,31,31 | 252 Def, 4 SpD, 252 Spe | Yes | Psychic, Recover, Aeroblast, Calm Mind | Yes | IWACYIAW 59022 | ####Rules for GTS trade * Do not Deposit any WHISMURS OR ABRAS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!1111!~! * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "SenpaiNoticeMe" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each * I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-10 09:04:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I may be wrong on this, but I believe you can actually downgrade your 3DS/2DS to an older firmware with this newest exploit. That would allow you to install CFW, and never need to worry about Nintendo patching anything ever again. I've got one of my consoles with CFW already and another with a Gateway, so I have no way of testing it, but I'm pretty certain its possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-13 05:45:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>"This game only dies when people stop playing it!", is kind of hard to take seriously when seemingly every opportunity to seriously play the game in a hyper-competitive atmosphere is quashed at every turn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-18 16:25:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Major Key #128273;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 00:57:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 01:31:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-23 02:47:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>sleep tight, pupper</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-24 20:54:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-28 16:28:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-28 18:30:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-30 04:01:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>good form, pupper</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-11 18:40:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-15 16:30:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ravi didn't turn when he was bitten by the rat because the disease can't travel across different species.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-27 18:45:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>get paid pupper</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-04 04:27:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-04 22:12:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, I just picked up a free CRT that must be ancient as its only input is through RF. So I guess I'm wondering if anyone uses an RF cable adapter for their setups (and if so what adapter), or does it cause lag? Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-05 02:18:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>My B.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shield Breaking Popo is not safe.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-07 05:07:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://gfycat.com/SmallPoshAnhinga</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-20 21:49:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Well this happened on day 5...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-22 18:13:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We just had 4 Escorts and a Consort in a ranked game.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-23 06:58:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me #129302;irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-25 04:34:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-25 04:35:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>For those that don't know, this was Microsoft's "teen girl" twitter AI that became "a Hitler-loving sex robot within 24 hours."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me #128465;irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-10 20:12:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-13 04:11:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Heeeeeeeeeres Major!*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-25 00:18:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Lol](http://i.imgur.com/HTg0rxz.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When someone reports you for cheating over Skype when you used process of elimination</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-25 18:31:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"I'm never streaming again" - Leffen</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-27 05:08:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://twitter.com/TSM_Leffen/status/725157851405160448</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"Hey man what are all these apps on your phone?"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-18 01:58:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-18 08:06:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a good thing I don't play anymore haha. I'm just here for the memes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-24 22:18:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>You might find [this interesting.](http://smashboards.com/threads/does-personality-influence-ones-choice-of-their-primary-character-survey.390855/) Although it is for Project M.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 23:06:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think Vince Gilligan actually stated in an interview somewhere that if you thought Gus and his friend were lovers "you wouldn't be wrong." Just from memory though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shiny Arceus! Level 100! [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-28 01:42:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>[hcg] **This Pokemon has had a Ribbon removed to make it GTS Trade able, IT WILL NOT PASS AS LEGIT.** Hey guys, I've been inactive for a while and figured I'd do a giveaway. **To anyone whom I still owe pokemon from a previous contest giveaway, message me and we can setup a time!** This is a pretty standard giveaway, except I will be giving the pokemon away on two Systems this time, to possibly increase speed. I have **60** of this pokemon to give away. **The only other thing I ask you post along with what you're putting up on the GTS is an answer to this question:** *Would you watch/follow a livestream of me giving away pokemon live?* If I decided to do this, anyone that followed the stream would receive an e-mail notification of when I went live and would most likely have first dibs at the giveaway. If you already have me added from a previous giveaway just trade me, if not use the GTS. Each Pokemon is holding a Silk Scarf. ####The Pokemon |[](/pokeball)|Species|M/F| Nature |Ability| IV Spread | EV Spread | Shiny | Moves| Pentagon | OT TID| |:-:|-|:-:|-|-|-|-|-|-|-|-| | [](/cherishball) |  #12450; #12523; #12475; #12454; #12473; | - | Adamant | Multitype | 31,31,31,31,31,31 | 4 Hp, 252 Spa, 252 Spe | Yes | Judgement, Blast Burn, Hydro Cannon, Earth Power | Yes |  #12487; #12475; #12523; #12471; #12486; #12451; 03075 | ####Rules for GTS trade * Do not Deposit any WHISMURS OR ABRAS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!1111!~! * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "SenpaiNoticeMe" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each * I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-28 02:43:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats on completing! Make sure to post some pictures of it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-28 04:55:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, to my recollection at the time of his death he had a wife and kids.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-28 05:33:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought I remembered seeing Kid's toys and stuff in Gus Fring's house, if he did all of that to convince Walter that would be something else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Manaphy + Shiny Jirachi Giveaway! [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-28 23:18:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>[hcg] **I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!** **I have 30 of each pokemon, and will be distributing them across two systems to increase the speed of the giveaway.** Manaphy is level 1, Jirachi is level 15 and holding a Stardust. If you already have me added from a previous giveaway just trade me, if not use the GTS. ####The Pokemon |[](/pokeball)|Species|M/F| Nature |Ability| IV Spread | EV Spread | Shiny | Moves| Pentagon | OT TID| |:-:|-|:-:|-|-|-|-|-|-|-|-| | [](/cherishball) | Manaphy | - | Timid | Hydration | 31,31,31,31,31,31 | - | No | Tail Glow, Bubble, Water Sport, Heart Swap | Yes |  #47932; #51032; #51068; #51313; 07235 | | [](/cherishball) | Jirachi | - | Jolly | Serene Grace | 31,31,31,31,31,31 | - | Yes | Wish, Confusion, Helping Hand, Return | Yes |  #12509; #12465; #12475; #12531; 12014 | ####Rules for GTS trade * Do not Deposit any WHISMURS OR ABRAS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!1111!~! * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "SenpaiNoticeMe" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each * **I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-28 23:59:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sent both of you your pokemon, chill out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-29 00:09:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Went back up the list and got you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-29 03:41:33</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>subject4247's References #2</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-04 09:21:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>My first Reference page was old and archived, but it can be found [HERE](https://www.reddit.com/r/PkmnGiveawayRefs/comments/3fd70d/gridelins_reference/) ### |IGN| 3DS | Friend Code| Time Zone| |-----|-------|-----|-----| |Agent X | subject4247 | 4055-5370-6999 | [US EST / GMT -5] | | [](/medalyellow) | Giveaway | Quantity | | :-: | :-: | :-: | | 1 | [All Competitive Gen1 Starter Pokemon! Shiny! (Hacked/Cloned)](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3bl1wk/all_competitive_gen1_starter_pokemon_shiny/) | 90/90 | | 2 | [All Competitive Gen 2 Starter Pokemon! Shiny! (Hacked/Cloned)](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3boxg0/all_competitive_gen_2_starter_pokemon_shiny/) | 90/90 | | 3 | [The three most American Pokemon: Snorlax, Mega Slowbro, and Vanilluxe! All competitive level 100 + Shiny! Hacked/Cloned](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3c8s0p/the_three_most_american_pokemon_snorlax_mega/) | 90/90 | | 4 | [Competitive level 100 + Shiny Latios and Latias! [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3f88d0/competitive_level_100_shiny_latios_and_latias/) | 60/60 | | 5 | [30 level 100 Shiny Kyurems! (Hacked/Cloned)](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3fcw1x/30_level_100_shiny_kyurems_hackedcloned/) | 30/30 | | [](/medalbronze) | Giveaway | Quantity | | :-: | :-: | :-: | | 6 | [Shiny Semi-Pseudo Legendary Pokemon! Competitive + level 100! [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3fgai7/shiny_semipseudo_legendary_pokemon_competitive/) | 60/60 | | 7 | [Competitive level 100 Keldeo + Victini GTS Giveaway! [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3fj4hv/competitive_level_100_keldeo_victini_gts_giveaway/) | 60/60 | | 8 | [Meloetta + Shiny Genesect Direct Trade Giveaway! Level 100! [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3fkku0/meloetta_shiny_genesect_direct_trade_giveaway/) | 58/58 | | 9 | [To Celebrate my friend's new Pokemon Tattoo, I'm giving away Shaymin and Darkrai on the GTS! [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3fyn6l/to_celebrate_my_friends_new_pokemon_tattoo_im/) | 60/60 | | 10 | [Shiny Xerneas Giveaway! Competitive + Level 100 [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3r1cey/shiny_xerneas_giveaway_competitive_level_100/) | 30/30 | | 11 | [Giving away Shiny Yveltals until I fall asleep or my 3DS dies! [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3rv59o/giving_away_shiny_yveltals_until_i_fall_asleep_or/) | 30/30 | | 12 | [Direct Trade Thanksgiveaway [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/3uf3up/direct_trade_thanksgiveaway_hackedcloned/) | 30/30 | | 13 | [Shiny Weavile + Shiny Lugia Giveaway! Level 100! Battle Ready![Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/4091fe/shiny_weavile_shiny_lugia_giveaway_level_100/) | 30/30 | | 14 | [Shiny Arceus! Level 100! [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/4ldg5t/shiny_arceus_level_100_hackedcloned/) | 60/60 | | 15 | [Manaphy + Shiny Jirachi Giveaway! [Hacked/Cloned]](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemongiveaway/comments/4lhlg9/manaphy_shiny_jirachi_giveaway_hackedcloned/) | 60/60 |</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 00:20:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shiny Regigigas + Shiny Zebstrika! Level 100! BR! [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 22:15:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>[hcg] ***To participate in this giveaway please answer the following survey question:*** **Should users giving away pokemon on this subreddit be allowed to post a link to their live stream (so the receiver can watch the giveaway progress live)?** (Y/N) *This would not allow users to post stream-only giveaways or anything else that would otherwise be against the rules.* I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done! I have **32** of each pokemon, and will be distributing them across two systems to increase the speed of the giveaway. ####The Pokemon |[](/pokeball)|Species|M/F| Nature |Ability| IV Spread | EV Spread | Shiny | Moves| Pentagon | OT TID| |:-:|-|:-:|-|-|-|-|-|-|-|-| | [](/premierball) | ~~Regigigas~~ | - | ~~Adamant~~ | ~~Slow Start~~ | ~~31,31,31,31,31,31~~ | ~~252 Hp, 252 Atk, 4 Spe~~ | ~~Yes~~ | ~~Drain Punch, Return, Thunder wave, Knock Off~~ | ~~Yes~~ | ~~Ayy Lmao 14412~~ | | [](/pokeball) | ~~Zebstrika~~ | ~~M~~ | ~~Timid~~ | ~~Sap Sipper~~ | ~~31,31,31,31,31,31~~ | ~~252 Spa, 4 SpD, 252 Spe~~ | ~~Yes~~ | ~~Volt Switch, Thunderbolt, Overheat, Hidden Power~~ | ~~Yes~~ | ~~FDA 57211~~ | ###Rules for GTS trade * Do not Deposit any WHISMURS OR ABRAS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!1111!~! * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "SenpaiNoticeMe" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each * **I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 22:23:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 22:28:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>no</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 22:33:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 22:54:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't see your pokemon on the GTS and moved on to the next person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 23:10:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol for the sake of all giveaways, please don't deposit Haunter or any other pokemon that evolves through trade, it definitely slows down the giveaway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 23:18:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its Zebstrika, not Zebstrike. I don't think you deposited it correctly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Live Streaming Keldeo + Victini Giveaway! [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-06 04:06:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>[g] You can watch the stream [HERE](https://www.twitch.tv/projectgiveaway)! I won't reply to comments saying sent, but you can track the progress of the giveaway on stream! Hey everyone, this is my first giveaway over here on PokemonPlaza, but some of you might recognize me from /r/Pokemongiveaway , as I did giveaways rather frequently over there. Anyways, I decided I'd do my first giveaway over here and see how it goes! ####[](#0) Pok #233;mon (Nickname) | Gender | Ability | Nature | IV-spread | Egg Moves | Original Trainer | Trainer ID | Type of Pok #233;ball | Level | Generation Mark (e.g. Pentagon) | Language ---------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|---------- Keldeo ( #12465; #12523; #12487; #12451; #12458;) | - | Justified | Modest | 6IV | Scald, Secret Sword, Icy Wind, Hydro Pump |  #65328; #12473; #12463; #12521; #12483; #12503; | 12014 | Cherish Ball | 100 | Pentagon | JPN Victini | - | Victory Star | Adamant | 6IV | Brick Break, Searing Shot, V-create, Zen Headbutt |  #65328; #12473; #12463; #12521; #12483; #12503; | 12014 | Cherish Ball | 100 | Pentagon | ENG ###Rules for GTS trade * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons, Whismurs) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "ProjectGiveaway" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each * **I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-07 01:07:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Live Streaming Shiny Diance + Shiny Lugia Giveaway! [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 02:50:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>[g] You can watch the stream [HERE](https://www.twitch.tv/projectgiveaway)! I won't reply to comments saying sent, but you can track the progress of the giveaway on stream! Hey everyone, just a quick little give away. Diance is holding a normal gem, Lugia is holding leftovers. Diance has had a ribbon removed to make it GTS Trade able, but the Lugia is completely legal. ####[](#0) Pok #233;mon (Nickname) | Gender | Ability | Nature | IV-spread | Egg Moves | Original Trainer | Trainer ID | Type of Pok #233;ball | Level | Generation Mark (e.g. Pentagon) | Language ---------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|---------- Diance ( #12487; #12451; #12450; #12531; #12471; #12540;) | - | Clear Body | Naive | 6IV | Moonblast, Diamond Storm, Earth Power, Return |  #12509; #12465; #12475; #12531; | 12125 | Cherish Ball | 100 | Pentagon | JPN Lugia | - | Pressure | Timid | 5IV | Psychic, Recover, Aeroblast, Calm Mind | IWACYIAW | 59022 | Dive Ball | 100 | Pentagon | ENG ###Rules for GTS trade * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons, Whismurs) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "ProjectGiveaway" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each * **I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Live Streaming Shiny Eevee + Ho-Oh Giveaway! [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-12 04:15:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>[g] You can watch the stream [HERE](https://www.twitch.tv/projectgiveaway)! I won't reply to comments saying sent, but you can track the progress of the giveaway on stream! Another give away :). Eevee is holding an ability capsule, Ho-Oh is holding a Choice Band. Both should be completely legal! ####[](#0) Pok #233;mon (Nickname) | Gender | Ability | Nature | IV-spread | Egg Moves | Original Trainer | Trainer ID | Type of Pok #233;ball | Level | Generation Mark (e.g. Pentagon) | Language ---------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|---------- Eevee | F | Adaptability | Sassy | 6IV | Quick Attack, Swift, Bite, Baby-Doll eyes | Alatreon | 31740 | Ultra Ball | 82 | Pentagon | ITA Ho-Oh | - | Pressure | Jolly | 6IV | Brave Bird, Earthquake, Sacred Fire, Recover | Tea | 11093 | Quick Ball | 100 | Pentagon | SPA ###Rules for GTS trade * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons, Whismurs) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "ProjectGiveaway" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each * **I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-12 05:23:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha its pretty chill, I didn't know how much I'd enjoy but the viewers seem to enjoy it a lot :) . Thanks for allowing me to do this unlike that other subreddit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-12 06:05:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did a couple with a friend, definitely recommended</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Live Streaming 6IV German Shiny Ditto + Shaymin Giveaway! [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-16 03:21:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>[g] You can watch the stream [HERE](https://www.twitch.tv/projectgiveaway)! I won't reply to comments saying sent, but you can track the progress of the giveaway on stream! The Shaymin has had a ribbon removed to make it GTS trade able. The Shaymin is holding a Life Orb, and the Ditto is holding a Metal Powder. ####[](#0) Pok #233;mon (Nickname) | Gender | Ability | Nature | IV-spread | Egg Moves | Original Trainer | Trainer ID | Type of Pok #233;ball | Level | Generation Mark (e.g. Pentagon) | Language ---------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|---------- Ditto | - | Imposter| Timid | 6IV | Transform | Alatreon | 57098 | Dive Ball | 100 | Pentagon | GER Shaymin | - | Natural Cure | Timid | 6IV | Psychic, Synthesis, Seed Flare, Air Slash |  #65328; #12473; #12463; #12521; #12483; #12503; | 12014 | Cherish Ball | 100 | Pentagon | ENG ###Rules for GTS trade * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons, Whismurs) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "ProjectGiveaway" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each * **I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-17 23:15:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just ask for whatever you want, and I'll tell you if I have it lol. It will be much faster than listing off what I have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-17 23:19:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I plan on making a video on the method after this, and probably like 20ish trash mon would suffice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shiny Kyogre + Shiny Groudon + Masterball Giveaway! [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-18 04:26:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>[g] You can watch the stream [HERE](https://www.twitch.tv/projectgiveaway)! **I am going to try something new, and have people submit their requests [HERE](http://goo.gl/forms/DMzzNdeYtPXLKOYs2) through Google Forms. INSTEAD OF THE COMMENTS SECTION!** Google Forms auto-updates and allows me to keep a very clean and concise spreadsheet, it also ensures that the people entering the giveaway are following the majority of the rules. **IF YOU ARE IN A COUNTRY THAT HAS BLOCKED GOOGLE FORMS, YOU MAY COMMENT ON THE THREAD TO SUBMIT YOUR REQUEST, BUT I WILL ONLY BE CHECKING THE THREAD SPORADICALLY.** Neither of these Pokemon will pass as legit, due to the fact Pentagon+Shiny Groudon/Kyogre is an impossible combination. Nevertheless, they are GTS-trade able. Each Pokemon is holding a Masterball. Have fun! ####[](#0) Pok #233;mon (Nickname) | Gender | Ability | Nature | IV-spread | Egg Moves | Original Trainer | Trainer ID | Type of Pok #233;ball | Level | Generation Mark (e.g. Pentagon) | Language ---------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|---------- Groudon | - | Drought| Adamant | 6IV | Stone Edge, Rock Polish, Fire Punch, Earthquake | Aww | 11213 | Ultra Ball | 100 | Pentagon | ENG Kyogre | - | Drizzle | Modest | 5IV | Thunder, Scald, Ice Beam, Calm Mind | May | 23223 | Dive Ball | 100 | Pentagon | ENG ###Rules for GTS trade * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons, Whismurs) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "ProjectGiveaway" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each * **I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-18 07:39:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>o</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to Clone Pokemon in Seconds (No Powersaves required.) [Fastest Possible Method]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 05:01:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>[i] A couple of people watching my livestream the other day pretty much had their minds blown by how I cloned Pokemon for giveaways. Since its a fairly new method, I'd figured I might as well make a brief tutorial/explanation as to how its done, and hopefully some people here can reap the benefits. If this method catches on, it could make cloning services un-measurably faster(as the cloning can occur during the trading process). Powersaves are not required, but a CFW or A9LH is. [HERES THE VIDEO](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1O2adFt9Vzw)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to Clone Pokemon in Seconds (No Powersaves required.) [Fastest Possible Method]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 05:11:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>[i] A couple of people watching my livestream the other day pretty much had their minds blown by how I cloned Pokemon when I was about to run out during a giveaway. Anyone that has ever done a giveaway, and has decided that they want to clone some more of the Pokemon can attest to the fact of how much of a pain it is... until now! Since its a fairly new method, I'd figured I might as well make a brief tutorial/explanation as to how its done, and hopefully some people here can reap the benefits. If this method catches on, it could make cloning services and giveaways un-measurably faster. Powersaves are not required, but a CFW or A9LH is. [HERES THE VIDEO](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1O2adFt9Vzw)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 05:48:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you follow that tutorial (first link in the description of video), there is almost no risk of modding your 3DS. But you have to follow the tutorial point-by-point to an absolute tee.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 05:52:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have no problem with the stance the Dev took in keeping the project Closed-source. Being a programmer myself (although nowhere near as good as the BootNTR dev) I can personally say that if I discovered a way to stream 3DS Gameplay without the need for a $200+ capture device, and Dump the RAM of live games, I too would be reluctant to hand over all of my hard-work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 06:37:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I also don't see it being the mainstay (as it is discontinued), but I respect the Dev's right to keep his code Closed-Source. I personally believe the majority of the people nagging for him to open-source it weren't going to do anything worthwhile with the code anyways, never mind the fact that they had nothing to do with the project and had no right telling him to open source it. Regardless of all of that, I like the guy just because he likes Shibes. Shibes are awesome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 06:42:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you watch the video in the main post, I am actually recording all of that footage using the same Boot NTR application.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 06:43:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I forgot to mention its only on the N3DS haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 07:09:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank You :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 08:11:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm willing to bet that your friend installed Injected_FBI into the H amp;S, and thats why its not view-able in Sysnand. This actually happened on a 2DS I was hacking for a friend. I was able to "find" it again by booting rxTools(I know right?) in Dev Mode. This ended up showing that the H amp;S App was already FBI.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 08:18:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's been a looooong time since I've used Pokegen, but I believe the solution to your problem is incredibly simple (if I remember correctly). I'm pretty sure you can actually just open two instances of Pokegen (so open the program twice), then open your HG save in one, and the B2 save in the other. Then just drag the pokemon(yes the actual icon) from their Box in the HG save to an empty slot in the B2 Save. Hope this helped :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 16:14:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need CFW or A9LH installed, there's a guide in the description.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 16:17:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>As long as your router doesn't bottleneck you, the top screen is pretty consistent at around 30fps. The bottom screen does lag, but I remember reading that if you want to prioritize the bottom screen you can change the settings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 17:52:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are they both .SAV files that you're trying to transfer to and from? After I posted this suggestion, I went and tried it on the old copy of Pokegen I had on my PC, and it worked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 19:17:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depends on where your warranty is from. If its like a GameStop Warranty, they have no way of knowing any damage incurred was from hacking, whereas if it's a Nintendo warranty you can pretty much just kiss it goodbye.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 19:33:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know there is a way to efficiently do this with Pokegen, but it's been so long. I think your best bet might be to trade the Pok #233;mon from the R4 to the legit B2 cart, and then transfer to X and Y</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 19:50:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly if you give me the .pkm files I can just trade them directly to your X amp;Y</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 22:32:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>No problem, I figured by the time I replied that you probably would've figured it out, but none of the other replies to your question looked terribly helpful haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-23 01:22:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>A friend of mine has an Old 3ds that he hasn't used in a long time that actually happens to be on Sys 2.1. I already dumped the OTP from it, but what is the best way to proceed in installing A9LH? (Since he doesn't have an emunand or sysnand backup or anything).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Live Streaming Shiny Deoxys + Shiny Lucario Giveaway! [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-23 04:09:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>[g] You can watch the stream [HERE](https://www.twitch.tv/projectgiveaway)! **I went to go grab some food, I'll be back in 20-30mins and resume the giveaway.** **I am going to try something new, and have people submit their requests [HERE](http://goo.gl/forms/jmxcQTJacq9LA8sI3) through Google Forms. INSTEAD OF THE COMMENTS SECTION!** Google Forms auto-updates and allows me to keep a very clean and concise spreadsheet, it also ensures that the people entering the giveaway are following the majority of the rules. **IF YOU ARE IN A COUNTRY THAT HAS BLOCKED GOOGLE FORMS, YOU MAY COMMENT ON THE THREAD TO SUBMIT YOUR REQUEST, BUT I WILL ONLY BE CHECKING THE THREAD SPORADICALLY.** Deoxys will not pass as legit, due to the fact Pentagon+Shiny Deoxys is an impossible combination. Nevertheless, it is GTS-trade able. Deoxys is holding a Focus Sash. ####[](#0) Pok #233;mon (Nickname) | Gender | Ability | Nature | IV-spread | Egg Moves | Original Trainer | Trainer ID | Type of Pok #233;ball | Level | Generation Mark (e.g. Pentagon) | Language ---------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|---------- Lucario | M | Justified | Adamant | 6IV | Close Combat, Bullet Punch, Ice Punch, Swords Dance | Vinicius | 57295 | Poke Ball | 100 | Pentagon | ENG Deoxys | - | Pressure | Jolly | 6IV | Extreme Speed, Knock Off, Super Power, Zen Headbutt | 20xx | 21213 | Dusk Ball | 100 | Pentagon | ENG ###Rules for GTS trade * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons, Whismurs) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "ProjectGiveaway" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each * **I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-23 05:36:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I went to go grab some food, I'll be back in 20-30mins and resume the giveaway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Live Streaming Shiny Rayquaza + Shiny Ferrothorn Giveaway! [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-25 05:17:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>[g] You can watch the stream [HERE](https://www.twitch.tv/projectgiveaway)! **I am going to try something new, and have people submit their requests [HERE](http://goo.gl/forms/ZHpMFeCImbw7f4Eo1) through Google Forms. INSTEAD OF THE COMMENTS SECTION!** Google Forms auto-updates and allows me to keep a very clean and concise spreadsheet, it also ensures that the people entering the giveaway are following the majority of the rules. **IF YOU ARE IN A COUNTRY THAT HAS BLOCKED GOOGLE FORMS, YOU MAY COMMENT ON THE THREAD TO SUBMIT YOUR REQUEST, BUT I WILL ONLY BE CHECKING THE THREAD SPORADICALLY.** Rayquaza will not pass as legit, due to the fact it has had an event ribbon removed to make it GTS-tradeable. Rayquaza is holding an Assault Vest, Ferrothorn is holding leftovers. ####[](#0) Pok #233;mon (Nickname) | Gender | Ability | Nature | IV-spread | Egg Moves | Original Trainer | Trainer ID | Type of Pok #233;ball | Level | Generation Mark (e.g. Pentagon) | Language ---------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|---------- Rayquaza ( #12524; #12483; #12463; #12454; #12470;) | - | Airlock | Adamant | 6IV | Dragon Claw, Draco Meteor, Extreme Speed, Earthquake |  #65335; #65320; #65318; #65297; #65301; | 01185 | Cherish Ball | 100 | Pentagon | JPN Ferrothorn | M | Iron Barbs | Brave | 5IV | Leech Seed, Power Whip, Gyro Ball, Protext | TonyP | 17388 | Dive Ball | 100 | Pentagon | ENG ###Rules for GTS trade * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons, Whismurs) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "ProjectGiveaway" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each * **I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-26 04:36:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-26 08:05:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Black N3DS XL (US) came with 9.6 Serial was QW1069</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-27 19:31:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 22:40:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 22:41:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me Irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 22:44:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 02:49:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any support is appreciated! Thank you, I'm glad this is also perceived as efficient for people entering the giveaway!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Live Streaming Shiny Arceus + Shiny Stunfisk Giveaway! [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 03:43:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>[g] You can watch the stream [HERE](https://www.twitch.tv/projectgiveaway)! **I am going to try something new, and have people submit their requests [HERE](http://goo.gl/forms/FMlwPAVHPBTvr8Dz2) through Google Forms. INSTEAD OF THE COMMENTS SECTION!** Google Forms auto-updates and allows me to keep a very clean and concise spreadsheet, it also ensures that the people entering the giveaway are following the majority of the rules. **IF YOU ARE IN A COUNTRY THAT HAS BLOCKED GOOGLE FORMS, YOU MAY COMMENT ON THE THREAD TO SUBMIT YOUR REQUEST, BUT I WILL ONLY BE CHECKING THE THREAD SPORADICALLY.** Arceus will not pass as legit, due to the fact it has had an event ribbon removed to make it GTS-tradeable. Arceus is holding a Silk Scarf, Stunfisk is holding leftovers. ####[](#0) Pok #233;mon (Nickname) | Gender | Ability | Nature | IV-spread | Egg Moves | Original Trainer | Trainer ID | Type of Pok #233;ball | Level | Generation Mark (e.g. Pentagon) | Language ---------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|---------- Stunfisk | F | Static | Bold | 6IV | Stealth Rock, Pain Split, Earth Power, Discharge | AyyLmao | 13337 | Luxury Ball | 100 | Pentagon | ENG Arceus( #12450; #12523; #12475; #12454; #12473;) | - | Multitype | Modest | 6IV | Judgement, Blast Burn, Hydro Cannon, Earth Power |  #12487; #12475; #12523; #12471; #12486; #12451; | 03075 | Cherish Ball | 100 | Pentagon | JPN ###Rules for GTS trade * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons, Whismurs) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "ProjectGiveaway" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 04:21:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're an interesting bunch haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 04:23:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>**SEEING AS MY THREAD WAS REMOVED AND I WAS TOLD TO POST HERE, HERE WE GO.** So this entire question/discussion is in regards to Rule 6, which can be seen here:  gt; Rule 6: Giveaways are ONLY Giveaways, no asking for anything in return, that defeats the purpose. This includes everything from pokemon to karma to favors. All giveaways must also take place within this sub. Trying to advertise by getting people to visit another site or take part in some task is not allowed. All contests should be done here. I have asked the mods in the past if I could use Google forms as a way for people to enter my giveaways, but they stated that all giveaway must take place within the subreddit. While this is a perfectly sensible rule, after doing several giveaways using Google Forms + Sheets, I believe that it may be the best way possible to do a giveaway, and I plan on showing those points. ***What is Google Forms?*** For those that may not know, Google Forms is pretty much Google's survey platform. It allows people to ask survey questions, and have the answers dumped into a nice and concise spreadsheet for easy data viewing + manipulation. ***Advantages*** * It is this spread sheet of data that is the most valuable part of doing a giveaway with Google Forms, as it live updates as responses are filled out. This allows for the person running the giveaway to keep track of their place in the giveaway with ease, and without needing the refresh the reddit page every minute. * If the survey questions are setup correctly, it will not allow people to deposit pokemon that are against the rules of the giveaway(so no more commenting on incorrect deposits telling people to deposit again). * Having all of the giveaway-entrants in the same place also allows for the person hosting the giveaway to host the giveaway on multiple locations (for example I have hosted giveaways on /r/PokemonPlaza and Twitch concurrently). * The live updating spreadsheet also allows people who've entered the giveaway to see where on the list the person hosting the giveaway is. * Additionally, if you are only giving away a set number of pokemon(say 60 for this example), you can cap Google forms to only allow 60 entrees. ***Examples*** [**Here is an example of the way I can view the entrants coming from Google Forms (Pretty sweet huh?)**](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1i-TT57-1cSsXj0QbCk8mfd5C9yYWQlfZFdHSMFdyBHA/edit#gid=1272211979) This live updates, and can be seen by anyone with the link, so people entering the giveaway can see where I am on the giveaway, as well as where they are on the list. [Here is what the raw data looks like coming from Google Forms.](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1NR0XnTkK3dXlT1DleHr4y7JxvSxl_vOyKaitScnspaE/edit#gid=848941535) ***Overall*** In conclusion, I can't really see much of a reason why people hosting giveaways on this Sub shouldn't be allowed to use this method. I have hosted easily 30+ Giveaways between this subreddit, other subreddits, and Twitch, and can say without a doubt that this is the most efficient method of doing a giveaway. If all giveaways must be held within this subreddit, then maybe consider making it so people must post in the thread + fill out the google form? This is such a great feature that really shouldn't be missed out on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 04:52:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>* To address this first point, there is an entire spreadsheet that can be organized by any means possible. It can be sorted by subreddit, username, pretty much anything. This method also gives a total sent for each individual category, making it very easy to keep track. And if making sure they are tied to a reddit account is such a priority, then make people post "deposited" or something to that extent in the thread. * For the 2nd point: No offence but what other benefits are sought from the community other than pokemon? Its not like linking people to an offsite Google Form is redirecting them through a paywall, if anything it benefits the community by keeping everything clean and concise, as well as encouraging others to host giveaways here. * Third point: Well maybe its a priority for the people hosting giveaways on your subreddit? Or don't you care about the "benefit of the community"? * This is a valid point that I am still brainstorming how to work around, I believe I can add a timer between the submissions for requests( on an IP basis). But other than that, I personally don't care too much about people making multiple requests, as long as they aren't hogging pokemon from anyone else. Overall, I think you guys are making GIVING AWAY POKEMON too strict. I want to help the POKEMONGIVEAWAY community by doing just that, giving away pokemon. But if you guys are planning on stonewalling me at any turn of making it convenient for myself, why should I hold giveaways here?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 06:12:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>You act like some impending grand-pokemon heist is about to occur? In the year I've been here on this subreddit, I don't think I've ever seen a single scam. And keeping a paper trail? Then make people post a copy of the sheets to reddit, or pastebin, or one of 100000 other sources? "Against our long-term interests"? Linking people to a Google Form is not even remotely the same thing as hijacking the subreddit. I REAAAAAALLY think you are over thinking this, and make this a much bigger issue than it needs to be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 06:52:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand that you guys have rules, and I understand why you have them. I just don't understand why there is such an immediate and harsh reaction to something that the community seems to support and would make a lot of users lives easier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 07:33:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright, well I'll await the discussion response.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 18:37:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>H Y P E</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 19:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-29 19:39:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>No Google account is required. Although as a life tip, I would recommend having one haha. But there is no need for a Google account to fill out the form.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-30 00:34:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are you asking exactly?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-30 03:43:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-30 08:42:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmao, how do you manage to stream monster even when Im not streaming?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Need Help Finishing off this VGC2016 Team.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-30 09:58:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Smeargle @ Focus Sash Ability: Own Tempo Level: 50 EVs: 252 HP / 132 Def / 124 SpD Calm Nature IVs: 0 Atk - Fake Out - Dark Void - Crafty Shield - Follow Me Groudon-Primal @ Red Orb Ability: Desolate Land Level: 50 EVs: 252 HP / 252 Atk / 4 SpA Brave Nature IVs: 0 Spe - Protect - Precipice Blades - Fire Punch - Eruption Dusclops @ Eviolite Ability: Frisk Level: 50 EVs: 252 HP / 120 Def / 136 SpD Relaxed Nature IVs: 0 Atk / 0 Spe - Night Shade - Trick Room - Will-O-Wisp - Skill Swap Palkia @ Sitrus Berry Ability: Pressure Level: 50 EVs: 148 HP / 104 Def / 148 SpA / 108 SpD Quiet Nature IVs: 0 Atk / 0 Spe - Spacial Rend - Gravity - Earth Power - Trick Room Kangaskhan-Mega @ Kangaskhanite Ability: Inner Focus Level: 50 EVs: 148 HP / 252 Atk / 108 SpD Adamant Nature IVs: 0 Spe - Fake Out - Double-Edge - Sucker Punch - Low Kick Scizor @ Choice Band Ability: Technician Level: 50 EVs: 252 HP / 252 Atk / 4 SpD Adamant Nature - Bullet Punch - Bug Bite - U-turn - Knock Off So I've been using this team on Showdown with a fair amount of success, but have had some kinks I want to edge out. First of all, I have never brought Scizor to a battle during the entire duration of having the team, so I could really use something else in that slot. I somewhat struggle with the Thundy + Kang lead, as my entire strategy pretty much revolves around trying to setup Trick Room and then sweep from there. I'm also open to suggestions on a different EV spread for Palkia, and Smeargle, as well as overall/general suggestions. Pretty much the only pokemon on this team I am dead-set keeping the way they are is Dusclops, and even then I may be open to swapping Wil-o-wisp for something. Any help is greatly appreciated!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-30 18:25:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>It doesn't take any offensive pressure from Kang, Survives a LO + Knock Off from Yvettal, and I was originally running mental herb on smeargle so I couldn't run it on Cress( who is what would be used here instead). Other than that it's a phenomenal weather controller, and has access to an insane range of moves ( like pain split and wonder room ).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-01 20:51:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you can figure out how to setup a flair on this subreddit and comment on a thread, you can fill out a Google form. If anything the Google form is more straightforward. And no offense, but idk what half of the points you mentioned are even talking about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-04 19:15:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, this really made me miss the old console Pok #233;mon games. I really wish they would make another Shadow Pok #233;mon game, or something to that extent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-05 06:25:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol, well at least this decision took 5 days to decide.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-05 20:51:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do I submit files? I have 1000s of .pk6 files laying around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-06 01:53:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool, I uploaded probably around 400~ish mostly competitive pokemon, I'll definitely upload more later!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-06 03:22:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know you've already gotten loads of suggestions and are probably swamped, but I figured I'd make a few suggestions anyways :). I think the site could definitely benefit from a section to upload "legit" event pokemon (that only allows certain submission), as well as other sections. As someone who is somewhat experienced in C++, and is a novice in web design, I think another logical step would be to add "tags" to uploads. You don't even need full-blown descriptions yet, simply allow the uploaded .pk6 file to be tagged as event, competitive, shiny, etc... Overall, I love the look and feel of the website, and will definitely be using it for both uploading and downloading!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-06 03:44:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya, it definitely would be difficult to do without human moderation, but there is usually never more than 2 legit events per month? It would be a section that wouldn't need to be updated that often. If you wanted to go for a full-on completely automated system, I think there is probably a db you can pull from that lists all of the information about any new event pokemon, so someone would have to upload a pokemon that matched that criteria in order for it appear in the section. If you need any help with anything just let me know, I run a Pokemon Giveaway stream, and have lots of resources available in this particular area haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-06 05:03:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can do this, and other files for you. In the future, you can use [This website](https://pkx.io/) to upload any pk6 files you have. **Edit** I don't really need anything in return for this, but in the future you left the PID and the encryption constant for the .pk6 file blank, just make sure you set those in the future.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-06 05:22:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make sure you add my new FC! I just updated my flair with the FC I'll be using haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-06 05:48:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I also uploaded an entire regular competitive dex! I love the site so far, I encourage everyone to use it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-06 06:21:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used this site almost as soon as it was announced on 3dshacks. For anyone wondering, the site is amazing! I have already uploaded 400+ competitive pokemon and plan to use it a lot in the future!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[FT] Pokegen [LF] Nothing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 22:36:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>[pg] Hey everyone I'm gonna be busy the next few weeks, so I figured I'd do some pokegen services for people today. I only request two things: 1. Make the .pk6 file(s) and upload them to [https://pkx.io/](https://pkx.io/). (This will save me a lot of time, and allow me to get to more people.) 2. Limit of 6 pokemon per person :) Once you've made the files, post the link here, and add my FC. Please use the legality checker in PkHex to ensure that the .pk6 is valid. The easier you make my life, the more people I'll be able to get to :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 22:52:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya, I don't see why not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 22:59:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya, you can edit all of that in the .pk6 file. If you don't know how to do that, then I guess you can just tell me what pokeball you want it in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 23:03:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright, Im going to wait until I have at least one more request from someone else, to limit the amount of times I need to edit my save. But I will trade you first!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 23:20:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I'm still doing them later thats fine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 23:20:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Done, and added.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 23:20:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have the initial 3 you requested, I can get you this one later, but I added you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 23:21:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 23:32:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I forgot to make the altaria shiny, smh, I'll get it for you after the next save I reset.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 23:34:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>You use a program called PKHEX, you can google a download link.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 23:44:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-09 23:44:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 00:14:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 00:14:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 00:33:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I trade them to you. Also, one of your links is invalid, and I'm pretty sure Shiny Victini isn't tradeable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 00:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can search for already made .pk6 files on the site, but otherwise ya haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 00:46:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anything lmao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 00:54:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Search for a Pokemon on the site, click on the one you want, and then copy + paste the URL that page.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 00:56:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya, I sent you the wrong one originally, I believe I sent you the correct one to follow up?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 00:59:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya, just keep it lol. Trade it to someone else or something haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 01:05:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I'll trade you shortly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 01:09:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 01:40:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 01:40:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 01:41:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I tried trading you earlier, but you were afk I think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 01:41:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 01:41:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 01:42:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 02:35:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 02:35:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I'll add you shortly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 03:18:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 03:18:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 03:36:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since you're only requesting one, just put something up on the GTS requesting Hoopa.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 03:41:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Take it down and put it back up, so its fresh in the queue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 03:42:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 03:43:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 03:45:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sent!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[FT] Lightning Fast Cloning Service (ONLY REQUIRES ONE TOTAL TRADE) [LF] Nothing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 06:20:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>[cs] Figured I'd follow up the Pokegen thread I did with a cloning service, in case anyone missed the Pokegenning. To keep it simple [THIS IS HOW I CLONE POKEMON](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1O2adFt9Vzw). It only requires you to trade me a pokemon, **and I can clone your Pokemon DURING THE SAME TRADE.** I only ask that each person only requests a maximum of 3 pokemon they want cloned. I will trade you back your original pokemon + 2 clones (3 total). So example: Person: "Can you clone my Charmander, Bulbasaur, and Squirtle?" you will end up with 3 Squirtle, 3 Bulbasaur, 3 Charmander. Just post the pokemon you want cloned, and add my FC! **EDIT: REMEMBER TO RULE 8 YOUR POKEMON, AS PER THE RULES OF THE SUBREDDIT**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 06:38:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya, I already have you added, so just trade me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 07:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure, just remember to Rule 8 them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 07:13:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's fine! Send me a trade request!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 07:28:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 07:47:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Doesn't matter to me if you keep it or not haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 08:03:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 08:27:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 08:53:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Added</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 08:59:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya, thats fine, just trade me when</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-10 16:35:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Impressive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>subject4247's Reference Page</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-11 00:41:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>**IGN:** subject4247 / Agent X **FC:** 4528-1926-9012 **Timezone:** EDT Since I do the bulk of my giveaways using Google Forms, Google Spreadsheets + Forms records the bulk of my results. Along side with the thread link for each giveaway will be a link to its accompanying spreadsheet. If this is not enough evidence/information an additional spreadsheet can be posted for some of the giveaways that shows 100% if the pokemon was sent or not sent. ####[](#0) Entry # | Transaction Type | Given | Received | Done with | Date | Points :---------:|:---------|:---------|:---------|:---------|:---------|:--------- 1 | [Giveaway](https://www.reddit.com/r/PokemonPlaza/comments/4omoli/shiny_kyogre_shiny_groudon_masterball_giveaway/) / [Spreadsheet](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1YfDn6a-HqUY_BefNLrupwAP_m8qvvDYg4wAdKhVAv20/edit#gid=12557798)| 56 Shiny Groudon / Shiny Kyogre | - | - | 06-17-16 | 280 pts 2 | [Giveaway](https://www.reddit.com/r/PokemonPlaza/comments/4peec8/live_streaming_shiny_deoxys_shiny_lucario/) / [Spreadsheet](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1fBjLDoOX-ou8Kkj8Sx0B_04-i8nfEVVxhJONqgnCPb8/edit#gid=124189441) | 64 Shiny Deoxys / ShinyLucario | - | - |06-22-16 | 320 pts 3 | [Giveaway](https://www.reddit.com/r/PokemonPlaza/comments/4pqr02/live_streaming_shiny_rayquaza_shiny_ferrothorn/) / [Spreadsheet](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1i-TT57-1cSsXj0QbCk8mfd5C9yYWQlfZFdHSMFdyBHA/edit#gid=1272211979) | 81 Shiny Rayquaza / Ferrothorn | - | - | 06-24-16 | 405 pts 4 | [Giveaway](https://www.reddit.com/r/PokemonPlaza/comments/4qd2ew/live_streaming_shiny_arceus_shiny_stunfisk/) / [Spreadsheet](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1GypJpYZJsWDIjzed2TKzRH8rGsq1Jyv1zgkioct0ax4/edit#gid=600208344) | 63 Shiny Arceus / Stunfisk | - | - | 06-28-2016 | 315 pts 5 | [Pokegen](https://www.reddit.com/r/PokemonPlaza/comments/4s24u3/ft_pokegen_lf_nothing/) | 98 Individually Genned Pokemon | - | - | 07/09/16 | 196 pts 6 | [Cloning](https://www.reddit.com/r/PokemonPlaza/comments/4s3yve/ft_lightning_fast_cloning_service_only_requires/) | 32 Clones | - | - | 07/09/16 | 64 pts ####[](#0) - **Current Points:** 1580 - **Number of Completed Battles:** 0 - **Total # of Given Away Pokemon:** 264</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-11 05:45:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd love to help, but I wouldn't be able to these until tomorrow. Just out of curiosity, is this for a VGC event? Or just battlespot?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Would people be interested in a relatively in-depth Pokegen/Cloning/Homebrew/Hacking Tutorial?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 05:41:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>[q] I see that a lot of people here within the past few weeks have been asking questions in this area. Such as "how do I pokegen?" "how do I get started with homebrew" "what if I only want to clone?" "I have a powersaves, can I pokegen?" I was thinking I could probably write up a pretty in-depth guide covering all of these topics, as I've been involved in the 3DS hacking scene since it pretty much originated. If you'd be interested or have suggestions or anything just let me know :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-12 06:37:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty much this. But there are a lot of people that are turned off by scary concepts like A9LH and CFWs, and this guide is mainly to show all the options.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-27 03:21:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 05:06:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is from memory, but I think she lied about being part Native American.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When everyone in top 8 is playing fox</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 19:09:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Martin Kaymer skips golf ball across the water for a hole in one.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 19:12:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Some people just want to watch the world Burn.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 19:30:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 19:54:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 20:07:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tried to submit this there, but it wouldn't show up for anyone else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 22:52:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the camera is shaky because of the wind, but thats just my 2 cents.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-04 02:57:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha, this is amazing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-04 05:14:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-04 05:40:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya they do this in their Monday practice round usually. This is the 16th hole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-04 05:44:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol I gotchu. Probably Friday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Life of a Falcon Main.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-08 00:22:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-08 00:23:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>/u/Chauncii, sorry its a few days late haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me #129309;irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-08 01:20:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Water is Warm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-08 02:14:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-09 20:21:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im so happy Plankton is Fox hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-16 02:50:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I absolutely love iZombie, and after season 2 it solidified itself as arguably my favorite TV show. With that said, I started watching it on Netflix with a friend as a joke, because we were looking for a horrible TV show; and nothing sounded worse than iZombie. It also gets almost no advertisement compared to other (and far worse) CW shows.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>To whoever is in this ranked game I apologize, but for some reason this game doesn't have a reconnect button. God Speed.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-16 07:42:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In 1931 a renowned archaeologist found himself lost six hours into a cave exploration deep in the Yucatan Jungle. When all hope seemed lost a "1000 year old" Blind Mayan Priest emerged from within the cave and guided him back to the surface; and I've uncovered the paper(s) that he wrote about it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-17 22:36:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have no idea if this belongs here or not, but I couldn't really find anywhere else to post this; if it doesn't belong here feel free to remove it. A while back I was reading about people that believed in the hollow earth theory, and decided to lookup what pieces of "evidence" these people used to support their claim. While 99% of the purported pieces of evidence had no scientific backing, or were just other crazy theory in and of themselves, there was one story that struck out to me.  gt;  gt; Robert Stacy-Judd, a noted archeologist from California, tells of being in the Yucatan and entering the stupendous  #8216;Cave of Loltun #8217; with a party of six researchers. They descended far into the depths of the Earth and then realized that they were lost. They became very concerned when all of a sudden from farther down in the depths, a light came towards them. The light turned out to be a torch carried by an old blind hermit who told them he had seen them clairvoyantly and knew they were lost. Even though blind, he proceeded to lead them back to the Earth #8217;s surface.  gt; The men were exceedingly grateful and asked the hermit where he lived. The hermit told them that the cave was his home and that he came to the surface every few months. When asked how he survived, how he found food and water to drink, he said he was cared for by the friends who lived in the beautiful inner city in the depths of the Earth. He paused long enough to have his picture taken, then disappeared back into the cave. Anyways, I did some research and couldn't immediately find anything online that was published by Robert Stacy-Judd pertaining to this, but further delving lead me to an Archive that had a list of his papers. I had several of the papers pertaining to "The Hermit of the Loltun" scanned, and what I found was rather amazing. While it completely has no mention of the Hermit being fed from beings within in the Earth, the rest of the story does seem to be true, if not more fascinating. If more people are curious I can probably post the full 30~ pages of PDFs on Robert Stacy-Judd's entire experience, but for now I'll just post some of the excerpts pertaining to the hermit. There is constant mention of a photograph that was taken with the Hermit, I was unable to find this but believe it may also be within the archive. [First Picture of Document](https://i.imgur.com/xb1stE5.png) [Second Picture of Document](https://i.imgur.com/RCC7DmK.png) **EDIT** I decided to post the full documents based on some of the questions I've been receiving. [Document 1](https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B4tiIt1c41d2R1V2YVhGU0k4eDg/view?usp=sharing) [Document 2](https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B4tiIt1c41d2Q1JneFRidGNNeXM/view?usp=sharing)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-17 23:14:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't believe its fiction considering the things like the newspaper article that were published, that a photograph was supposedly taken, and that its documented that Robert Stacy-Judd did do lots of exploring in the Yucatan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-18 00:17:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Robert Stacy-Judd had guides with him that could translate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-18 04:10:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright, I feel like I'm as blind as a hermit, can anyone make out if any of those pictures is the hermit in question haha?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-20 20:41:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you see the zippyshare link in the comments.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-21 04:20:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Congratulations to the Senior Pokemon World Champion!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-21 23:37:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Carson Confer(USA) takes it over Yuki Wata(JPN) 2 - 1!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Congratulations to the Masters Division Pokemon World Champion!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 00:35:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Phenomenal play from **Wolfe Glick(USA)** to take it over Jonathan Evans(USA) 2 - 0!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 01:21:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think since they finished up yesterday they also did the award ceremony yesterday?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 03:13:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a joke...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 03:30:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why, are you personally offended or something?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 03:41:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll try my best to answer this, anyone can feel free to correct me if I'm wrong.  gt; What are they writing on those pieces of paper? Several things. Usually they keep track of their opponent's Pokemon moves + items they are holding. This can actually play a big role in Best of 3 games as a smart player can choose not to reveal certain moves and then surprise the opponent the next game. They also occasionally keep track of damage calculations, for example in game 1 of this set Jon's Mega Gengar Sludge Bomb did just enough damage to Wolfe's Kyogre that a Water Spout from Kyogre wouldn't knock out the Gengar. Some players also write down what turn of trick room/tailwind the game is on etc... Generally any information that might be useful later on in the game will be written down by some players.  gt; Why do they have headsets? This I could be wrong on, but I believe it is in part to keep any noise from the crowd to reach the players. It is also used to communicate with the other player/judges in the event that they need to. Sometimes, in matches between international players, you will see a third "Judge" who often serves as a translator for one of the players.  gt; Who are the two Pokemon professors watching over their shoulders and why do they have headsets? These are Judges, I really am not entirely sure what they do in VGC (video game championship), but I imagine it is to make sure that everything runs smoothly. In the event of something bizarre (like a disconnect between the players) I imagine they have some protocol.  gt; What do they both sign there after its over? I imagine this is almost like a golf scorecard, where both players sign a scorecard agreeing the final score of the match. If you have any other questions feel free to ask, VGC is by far my favorite format of Pokemon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 04:19:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya Verlisify is cancer incarnate, just don't pay attention to him and the VGC community improves 10 fold.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Live Streaming Shiny Latios + Shiny Latias Giveaway! [Hacked/Cloned]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 05:35:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>[g] You can watch the stream [HERE](https://www.twitch.tv/projectgiveaway)! Sorry for my spontaneous hiatus, life's been busy lately. Felt like streaming again, we'll see how it goes. **I am going to try something new, and have people submit their requests [HERE](https://goo.gl/forms/dw0jiwVvnX2dDUlw1) through Google Forms. INSTEAD OF THE COMMENTS SECTION!** Google Forms auto-updates and allows me to keep a very clean and concise spreadsheet, it also ensures that the people entering the giveaway are following the majority of the rules. **IF YOU ARE IN A COUNTRY THAT HAS BLOCKED GOOGLE FORMS, YOU MAY COMMENT ON THE THREAD TO SUBMIT YOUR REQUEST, BUT I WILL ONLY BE CHECKING THE THREAD SPORADICALLY.** Both Pokemon are holding Soul Dew. ####[](#0) Pok #233;mon (Nickname) | Gender | Ability | Nature | IV-spread | Egg Moves | Original Trainer | Trainer ID | Type of Pok #233;ball | Level | Generation Mark (e.g. Pentagon) | Language ---------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|---------- Latias | F | Levitate | Relaxed | 6IV | Defog, Draco Meteor, Psyshock, Roost | Ash | 01337 | Poke Ball | 100 | 3rd Gen | ENG Latios | M | Levitate | Lax | 6IV | Dragon Pulse, Psychic, Luster Purge, Roost | Winrar | 10224 | Master Ball | 100 | 3rd Gen | SPA ###Rules for GTS trade * Deposit any Pokemon that isn't incredibly common (i.e Starters, ZigZagoons, Whismurs) * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "ProjectGiveaway" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * With that said, you can request one of each</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 07:53:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>God forbid children saw someones middle finger. Seriously, its not that big of a deal. I'm just mad that people are trying to discredit his win because of this, its literally the most minor thing in the world to complain about. Its controversy for the sake of controversy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 08:12:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's a kid himself, its not like its some 30 year old guy walking up in my kids face and flipping him off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 08:23:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I understand that, but he didn't do it even remotely seriously or with malice intentions. At the end of the day he's a kid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 08:30:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not saying they should be immune from punishment, I'm saying they shouldn't be held to the same standard as some of their older peers. It was a joke gone array, nothing more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does voice chat actually work for anyone [PC]?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-24 03:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I swear a year ago when I first got Rocket League, you could actually coherently hear people over the voice chat. But this entire Summer, whenever anyone speaks it mostly cuts out or is garbled. Does anyone else have this problem?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Garbage is a bunch of miscellaneous pieces of trash, yet it has a distinct smell.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-24 23:17:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-26 23:56:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello im Raidan forester but you can call me Raids, im a 13 year old gamer and i lov...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-27 06:34:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Loveseats</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Garbage is a bunch of miscellaneous pieces of trash, yet it always has the same distinct smell.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-29 19:32:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-13 20:22:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Easiest way to do this is to have a hacked 3ds. Otherwise you're going to have to transfer them to a legit B/W/2 cartridge and then go from there. But even if you go that route you might run into issues transferring them through the pokebank, because I'm guessing the "RNG" pokemon wont appear as legitimate. **EDIT** And to transfer them to a legit B/W/2 cartridge you're either going to need something like an R4 or maybe one of those old apps that allowed you to transfer custom pokemon over like a fake wifi hotspot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Going Insane trying to unbrick this phone.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-14 23:27:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friend's Droid Turbo is stuck in a boot loop, and I've been trying to reflash the stock firmware onto it using [**THIS GUIDE**](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6avEPGWB8E0). However, seemingly every firmware file I try always leads to : D:\comeon gt;fastboot.exe flash system system.img_sparsechunk1 (bootloader) has-slot:system: not found target reported max download size of 536870912 bytes sending 'system' (235141 KB)... OKAY [ 7.363s] writing 'system'... (bootloader) Invalid signed image (bootloader) Preflash validation failed FAILED (remote failure) finished. total time: 7.458s I've run *mfastboot.exe getvar all* which shows me: (bootloader) ro.build.fingerprint[0]: motorola/quark_verizon/quark:5.1/S (bootloader) ro.build.fingerprint[1]: U4TL-49/5:user/release-keys (bootloader) ro.build.version.full[0]: Blur_Version.23.21.49.quark_veriz (bootloader) ro.build.version.full[1]: on.verizon.en.US Any help as to what firmware to try will be appreciated, although I've tried literally 10 different firmwares at this point. Any general advice/troubleshooting will be appreciated as well! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-14 23:45:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Locked, never been rooted or anything like that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-15 00:10:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>All drivers installed, and I couldn't get RSDLite to work on Windows 10. I was thinking the same thing, but I can occasionally get the phone to boot and everything operates perfectly fine for about 5 minutes before it resets and goes back to the boot loop. I'm not entirely convinced that I'm not messing up something with the firmwares, but I've tried so many all with the same results</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-15 00:34:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>If none of this works, any other ideas to get the phone back to a usable status?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-25 20:29:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last season we saw you step into the commentary/casting side of things; even though you are planning on competing this season, do you ever see yourself going back to commentating?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Police: Cow struck and killed by milk truck</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 22:09:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-12 21:27:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's interesting, as a competitive smash bros player I see the admissions fee and think its not that bad. With that said, I'm not sure that charging this much for admissions is the best idea, given this seems to be the season that VGC is really trying to expand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Well said Taco Dog, well said.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-12 22:49:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Garbage is a bunch of miscellaneous pieces of trash, yet it always has the same distinct smell.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-12 22:54:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is this a meme?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-14 05:09:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(brest)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-17 02:55:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-18 20:40:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>What ever happened to the video Dan Salvato made trying to dismiss this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[PC] [H] 2xChamp1 Crates, 5xChamp2, 4xChamp3 [W] Dominus Skins or Discotheque</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-19 19:34:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[PC] [H] Used Rare African Rhino Horns (Uncommon Topper) [W] Anything</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-30 01:23:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I figured I'd try and do something where I start with a low item, and see what I can manage to trade my way up to. As you may know Rhino Horns (Uncommon Topper) are extremely hard to come by now-a-days with them being endangered species and all /s. [Here's a picture of these babies, I got over 115 Goals out of them.](http://i.imgur.com/3ZIqOwo.jpg) I'll accept probably anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Where is target?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 04:59:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>THE SUBREDDIT IS IN ANARCHY! PRAISE HELIX!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 18:11:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 14:47:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>P R E A C H</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"Today has probably been my favorite day ever shooting iZombie." - Rose McIver</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 14:53:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What would you like to see as a Day 1 Sun/Moon Giveaway?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-06 00:22:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>[q] If in theory I were to hold a Giveaway on Sun/Moon's release date for Sun and Moon, what would you like to see? I don't want to do any maxed EV/IV Level 100 Pokemon, as the it will be Day 1, but other than that I'm open for suggestions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What would you like to see as a Day 1 Sun/Moon Giveaway?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-06 00:41:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>[?] If in theory I were to hold a Giveaway on Sun/Moon's release date for Sun and Moon, what would you like to see? I don't want to do any maxed EV/IV Level 100 Pokemon, as the it will be Day 1, but other than that I'm open for suggestions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-06 01:17:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Using my Sun/Moon game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-06 06:00:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Theres an entire new generation of Pokemon, and you want Gen 1-3 pokemon on the first day or release.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>They're one and the same</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 17:04:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Taco Bell is changing the game</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 22:51:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[D][POTENTIAL SPOILERS] There has officially been a Shiny Wondertrade on Pokemon Sun / Moon</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 00:29:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>[D]PKHeX officially supports Sun and Moon! 10 days before release! I figured I'd go ahead and do one Shiny Wondertrade just to say I was first :). [Here it is.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LMJNQhnVGrs amp;feature=youtu.be)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[POTENTIAL SPOILERS] There has officially been a Shiny Wondertrade on Pokemon Sun / Moon</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 00:55:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>[i]PKHeX officially supports Sun and Moon! 10 days before release! I figured I'd go ahead and do one Shiny Wondertrade just to say I was first :). [Here it is.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LMJNQhnVGrs amp;feature=youtu.be)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 02:34:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't get NTR to stream outside of the FriendLink or whatever its called, I have no idea how other people are streaming regular gameplay. Let me know if you find out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 04:52:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure, I'm not at my 3DS rn. But once I'm back, I'm down</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 05:32:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Risk it for the biscuit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 14:40:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some people never change.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 17:29:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not even gonna lie this entire post was self-promotion, but considering PKHeX is responsible for 95% of this subreddit's content I'd argue it's pretty relevant. Whatever, at the end of the day at least I contribute something to this community.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 17:55:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya because you can't clone PKHeX'd pkmn with powersaves right? You got me there. Whatever, at this point I exist on this subreddit just to spite you. I'm literally only going to do giveaways here following the rules just to annoy you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 18:59:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-10 13:39:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll let you know haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I hope you're ready for this Sun and Moon Giveaway November 19th!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-13 21:19:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>[i] [THE GOODS!](http://i.imgur.com/nQnHjjY.png) The giveaway is going to be November 19th, around 8pm~ EST. That time is not set-in-stone and is subject to change ;) **Edit** USA  gt; Europe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-14 00:04:15</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-14 05:00:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just an FYI it takes a bit to get to the point in the game where you can use the GTS. And I also ordered the Steelcase from Amazon :) . I can't wait!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-14 17:15:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>yuuup</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-15 21:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its not too far into the storyline, but it does take a bit to get to. For reference, I think it took me 17 hours in-game time to finish the main story (longest by far for any pokemon game haha), and I want to say I had access to the GTS by hour 3~4? I'm not sure though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-17 05:32:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>To my knowledge your two options are trying to play the game through Citra (A 3DS Emulator), or trying to use something like [InputRedirection](https://github.com/Kazo/InputRedirection/blob/master/README.md), although I'll be completely honest and say I have no idea how InputRedirection works. But I think Citra may be your best bet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I have good news for you...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-19 07:02:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shiny Gen7 Starter Giveaway Number 91029, this time with a Masterball!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 06:46:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>[g] So I know there has already been 1000x of these giveaways, but I did announce probably before anyone else that I was going to do this giveaway (with picture/video proof haha). Anyways, sorry for being 4~hours late, ran into some delays. Each Pokemon is Shiny and holding a Master Ball :) There are **33** Pokemon total, so act quick :) ####[](#0) Pok #233;mon (Nickname) | Gender | Ability | Nature | IV-spread | Egg Moves | Original Trainer | ID | Type of Pok #233;ball | Level | Generation Mark (e.g. Pentagon) | Language ---------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|----------|---------- Litten | F | Blaze | Adamant | 6IV | Scratch, Ember, Growl | ProjectGive | 993401 | Poke Ball | 5 | Cross? | ENG Popplio | F | Torrent | Adamant | 6IV | Water Gun, Growl | ProjectGive | 815193 | Poke Ball | 5 | Cross? | ENG Rowlet | M | Overgrow | Adamant | 6IV | Tackle | ProjectGive | 815193 | Poke Ball | 5 | Cross? | ENG ###Rules for GTS trade * Please Deposit something not incredibly common * Post your IGN, Name of Pokemon you're trading, level, Gender, and requested Pokemon. * Set GTS message as "ProjectGiveaway" * Be considerate, please do not spam multiple requests * **I'm not gonna reply sent to every comment because that's such a hassle, so just be on the lookout for if your trade went through, and reply to your post once it is done!**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 07:04:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't see your deposit. Feel free to redeposit something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 07:05:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't see your deposit. Feel free to redeposit something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 07:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rowlet is Male</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[OUT][HACKED][GEN7] Live Streaming 3+Boxes of Miscellaneous Shiny Pokemon!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 03:16:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can watch the Live stream [HERE](https://www.twitch.tv/projectgiveaway)! [Here are the 3 Boxes that are being wondertraded!](http://imgur.com/a/7iw89) I may do more depending! Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[GEN7] Wondertrading 3+Boxes of Miscellaneous Shiny Pokemon! Live on stream!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 03:17:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>[g] You can watch the Live stream [HERE](https://www.twitch.tv/projectgiveaway)! [Here are the 3 Boxes that are being wondertraded!](http://imgur.com/a/7iw89) I may do more depending! Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 07:43:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, my bad, thank you :) . I forgot to close the thread, this wrapped up about half an hour ago anyways</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Magnitude 7.2 quake at sea shakes Central America as hurricane hits</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-24 20:49:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yes, yes you are.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-24 21:25:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>/u/subject4247's Reference Page</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 05:21:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pokemon Exchange: ####TRADES Number |Item Traded |Item Received |User |Permalink :--- |:--- |:-- |:--- |:--- 1 |5 Genned Pokemon | Twitter  amp; Twitch Follows |/u/reddumpling |[Link](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemonexchange/comments/5ertef/h_genningcloningeditingshiny_eggshacking_related/dafavqq/) 2 |2 Genned Pokemon | Twitch Follow |/u/Indy2300 |[Link](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemonexchange/comments/5ertef/h_genningcloningeditingshiny_eggshacking_related/daer5k1/) 3 |5 Genned Pokemon | Twitter  amp; Twitch Follows |/u/heythanksbye |[Link](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemonexchange/comments/5ertef/h_genningcloningeditingshiny_eggshacking_related/daerkxz/) 4 |5 Genned Pokemon | Twitter  amp; Twitch Follows |/u/PKFuzzy |[Link](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemonexchange/comments/5ertef/h_genningcloningeditingshiny_eggshacking_related/daesite/) 5 |Nature Change | Twitch Follow |/u/Diablo_Oce |[Link](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemonexchange/comments/5ertef/h_genningcloningeditingshiny_eggshacking_related/daetn6a/) 6 |5 Genned Pokemon | Twitter  amp; Twitch Follows |/u/Nick1696 |[Link](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemonexchange/comments/5ertef/h_genningcloningeditingshiny_eggshacking_related/daettlt/) 7 |5 Genned Pokemon | Twitter  amp; Twitch Follows |/u/BlazeKnight7 |[Link](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemonexchange/comments/5ertef/h_genningcloningeditingshiny_eggshacking_related/daeuzow/) 8 |2 Genned Pokemon | Twitch Follow |/u/DragonSlayer09 |[Link](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemonexchange/comments/5ertef/h_genningcloningeditingshiny_eggshacking_related/dag0axo/) 9 |5 Genned Pokemon | Twitter  amp; Twitch Follows |/u/Zang33 |[Link](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemonexchange/comments/5ertef/h_genningcloningeditingshiny_eggshacking_related/dafgqbv/) 10 |2 Genned Pokemon | Twitch Follow |/u/morei |[Link](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemonexchange/comments/5ertef/h_genningcloningeditingshiny_eggshacking_related/daeyqb8/) Pokemon Exchange: ###SALES Number |Item Sold | Amount Received |User |Permalink :--- |:--- |:-- |:--- |:--- 1 | 3 Genned Pokemon | 2.62 #8364; Paypal |/u/heyiamkev|[Link](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemonexchange/comments/5flbwz/lf_3_genned_pokemon_sunmoon_h_262_paypal/) 2 | Legit: Solgaleo, Buzzwole, Kartana, Silvally | $3.43 Paypal |/u/patricpn|[Link](https://www.reddit.com/r/Pokemonexchange/comments/5fgzmd/lf_solgaleo_buzzwole_kartana_silvally_h_paypal/dam8e6c/) Other Pokemon related subs: * [Over 15 Hacked/Cloned Giveaways on r/Pokemongiveaway ](https://www.reddit.com/r/PkmnGiveawayRefs/comments/4mhb82/gridelins_references_2/) * [Some of my r/PokemonPlaza references](https://www.reddit.com/r/PokePlazaReferences/comments/4s7syj/gridelins_reference_page/) * [Proof I am available for Gen7](https://www.reddit.com/r/PokemonPlaza/comments/5dwqb7/shiny_gen7_starter_giveaway_number_91029_this/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[H] Genning/Cloning/Editing/Shiny Eggs/Hacking Related Services [W] Twitter/Twitch Followers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 05:48:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>[hacked] [My Reference Page](https://www.reddit.com/r/pokemonexchangeref/comments/5erpoa/ugridelins_reference_page/) So I just recently found this subreddit, and I think I would like to open up a shop here. But to build my reputation first, I'm going to offer my services simply for Twitch/Twitter Followers. I can provide the services listed in the title for both Gen7 and Gen6! [Check here to see if what you are asking is legal in Gen7](http://www.serebii.net/sunmoon/unobtainable.shtml) * **2 X** Genning/Cloning/Editing/Shiny Eggs/Hacking Related Service -- **IF** you follow my Twitter [**HERE**](https://twitter.com/ProjectGiveaway)(and provide proof) * **2 X** Genning/Cloning/Editing/Shiny Eggs/Hacking Related Service -- **IF** you follow my Twitch [**HERE**](https://www.twitch.tv/projectgiveaway)(and provide proof) * ADDITIONAL **1 X** Genning/Cloning/Editing/Shiny Eggs/Hacking Related Service -- **IF** you follow both my Twitter and Twitch. So in total you can receive 5 services for following both my Twitter and Twitch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 07:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you want the Ninetails level 50 or 100, you have a mismatch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 07:09:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can trade you now for the ID Pokemon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 07:10:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you want the Ninetails at 100, both of your pokemon are ready.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 07:17:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you want your request pokemon shiny(if they can be)/level 100?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 07:32:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, give me 10 minutes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 07:42:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm online right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 07:43:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm online right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 08:10:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you trade within the next 10 minutes? If you can I'm ready to trade now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 08:19:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I can do that extremely quick. I'll add you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 08:21:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm online.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 08:26:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go to the Friend's Plaza, and then Link Trade</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 08:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>One sec, I'll fix the Raichu, just noticed I put in the wrong one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 08:45:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>its ready</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 08:50:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to sleep now, but I'll make sure you're first on my list tomorrow :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 08:53:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idk how I'm just seeing this, but I got banned and fixed it the other way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 09:02:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn, my bad on that, I did a request very similar to yours not too long ago and think I mixed some of the files up. I'm going to sleep right now but I have no problem giving you the Tape+Leftovers, and an additional Pokemon you want Genned Tomorrow. Sorry about that again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 09:03:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably around 1amEST 11/26?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 07:51:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm available right now if you are, if you aren't available in the next 30-40 mins reply and we can set up a time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 07:51:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm available right now if you are, if you aren't available in the next 30-40 mins reply and we can set up a time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 07:51:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm available right now if you are, if you aren't available in the next 30-40 mins reply and we can set up a time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 07:52:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm available right now if you are, if you aren't available in the next 30-40 mins reply and we can set up a time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 07:52:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I'm available right now if you are, if you aren't available in the next 30-40 mins reply and we can set up a time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 07:52:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm available right now if you are, if you aren't available in the next 30-40 mins reply and we can set up a time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 07:52:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm available right now if you are, if you aren't available in the next 30-40 mins reply and we can set up a time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 07:53:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm available right now if you are, if you aren't available in the next 30-40 mins reply and we can set up a time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 07:53:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm available right now if you are, if you aren't available in the next 30-40 mins reply and we can set up a time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 07:54:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm available right now if you are, if you aren't available in the next 30-40 mins reply and we can set up a time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 07:56:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 08:13:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>So Tapu Koko is Shiny locked, and Tyranitar can't be traded till the Pokebank is released haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 08:17:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Online right now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 08:17:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Online right now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 08:18:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I'll add you shortly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 08:24:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 08:34:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im ready, if you are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 08:46:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>So Scizor currently can't have knockoff or Superpower I believe, I just got rid of those moves if you want to give it a try now?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 05:23:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm online right now, if that works for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 05:46:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm online right now, if that works for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 06:26:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im in the festival plaza, send me a trade request when you can.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 22:35:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can do this for you, in 30-40 minutes if that works for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 23:23:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright they're good to go, I'll PM you my paypal stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 23:43:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I suspected this might happen, Sceptile is currently blocked from being traded because Pokebank isn't released yet, but I'd be happy to Gen you something else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 02:21:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to say that would be legal. But your friend would be better asking r/legaladvice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 17:58:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you still haven't found someone to do this, I have all of these legitimate except for the Genesect</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 19:15:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just to be clear you're only looking for these Pok #233;mon, not any specific Nature's or IVs or anything?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 20:08:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, I have all of those and can trade right now + PM you paypal stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 20:11:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya no problem, just PM me when you're good to go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 06:54:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright, I'm online and ready to trade</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[OUT][HACKED][GEN7] Live Streaming 5+Boxes of Miscellaneous Shiny Pokemon!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 03:40:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can watch the Live stream [HERE](https://www.twitch.tv/projectgiveaway)! Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[OUT][HACKED][GEN7] Live Streaming 5+Boxes of Miscellaneous Shiny Pokemon!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-03 02:51:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can watch the Live stream [HERE](https://www.twitch.tv/projectgiveaway)! Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-10 08:04:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>[My sides holy shit, I can't even.](https://i.imgur.com/vBx1fmj.png) Anyways, I'd like to say that I found this community extremely helpful and well receiving. The "one thread you quarantine people into" has helped me on more than one occasion, and when it doesn't I just go to gbatemp. If you're easily upset by not being able to understand lingo, just google it, thats what most of us did. P.S I also enjoyed how you didn't have the guts to post this on your main reddit account, and had to make a throwaway just to do it ;) Can't lose that precious Karma.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-25 05:48:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you have a decent computer, playing on Dolphin is usually the best solution to not having a CRT. If that doesn't work, despite what anyone says about how terrible LCDs are (they are terrible, don't get me wrong), playing Melee will always be better for you than not playing Melee. The one thing I will caution you against is playing to beat the CPU, if you're playing by yourself look into practice routines, or something similar, never play to beat the computer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>squidward irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-26 03:10:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 08:20:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>1) You will **NOT** be banned for using it. 2) Using it in the battle tree will only potentially hurt your own integrity. 3) No.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>squidward_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 08:33:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 06:44:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Meow*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Maybe not the best choice of words to paint on staircase. (X-Post /r/Pokemon)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-04 23:22:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 03:45:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>squidward irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-21 06:16:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-21 06:26:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-21 20:03:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was a brand new episode last night haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So this happened at the end of Linus's AMD RYZEN 7 Review video....</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 22:50:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 23:00:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hadn't seen this posted yet? Am I missing something?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Amazing Bat Catch by Mets Prospect Luis Guillorme</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 23:26:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #8216;I sleep pretty good at night #8217;: Casey Anthony speaks about daughter #8217;s death for first time since trial</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-08 05:07:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Beatles - Get Back</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-08 18:52:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>absolutelynotme_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-14 06:19:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 04:10:31</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; SHOTS FIRED Into the kid ayoooooooo ^^toosoon?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New Jamflex logo I made with my phone</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 17:39:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 21:45:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly I made this meme like half a year ago when some other drama was happening, I think I might have had the Nook app already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 23:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cyka blyat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can someone explain this to me?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 21:26:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I finished season 5 a few days ago, and like seemingly everyone else I was not terribly impressed. One of the problems that stuck out to me the most was the entire situation with Frank pushing Cathy Durant down the stairs. Why did Frank do this? The viewer is lead to believe he's doing this to keep Cathy from testifying, but Frank then goes ahead and resigns anyways claiming he was planning the downfall all along. It is also to my recollection (although I may be wrong) that Cathy did not know *that much* about the crimes committed by the Underwoods. If anyone can help and explain why Frank did this, it would be much appreciated. Thank you :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 19:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think there's an episode where Clive makes a reference to Liv not being able to understand Romanian anymore or something like that. I could just be misremembering the scene though. Also, just based on watching 3 seasons of the show, I'd say the skills are temporary.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[USA-MA][H] Pokemon Box Ruby  amp; Sapphire, Zelda Collector's Edition, Zelda Wind Waker, Luigi's Mansion + More. [W] Paypal or Local Cash</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 20:35:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm looking for $235~ from Pokemon Box and $75 for the other games. I'm negotiable, and have other games if interested. Any questions, just ask. Pictures: [Proof1](http://i.imgur.com/OMJtZLo.jpg) [Proof2](http://i.imgur.com/n9hBQ4R.jpg) [Proof3](http://i.imgur.com/nzhvMcr.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 22:32:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd up for selling Crash Bandicoot The Wrath or Cortex, Tak2, and maybe Super Mario Sunshine if the price was right. My other GC games I'll probably hold onto for now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[US,US][H] 60~ somewhat older cards [W] Paypal + General knowledge of what they're worth</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 23:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I used to collect Pokemon cards as a kid, but just to play with them etc... I recently found them and thought I should sell some of them on *Let Go.* I was supposed to meet with someone today to sell/appraise the cards but I think he flaked, so now I'm turning to you kind people to hopefully just give me an idea on what these are worth/sell any of them if you are interested. Photos of cards: [Here](http://imgur.com/a/1xYvc) Sorry for the terrible pictures, I have no idea how to properly take pictures of these cards with the insane glare. Any help/knowledge will be greatly appreciated! *Also fair warning, some of these cards were heavily played with i.e Charizard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 23:39:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have no idea what that entails, but if it's not that expensive I don't see why not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 23:43:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a complete noob to this so you'll have to tell me what a toploader is, but what cards are you interested in haha?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 23:48:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ohhhh I have one of those haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 00:02:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://imgur.com/a/aOGGn In order its goes Suicune back, Suicune front, Mewtwo back, Mewtwo front. Suicune appears to have a slight bend in the top right corner and Mewtwo appears to have some *light* scratching on the main picture.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 00:09:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have no idea what any of these are worth, like I've looked up approximate prices on ebay and trollandtoad but I know that mine aren't mint. Is $60 just a completely wrong number, I really have no idea haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 00:12:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, I'll keep this in mind, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 01:44:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make me an offer haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Taco Bell.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 06:04:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-13 20:17:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-15 02:32:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>$20? Condition seems to be the best of my cards, but I'll check again when I'm home.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My experience using the LetGo app</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 00:41:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>subject4247's feedback</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 07:47:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Historical Feedback: +0/-0 Current Feedback: +0/-0 Location: MA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 19:35:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 19:38:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-21 04:00:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>NO!!!!!!!!! Natalie was my favorite! I was starting to like the Major + Natalie team!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 04:00:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Dont be a dick"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 04:02:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure if anyone else felt this way, but it definitely felt like this episode was somewhat planned as the last episode of the series (incase it wasn't renewed for season 4). Overall, a fantastic episode, this literally changed all of the season 4 predictions I had.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Japanese  gt; English] Translation of the Pink Disc + Pink Pamphlet</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 19:51:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>$50 Pickup today! (Sun is still sealed!)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 07:55:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We ordered one American copy... 8 European copies showed up...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 21:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me #127754;irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-05 22:07:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Second Deadly Shooting in Baltimore #8217;s  #8216;Nobody Kill Anybody #8217; Weekend</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-08 00:45:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 07:06:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll swing right now mate, that movie was fucking phenomenal, you need to check yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 22:59:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 00:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seriously, I have no idea why you're being down voted. If you weren't going to Melee tournaments and your controller was your john, UCF is not going to magically make you place better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stormy Weather - The Spaniels, "Doo Wop 50 Vol. 2" [Soul]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 03:09:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>iZombie is leaking</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 23:28:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 14:59:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya sorry, a lot of subs won't accept submissions without the names blurred out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL in 2010 the fastest super computer in the entire U.S Defense Department was primarily compromised of 1760 PlayStation 3 Consoles</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 18:35:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 04:12:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Counter example?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 04:50:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya but that has nothing to do with this being the fastest DoD computer?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 07:19:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>1776 was a good year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I fell through the map when I landed, and was able to swim under the entire map.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 22:28:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me~irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 19:29:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to Navy Seal Copypasta</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 05:10:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 05:30:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.wikihow.com/Hack</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to defend Trump on Twitter</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 19:08:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 19:09:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.wikihow.com/Join-the-U.S.-Army</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 08:18:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't believe the username MeleeSmash was not taken on reddit until three hours ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to give a presentation while on heavy Hallucinogens</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 09:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 09:13:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.wikihow.com/Develop-Training-Materials</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Always have three desktop shortcuts to Google Chrome, in case you forget where two of them are</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 16:11:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 16:11:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.wikihow.com/Become-a-Professional-Photographer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL in 2013 the Pirate Bay faked moving its servers to North Korea. Various news outlets including NBC and 'Business Insider' reported the event as factual, without ever updating that it was a hoax.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 16:58:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 16:59:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Links to the Business Insider and NBC articles: http://www.businessinsider.com/pirate-bay-claims-north-korea-server-2013-3 http://www.nbcnews.com/id/51042239/ns/technology_and_science-tech_and_gadgets/t/pirate-bay-bootleg-site-moves-north-korea/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 18:15:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my gosh, that's amazing. Thanks for digging that up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 23:19:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's true, or it could be a saved webpage or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>South Korean Politician Brought A Golden Pan to Discuss the Success of PUBG to a Government Audit Hearing for Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 14:37:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 17:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>For those wondering there are about 1 million legal immigrants that come to the U.S every year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Texas can split into five states whenever it wants and without congressional approval. It only requires the approval of its own state legislature.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 17:39:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 17:58:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is the U.S constitution, a short clause in the state's 1845 annexation agreement says  gt; "[n]ew States, of convenient size, not exceeding four in number, in addition to said State of Texas, and having sufficient population, may hereafter, by the consent of said State, be formed out of the territory thereof, which shall be entitled to admission under the provisions of the federal constitution." [Source](http://www.slate.com/articles/news_and_politics/history/2012/11/texas_secession_how_the_lone_star_state_could_mess_with_the_rest_of_us.html) The argument is that congress already approved the split of up to 5 states when agreeing to the annexation agreement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 04:25:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not disagreeing with you, but all of the affordable/subsidized/recovery housing in the world is not going to fix the problems that a homeless heroin addict struggles with. Especially on the scale of the Portland problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>THE SUBREDDIT IS IN ANARCHY. PRAISE LORD HELIX</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 04:29:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Question about the ghost Jigglypuff flying around the sub.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 05:09:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay so I might sound like a crazy conspiracy theorist, but I swear I've seen this jigglypuff float around this sub before, and not just around Halloween. I've been afk at my computer while playing melee/working and I could've sworn after a while the Jigglypuff will float by. Has anyone else seen this? Can any mods confirm?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 05:25:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I swear I've seen it more than once over the past year! It's real!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 05:27:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>THANK YOU! I knew I couldn't be the only one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 14:10:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Psyduck :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 15:58:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm onto you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to be the life of a party</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 18:44:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 18:44:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>[How to Tell if Someone Is Lying About Using Drugs](https://www.wikihow.com/Tell-if-Someone-Is-Lying-About-Using-Drugs)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 07:25:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't remember where I was during most of important international events that have happened in my lifetime. But I will never forget that I was laying in bed at 2am when /u/McFluffigins got his beaver.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 17:31:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I came here to say just this, with some fairly safe and straight forward hacks you can literally play every handheld gen 1 - 7 game on the 3DS. Pretty amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 19:23:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've heard that too, but I figured some are probably easier to find/catch in the older games as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 21:52:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh man that's a good point, I completely forgot Birch keeps giving you starters for every subsequent elite4 completion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>metirl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 07:39:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 23:37:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>The logo isn't too bad, but that motto...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 22:00:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should [follow this guide](https://faq.oit.gatech.edu/content/how-do-i-setup-my-junk-mail-settings-office-365-outlook) to disable your junk folder, and really let it flow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A volunteer at a cat rescue turned on the vacuum [x-post r/pics]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 22:45:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 22:45:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Original post can be found [HERE](https://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/7lib7z/a_volunteer_at_our_local_cat_rescue_turned_on_the/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 20:15:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Atlassian send you a Hackerrank challenge if you make it past the initial resume screening.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 07:22:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same thing just happened to me? What's going on? **EDIT** It's happening seemingly every game?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 07:28:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh what the hell, this isn't even my post but is there anywhere to discuss this issue??? I can't get into a single game because of this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 08:01:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmfao, so you removed everyone else's posts besides yours. Nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I cannot be the only person with this problem.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 20:16:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 21:13:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>NoFunZone :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me #127791;irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 22:54:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I cannot be the only person with this problem</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 18:55:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hmmm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 23:34:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 02:23:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tent - 1 Jeana - 0</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Has anyone else not gotten a 15x Scope in several months?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 23:32:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I looted a 15x scope off of someone today, and until that moment had almost completely forgotten they existed. I started thinking about it more, and I'm mostly positive that I haven't seen a 15x scope since before Miramar launched. Has anyone else experienced this? Did they make them more rare in crate drops? I feel like I have seen just as many AWM and M24 crate drops, just never with the 15x they used to come with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Whatever came of this? It was originally posted almost a year ago.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 21:07:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me #127791;irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 23:18:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 05:54:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so irrationally mad right now that of all the shit they left in Season 2 this got cut.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What pay-to-win looks like in real life</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 17:55:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What pay-to-win looks like in real life</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 22:14:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Squirrel has a close call with a Lamborghini</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 19:29:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Squirrel has a close call with a Lamborghini</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 21:49:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When Tatsuo Horiuchi retired, he decided to try his hand at art. But instead of spending money on paints and brushes, Horiuchi used what he already had pre-installed on his computer #8212;Microsoft Excel.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 18:52:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Taco Bell Drive Thru</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 19:38:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 19:43:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the real surprise tbh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 20:11:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This is the top comment on the video.](https://i.imgur.com/lusSGVQ.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I hate it when the house smells</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 21:50:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 23:25:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 04:50:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Incense I'm assuming</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My experience trying to sell things locally on the LetGo app</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 23:06:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 23:12:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the record I messaged this person and asked them if they could tell me some of the specific things they were selling and they just replied "everything"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What it's like being wobbled in tournament for the first time</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 22:57:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thanks to everyone's help here I was able to hack this bad boy in under 30 seconds!!!!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 21:31:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 22:55:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think he was joking, but the original dev has pretty much vanished off the face of the Earth since selling to Jagex. Twitter inactive for 5+years etc...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 05:50:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm waiting for the smackdown too, but it's possible that he has other leaked passwords out there from hacked forums etc... Also if the RAT'r had half of a brain he would've been able to pull possibly different/old rs passwords from say something like his netflix account.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>u/subject4247's circle</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 06:17:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can't even think of a title for this</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 21:55:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 02:50:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Regardless of who wins now... #NotMyTopModel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Remember the Stuxnet malware?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 22:03:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Russian Scuba Diving</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 20:19:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Be careful where you stomp your feet</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 20:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>These Leaves...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 21:21:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hmmm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 22:44:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hmmm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 00:15:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Swans feeding Koi Fish</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 00:26:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Get out of my spot please</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 02:38:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 06:01:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't mark it as NSFW, a mod did</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to get your dog to eat veggies</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 19:57:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Peekaboo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 21:07:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Deer vs. Car</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 21:32:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You see Comrade, this is how you play guitar</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 21:52:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hmmm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 17:48:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I have no idea what this means in Russian, but the search results for it are hysterical</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 19:38:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Best  #128049; Buds  #128054;  #128149;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 19:54:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 23:45:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe so haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hey, let me in please</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 06:08:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to make a 20-something year old cry starterpack</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 06:57:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 06:59:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>A Shar Pei I believe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 00:34:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>[https://www.wikihow.com/Make\-a\-Realistic\-Farting\-Noise](https://www.wikihow.com/Make-a-Realistic-Farting-Noise)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to instantly get rid of armpit sweat</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 00:36:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 00:36:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>[https://www.wikihow.com/Make\-a\-Realistic\-Farting\-Noise](https://www.wikihow.com/Make-a-Realistic-Farting-Noise)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 02:57:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dammit, this should've been the title</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hmmm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 17:49:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Filling a car with cement</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 18:02:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Russian "Scuba" divers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 08:45:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 08:47:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I usually just rip the videos, but this one was on a private page that I couldn't rip from. Also I didn't want to render an entire video just to crop out the first two seconds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 18:02:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>So how would you have done it? And how would you have cut off the first few seconds without re-rendering?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 19:22:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>But you still need to render? Whereas I just just upload what I recorded, and didn't have to render at all?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 22:16:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think there is a miscommunication between what I've been meaning saying rendering and you are lmao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hidden files on Kanyewest.com</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 02:59:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Someone figured it out: https://twitter.com/harper/status/990091520702320640?s=19** So I uhhh ran [Kanyewest.com](https://Kanyewest.com) through Jdownloader2, to try and download the track hosted on the site, but all I found was hundreds of really weird screenshots and picture\+some videos. Lots of trump/republican stuff too. I uploaded the file below so you can look through it, if you don't believe me just run the website through jdownloader2. [https://drive.google.com/file/d/1xAVLjjAfIx3CCiGATe6u9w4d16e3b5\-W/view?usp=sharing](https://drive.google.com/file/d/1xAVLjjAfIx3CCiGATe6u9w4d16e3b5-W/view?usp=sharing) [https://i.imgur.com/8mzfTov.png](https://i.imgur.com/8mzfTov.png) These links were there as well, but I didn't download them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 03:22:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya this makes sense, I wonder why that is</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 03:31:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder if this guy made the website.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anyone know what this is or what it was used for?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 20:15:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 23:37:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>/u/siderinc did you ever figure this out?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Clean inside and out</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 06:20:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Paid $130 for everything, all games were CIB, all wires included, and came with two memory cards!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 04:38:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 04:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was rough too, in the listing it was laying face down and really looked like a second original controller, but I was still very happy overall!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 17:51:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Craigslist!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 17:52:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 17:52:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is indeed my cat's tail haha!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Picked these 7 games up online for only $42</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 19:31:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 22:42:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you're talking about the memory card for Pokemon Colosseum? That's just the sticker that went on that memory card, it says "59" maybe that's the "sD" you're seeing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 02:52:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I literally posted this a few weeks ago and got half as much Karma: https://www.reddit.com/r/aww/comments/8cykoa/how_to_get_your_dog_to_eat_veggies/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 15:35:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Leaf green certainly looks real, usually you can tell by the size of the 'E' rating, but you might need to check the teeth(pins?) To see the size of the "Nintendo  #174;" to know for sure. I don't know enough about Wolfenstein, or other non-pokmon games in general, to know for sure; but I don't think Wolfenstein is a commonly faked cartridge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 00:40:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could be wrong, but to my recollection the Non XL N3DS was much more prevalent in Japan than it was in the US, probably part of why you're having a hard time finding a lot of them. The only US ones I remember are the black friday Mario edition and the Pokemon Red/Blue one that you are talking about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 01:09:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya I'm not sure how you feel about Custom Firmware or anything like that, but I see some Japanese Non XL 3DS's on ebay for relatively fair prices; if you install a custom firmware on it, or use appropriate homebrew tools you can play games region free with it. I only suggest that because it will probably be your cheapest/easiest option if you're dead set on the Non XL version.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 04:55:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>How is it tested? Around here they just check the check engine codes or whatever, and I have a buddy that can clear the light+codes for something like 50-100 miles so his car can pass emissions inspection.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 05:02:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure what it's called, but my buddy has some check engine code scanner thing that plugs into the O2 sensor. It shows all of the codes/faults and has the option to clear all codes (for 50-100 miles). I've had it done to my car, and when it got inspected the people said they couldn't see any codes/faults on their end.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 05:09:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh dang, they must use a better test or your car must be newer or something. Well another thing people do around here is get something like a PO Box or temporary address in another state and register the car there. That's pretty extreme, but just something to keep in mind. Good luck though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 06:26:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>"With money and strength I will become awesome." This is me irl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 07:16:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah yes, there it is. The stupidest thing I've ever read in my 5+ years on Reddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 07:31:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ironic you say that considering you don't think parents should HELP their deaf children fucking hear.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 14:46:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don't deserve the amount of down votes you got for this. A note like that, whether true or not, is a great way to get positive ebay feedback from buyers who would otherwise never bother. And just look at the comments section of this thread it's all people that are now going to buy something from this seller, that previously never would have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 06:24:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya I mean you just described what people want in Melee HD?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>$20 off Overwatch Merchandise Cose</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 08:37:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 08:38:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's only good for a few more hours hopefully someone can use it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 12:51:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your friend can make an another account and enable family sharing with the original account. You will keep your games that way, but not the progress. Your friend also sounds a little OCD.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Russian  gt; English] I tried translating this with an app online, but the words in quotations do not make much sense to me.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 17:27:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 17:28:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>The app tells me that it is:  gt; THERE ARE WORDS THAT HURT. THERE ARE WORDS THAT KILL. THERE ARE THERMOS' 'KACUK""Kalidor' and SOCKET' Any help would be greatly appreciated!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 17:36:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it supposed to be funny?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 17:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahhh haha, thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 20:06:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh this makes a lot more sense. Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 09:55:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>L</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to survive in Flint, Michigan</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 10:04:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 10:04:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.wikihow.com/Make-a-Realistic-Farting-Noise</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's a little last minute, but hopefully someone at GDQ can see this before the PepsiMan run.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 07:24:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 06:46:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 04:44:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>My condolences</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 23:24:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd personally worry more about finding a new job, and a lot less about your current hellhole. Even though you haven't performed up to their borderline ridiculous expectations, the fact they keep moving you around to different projects means that you're not easily replaceable. I think your boss giving you the "threat" pretty much indicates they're gonna start looking for someone to replace you, so you should take priority in doing the same.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 19:19:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is bullshit. From what I remember reading, it wasn't the FAA that banned cell phones being used on planes, it was the FCC. The FCC figured that any phone calls made from a plane would use traffic on dozens of cell towers all at once, instead of the one tower you use when you're on the ground. Now based on my understanding of Wide Area Networks, this explanation is also bullshit, but that's another discussion haha. But phones messing with airplanes instruments is complete bs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 19:24:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Complete bullshit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 19:27:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>A B.S degree in Computer Science and Computer Security. If .exe to .apk converter out there actually isn't just a virus, the functionality of the output apk will be extremely limited and most likely will just throw you lots of errors.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>IsItBullshit: China owns every Giant Panda in the world, including any offspring the Giant Panda's may have.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 07:43:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I find this incredibly hard to believe and feel like it would be something nearly impossible to keep track of, but everything I Google seems to suggest that it is the case.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Welding + Air Guitar</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 02:23:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hmmm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 13:21:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:52:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey hey hey, that's definitely not all of us. Some of us are from East Jesus State University.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 00:44:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s insane, and I thought the NYC rate sounded rough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New meaning of electric guitar</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 04:43:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When your girl sends you nudes without asking</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 05:09:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>