<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject8094</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-30 23:45:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>So for those wondering, I have added a few extra fans in my case, with one being on the other side of my radiator. I am currently running 4.6GHZ at 1.280V. Stress tested with a maximum temperature of 75C. Looks like success to me! Thanks, guys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 04:11:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I installed a fan on the opposite side of my radiator. One pulls air in, the other pushes air out. I installed another fan on the top of my case above my CPU that acts as an exhaust. I also set my fan speeds to maximum via the BIOS settings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-10 05:16:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I realize that now. But because I am dual booting, I needed to partition off storage for both Windows 10 (180GB) and for Linux (60GB). However, I did this twice. Did I make too many unnecessary partitions to my C Drive?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 02:38:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>By definition, the word great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 05:43:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do they offer TRX (Tron)?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 20:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here #8217;s](https://imgur.com/a/cO0Oi) a picture of the rest of the conversation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 22:17:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, don #8217;t think twice about it. There #8217;s many older individuals at USF. I was talking to a man who was in his later 60 #8217;s, he retired from being a physician and wanted to study psychology, or some sort of art degree. Now on the other hand, the area, has its ups and downs. The main two roads near campus is Fletcher and Fowler. Fletcher is not a good part of the area, whereas, Fowler isn #8217;t that bad. You can look at the crime statistics around USF, we #8217;ve had two armed robberies in the past few months, but overall, it #8217;s nothing to be worried about, so long as you are not walking down Fletcher late at night. I would definitely recommend off campus housing. But it #8217;s not cheap around USF. On average you are looking at spending around $600-700 a month for something nice and near campus. You can find some cheaper apartments a bit further away from campus for about $500-550 a month, although I wouldn #8217;t recommend it. Good luck. Edit: USF is by far one of the better universities for undergrad and graduate research, I #8217;m not very active on campus myself so I couldn #8217;t tell you exactly how to go about it, but there are numerous opportunities in research. Edit: grammar</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 00:02:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Darkjokes  gt; top jokes  gt; all time  gt; scroll down to number 14  gt; read the same exact joke. Congrats.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 20:14:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Bluh........bluh.........bluh........bluh"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 23:16:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So who #8217;s gonna tell him?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 23:52:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 02:02:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had a good laugh at this one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 05:36:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Accept my best comment award</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 03:55:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>C</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First ever eco-friendly and race neutral muskita n' spider repellent - it's called chicken.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 19:41:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 02:02:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Amazing Dark Souls cosplay</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 03:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #128293; Spotted Eagle Ray</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 02:04:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>