<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject4002</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fascinating Video Infographic of Internet Traffic Volumes After the East Coast Earthquake this Week</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-27 05:17:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-27 05:21:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>More graphs and analysis on this phenomenon: http://blog.comscore.com/2011/08/internet_seismometer_virgina_earthquake.html</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fascinating Video Infographic of Internet Traffic Volumes After the East Coast Earthquake this Week</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-27 15:20:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-27 15:21:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>More graphs and analysis on this phenomenon: http://blog.comscore.com/2011/08/internet_seismometer_virgina_earthquake.html</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Want my production company to shoot a kick ass music video for you this weekend for free?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-17 00:15:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>It will be amazing. Post an original song by you or your band that you'd like a music video for. DC/NoVA metro area. www.subject4002.com</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Want my production company to shoot a kick ass music video for you this weekend for free? (xpost from r/NOVA)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-17 00:26:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-18 15:56:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love the band's style! Let's do this. I shot you an email.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Beautiful thunderstorm over the National Cathedral in Washington DC last weekend</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-28 00:31:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Great Falls National Park near Washington DC [2560x1300] [OC]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-19 01:13:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Eerie photo I took of the C amp;O Canal at night in Georgetown, Washington DC</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-19 01:54:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-19 02:01:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Amazing city!](http://i.imgur.com/Cqm8q32.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-19 02:17:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! High praise, coming from "BigDickTrickle".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-19 02:59:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure thing! PM me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-19 20:40:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup. But don't tell anyone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dancing on the rocky Pacific Ocean coast [OC]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-14 20:04:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-14 22:37:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Muir beach in Marin, just north of San Francisco.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>One of you didn't get the memo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-21 05:42:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Looks like someone didn't get the memo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-21 05:54:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I was taking this time-lapse and Capitol Police came to tell me tripods weren't allowed... I told them to look up at the current state of the sky and reconsider. They let me stay.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-01 22:36:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-01 22:37:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Actual time-lapse video](https://vimeo.com/63064239)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-02 00:15:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! After Effects</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-02 00:16:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could not agree more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-02 18:22:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Keep up the learning! It's a steep curve, but it's so incredibly rewarding when you begin to master it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-02 18:36:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was a challenging shot due to the very high dynamic range in the scene (the sun was very bright and the side of the Capitol shown is in a very dark shadow). I used a Canon 6D; Canon 17-40 f/4L @ 17mm Due to the high dynamic range, this was an HDR time-lapse, so I took 1389 total photos in sets of three (one neutral exposure @ 1/500sec f/8 ISO100; one underexposed at 1/2000 sec; one overexposed at 1/125). Combining each of those sets of three resulted in 463 final frames. The lapse ran from 5:30pm-6:47pm. So, each set of three photos was kicked off every 10 seconds. I took my folder of RAW files and processed them into three versions of the time-lapse - one favoring the underexposed shots (for the opening where the sun is really bright), one favoring the neutral exposures, and one favoring the overexposures (for the end after the sun has gone behind the Capitol). Then, I cross-faded these different versions in After Effects. Keep playing around with time-lapses. They're really fun but certainly pose some technical challenges, haha! What specifically are you having trouble with in yours? I can offer some advice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-02 18:40:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, it is! For those of you who are photographers in DC (and those of you who aren't, too!), don't take this all for granted. We have a stunningly beautiful city.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-02 18:41:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow! Thanks for this wonderful compliment! Sure thing! I'll send you the full resolution version.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-02 18:50:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most everyone I know doesn't appreciate just how beautiful our city is - and how friendly most everyone is (in most places). I grew up in Jersey, so I've seen the other side.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-02 18:56:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>See my reply to the other comment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-02 18:57:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>See my reply to the other comment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-02 19:00:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everyone always jokes about the "ever-present security/secret-service sniper" in DC. I don't doubt that they exist (especially around the White House), I've just always wondered where they are all hiding - because if they have a line-of-sight to me then I must have a line-of-sight to them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We live in a beautiful city. Here's a time-lapse of the Jefferson Memorial.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-08 22:12:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-08 22:54:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please let us know, OP! I'd love to go try and recreate this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-09 00:34:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't had too much trouble using tripods around the monuments, so long as I'm not in people's way. They're more strict around the Capitol building, though. This time-lapse was taken with a Canon 6D and a Canon 17-40mm f/4L lens. I used a very strong neutral-density filter, which allowed each exposure to be 1.3 seconds long, despite the camera facing the sun. This allowed me to achieve a near-360 degree [shutter angle](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rotary_disc_shutter). That is why the motion of the people appear to be smooth/fluid as compared to typical time-lapses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-09 00:59:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Before shooting the time-lapse, I just recorded a 20-second normal video and used the sound from that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-09 01:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>13 minutes. 403 frames, 2 seconds apart each. The clouds were moving really quickly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Someone in Bloomingdale's marketing department got a little too trigger-happy with the Photoshop stretch tool</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-13 05:27:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-16 20:22:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, here it is: https://www.nga.gov/exhibitions/villarealinfo.shtm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The National Gallery of Art in Washington DC has a stunning LED light sculpture. This is a completely unedited photo of it and my friend.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-18 03:30:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-18 03:31:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I tried my hand at a similar shot.](http://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/20ophr/the_national_gallery_of_art_in_washington_dc_has/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-23 19:14:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone let god know that he got a little carried away with the photoshop stretch tool again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Time-stacked image of the Lincoln Memorial I created from 165 photos taken in a row during sunset.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-23 21:48:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-23 22:25:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here's the time-lapse I created it from.](https://vimeo.com/69840457)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-23 23:35:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>[That's one angry baby!](http://imgur.com/2KKVi6e.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-24 00:04:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Time stacking isn't actually all that difficult technically. Load up your photos in Photoshop by going to File -- gt; Scripts -- gt; Load Files into Stack. Each one of your photos in the time-lapse will now be its own layer. Now, take all of the layers except the very bottom one and set them to the "Lighten" blending mode. That's it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-24 02:21:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>When taking time-lapses, everything should be in full-manual mode (the exposure, the focus, the ISO, EVERYTHING) and you shouldn't adjust the settings mid-time-lapse unless you really know what you're doing. If you're really in full manual and you're still seeing some flicker, then you've got the "hard" kind of flicker to get rid of. Read up on time lapse flicker - there's a lot of good info on this and some software to correct for it (I use GBDeflicker). If your night time lapses are too dark, then exposure each frame for longer, open your aperture up, or increase your ISO (but don't do this mid-time-lapse!).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-24 16:11:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will be getting some very long night time-lapses of DC soon...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-24 18:55:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I liked the sense of energy and interest they brought to the lower-left of the image. It felt too empty/stoic without them in there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-25 17:51:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>As long as you're not in the way, they usually allow it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-27 05:44:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice shots! Yes, renting new types of lenses is great fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-27 05:50:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>This. A million times, this. Then, join meetup.com groups that do your hobby. Best part is: you find new friends, develop a new skill, and have fun! In other news, maybe having a girlfriend is enough social simulation to prevent you from actually being motivated to act on everyone's advice here. Not saying you should break up with her, just that that's something you should be very aware of. I've seen it happen countless times before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-27 06:05:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're given a few slices of bread and cheese every day, you'll survive, albeit slightly hungry and unsatisfied. If you're starving with nothing to eat, you'll go out and learn how to kill and eat a [insert large game animal of your choice here]. Recognize that you're getting some bread and cheese now but life would be much more fulfilling if you went out hunting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ITAP of the Lincoln Memorial in Washington DC at sunset [time-stacked photo made from 150 exposures]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-10 04:08:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-10 04:09:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This is the time-lapse the photo was made from.](https://vimeo.com/69840457)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Most beautiful city on earth at this time of year</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-12 17:19:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-13 03:55:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I took the photo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-14 20:14:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure thing! Just please credit www.subject4002.com if you can. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-14 20:18:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! Yes, I had a very strong neutral density filter so the exposure was 3 seconds long, to give the water that dreamy feel. I also used a polarizing filter that darkened the sky relative to the trees. Finally, when processing the RAW file in photoshop, I did (ever so slightly) tint the photo pink (it already had a decent amount of pink hues to it).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-14 20:22:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I took it from just south of MLK Memorial.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-16 06:50:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sound coincidences - like when windshield wipers match the beat of the music that's playing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Did you see that beautiful storm last night? I was at the Lincoln Memorial and captured this photo of a couple visiting from Kentucky watching the lightning show.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-27 00:36:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-27 05:09:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Accurate edit. I combined 4 photos to capture the feeling of the storm over the course of the evening. The couple showed up about 15 minutes after the storm clouds were at their peak. You can see all original 4 photos, unedited (other than RAW demosaicing) [here](http://imgur.com/1lSXy58.jpg). All photos were f/9, 15 sec, ISO-100. No HDR - the interesting coloring/contrast comes from all the lightning in each 15 second exposure (the blue) and the movement of the clouds (lit up by the orange/pinkish hue of the city lights). The only other thing I did was mirror the right spotlight to the left side (because I didn't like that the left one was brighter and wanted balance).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-27 05:09:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not HDR. See my other comment for settings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-27 05:11:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-27 23:32:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not really.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-01 03:47:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here you go.](http://imgur.com/c5YSfYX.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Last night's thunderstorm over the Hudson was truly stunning</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-07 20:28:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ITAP of an epic lightning bolt over the Hudson River in NYC this weekend</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-09 03:17:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stunning sunset over the Hudson River from New York City</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-03 01:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stunning sunset time-lapse from last Sunday</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-03 01:39:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-03 02:54:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I took a photo every 4 seconds, for 45 minutes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-03 03:39:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I created a 2,000 megapixel photo of sunrise over Dubai from 105 individual photos stitched together.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-08 18:48:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-08 19:22:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>These are the "Executive Towers" in the Business Bay district.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-08 19:25:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! PM me your resolution and I'll send you a version to use.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-08 21:41:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://research.microsoft.com/en-us/um/redmond/projects/ice/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-08 22:09:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfortunately, I couldn't get onto the roof of the building next door - that would have given me a more-centered angle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-08 23:59:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish! I was there a few months ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The strangely peaceful howl of the wind and snow swirling down a desolate 8th avenue was suddenly interrupted by the oncoming roar of snow plows</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-24 05:40:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wandering New York City's completely deserted streets at midnight during the blizzard</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-24 18:04:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-24 22:07:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! Canon 5Ds; Canon 135mm f/2L</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-12 14:33:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New York City just witnessed an absolutely massive lightning strike completely spanning the Hudson River. I happened to have my camera set up to capture it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-26 01:58:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-26 02:17:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's really my shot. I would like to assume the better of humanity and hope that at least some people will give me (www.subject4002.com) credit if they use it. I still have the full 50 megapixel image, too. Edit: thanks for the gold on the original post, kind redditor! If anyone wants a framed print of this, I'll be doing a print run in one week. This was shot with a Canon 5Ds, so the full image is 50 megapixels. That means you can enlarge this bad boy a lot. I'll make a print AT COST for anyone who PMs me a request in the next 48 hours.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Exactly one year ago, I took a 40-megapixel photo of a lightning strike in New York City. I spent hundreds of hours over the past year painstakingly creating an exact replica with one difference #8230; it's 5,449 megapixels.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 02:00:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Exactly one year ago, I took a 40-megapixel photo of a lightning strike in New York City. I spent hundreds of hours over the past year painstakingly creating an exact replica with one difference #8230; it's 5,449 megapixels. Here #8217;s a section of it that I particularly like. 2560x1440</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 02:02:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 02:07:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here's the original post.](https://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/4ulqap/new_york_city_just_witnessed_an_absolutely/) [Here #8217;s how I increased the photo's resolution by 13,500%.](http://vastphotos.com/blog/2017/06/15/upconverting-the-hand-of-zeus/) [Here's the 5,449-megapixel version.](http://vastphotos.com/photo/the-hand-of-zeus-by-dan-piech) [Here's the original 40-megapixel version.](http://vastphotos.com/photo/the-hand-of-zeus-single-exposure-by-dan-piech) When I posted the initial photo, many of you asked for a version to use as a wallpaper. [You can download a 2560x1440 section of the photo here.](https://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/6pkbo6/exactly_one_year_ago_i_took_a_40megapixel_photo/) Many of you also asked for prints of the original photo. I posted in a comment that I'd make prints at-cost for redditors. I'm (finally!) making good on that promise, now that I've started [a company](http://vastphotos.com) that can do that. Code "redditfriendsonly" takes 50% off a ready-to-hang print of [the original photo here](http://vastphotos.com/photo/the-hand-of-zeus-single-exposure-by-dan-piech).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 02:11:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here's the original post.](https://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/4ulqap/new_york_city_just_witnessed_an_absolutely/) [Here #8217;s how I increased the photo's resolution by 13,500%.](http://vastphotos.com/blog/2017/06/15/upconverting-the-hand-of-zeus/) [Here's the 5,449-megapixel version.](http://vastphotos.com/photo/the-hand-of-zeus-by-dan-piech) [Here's the original 40-megapixel version.](http://vastphotos.com/photo/the-hand-of-zeus-single-exposure-by-dan-piech) Many of you also asked for prints of the original photo. I posted in a comment that I'd make prints at-cost for redditors. I'm (finally!) making good on that promise, now that I've started a company that can do that. Code "redditfriendsonly" takes 50% off a ready-to-hang print of [the original photo here](http://vastphotos.com/photo/the-hand-of-zeus-single-exposure-by-dan-piech).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 02:26:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I've been using it as a desktop background myself for the past few months because the photo has enough negative space for icons to not be backdropped by visual complexity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 02:29:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>This gif was made with the new 5,449-megapixel version. [Here's the 5,449-megapixel version.](http://vastphotos.com/photo/the-hand-of-zeus-by-dan-piech) [Here's the original 40-megapixel version.](http://vastphotos.com/photo/the-hand-of-zeus-single-exposure-by-dan-piech)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 03:02:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, VAST photos (the ultra high resolution photos my company [VAST](http://vastphotos.com) creates like this one) are not cheap. That's because they are, objectively, the highest quality fine art photographs and prints ever made. Also, each of us artists can spend more than 100 hours and many thousands of dollars creating just one of our VAST photos. They are labors of love that we pour a lot of ourselves into. Also, we use expensive technology to create our photos and prints. For example, we use rotational gimbal mounts for our high-end cameras as well as custom-built computers to process the hundreds of gigabytes that these photos can be (I have one photo that, with layers, is over 1 TB). One of our computers, alone, is as powerful as 12 Apple MacBook Pro computers combined. We spare no expense in the printmaking process and use the very best technology and materials. The printer we use is the highest resolution chromogenic printer in use on the planet and uses extremely fine lasers to expose the image on light-sensitive paper (unlike most other photographs you buy which are just ink sprayed on paper). There are only a very small handful of printers the same as ours in existence. Prior to us, the printer was used to print currency and military surveillance images. This technology is not cheap. Many VAST photos are limited editions, meaning that only a small number of prints will ever be made of them (usually only a few dozen). This, in addition to elements like the actual real hand-written signature from the artist, gives you the confidence that a VAST Print is a unique art piece and not something that's going to be on everyone's wall. Finally, there are many other photographers out there today who are selling their shockingly low-quality large-format photo prints at prices like these, based on shady marketing tactics (that focus on building a fabricated "brand" around the photographer) and misleading information about the quality and technology used. We want to be different and instead focus on the authentic quality and craftsmanship of our artwork because it speaks for itself and is genuinely, by any objective measure, vastly superior. tl;dr: a [VAST Print](http://vastphotos.com/prints) is a truly unique and objectively superior masterpiece created by a cutting-edge photographer at the peak of their craft with no expense spared in its creation. Buying one is supporting our team of photographers, engineers, artists, and computer scientists who are hard at work innovating new techniques at the intersection of art, photography, and technology. If that's a mission you want to support, then we ask that you consider buying one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 03:05:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. I spent an extremely long time [putting this together](http://vastphotos.com/blog/2017/06/15/upconverting-the-hand-of-zeus/).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 03:06:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Totally fine! Your kind words are enough!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 03:07:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>The full 5,449-megapixel version of this photo would be much too difficult to share here on reddit. [You can explore the full resolution photo on my company's website here.](http://vastphotos.com/photo/the-hand-of-zeus-by-dan-piech)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 04:09:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I put a lot of time into this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 04:25:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfortunately, I did not capture it on video. That would have been cool, though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 13:19:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Correct! The full resolution file is 16.8 GB. This is listed along with other technical specifications if you [scroll down on the page here.](http://vastphotos.com/photo/the-hand-of-zeus-by-dan-piech)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 15:07:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the heads up! I'm pretty sure we fixed the bug.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 15:08:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the joy of creation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 15:14:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I made this because I love creating things and trying to tackle genuinely difficult challenges. [Here's how I made it.](http://vastphotos.com/blog/2017/06/15/upconverting-the-hand-of-zeus/) Solving the challenges associated with its creation is helping me to grow the knowledge-base of techniques used by the community of ultra high resolution fine art image-makers that [my company](http://vastphotos.com) is cultivating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 15:23:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>None taken! The "redditfriendsonly" code brings that down to our cost, as I promised Reddit a year ago. But yes, it's still not cheap because these are fully-finished, ready-to-hang prints, face mounted on glass using the highest resolution photographic printer in use on the planet. [You can learn more about why these are not cheap here.](http://vastphotos.com/prints)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 15:28:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>The "redditfriendsonly" code brings that price down to our cost, as I promised Reddit a year ago. But yes, it's still not cheap because these are fully-finished, ready-to-hang prints, face mounted on glass using the highest resolution photographic printer in use on the planet. [You can learn more about why these are not cheap here.](http://vastphotos.com/prints) PS: shipping costs are built into that price, as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 15:34:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, it would! Unfortunately, there are no image sensors out there even close to that high of a resolution.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 15:34:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! You can zoom in to that area on [our website](http://vastphotos.com/photo/the-hand-of-zeus-by-dan-piech).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 15:39:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree! I've spent over a decade photographing thunderstorms and it is still the most impressive storm I've ever come across.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 16:38:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for your thoughts. I think you bring up some good points that I'd like to address because I absolutely agree that the art should stand on its own accord. My response was directly addressing OP's question of why our prints are so expensive, which is why I had to go into some detail that sounds like a "marketing pamphlet." For example, the printer we use is insanely expensive to operate - much more than any other printer out there. So, I needed to convey some of the business aspects of what we do that OP couldn't have known just from looking at the artwork itself, on a website, in gif form. I preferred to answer OP's business-oriented question of "why is this so expensive" with objective business-oriented details instead of just "because art." Yes, I wholeheartedly agree that I should probably have toned down my use of buzz-word adjectives, but that is just how I write about this stuff because I'm genuinely super excited about it and I want to try to convey that excitement to others. Yes, you're absolutely right that you can never "extract more detail out of the subject of a photo" if it's not there in the first place. That's why my company is innovating new approaches to make ultra high resolution fine art photographs that are 100s of times higher than typical photographs by using "loopholes" around this fact (e.g. stitching together 100s of individual photos, etc.). [Have a look at my blog post detailing how I created the 5,449-megapixel photo and you'll see what I mean.](http://vastphotos.com/blog/2017/06/15/upconverting-the-hand-of-zeus/) Thanks again for your thoughts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 16:53:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also, just so we're clear, I'm criticizing the photographers who misrepresent the quality of their work through misleading marketing tactics and, at times, outright lies about the objective, technical details of the work. The vast majority of large-format, ultra high resolution photographers out there do not to do this... and are doing really great work that we support wholeheartedly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 19:24:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can zoom in on the two areas where lightning strikes [on our website here](http://vastphotos.com/photo/the-hand-of-zeus-by-dan-piech).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 19:30:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a combination of "just because I love doing this" (it was my hobby for the past decade until I decided to make a company out of it) and also because prints should be made at 300ppi (300 pixels per inch) to appear sharp to the naked eye. Typical digital photographs can only be printed about 20 inches wide before they begin to drop beneath 300ppi quality (i.e. they no longer look sharp up-close). You see blurry large-format prints of typical photos everywhere... because the photos have been enlarged to sizes their resolutions don't permit. We work hard to create [VAST photos](http://vastphotos.com) because, unlike typical photos, they can be printed dozens of feet wide and remain extremely sharp/clear.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I created a 5,449-megapixel photo of a lightning strike in New York City. Here's a 1.7-megapixel version. The full resolution version (link in comments) is 3,156x higher quality.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 01:00:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 01:00:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>One year ago, I took [this 40-megapixel photo](https://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/4ulqap/new_york_city_just_witnessed_an_absolutely/) of a lightning strike in New York City. I spent the past year creating a 5,449-megapixel photo that looks nearly identical to it, despite being made almost entirely of new material from dozens of new photographs. [Here's an in-depth walk-through of how I did it.](http://vastphotos.com/blog/2017/06/15/upconverting-the-hand-of-zeus/) [You can explore the full resolution photo here.](http://vastphotos.com/photo/the-hand-of-zeus-by-dan-piech)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 18:23:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just so we're clear, I'm criticizing the photographers who misrepresent the quality of their work through misleading marketing tactics and, at times, outright lies about the objective, technical details of the work. The vast majority of large-format, ultra high resolution photographers out there do not to do this... and are doing really great work that we support wholeheartedly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 04:32:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excellent color balance and tones. Beautiful work!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 04:37:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great composition and use of negative space. The hue of the background is also nicely original - not a color tone typically seen in many photos. Well done!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 04:41:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very moody, atmospheric, and abstract. Love it. Nice work!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 04:43:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great work! Simple, powerful, and evocative.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 04:49:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the sky looks great in this. Are you shooting in raw? If not, you can get a lot more detail/light in those shadows. If you are, use Adobe Camera Raw to increase the "shadows" and the "blacks". Or, you could blend multiple exposures with different exposure settings (one for the sky and one for the trees).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 05:08:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi! I took the photo. Thanks for your opinions and criticism. You are correct that it was taken late in the afternoon while the sun was still up behind the clouds that are behind the camera (you can see the brighter areas of the clouds reflecting off the skyline). It was dark enough for the street-lights in the lower-right to be on already, though. The darkness in the image is a result of two things: the storm clouds were VERY thick/dark and I was also using a strong neutral density filter. The haloing around the buildings that you mention bothers me as well. The final image you see here is just a quick raw to jpeg conversion I did using Adobe Camera Raw - and an increase in the clarity slider will have that consequence (as I take it you probably know). I normally would have spent time cleaning up halos like that, however I just quickly posted the image to Reddit after the lightning strike happened (and quite frankly, expected it to not really go anywhere). I realize that there are a lot of fake "photoshopped" lightning strike photos on Reddit and that you may think this is another one of those, but it is not. This was an actual strike that happened and many of us who live in the area saw it and are well aware of the giant tree that is no longer in the park as a result. [You can see our discussion about this in the original thread here.](https://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/4ulqap/new_york_city_just_witnessed_an_absolutely/) Finally, the "master photographers" aspect does not pertain to this photo. It pertains to [a company I started](https://vastphotos.com) that creates images that are hundreds of times higher resolution than this one using advanced image creation/processing techniques. For example, [I created a new version of this lightning photo that is 13,600% higher resolution than the original](https://vastphotos.com/photo/the-hand-of-zeus-by-dan-piech). At 5,449 megapixels, it is by far the highest resolution image ever created of a lightning strike. [You can read an in-depth technical walk through of how I created it here.](https://vastphotos.com/blog/2017/06/15/upconverting-the-hand-of-zeus/) Our company has a mission to improve the art and craftsmanship of ultra high resolution image-making. It sounds like you have an eye for perfection and quality, so I'd love to chat with you more about this if you'd like - because I have that same type of OCD perfectionist mindset. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 05:12:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. [Here's the thread with the images.](https://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/4ulqap/new_york_city_just_witnessed_an_absolutely/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 05:13:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Close. It was taken from the Independence Plaza complex which is a bit higher up than that bridge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 05:24:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for mentioning us! By the way, our company, [VAST](https://vastphotos.com), creates ultra high resolution photographs. The image you linked to and that this thread is about is NOT one of those. It's a "typical" high-end 40-megapixel photograph shot with a Canon 5DS R. As part of building the company, I spent hundreds of hours creating [a new 5,449-megapixel version of the image that you can explore here](https://vastphotos.com/photo/the-hand-of-zeus-by-dan-piech). It may look the same as the original (which was the goal), but if you scroll down on the page, there are tools that allow you to zoom in and see how much higher resolution the image is than the original (and as compared to all other typical photographs). [You can read how I created it here.](https://vastphotos.com/blog/2017/06/15/upconverting-the-hand-of-zeus/) This is the type of work our company does.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 05:47:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a good question. I've spent over a decade photographing lightning and can let you know the major reasons why: * The first reason is that the clouds you see in the photo are actually very far away from the strike itself. This strike happened far out in front of the rain wall (that has lower-hanging clouds). The lightning is coming from clouds that are nearly directly overhead and far out of frame above the image. * The second reason is that this did not happen at night in a completely dark environment (where the dominant light source would have been the strike itself). The sun was still a couple hours away from setting, so the clouds and skyline had some light already on them naturally. Therefore, the lightning didn't make much of a difference. * The third reason is that I had a strong neutral density filter on the lens. This allowed me to use a 10-second exposure despite the fact that it wasn't nighttime. As a result, the lightning was only contributing light to the scene for a tiny fraction of the time the scene was exposing (and therefore had a relatively negligible impact on the lighting of the overall scene). Thanks for your curiosity! It's that same type of curiosity that got me started exploring photography in the first place, so if this type of stuff interests you, get out there and shoot!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 15:49:50</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; At that point it just seems like you're so far away from the original it might as well just have been a composite with an added lightning in post like so many others do. Yes, I agree that the new ultra high resolution version of the photo (which is not what OP posted here) is absolutely more "artwork" than "photograph". However, my goal was to identically mimic my original single-exposure photograph as closely as possible. [Here is the original 40-megapixel true photograph of the strike (on the left) side by side with the new 5,449-megapixel "photographic artwork" (on on the right).](http://i.imgur.com/hYJK3Oj.jpg) There was a good bit more involved in the process of creating the new version than what you listed. I had to carefully adjust all the coloring/shading/highlighting throughout every tiny part of the image as well as find ways to dramatically upscale the sky from the original without causing banding or splotching (among other things). I spent hundreds of hours doing this because I wanted to have the best of both worlds: a great "photograph" (emphasis on the quotes) of a lightning strike that's ALSO one of the highest resolution images ever created (which is not something that can be created during a fleeting moment of a lightning strike).  gt; the only thing connecting the final print and the event is that 'trust me, it looked almost exactly like that when it happened and i re-created it pretty closely'. I'm not asking anyone to trust me because I don't have to - you can can see the original true photograph I took and compare it to the new ultra high resolution version. Maybe you missed the point that there are two separate images we're talking about: [my original photograph](https://vastphotos.com/photo-special/?p=the-hand-of-zeus-single-exposure-by-dan-piech) of the actual strike and [the new ultra high resolution image/artwork](https://vastphotos.com/photo/the-hand-of-zeus-by-dan-piech) I created to identically mimic the original photograph.  gt; but i'm also very careful not to pretend it isn't a digital edit/comp using different elements etc. I could not agree more! There are few things that aggravate me more than someone who tries to pass off a fabricated image (that has elements that weren't in the original photograph, etc.) as a real photograph. I've spent over a decade of my life trying to get lightning photographs and have almost been struck a few times as a result. The ONLY reason I do that is so that I can say that the moment I captured was a real moment that actually happened. I could easily photoshop the most impressive lightning strike "photograph" you've ever seen in a couple hours right now (and do so with a great degree of care so that it would be very difficult to identify as a fake) but then we're not being true to ourselves, nature, or others... unless we call it what it is in that case: not a photograph but rather artwork. That's why I'm very careful to be very up-front that my new ultra high resolution image is a "photographic artwork" - and I'm not hiding my process. [I've fully detailed it here.](https://vastphotos.com/blog/2017/06/15/upconverting-the-hand-of-zeus/) Thanks again for your thoughts. If you know other people doing work I'd like this, I'd absolutely love to talk with them about potentially joining our team of photographers, engineers, and artists at [VAST](https://vastphotos.com).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 16:00:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I do get scared but I also get exhilarated by it... and the exhilaration usually outweighs the fear. I imagine that it's the type of feeling that base jumpers get (but to a much smaller degree!). Also, I usually try to be somewhat careful about where I am (for example, in this photo, there are some other very tall buildings behind the camera that would *probably* get struck before I do). Yes, I had a closer call on a beach in New Jersey many years ago. Lightning hit the sand about 300 feet away from me. Also, a few years ago I was on the top floor of a high-rise photographing out of the windows when the roof above me got struck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 16:03:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm happy to have provided your background! I do the same thing with backgrounds - only using darker images for the same reason (I also think it saves battery life - but I don't know if the difference is appreciable enough to notice).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 16:08:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I completely agree with what you're saying about people not understanding that most lightning strike photographs are long exposures (that sometimes have multiple strikes in them). This was taken with a neutral density filter (it was dark but it wasn't nighttime outside so I needed it) which allowed me to use a 10 second exposure. That being said, this was the only strike that happened within that 10 second exposure period. The strikes you see in the image are from a single moment. Here in New York City, our thunderstorms usually aren't super active. They don't have a strike every couple seconds the way that storms further south do. At the time I was photographing this storm, it was producing a bolt about once every 30-60 seconds or so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Gotham Square, 6-gigapixel Digital Image from 189 Photographs, 1400x1400px</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 13:45:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 13:52:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the midtown Manhattan skyline in New York City from across the East River. I spent hundreds of hours putting the image together from 189 individual photographs which I took at midnight on New Years Eve last year. The full size image is 5,935 megapixels and can be enlarged to 21 feet tall/wide and still remain perfectly sharp to the naked eye (300ppi). [You can zoom in on the full size image (77,039x77,039px) here.](https://vastphotos.com/photo/gotham-square-by-dan-piech)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>There's a spectacular hosta plant in the New York Botanical Garden that most people don't know about. I created a 344-megapixel photo of it by stitching together 36 separate exposures.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 18:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 18:13:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've posted a map to where you can find this specific plant in the New York Botanical Garden as well as the technical details of the photo + capture technique [here](https://vastphotos.com/photo/newborn-by-dan-piech).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I spent 160 hours creating a 600-megapixel composite image of New York City from 189 individual photos I took of the Manhattan skyline.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 00:40:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 00:41:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>[You can view the full 600-megapixel photo as well as learn more about the process I used to create it here.](https://vastphotos.com/photo/a-new-york-dream-by-dan-piech)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 01:08:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's [The Franklin D. Roosevelt Four Freedoms Park](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Franklin_D._Roosevelt_Four_Freedoms_Park) on the southern end of Roosevelt Island in the East River.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 01:48:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely! I'd love to see the result when you're finished. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 01:56:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>It took about 3 hours to shoot the photos (they were all shot on New Years Eve last year - the bright light you see in the sky is from the Times Square celebration). Nearly all of the time was spent in post-production.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 04:29:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>The website officially launched in July, but was live in beta while I built it starting last fall.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 04:36:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha! Very creative!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 05:03:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good catch. I wrote that story for the website a few days ago and have since tried to be more scientific with my estimate of how much time I think I spent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 14:21:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure, go for it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A New York Dream, 602-Megapixel Digital Composite from 189 Photographs, 1400x1400px</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 18:26:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 18:28:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Creating this took me 160 hours over the past year. I captured the 189 source material photographs on New Years Eve. The light in the sky is from the Times Square ball drop celebration. The full image has enough resolution to be enlarged to 7-feet wide while remaining perfectly sharp to the naked eye. [You can read more about how I created this as well as explore close-ups of the full 602-megapixel image here.](https://vastphotos.com/photo/a-new-york-dream-by-dan-piech)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 19:45:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I manually constructed most of it (instead of just using the polar coordinates filter in Photoshop) so I could have complete control. That's why it took me so long to create.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 00:44:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>It does appear only once. You might be thinking that the Chrysler Building (at about 10 o'clock in the image) is the Empire State Building.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"A New York Dream" - composite image created from 189 photographs of the New York City skyline</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 22:49:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 22:51:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Creating this took me 160 hours over the past year. I captured the 189 source material photographs on New Years Eve. The light in the sky is from the Times Square ball drop celebration. The full image has enough resolution to be enlarged to 7-feet wide while remaining perfectly sharp to the naked eye. [You can read more about how I created this as well as explore close-ups of the full 602-megapixel image here.](https://vastphotos.com/photo/a-new-york-dream-by-dan-piech)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I blended 105 exposures to create a 620-megapixel photo of New York City transitioning from night to day after a snowstorm. [8000x3050]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 18:18:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 18:21:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Creating this took me over 100 hours of work, from planning the shoot to stitching and blending the images. The full photo is 28x higher resolution than a typical professional photo. It can be enlarged a dozen feet wide and remain perfectly sharp to the naked eye. [You can read more about the creation process and explore a higher resolution version of the photo here.](https://vastphotos.com/photo/new-york-transitions-1-by-dan-piech) Also, you can follow me at @dan_piech on Instagram where I'll be posting more ultra high resolution photos I've created like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 21:36:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! The scene has many tiny details that are fun to explore. For example, I didn't realize until after creating the photo just how much rooftop graffiti there is throughout the city. [Here's an example.](https://i.imgur.com/eXvEmcE.gifv)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 22:11:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, it was! You can see location details and more info about the photo [here](https://vastphotos.com/photo/new-york-transitions-1-by-dan-piech).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 22:13:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's 6th avenue which runs up the heart of Manhattan. You can see a map of the location on the page [here](https://vastphotos.com/photo/new-york-transitions-1-by-dan-piech).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 22:19:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I quit my job last year to start a company that creates the highest resolution fine art photos and prints ever made. You can buy one of our ultra high resolution, limited-edition prints of this photo [here](https://vastphotos.com/photo/new-york-transitions-1-by-dan-piech). Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 22:21:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha! Yes, I actually debated photoshopping that billboard out of the scene but then chose not to in order to retain the integrity and authenticity of the scene.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 22:24:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good idea! I actually already did that! Here's a [2,002-megapixel version of just nighttime](https://vastphotos.com/photo/new-york-wonderland-cropped-by-dan-piech) and here's a [621-megapixel version of just sunrise](https://vastphotos.com/photo/january-dawn-cropped-by-dan-piech). And here's a [black  amp; white version](https://vastphotos.com/photo/midnight-in-manhattan-cropped-by-dan-piech) which is my personal favorite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 22:32:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was taken from the top of a hotel in west SoHo. You can see a map of the location if you scroll down to the "Tech Specs" section of [the page](https://vastphotos.com/photo/new-york-transitions-1-by-dan-piech#techSpecs).  lt;-- that link should hopefully deeplink to the section of the page.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 22:36:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have printed it - through my company, [VAST](https://vastphotos.com/). It looks pretty spectacular in large-format sizes. You can get up close and see all of the intricate details of the city.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 22:37:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep! I quit my job last year to start a company specifically to do this: [VAST](https://vastphotos.com/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 22:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! Correct, nearly all of the time was spent in post-production. One of the biggest challenges was that I was shooting through a double-pane window which causes intense glares from point-sources of light at night (which a cityscape scene is filled with!). So, I had to carefully photoshop out thousands of individual glares. I spent two days alone doing that. I used Autopano Giga to do most of the stitching for this photo. Then, I used Photoshop to do most of the blending. I also have some custom scripts I've written to do some demosaicing on the raw files before stitching (for color grading purposes). I mount my camera on a manual gimbal from Really Right Stuff (can't say enough good things about it!). This is critically important because it allows me to rotate the camera around the "no-parallax-point" while shooting the images (so that the camera's perspective on the scene remains precisely fixed). I don't use any automated software or hardware during the shooting process because I want to have full control over the shooting process and by focused in the moment - paying attention to all the little details in the scene (instead of just pressing "go" and letting a machine do the work).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 22:52:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mount my camera on a manual gimbal from Really Right Stuff (can't say enough good things about it and the company). This is critically important because it allows me to rotate the camera around the "no-parallax-point" while shooting the images (so that the camera's perspective on the scene remains precisely fixed). I don't use any automated software or hardware during the shooting process because I want to have full control over the shooting process and be focused in the moment, paying attention to all the little details in the scene (instead of just pressing "go" and letting a machine do the work). I used Autopano Giga to do most of the stitching for this photo. Then, I used Photoshop to do most of the blending. I also have some custom scripts I've written to do some demosaicing on the raw files before stitching (for color grading purposes). You can read more about my equipment and technique [here](https://vastphotos.com/technique/). I'd be happy to do an AMA if people want - I've spent the past decade refining my technique for creating gigapixel photos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 23:09:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I quit my job last year to start a company that creates ultra high resolution photos like this. We then print them using the highest resolution photographic printer in commercial use. You can buy a large-format print [here](https://vastphotos.com/photo/new-york-transitions-1-by-dan-piech).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 23:09:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a really interesting idea! Thanks for that!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Midnight in New York City. A heavy snowstorm. A lone figure wanders the deserted streets.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 18:26:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 18:26:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I created this cinemagraph using source material from [this photograph I captured a few blocks from Times Square](https://vastphotos.com/photo/the-phantom-in-the-blizzard-by-dan-piech) during one of the most severe blizzards in New York City history. PM me if you'd like an mp4 version of this. I've created many different resolutions/sizes/aspect-ratios - they look pretty cool when looped on a TV or monitor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>At midnight on New Years Eve, I took 189 images of New York City aglow with the light from the Times Square celebration. I then stitched them together into an enormous 6,410 megapixel photograph. [12000x2660]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 18:29:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 18:38:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>The 12000x2660 image posted here is the maximum image resolution that will render on most mobile devices. The full resolution photo is 201 times higher resolution and can be enlarged to 47 feet wide while remaining perfectly sharp to the naked eye. [Here's a gif zooming in on the epic "Good Defeats Evil" statue that's part of the scene.](https://i.imgur.com/Wdor1JQ.gifv) [You can read more about the full resolution photo and zoom in on it here.](https://vastphotos.com/photo/requiem-for-2016-by-dan-piech) Also, you can follow me at @dan_piech on Instagram where I post ultra high resolution photos I've created like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 19:06:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! It took me about two hours to capture all 189 images.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 19:47:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Having a good lens and camera helps, yes. But, the primary way I achieve really high resolutions is by stitching together hundreds of images of a scene. Each image is only one tiny section of the scene (zoomed in using a long telephoto lens) but together they make up the entire scene. It's a fun technique!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 23:06:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>All of the images were taken from the exact same location using a precise gimbal that allows the camera's perspective on the scene to remain fixed as it rotates.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 23:38:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I process the raw files into 16-bit TIFs, then stitch, then repeat that process multiple times (to create multiple versions of the stitch). Then I layer those stitched versions in Photoshop and blend!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 23:53:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! Feel free to PM me if you ever want help or a critique.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 01:54:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>16-bit is higher quality. [More info on why here.](https://www.diyphotography.net/8-bit-vs-16-bit-color-depth-use-matters/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 03:31:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great question! I don't actually know! If anyone knows why that building has that giant tear, I'd love to know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>