<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject8361</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Research as an Undergrad</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-17 09:07:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>hey I'm an incoming freshman interested in doing research at some point in the computer science dept. do any freshman/underclassmen get research positions? any advice on how to get them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>CS class waitlist?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-02 19:57:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm currently 8th on the waitlist for an 86 person CS class. I REALLY want to take this class. Do you think I'll get in, or should I look at other options?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-08 06:53:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>go for it. If you really want to go to Columbia, ED is the way to go. If you don't get in, you'll likely get deferred which'll put you in the regular applicant pool but with a slight advantage (CU wants to retain yield, so if they're choosing between you and a very similar RD applicant, they'll pick you because they know you really want to go to Columbia.) The only reason not to do ED would be if you are going to need to rely heavily on financial aid (you don't want to be bound to Columbia if you can't necessarily attend due to financial circumstances) or if you're not absolutely positive that Columbia is the place for you. But based on your question, I'd definitely suggest ED. Best of luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 06:20:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>by dedicating my life and soul to school for four years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-05 23:32:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>who says i'm a dude... i'm definitely a girl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-19 20:16:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wasn't given an interview whereas a kid at my same school was. I got in, he didn't. It means basically nothing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-16 08:16:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with what others have said, but I want to tell you that I have a lot of sympathy for you. I was deferred from MIT Early Action and I was literally exactly you this time last year. My advice: start looking at other schools. That by no means implies that you won't get in RD (in fact 2 of my close friends were deferred and then accepted). However, the worst that can happen is that you're rejected RD and end up at a school that you don't love because you're still thinking about Columbia. Yes, Columbia may seem perfect right now, but I guarantee you there are at least a couple schools out there that will be great fits for you. Definitely keep doing well in school, send Columbia an enthusiastic letter of interest in the spring, and don't get too down on yourself. I never thought Columbia would be a good place for me but I love it now! Best of luck :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-16 08:29:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup, they're not going to be more likely to let you in if you choose one major over the other. Also, you have quite a bit of time to figure out what you want to do, and CS and CE are somewhat similar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Summer TA Application</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 04:59:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I submitted an application to be a TA this summer on April 5th and haven't heard anything back. Does anyone know how long it takes them to give a decision?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 22:34:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>CS?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-13 09:10:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah. I think if they tried to impose a credit limit on SEAS, there'd be a literal revolt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Brutal</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 19:45:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Origami torus (555 pieces of paper)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-21 06:18:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sierpinski's Hexagon</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 04:09:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Phizz Torus (555 units)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 04:51:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 05:34:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Take 1007 for sure. It's honors intro to programming (but it's not an intro i promise). I was in the exact same position as you last year and I went to the first 1007 lecture and really loved it. I honestly learned a ton and feel a lot more prepared for every future CS class.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-01 05:42:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup, about 17 hours. Did it over a period of a week or so, though, so it wasn't so bad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-01 05:44:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's a combination of hexagons, pentagons, and heptagons! the hexagons provide neutral curvature (i.e. can lie on a flat plane), the pentagons curve inwards (so they are present on the outer edge of the torus), and the heptagons curve inwards, so they are on the inner edge of the torus.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"The best thing about a Boolean is that even if you are wrong, you're only off by a bit."</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 03:31:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 05:26:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol @ oracle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 02:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Poplulation" hehe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>why are people so mean</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 23:38:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 17:31:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>wager</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 18:44:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>wager</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-05 06:18:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>pretty mediocre. elite Ivy League institution with renowned professors, state of the art lab facilities. meh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-05 06:46:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>k fair</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 10:01:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a nice wholesome TIL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 08:15:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tessellations!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Every programming assignment ever</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 05:12:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dammit Linda</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 04:27:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 05:49:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Fuck Java" also fits the criteria</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 06:42:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Slurping</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 09:01:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>The most disturbing thing about this video is how much pollution is being produced by that truck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 23:06:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>knowing how to spell their name correctly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to give your students a heart attack</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 08:14:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I made some intersecting cubes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 10:18:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 19:18:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was the plan but then I ran out of paper haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 12:03:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I currently go to Columbia and tbh I feel like you should #8217;ve submitted this with your application</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 11:41:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn #8217;t get a Columbia, Cornell or Yale interview and I got into all 3 of those schools. Another kid from my high school who lived about 10 minutes away got interviews to all of them. Don #8217;t sweat it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 10:34:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brush your teeth in the shower! Saves so much time and water</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 05:46:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Psych!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 06:38:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>SEAS CS major here. Currently in 2 actual CS classes, one math class required for the major, one CS class in a different department, and one fun class (psych)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The neglected constant</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 10:55:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 06:21:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah. depending on the credits you have it might be a little difficult, but there #8217;s nothing preventing you from doing so</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 07:26:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>SPONGE LADY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>CS PhD as columbia undergrad</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 04:30:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a current Columbia undergrad studying CS. I'm interested in getting a PhD at Columbia. How much easier (if at all) is it to get into their CS PhD program as a columbia undergrad? any advice?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 15:38:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that the ivies especially seem to arbitrarily value random things. For example, I was a prospective CS major applying to Columbia #8217;s engineering school. I had really strong math and science test scores, showed demonstrated interest in engineering/computer science through my ECs, etc. When I got accepted to Columbia, my admissions officer wrote a letter and included what she thought made me stand out/why I was accepted. You know what she said? It was because I took Latin in high school and had some peripheral involvement in our school #8217;s Latin club. That was why I got in. I didn #8217;t even like Latin that much lol. Had I been the exact same applicant but without that particular EC I probably wouldn #8217;t have gotten into Columbia.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Harvard admissions consistently rated Asian Americans lower on personal traits</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 17:14:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://mobile.nytimes.com/2018/06/15/us/harvard-asian-enrollment-applicants.html?smid=fb-nytimes amp;smtyp=cur</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 21:20:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>no. One key difference: decreasing the number of Asian acceptances is \*increasing\* the number of white acceptances. If it were truly affirmative action, decreasing the number of asian american acceptances would allow more underrepresented minorities to be admitted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 15:44:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would always smell the bacon through my window in the morning. Tbh I really liked it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>But I just wanted a piggy back ride!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 20:17:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Solarized dark syntax highlighting not happening</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 04:34:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is probably a very dumb question but I've noticed that the syntax highlighting for solarized dark isn't showing up when I'm in vim. The weird thing is when I SSH into my college server and open any file, the solarized highlighting is there. Presumably, there's something in my vimrc that's disabling it. I'm using a combo of themes and fonts from [here](https://gist.github.com/kevin-smets/8568070). I've looked extensively in my vimrc for anything that could be preventing the proper colors from showing up but I can't find anything. Anyone have any advice? I've attached 2 photos below-- one without the highlighting and one with the highlighting which shows up when I ssh. https://i.redd.it/aa61bqrhnm911.png https://i.redd.it/bn1ruirhnm911.png</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Got hit by a car on my bike</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 05:34:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was biking in NYC today and I got hit by a car turning into the bike path. I had a green light and the right of way and the driver immediately admitted fault. I'm not super injured but I do have some pretty bad back pain and some nasty bruises on my leg. My bike also got pretty damaged in the incident (likely 100-200$ worth). I didn't get any of the driver's contact info or license plate number, but I'm pretty sure there were surveillance cameras at the intersection. Would it be worth it for me to open a police investigation and try to get the guy to pay for my bike repairs or any medical costs? I'm not sure if I forgave my right to this when I told him I was okay and that he didn't need to stay. There were also plenty of witnesses at the scene who would probably attest to him being at fault. I know this probably doesn't seem worth a couple hundred dollars of damage but I'm a broke college student and really can't afford for something like this to happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do apps change without me updating them?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 05:13:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Today I opened the Facebook app and noticed that there were a lot of new UI changes (i.e. all the icons on the bottom are different). I haven't updated the app for a couple weeks so I'm wondering how facebook was able to push this change on my phone without asking me for permission. What's the point of having users update their apps when developers could just magically push all their changes?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wait for it...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 07:31:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not quite what I was looking for...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 07:32:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 07:34:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>TAKE 1007!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Good job buddy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 08:18:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 07:14:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s a super interesting class that teaches concepts you can #8217;t really learn in other classes (high level design principles, GUIs, etc.). That being said, you need to have prior programming experience to take it (I.e a 4 or 5 on APCS). I might be biased because I #8217;m a TA but  #175;\_( #12484;)_/ #175;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>