<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject8721</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-16 20:28:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, yea makes total sense...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-16 20:56:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I totally agree. The DZ gives me a thrill like no other game I've played. It's a love/hate relationship. To be candid, that fine line between friendly and foe is what keeps the DZ fresh for me. Just wish the trash talk wasn't this bad. It's worse than COD and I left COD for that reason.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-16 20:57:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same here. The only reason I go rogue is by pure accident. Wish there was a flag for accidental rogue instead of displaying 19 secs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-16 23:08:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>And at what point did I get too serious? And why are you so butt hurt about posts you don't like that you feel the need to retort with something juvenile as "fucking retarded"?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 00:16:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no I still love this game. And I'm fully aware and accept the DZ for what it is. That's half the fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 03:18:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The perfect anthem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Devil Is In The Detail</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 15:58:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I freakin love this game simply for the fact that Massive has taken the time to make sure every detail is accounted for. It makes for a truly immersive experience. Here are a few of my faves: -Foot prints left on the snow -The barrel of the gun burning red hot after a mag dump -Snow collecting on your clothes -Graffiti art that could pass as legit in real life (finding new ones everyday) -Civilians mourning their loss -Bars and restaurants with full menus -Textures everywhere -Environment destruction -Dense fog -And of course dogs pooping in the street ***Looks like a lot of agents are equally observant. Awesome to see that their hard work wasn't put to waste.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 16:21:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>That makes total sense. Some amazing graffiti art.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 16:36:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea man that would be great. I'm very curious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 17:21:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit no!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 17:21:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's all about the driver.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 17:22:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have not noticed that. That's pretty cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 17:22:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would totally rock a Heavy Cleaner outfit with my Firecrest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 17:23:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep! Also tires popping and flattening.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 17:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's absolutely awesome man. Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 17:58:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also shot a fish tank and the water spilled out onto the carpet and it was soaked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 18:02:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also the soundtrack is excellent. It def helps set the mood and tone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 18:06:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ever wonder if the animals are infected as well? I mean the birds are literally flying in and out of the DZ!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 18:47:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something bit me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 18:49:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea you're right. BL2 will always hold a special place in my heart.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 19:28:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea dude. I try to enter some of those buildings but I guess not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 20:07:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha. That's good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 21:26:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I couldn't of said it better myself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 21:26:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd muck around in the UG for that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 22:38:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm gonna have to try this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-19 00:21:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh yes. That is what kept farming interesting. There were different weapon types and different manufacturers. You want a pistol that shoots explosives rounds? Go Torgue. You want a rocket launcher that obliterates everything within 3 miles? Go Maliwan!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-19 00:22:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wtf?! I've never noticed that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-19 05:24:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I understand real life firearms. I own several but the fact that in this game it glows is what I was referring to in the "details of the game."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-19 13:23:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn this is what I'm talking about!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Songs Coming From The Radios</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 20:04:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know if this has already been asked but does anybody know if the songs coming from the radios in the different house districts are original songs by real artists or original songs created by massive?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 14:02:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then would the group's turrets and mines hurt friendlies as well? I like the OP suggestion. Slow down strafing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-31 01:41:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>She draws a flower to draw males to her flower!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-01 20:39:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea...internet is a helluva drug...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-01 20:41:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>But I enjoyed your commentary.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 23:31:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Remember. Dicks are always bigger on the internet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 17:46:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn dude. That's solid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 17:49:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea I watched his vid too. And I totally agree with him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 18:51:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>He stated why he doesn't PVP. And made a series to make it better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 18:54:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand what you're saying but you're only used to reloading while sprinting cause that was originally implemented from the beginning. Like many other things, Massive has changed the original content to suit their needs. He makes a compelling argument that other shooters don't allow reloading while sprinting because it promotes tactical play and not just convulsing around between mags.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 20:18:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Marco is an excellent gamer but he's more of a PVPer and from watching him I feel that he is biased to the skills he has and the DZ. He likes to theory and build and his research is amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 21:17:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is like...the best idea I've ever heard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 21:33:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>100%. He's a smart dude and used the broken mechanics in the game to his advantage. And who can blame him? But he does realize that the broken aspects need to be fixed so I tip my hat to him for that. That being said, I don't think Marco would enjoy the DZ as much if these things were fixed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:03:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea, you caught me. I'm Skill-Up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:05:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Intelligent discussions and debates don't happen anymore. They turn to verbal warfare and devolve to childish banter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:14:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh to be young and fruitful. I admire your tenacity and attitude. Good for you. I hope you keep loving this game just as much as I do. I miss the beginning...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:41:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the most asinine comment yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:45:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's interesting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:52:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>He lists the games he played PVP on and pointed out what makes them different and what works. Yes, the DZ is unique. Yes, there's not another game out there like the DZ. Yes, he rarely plays the Dz. He doesn't like going into the DZ because of what he thinks is wrong with it. It's his opinion and I agree with a lot of it. I've played the games he's mentioned too and it's fair and balanced. So therefore am I also someone that doesn't get the DZ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:59:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm gonna give a basketball analogy. The great players never become great coaches. It's usually the ones that weren't good enough and sat on the bench and absorbed the game and broke down the schemes and gained the knowledge that turn out to be amazing coaches. Skill-Up isn't the best and he acknowledges that in his commentaries. However, it doesn't take the best player to understand how and what works.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-04 01:34:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone just learned to read!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-04 01:48:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excellent reply Skill-Up. One of the reasons I'm subscribed to you is not only the content you bring but the manner in which you bring it. Supplying information and education without sounding pretentious but respectful on a consistent basis is difficult; especially when the voices on the internet can be harsh and idiotic. Please do continue to be a positive force.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-04 02:57:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's like...you're opinion, man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-04 04:25:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry but how is that selfish? Also, where did you get your sociolinguistics degree?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-09 17:47:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bahahahahahaha!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-11 20:29:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Butthurt City?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 16:38:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a necessary good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 15:57:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>He ganked him?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 16:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is simply a case of getting what he deserved.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 17:46:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>It doesn't matter if on PC, console or a Walmart parking lot; he dished it and then got served a nice big plate of "lulz".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 18:35:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>The dude got killed. Whether or not it's on PC is irrelevant. There are proper players on all platforms.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 18:50:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm telling you it's irrelevant because depending on the platform the gameplay dictates the outcome. PC players have more control therefore the aiming is faster and more accurate while on consoles it's more difficult. It would be like a comparing a minor league team to a major league. Same game but different skill level. My point is that you're playing against the competition that's afforded to you. And again, what does this have to do with OP?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 18:56:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude just enjoy the vid. He survived. It's hilarious. It doesn't always have to be about skill.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 19:13:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 00:12:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Edit: damage would obviously be determined by the gun but increase stagger and decrease movement by caliber. From pistols dealing less stagger to shotguns dealing the most while not in cover.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 00:24:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now I have to cosplay a support station...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 00:37:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 18:12:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>WHERE ARE THE FUCKING FURRY CATS?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 18:14:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Positive, Ramos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-19 18:15:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>This has happened to me many times. While engaging in a PVP I start shooting knowing my health is gonna go down so I wait a split second till the last segment to pop my medkit. I know I hit the damn medkit and booster but died anyway. Only to see the green splash from my booster floating above my cold dead body.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 06:39:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>1239.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 06:41:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I am whining. No, I will not join them. Why? Cause I'm not a sheep. The problem is this is not what Massive intended the DZ to be. It's all about damage control at this point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 06:43:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>1239 hours.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 06:44:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 13:35:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I won't be either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 13:47:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hear what you are saying. Maybe it's all in the manner of how the damage is proc'ed. With Nimble I have to first get to cover (which means I'm still for a second) then identify another source of cover then perform the move. Once I get to the destination (which I'm vulnerable again cause I'm standing still) then I have to identify the agent and start shooting within the 5 second period. I'm playing on XBone with a controller and it takes a lot of practice to execute this properly consistently. I do feel like I'm using this as intended. On the other hand, hitting a button to proc competent/adept then switching weapons is a lot faster and efficient. Also, the talent lasts for 10 seconds. This is an exploit in my opinion. It doesn't really matter I guess. My choice to play this game "exploiting" other mechanics.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 13:49:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>This game will never be "fixed".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 13:49:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't get ganked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 13:52:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do have a DE set and I've played around with it. It's quite fun and different indeed. However, yet again, I wish they would change who got the kill by the person who put them in the downed state rather than the final blow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 13:53:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>He did kill me. It just took him a little longer than he expected. Which isn't any longer without Nimble.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 13:55:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree it could be the lag. But I never got folded this fast ever in the DZ. This is no exaggeration. From full health to dead in less than a second. From medkit plus booster to dead in a second. What?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 14:15:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please explain what it could be then.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 14:16:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you have a source?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 15:00:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a combination of things. 1) There isn't another game out on the market right now that interests me 2) Most of the friends online play TD 3) I have invested too much time and want to see it through to the end 4) I truly love this game. The attention to detail and the unique experience is addictive. Even though it is rotten at its core, TD keeps providing entertainment for me with all it's flaws.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 15:59:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea dude seriously. I don't understand how they don't see how certain weapons and skills and talents will affect the game pre-release. Shit, look at the recent PTS.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 18:21:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 18:26:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, then what is killing me so fast? If it isn't the shotgun talents then what's obliterating me? How much more armor and health must I stack? I already have 480,000 stamina with 55.8 armor. Exactly how do I combat this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 18:57:52</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128554;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 02:56:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish I had your virtue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 06:28:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look kids! Big Ben!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-24 06:25:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Clap. Clap. Clap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Division...the little scratch on the roof of your mouth that would heal if only you could stop tonguing it, but you can't.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 21:59:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>About three weeks ago I posted a goodbye message. It got deleted for obvious reasons. But here I am again. I put down the controller for a whole week and yet the entire time I had to find excuses not to play. With all the bugs, exploits, and no "new" content in the future coming I still absolutely love this game. The allure of TD is unshakable. Why can't I quit you?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 22:01:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anybody willing to show me how to complete Stolen Signal? I haven't attempted it yet. The group I run with has all pretty much given up. XBONE: fancylove.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 22:18:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. It's satisfyingly frustrating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 22:44:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or you stay with her cause she gave you the claps and might as well see what she gives you next.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 22:48:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn dude. That's one cold bitch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 00:01:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Screw you...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 03:59:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You sir get all the points for getting the reference!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 06:01:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 06:03:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Division is life!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 06:15:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I totally agree with you. I've logged three times as many hours as you. Even though this game will frustrate me to no end I just drown in the beauty of this engine. This game will always be a disappoint for me cause the potential is there and if they could have fixed all the issues before 1.3 the player base would be thriving right now. Either way, I'm still sticking with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 06:24:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>But the bugs! Don't you miss the bugs?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 06:43:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know about that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 16:54:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea I remember when entering UVHM it was a pain to take down NPCs; especially when they brought in OP levels. However, in TD the scaling used to be terrible pre-1.4 but acquiring gear and killing enemies is a lot easier now. I'd get to WT5 and not worry too much about solo difficulty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So, this is how lady bugs do the dirty...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 21:40:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 16:24:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Upvote for being topical and sexual innuendo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 02:30:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>This should help. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 18:05:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seriously. I grew up watching MJ. I was such a fanatic that I owned his clothes, cologne, signed piece of crap plate my parents bought for me from QVC. But still no Jordan shoes....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-15 15:48:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's right!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-15 15:49:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe it was the alcohol inspiring me but this looked like a giant vagina from the side.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-15 16:28:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Update soon...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My Gma's Cat. 1 Year Old. Her name is Yepunah. (Pretty One in Korean)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 22:59:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-17 04:21:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel bad for Maru. Boxes are like it's thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 17:54:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>One year later. Her eyes still hypnotize me.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 18:37:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 18:39:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 19:17:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I also love the moment when he just gave up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-22 13:58:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahahahahaha! Her reaction went from SHOCK to AWE in like .25 seconds!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-22 14:06:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>"If a rat were to walk in here right now, as I'm talking, would you greet it with a saucer of your delicious avocado?" Yes, yes I would.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-22 18:13:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well said.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 19:57:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>People like Paltrow and McCarthy are a cancer to our modern society. Shame on them for using their notoriety to promote bs holistic "medication" to "cure" problems that people don't have. The real shame is that they feel empowered and viewed as a deity instead of a celebrity endorsing crap to enhance their image.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Y U WAKE ME</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-26 23:13:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Y U WAKE ME</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-26 23:41:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>He's the hero Gotham deserves, but not the one it needs right now.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-26 23:54:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Being A Cat Is Hard Work</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-27 15:21:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-29 19:15:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I did. I made sure to be as detailed as possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-29 19:22:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. It would alleviate the frustration of sifting through loadouts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-29 20:09:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shia LaBeouf</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-29 22:31:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be interesting. Don't know if Massive would go for this though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Chuck Norris is a true badass</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 14:07:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 20:14:32</DATE>
    <TEXT> #129297; #129297; #129297;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Owner said stay, so he stayed</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 21:44:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #128514;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 02:41:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 18:19:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel reborn again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My Mother's Gardening Buddy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 15:17:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yepunah is very tired</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 15:36:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 15:50:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dallas respresent!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>James Bond should be dead by now. If not from bullets and knives then at least from an STD. He has slept with so many women!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 18:26:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 19:18:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is interesting. I never thought about that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 04:17:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't. Stop. Watching. Jason Bateman continues to impress. Also, really cool foreshadowing with the opening "O" in every episode. It keeps you looking out for the clues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 01:10:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right after a cold open, the letter "O" appears for Ozark. Then a cross hair appears in the center of the "O". Each quadrant has a symbol. Each symbol represents key turning points or symbolisms for the plot in the episode.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"O" is for Ozark and Oh My...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 15:45:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>10 hours. That's how long I sat in front of my television watching Ozark. Rarely do I shoo away friends and being social for a tv show but I could not get my butt off my couch for 10 hours straight. I admire the quality that Netflix brings to the living rooms with Ozark. The only reason I gave this show a chance was for Jason Bateman. Loved him in AD and every comedic role he filled in movies but I didn't know he could tap into a dramatic role and pull it off with such ease. Ozark brings the heightened tension and plausible scenarios with such unsavory characters that I've missed since Breaking Bad. But dare I say I think I'm enjoying Ozark more than BB! And Laura Linney is a delight! EDIT: Also the "O" after the cold starts for every episode reveals four symbols that foreshadow what happens in that episode. Really cool idea. It keeps you engaged to figure it out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 16:08:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know right! The writing and acting is excellent. And the pace is just perfect. There's never a lull in the story and they sprinkle the right amount of tension.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 16:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely. I didn't see the trailer either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 16:14:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm gonna have to check it out now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 16:18:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm on pins and needles. The season ender was a shocker.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 16:26:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's unfortunate. Episode 8 where it showed how they ended working for the cartel is one of my favorite episodes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 16:37:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>You won't be disappointed. Also no Skylar so...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 16:37:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well...he did make a huge mistake...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 16:39:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I totally agree. This show could have been on HBO.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 16:46:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>She does sell her character quite well. I hope to see more of her in the next season.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 16:52:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha. I understand your sentiment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 16:57:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I recommend giving it a chance. If you can.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 17:00:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 17:26:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mmmmmmm...that's a good question. The show deals with a family with two children and how it affects them, I think some of the violence and adult content is graphic , however, this depends on your parental guidance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 17:29:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha. I know. I keep waiting for Michael to lift the dinner table center piece to reveal small boxes of cereal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 17:30:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it hasn't clicked for you yet then I doubt that it will for you going forward. But! Hopefully you prove me wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 17:31:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh...they know how to mess things up too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 17:32:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>He also directed a few episodes. He really surprised me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 17:38:03</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128542;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 17:55:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shhhhh!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 18:05:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hear Narco is excellent. That's my next show. Starting tonite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 18:06:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea, I haven't watched "cord" tv in like four years. I have no desire to give them my money.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 18:16:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>The similarities to BB are apparent and it's fair to say that it tries to be BB. However, after the pilot you will see the difference. To me, BB had this long story arc about White and his battle with cancer and the cartel and teased you from time to time with the future and the background with small samples. The fear and terror from the cartel didn't really kick in till the later seasons. Here in Ozark, the terror begins from chapter one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 18:17:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great points.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 18:23:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's so much going on here...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 18:28:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha. I don't mind subtitles. Actually, when a show or movie is really good I'll rewatch them with the subtitles on. Sometimes there's some text that I miss the first go around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 18:29:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do it now!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 18:30:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh! Do you cringe at the characters?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 18:35:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand the pain...all too well...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 18:56:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Give it a chance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 18:59:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Everything they do is so dramatic and flamboyant. It makes me want to set myself on fire!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 19:11:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you find the show is accurate to the Ozarks?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 19:14:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did not expect it either. A great season ender.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 19:17:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the what?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 19:30:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>That whole episode is from the past. If I remember correctly those were two separate gold games. And the mom part is also before he met the other FBI agent. In which is heavily implied that they were a couple.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 19:49:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I believe so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 21:09:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is but ya not abundant and obscene. The only nudity is in the strip club. And that's rare.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 21:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh shit! Is Jason pretty chill or is he stuck up?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 21:31:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wanna say episode 2 or 3.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 21:41:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like this guy even more now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 22:16:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea you're right. Anytime someone attempts a non-linear plot they're obviously copying Pulp Fiction.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 22:49:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was looking for this! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 02:26:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 02:31:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmmm I'm gonna have to recheck that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 04:17:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea man I just found that out. That is just so cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 04:19:25</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128513;we have another addict.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 05:06:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 05:06:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>You won't be disappointed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 13:32:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bahahahaha. *SLAP!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 13:37:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh really?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 14:08:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>You imply this is astroturfing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 14:50:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol. I wanna party with that dude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ELI5: Why do Chuck Taylor's cost so much when the materials and craftsmanship seem not as comparable as other "sports" brands?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 14:54:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 14:59:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, to be candid, I do feel special when I put on a fresh pair of Chuck's but it's getting harder to justify shilling out $70 for some canvas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 15:08:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you carrying the wheel?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 15:08:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Economics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 15:19:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're incredulous.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 15:37:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>After reading some of the replies I want to visit as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 16:32:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea my tv is still intact.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 17:02:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god. That kind of time has expired for me. I'd prob be the dude at the bar riffing about how my mother's' rape horn pisses off the next door neighbors.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 18:09:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow. I don't know where you live but here in the DFDub the cheapest I've seen is at least twice the price and with a BOGO half off sale.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 18:10:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work for Netflix. Drama Marketing division. As you can tell, we need all the help we can get.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 18:31:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 14:40:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol. Glad you enjoyed it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 21:14:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apparently you do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 21:16:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are one charming fellow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 13:27:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm gonna say that it was dragged out for dramatic purposes. Him being a man of god, then his faith being shaken, it is the perfect opportunity for character speculation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 04:04:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hooray!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 04:05:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't wait.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 14:05:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think he was paying back with his money. EDIT: I could be wrong though. I'm prob wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 16:40:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>To this day, Contact is still one of the most influential films I have ever seen. The direction was clear, the acting superb and the soundtrack is just damn beautiful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The older I get the more I'm careful about what goes in my mouth cause I'm worried about how it will come out the other end at the most inappropriate time.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 13:36:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 14:13:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my god. The last time I went on a mountain hike I took a double dose of Imodium AD just to make sure I won't have to poop in the woods next to bears. Worst mistake of my life. I was already dehydrated and had been munching on fiber rich bars and beef jerky. I didn't poop for four days. The drive back home my buddies wanted to have a nice meal. We stopped at a steak house. I knew I'd be in trouble so I tried to let out my contents. I sat on that toilet for twenty minutes. I pushed and pushed but nothing would come out until it finally happened. The only way I can describe the scene is like when you open a champagne bottle and the cork fiercely explodes out with strict determination. The best poop of my life...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 16:46:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. Don't forget the churros.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 16:48:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>You white, you're Gary Oldman.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A female's physical attractiveness isn't judged by men's gawking but rather by other female's scrutiny.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 16:04:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 18:51:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been on for about two months now. I had never heard the term "ghosting" until recently. Is this a frequent thing? I was talking to this profile and I thought we were doing fine then one day nothing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Interesting theory on how contemporary popular music is crafted.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 18:58:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 21:39:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! As a music theorist, this made my brain wet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If I weren't so tired I'd...mess you...up right no...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-25 22:12:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We did it America. We have cured bloating of the face.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 15:01:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Visited Ar-Ken-Saw for the first time.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 14:59:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Work Downtime. Suggestions for characters welcomed!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 01:14:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 01:36:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You got it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 05:48:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks mate!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 15:18:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>God bless America.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 20:33:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jack would be proud.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 20:38:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>So how does this work? I bought BL2 last week and already have two game saves. If I install from HB, does that erase my saves?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 13:33:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spoiler alert: you're a bitch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 17:55:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>The first play through was awesome. The second not too bad. Then you realize certain gear takes too much effort to acquire. Not in terms of farming bosses but length of time just to get to the destination. Also, not enough unique side missions to help level your character(s). That being said, I enjoyed all the characters and their builds. I plan on repurchasing on steam to play again. I had all the characters max level on Xbox but oh well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Work Downtime Updated</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 19:18:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 04:24:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! Any suggestions?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Work Downtime Updated 9/14</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 20:21:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Oh it's good to be back at my old college bar</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 04:21:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 16:38:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are viruses a common thing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 16:41:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excellent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 16:43:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been an iOS user since inception. After the latest Apple reveal I'm thinking of switching. This is very helpful. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 16:51:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Several safe stores? Please explain.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 16:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm debating between the V30, S8 and the upcoming Pixel. What do you think?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 16:59:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did not know that. Aright sounds good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 17:03:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Solid. Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 17:40:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about the OS itself? The argument for different hardware is a matter of taste. Is there anything buggy or just plain ugly that you don't like?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 17:58:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's good to know. The one thing that is really steering me from switching is iMessage. I've heard of Google Hangout but are there other options for messaging and sending video uncompressed?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 18:17:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahhhh ok. Well thanks dude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 19:15:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Raider Tomb starring the girl from a familiar movie poster.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 22:09:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>The end game is definitely the best part of this game. That's where your build really starts to shine. The only thing that sucks about the end game towards lvl 73 and up is the gear tends to become more selective. Most don't balance well and are forced to use specific items.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 15:08:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not discouraged. Just more difficult I guess. EDIT: not difficult. Just requires too much effort.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 22:58:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>He really knew how to set up his teammates.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Great, kid. Don't get cocky.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 14:34:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I will be opening up a burger joint here soon. Thinking about calling it Seymour Buns. Reddit, what do you think!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 17:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most of my friends think it's fun and light but the females say it sounds gross. Like a crappy cheap greasy spoon. The vibe will be more In-N-Out and less Shake Shack. Everything will be made from scratch. This will also be located in DFW, if that makes a difference. Comments, critiques, criticisms?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 17:59:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>If Matt let's me...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 17:59:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sweet!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 18:00:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn it...so assless chaps won't work...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 18:02:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Especially the sourdough. Love me some sourdough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 18:25:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my god. I'm a cheeseburger purest with the potato bun but that tang from sourdough just works with the fatty beef!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 19:03:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 19:03:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>You found the mascot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 19:04:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excellent ideas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 19:04:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have a fan here!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 19:20:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>This. This is the kind of response I was looking for.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 20:00:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>You just gave my heart a hard on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 20:02:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you a Dallasite?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 22:44:22</DATE>
    <TEXT> #129299; Pretty please!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 22:45:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh yea. The glazed donuts for sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 22:45:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 23:30:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's great advice! Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 23:57:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well this is an invite in advance Reddit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 00:49:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck?! This is brilliant!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 03:17:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>You just might have given birth to the slogan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 03:19:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh I have plans for pun burgers. The trick will be to not come off as aping Bob's. But he had such good burgers...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 03:20:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 04:36:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's in the works still. Negotiating location.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 04:38:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea it will be located in DFW somewhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 17:04:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>True. My second option was Captain Beef Curtain Burger. I don't think that'll fly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 13:54:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty mild. Considering I've hit my lil sis in the face with a golf club. Multiple times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The zombie apocalypse has started, what is the first non-weapon thing you grab?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 15:45:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 16:41:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Indeed. Good call.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 16:41:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awwww</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 16:43:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gotta keep the chaffing at bay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 16:55:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've got one bob and another on the way. Complete with medical essentials, water tabs, fire starters. Got another bag for my 10/22 and plenty of ammo to last a few months.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 17:04:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol. In all seriousness, it's kind of overkill...until it happens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 17:06:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know man, I'm kinda hoping for one to happen. Like having car insurance, what's the point if you don't use it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Redditors with last names that are also popular product brands, how does it attract or repel you from using that brand and why?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 13:45:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 14:12:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Help me dispel some Windows10 vs MacOS myths</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 14:32:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been a MacOS user since 2008. My iMac has treated me well without any hiccups other than doubling up on the RAM a few years ago. Now I'm on the market for a laptop and am seriously considering switching to Windows 10. Build quality isn't a concern for me. I think now more than ever the difference between choosing one over the other is the OS experience. I've had many Windows products in the past and they all have never lasted me longer than 2-3 years. In the beginning, the experience is zippy and lag free but then overtime the sluggishness just brings frustrations. I've never had this problem with my iMac. Why is this? Or does the user require some hands-on maintenance to help lengthen the overall life expectancy of the Windows platform? Also, is malware protection still necessary? Any advice helps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 15:10:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is all good advice. I've been looking at the Surface brand lineup, leaning towards the Surface Laptop. A friend of mine just bought a XPS15 and have had some driver issues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Surface users, how has your experience been so far?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 15:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm looking to switch over from MacOS and the Surface line looks mighty intriguing. Please be brutal with your honesty!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 15:19:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well shit. Care to elaborate?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 15:28:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my god.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 15:52:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>How often do you reset?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 15:59:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excellent. This makes me feel more confident.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 17:09:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is exactly what I wanted to hear. Finally something positive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 17:11:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>In your experience, are hardware issues a rarity?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 18:00:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>What kind of complaints on Windows do you speak of?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 18:04:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think I'd mind 10S. I won't be downloading too many apps and from what I can tell the Store has all the options I need.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 18:05:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you mind sharing your specs? I'll be doing some video and photo editing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 18:16:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 18:17:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is excellent stuff. Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 18:52:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well said. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 20:52:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was a perfect response.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 00:49:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the reply. Do you find the Surface lineup to be on the well-built side?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 02:22:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>What kind of programs are you running? Has the performance been pretty good?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 13:17:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>The i5/ 8GB/ 256GB version seems to be the sweet spot. I haven't heard of the yellowing screen phenomenon though. I'll be doing mostly some photo editing and light video editing but nothing intensive like 4K. Do you think the specs would suffice?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 13:46:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice! And what kind of work do you do on the laptop?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 13:52:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>From what I understand the internal fan rarely kicks in. And even if it does it is super quite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 13:56:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's good to know. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How important is read/write speed?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 14:34:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm about to pull the trigger on the Surface Laptop (yes, I understand, for the money, I can get something better). From the reviews, the Laptops SSD performance seems to be on the weak side compared to its competitors. The main tasks I'll be performing: Internet browsing Lightroom editing (Light) Premiere editing I am in no way tech savvy (obviously) and have posted previously before on this sub and I feel the honest opinions from this community are the best opinions. Any input is welcome. Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 15:27:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the input.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 17:03:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That i7 with 8G of ram is $1600... #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Apparently, it's illegal to take a photo of the Eiffel Tower at night</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 01:06:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 04:56:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're a loner Dottie, a rebel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Adobe Premiere</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 18:16:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm thinking about purchasing a 2017 MacBook Pro 13 inch with 128G SSD and 8G RAM. Will this be enough RAM to do some light editing in Premiere? Or do I really need to stop up to $2k+ and get 16G? Any advice will help. Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 22:11:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excellent. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 20:23:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Borderlands 2. Played it on Xbox 360, Xbox one and now my Mac. Have multiple toons with mules on all platforms...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What common phrases or expressions do you hate the most?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 14:24:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 14:28:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bahahahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 14:28:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Totally.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 14:39:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can agree.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 15:01:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's me everytime I go out to the bar with friends and look at the tab.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 15:48:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea. Like that's exactly what I want to hear at that moment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 13:32:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mostly played Zero but I have significant hours on all the characters. Lately, my fave has been Maya and Krieg.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Leave no plastic behind</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 13:41:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 18:33:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Keeping all options open.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 21:28:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m assuming by  #8220;eliminate #8221; roll the plastic into a ball and shove it up your hole as a cork?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 21:28:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hell yea! I love this company.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 13:55:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 17:56:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>In terms of character back stories: it dives deep into Handsome Jack and Claptrap mostly. It also shouldn #8217;t hinder you from Tales. The gameplay I feel is superior to BL1/2 with the zero gravity mechanic, ground stomps and freezing debuffs. But replayability lacks considerably compared to BL1 and definitely BL2. Some bosses are not refarmable and the gear are mostly rehashed and renamed from BL2. However, if you enjoy BL2 then the Presequel is worth a shot. Every character is awesome to play to almost max LVL and you #8217;ll end up wishing that a couple shows up in future iterations. Happy looting! Edit: I freakin love Athena and her skill trees. I wish I could play her on BL2.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 18:01:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. The only replayability is trying to max out the characters along with specific COMs. The gear doesn #8217;t really matter in this game much in which kinda goes against what BL is but builds are where it #8217;s at.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 18:02:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damnit, now I #8217;ve got the itch, I guess I #8217;ll buy this game again now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 18:04:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like Athena for her elemental prowess. She #8217;s all about maintains stacks and using her shield to your advantage. Claptrap is fun but also kinda RNG depending on his abilities. He is def OP though. To be candid, I would start with Athena but you #8217;re gonna end up playing all the characters. Trust me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 18:08:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol. Yea me too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 23:25:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fracture?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 16:51:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>HAM</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 16:53:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>12 Years A Slave</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 14:39:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I went to college in Denton, known locally as  #8220;Little D #8221;, baby brother to Dallas  #8220;Big D #8221;. The motto followed me still after high school...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 14:42:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Touch #233;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 14:57:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aveda.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 20:42:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will this be PTAs first Oscar glory?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Saw this in an East Texas men #8217;s restroom</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 20:49:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 21:40:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was in a local diner right outside of a wildlife management area. I was the only Asian at this restaurant. Pretty sure I was the only Asian in the entire county. I felt like an animal in a zoo...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 14:17:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>2001: A Cat Odyssey</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 17:49:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t know what you #8217;re talking about, HAL.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 20:48:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry, Dave. I'm afraid I can't do that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 02:45:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is why I love Reddit too. It #8217;s something to live for.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My gma #8217;s kitty has an eclectic palate and she insists on the right flavor combination.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 13:37:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 14:01:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s both of their best qualities.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>That time Bear was totally sane</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 15:27:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 16:07:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh sorry. I forgot to tag it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 16:13:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re absolutely right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 16:46:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>In the next episode, Seal underwear.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 22:42:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve smoked for quite a while now. Quit a few years ago to try out vaping. Quite frankly, The feeling isn #8217;t the same. It #8217;s like drinking Coke Zero for the taste of Classic Coke. But just like intaking unnecessary sugar, I enjoy smoking and don #8217;t really care for the negative health impact.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>There #8217;s something unsettling about these piggies</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 18:11:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The man who invented ballpark nachos passed away Sunday. He was 84.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 18:21:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 18:26:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Refried Liberto</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 19:04:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s essentially a condiment for everything around here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 21:42:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s alright. He gave all he could before he departed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 00:14:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Neva! And the chips were so crispy and salty. The edges of my mouth were always cut by them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Look at this wall made from old bourbon barrels. And a friend who couldn #8217;t help herself.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 13:18:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 19:07:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can confirm. I sell tile. We used to carry authentic Saltillo straight from Mexico. But now they #8217;re all designer crap with even shittier quality. The prints are fake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A film about the inevitable collision of a comet to earth, Deep Impact highlights the drama and despair of humans rather than hurling spectacle and bedlam as Armageddon did the same summer of 1998.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 23:44:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 00:20:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Diane Warren wrote sweet sweet songs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 01:30:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>That does sound intriguing. If you remember make sure to post it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 14:57:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is. I had never heard of everclear until college. A buddy gave me a flaming shot of everclear. I was about to blow out the flame when it tipped over my hand. In a matter of seconds, a gigantic bubble formed on my skin. I don #8217;t recommend taking shots of everclear, flaming or not. I also don #8217;t recommend being friends with people who drink everclear.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 15:09:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesse Eisenberg has really nailed this part.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 00:08:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sherpas get no love...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 03:01:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s some great insight. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 04:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>The first and last mountain I climbed was Long #8217;s Peak. I don #8217;t even know if you consider that a climb. More of a difficult hike. I wasn #8217;t acclimated to the altitude and definitely wasn #8217;t in Colorado shape to do it. Took us 14 hours to go up to the peak and down. I had bruises all over my legs. The single best and worst experience of my life. I want to do it again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 12:15:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You win.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 12:25:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m really into Meateater. Some of the situations Rinella gets into is incredible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What does it take to be a Blue Planet II cameraman?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 13:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 16:17:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really? Damn dude, this vid just made me want to do it even more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 16:31:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh it was thick. Too thick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 16:48:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>And yes, he keeps saying clip. I #8217;m sure he meant magazine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 20:59:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try Legend Sniper COM.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 13:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which one will be the Judas Mouse?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The camera is acting funny</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 15:54:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 17:41:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure. Just decided to get jiggy wit it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 19:53:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have that exact same laptop. It takes thirty mins to open up Excel. Passing out saves time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 20:31:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that #8217;s exactly what it is. When you first turn on the camera you can hear the IS and then eventually settles down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SKILL</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 05:42:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>That time the DeVry University basketball team scored 141 points...and lost</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 01:32:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 14:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I laughed so hard from this comment my phone is covered in saliva.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 16:50:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>All true. This will be for my friend #8217;s kids. We #8217;re avid gun enthusiasts so I #8217;m sure his kids are well aware of the dangers of irresponsible gun ownership and handling. But then again, Nerf guns are fun and a good primer for gun etiquette.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 16:51:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah yes. I ordered two guns and two face masks. Just to make them understand that even with styrofoam bullets protection is important.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 16:51:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perfect math.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 16:52:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>These will be for girls!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 02:40:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn that #8217;s a crazy life story. But I guess he made his point in the end.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 15:25:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Melee Zero mobbing is pure joy. Especially if you can chain multiple kills. You #8217;re basically in Deception foeva!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Queso and chips at Chipotle</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 22:27:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dallasite here. I #8217;ve never really been a fan of Chipotle and haven #8217;t eaten there in almost a year. Then I hear about this new queso  #8220;done Chipotle way #8221; and I abstained. Until right now. First of all, this is not queso. This is a goopy puddle of cheese. I don #8217;t taste the tomatillo and it #8217;s terribly under seasoned. And! It #8217;s $3.45 just for the queso and chips! My entire meal cost $12.20 without a drink. I understand most people don #8217;t enjoy the synthetic flavor of American or Velveeta but I #8217;ve grown up on this shit my entire life. All the Tex-Mex restaurants around here have a synthetic cheese version of queso and it #8217;s freakin delicious. Without Velveeta, the melted dip is just missing something. Anybody else feel this way about Chipotle and their failed attempt at convincing me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 22:35:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven #8217;t tried Chiloso yet. I do like Freebird #8217;s queso though and Qdoba. Chuy #8217;s queso is pretty damn tasty IMHO.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 22:37:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Qdoba is great. I haven #8217;t been up north but I #8217;d imagine Tex-Mex to be quite rare.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 22:38:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>And the price!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 23:02:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Grinding for gear is gonna be somewhat rough at this stage. If you #8217;re in TVHM then I #8217;d farm Terra for Hide shield. If solo farm the Love Thumper. A Ninja COM that boosts Killing Blow and Backstab would suffice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 23:02:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn straight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 23:03:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea I don #8217;t know what the chef heads at the big Office was thinking. This is a disgrace. Sometimes you just shouldn #8217;t mess with something that #8217;s delicious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 23:05:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. I don #8217;t understand the love. I #8217;ve never came away satisfied. Just full of regret.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 23:06:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another reason for me to move to  #127464; #127462;!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 23:30:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Taco trucks are amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 23:40:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Road stayed with me for a long time. The scenario isn #8217;t new, the overall color just like the world portrayed is depressing. I agree that it #8217;s not a movie that is rewatchable probably because the main characters and the shitty situations they get into was replayed in my head for over a week. However, I will play certain scenes on my player from time to time cause it #8217;s just so damn good. Two in particular: the scene when they find the underground food supply (it brings a little light into their lives) and the  #8220;abandoned #8221; house scene where they find the human livestock (sheer terror).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 23:45:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>The audience had to of shared the sentiment with the kid. He felt safe and food was finally abundant. Why leave? Cause the adult really understands what #8217;s going on with the world.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 17:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I consider BL2 to be my most favorite game of all time. Not even close to anything else. Even nostalgia like Super Mario, Zelda, Mega Man or even Vice City don #8217;t even come close to holding a candle to BL2. When this game first came out I was hooked from the opening music sequence. This was the first game that introduced me to addiction, hoarding and research. The gameplay is unique, not because it pioneered the FPS looter shooter genre, but because with each play through with each character with different gear with different groups changes the experience everytime. The replayability is off the charts and if you get bored doing one thing you can easily do something else and it #8217;s a fresh game. BL2 will still be played ten years from now. Even when BL3 comes out, BL2 will still be either on the shelf or digital library winking at me to pick it the fuck up and play.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 20:24:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really didn #8217;t mind TPS. I enjoyed the 60+ hours I put into it. The thing that was really lacking was fresh gear. Most of the legendaries that you grinders for was rehashed from BL2 so that kinda sucked the fun out of original content.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 20:26:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love the Hornet. Just wish it came in different elements then it would be amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 19:10:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the hell is this?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 12:34:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>This GIF right here makes me go through a roller coaster of emotions everytime. Sadness, guilt, happiness and retribution all rolled into one bite-sized snack.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 13:27:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Such an inconvenience.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 12:35:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any game before the internet. Devs can rush games out now and patch it up later.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 13:01:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>The hardest heterosexuals are usually the biggest homosexuals.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Master of Excel Art</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 13:19:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 15:48:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Such great table side manners.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 15:49:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here cums the bride?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Local radio station here in Dallas plays a commercial from an insurance company with a catchy song. What are some of your city #8217;s most infectious jingles?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 16:41:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 17:10:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shop me first. Shop me last! Either way come see Clay!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 17:21:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Auto Flex Lease oh yea!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 17:46:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>This must be local. I haven #8217;t heard it here in DFDUB</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 17:51:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this a carpeting company?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Magic Of Making Sound (2017) You #8217;ll never listen to movies the same again</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 18:10:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 18:23:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>This jingle must be really catchy for this to work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 19:28:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have something similar here. It #8217;s a home lending service co and the dude has a buttery smooth baritone voice. He also ends every commercial with  #8220;bless your heart #8221;. In the south, it #8217;s not what you think it means.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 19:29:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d feel weird walking into that store and yelling  #8220;where #8217;s Wolfman?! #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 23:17:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very true. I went to sounds engineering school and can attest that you #8217;ve done a great job when people don #8217;t notice it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 18:11:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is def from the 90s. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Modular Body</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 02:55:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rhino birth. Still makes me cry watching.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 16:04:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 16:27:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>You just made my day. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 16:30:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>She #8217;s pretty fly for a white girl.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 17:17:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Open the bathroom door Hal!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 14:23:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hooman:  #8220;What #8217;s this code here ...pawing-top: 50paws;... #8221; Pupper:  #8220;Whats code? #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 19:23:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Red Text Flavor:  #8220;Blow Real Hard #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 23:46:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>How dare you talk to another girl in front of your girl! Same thing with me and my ex. Met one of my HS classmates at a grocery store. She was def the hottest in our class. Then twenty years later, she #8217;s divorced with two kids. The father I used to know too. Awkward...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 17:52:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kinda looks like Bob Belcher Ant. Edit: Bald</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 15:07:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>And it #8217;s the price he paid</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pleasantly surprised Guy Fieri is not in the news for a sex scandal</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 17:26:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 17:28:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I genuinely enjoy the dude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 17:32:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>These days an accusation is as good as a conviction.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 17:39:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea I vaguely remember that. I guess I #8217;m surprised more that droves of more accusations haven #8217;t come out recently. With all the downfall of celebrities.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Aventuras de Batman - Taco Tuesday</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 19:00:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 13:37:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m glad you noticed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 13:57:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have literally watched this back to back for the last ten minutes. I can #8217;t drink my morning coffee cause I #8217;m laughing so hard!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 14:09:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everything about the last update was great...except for PM. What were they thinking?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 20:54:43</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;I ate your mouse so you can stop chasing it #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My grandmother #8217;s cat loves to be scratched by lint rollers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 23:18:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 23:22:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea I guess roll is more appropriate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 23:25:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your precision is surgical.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 01:02:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same with her. The brush just scrapes off the hairs and flies into the air.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 04:29:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Both.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 13:26:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh yea I didn #8217;t include the 2x Tenebrae and 3x Ferro #8217;s Mask.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;m at work currently. Like most days I get my shit done early and have to figure out what to do for the next six hours. What do you do to hide in plain sight?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 19:14:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 19:17:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have to  #8220;appear #8221; that I #8217;m working.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 19:39:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea I #8217;ve tried that. Reddit mostly. I #8217;ve also recently picked up perfecting cursive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 19:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is actually something I can do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 19:47:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Genius.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 19:49:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol. I will do that sometimes. But it makes me more anxious to leave work early. Also, I drink so much coffee during the day, from sheer boredom, my mind and heart is racing with thoughts of doing shit except work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 19:55:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is just a job while I find a location for my new career: restaurant owner. Been here so long that I know more than my managers and I haven #8217;t properly trained my replacements for job security.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 19:56:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d buy you a beer if I could.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 19:57:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait. What #8217;s mudding?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 20:09:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>This looks pretty cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 20:48:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks man!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 13:48:43</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Nearly 1 in 4 homicides in Oregon involves intimate partners. #8221; Oregon is for lovers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 18:04:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The raw egg in piping hot broth is the best way to make the end product a creamy umami-bomb experience. I do this all the time including ramen. Source: I am Korean.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 19:38:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>If people didn #8217;t know better they #8217;d think we were speaking in code or something. But yes, kimchi fried rice is probably make most favorite. The caramelized crust at the bottom is one of the finest things in life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 02:18:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine would be The Professional. Directed by David Fincher. Composed by Danny Elfman.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 06:59:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have followed Skill Up since day ONE. He enticed me to buy this game and guided me to stick with it. With all the flaws and hiccups that TD has had since launch, and the countless amounts of times I quit this damn game, I agree with Skill Up and will continue to play because now The Division is complete. I truly wish this game we have today was the game at launch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 06:27:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m on XBone so I don #8217;t know how it works on other platforms, but try to matchmake and join and then leave the group.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Toys That Made Us | I laughted like a kid</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 19:17:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>If y'all haven't checked out TTTMU on Netflix you need to give it a chance. The inception of some of these toys and how they marketed it to kids is amazing. This was a hilarious peek behind the curtains and into the minds of the creators. I especially loved Episode 3: He-Man. The banter and clashes these people had can only be described as "kids in a toy store". It also shows how a toy company back in the 80's really was pulling shit out of their asses and hoping that something would stick. And the interviews given by the employees definitely proves that working for a toy company back in the day was pure joy. Also brought back some fond childhood memories.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 21:17:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I enjoyed every episode. Very entertaining doc on childhood nostalgia.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 21:19:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>At the end of the season I wished there were more episodes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 22:48:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have a point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:41:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree. I hope they cover TMNT and Legos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Italians of Reddit, movies (especially Gangster flicks like The Godfather) always show Italians eating pasta, pasta, pasta and more pasta with a loaf of bread for every meal. Now this can #8217;t be true right? What really is a typical dinner for Italians?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 17:08:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 17:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe it was the places I visited in Italy but every meal we had there consisted of pasta and some sort of bread dish with amazing cheese. I love Italy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 19:03:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not trying to sound like an ass but an honest question. Are Italians regarded as healthy and not plagued with obesity?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 01:03:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 01:14:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know I never thought about that. The other buses were probably a part of the plan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 02:07:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was a bad post. I was rewatching The Dark Knight and wrote it in haste. I was just thinking that all his movies have incredible pace and skim over some details that bother me but it #8217;s true that other movies are the same way. Nolan #8217;s writing just seems to do it more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 17:11:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re clearly a fan of convenience.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 17:15:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well...yea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 18:10:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I recommend watching MarcoStyle on YouTube. He puts out great content with stats and logic to back it up. Of course he is coming from a PC stand point but most of the things he says is fact.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 14:16:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I really needed it I couldn #8217;t get one to save my life. Now they drop for days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 05:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s a good point. Fuel to feed the fire.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Punisher [Netflix] | I am surprised</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 06:29:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right off the bat, I don't know the lore of The Punisher, I have never read a single comic book; the last anything about The Punisher that i have seen is the rendition by Thomas Jane; and I'm not the biggest fan of "superhero drama". Countless articles, threads and recommendations forced me to give this series a chance. Much reluctance was there but the one driving force that gave me hope was Jon Bernthal. I enjoyed his portrayal of Shane on The Walking Dead, and by far to this day, he is still my favorite character and Jon did not disappoint. His thespian prowess continues to impress me and I await with such giddy for the next installment of this series. The demeanor of the character, the ruthlessness of justice, the uncanny ability to draw me in to understand what exactly The Punisher stands for, has quenched my thirst for revenge. I am now a believer in the series of superheroes that can be done correctly like how "The Dark Knight" did for cinematic superheroes. I love you Jon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 06:33:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your breath smells of bok.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 06:34:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Get it checked dude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 06:39:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good luck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 06:41:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the recommendation. I #8217;ll give it a watch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #8220;Leather #8221; on car dash is plastic stitching</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 20:40:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Planet Earth II - The Scarlett Heart</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 03:54:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm late to Planet Earth II. Though I enjoyed the original PE when it came out ten years ago, I finally took the time to watch all six episodes in one sitting. Every second of this series is pure entertainment. Sir David Attenborough soothed my ears while the stunning cinematography made my eyes smile for six hours straight. The one particular scene that stood out for me was Episode Six; where they concentrated on a bowerbird in the city. According to Wikipedia: "Bowerbirds...are renowened for their unique courtship behaviour, where males build a structure and decorate it with sticks and brightly coloured objects in an attempt to attract a mate." This one bowerbird had collected strings, plastic lids, toy cars and other colorful mad-made objects to place in his collection of seduction. But it wasn't enough. He needed his pi #232;ce de r #233; #183;sis #183;tance. So, he went to one of his "neighbors" and stole a small fabric heart in bright attractive red. Surely this was gonna get the job done. He absconds with it and beds the heart in his domain. It works. Another bowerbird notices his diligence and the primal game begins. I won't spoil the rest for those who haven't had the privilege of watching PE2. All I can say is you're missing out. The BBC really knows how to package a documentary. PS, I love you Sir Attenborough...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 15:27:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>JERRY! JERRY! JERRY!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 19:21:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn #8217;t watch last years super bowl. What commercial is this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 19:59:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ummm...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 05:23:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>So close man. So close...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 05:23:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> #129310;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 05:24:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll grab a screenshot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 12:35:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>So you had a good time?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 12:37:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know...it doesn #8217;t seem right. I barely got one Hunter #8217;s Faith mask yesterday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 12:38:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry mate. That does suck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 12:39:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 12:40:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 12:40:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shit. That is disappointing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 12:41:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine was an hour earlier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 15:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last GE I was short a backpack to complete Pred. That really irritated me. Especially since I acquired like 10 Pred holsters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 19:24:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had similar luck with the exotics. Also a lot of Liberator. I don #8217;t understand why they include exotics in the RNG when they can be bought.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 19:59:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>This ambush did force me to play differently but I don #8217;t see why they would have to change anything about NPCs and their HP/Damage. By keeping the  #8220;ambush modifier #8221; it cements this game as a cover shooter. I actually enjoyed this GE more than the last one and would love for this to continue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 20:23:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I enjoyed soloing Warren because I grinded for the gear and understanding the tactics. A lot of people do solo this game. If you want higher difficulty then join a four man group in incursions and other legendary content and then test your mettle. An RPG should reward you with a gameplay that makes you feel powerful and that #8217;s enjoyable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 20:29:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re right. Keep fighting the good fight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 16:32:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol. Exactly! I think I #8217;m The Terminal. Next to the HVT vendor. But I could be wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 16:34:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I usually only pay attention to gameplay and QoL patches. Too busy grinding to care about anything in The Terminal other than the Recal and Optimization stations.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 03:23:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice setup man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 16:56:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 18:46:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agree to disagree.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Al Michaels and Cris Collinsowrth get paid to watch football and they are confused with the new catch rules.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 04:04:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 04:07:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha. Yep. I am one of them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 12:48:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn #8217;t know that was possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 18:44:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>My  #8220;R #8221;,  #8220;T #8221; and  #8220;I #8221; are never consistent in cursive. In both upper and lowercase. I #8217;d like to see some examples of how you write these words below: Error/error Transfer/transfer Idiot/idiot Any posts will help. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 19:11:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>An attempt was made.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 16:11:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wright is a gift that keeps on giving.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 22:39:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do you prefer thin cut fries or thick cut fries and from where?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:42:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:43:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does KFC #8217;s wedges count?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:45:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was a great year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:45:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. I made some double-fried extra thin fries in peanut oil over the weekend. Oh my...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:46:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this a regional thing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:46:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could never get down on sweet potatoes for some reason.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:47:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>They #8217;re pretty good fresh but gets soggy real fast. Probably cause they serve fresh cut fries.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:48:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m gonna have to make some now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:50:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aren #8217;t they called frites or something? I wanna try some one day. And yes, mayo goes great with fries.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:52:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>McD for sure still king of the spud mountain. I hear Jollibee #8217;s is amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:53:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder if a dipping sauce of salted caramel and marshmallows would compliment it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is a Zaxby #8217;s near me. I #8217;ve never been. I shall give it a try now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 18:00:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 18:01:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will always have a sweet spot in my heart for crinkle cut.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Use NPCs as your ally when extracting solo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 18:14:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I generally like to solo the DZ. I #8217;ll accept invites once I a while but the majority of the time I #8217;d rather have Netflix playing on the side and clear landmarks and farm DivTech alone. For solo players, extracting can be a giant flame to rogue moths. So, whenever possible I will use the NPCs to my advantage. Every extract point has at least two enter/exits. I #8217;ll call the extract on one far point of the zone. This will alert the NPCs to arrive. Then I will put a few rounds in the NPCs and then run under or around to the other side of the extract point and wait. If my XP meter starts going up then I can assume two things: either another faction has shown up and it #8217;s all out warfare OR other agents have shown up and are clearing out the aggroed NPCs. At this point I have two options: fight or flight. If the other agents are still distracted then I #8217;ll wait till the last 10-15 seconds, drop a shock turret and place my loot on the rope. Or you can escape and try at a different location. I #8217;m sure other agents have tried this method but for those who are new give this a shot. 60% of the time it works everytime.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 18:15:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 18:15:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>What #8217;s Freddy #8217;s?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 18:40:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perfect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 18:41:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice. I don #8217;t think there #8217;s one of those here in DFW.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 18:47:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. I #8217;ve unloaded at the 60 sec mark and that rarely ends well for me. I #8217;ve also put my loot at like 12 secs and have the rope cut with literally a millisecond to spare. But it #8217;s the DZ and it #8217;s what I love.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 19:16:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Remember the time when rope cutting wasn #8217;t a thing. That implementation just made going rogue more appealing. There #8217;s also an accommodation for rope cutting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 19:17:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely. When Striker, the more NPCs the better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 19:26:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I will say the rope cutting has one advantage. If they do cut it and they kill you it gives you an additional 150 secs to get it back from then.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 19:27:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha! I #8217;d cut rope just to get that accommodation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 19:32:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s how I got one of The House in the DZ. As soon as I saw the red spire my eyes opened wide and as I got closer to the drop I prayed and hoped for a good roll House. And I was blessed. Immediately I worked up multiple scenarios in my head of which extract point to go to. I just chose the nearest one to a safe point and used this tactic. Oddly enough it was a heavy that proc #8217;d my nomad once and my ult while roping but I survived! That was a good day in the DZ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 19:51:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be epic. Also would like the option to BFG the chopper.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 20:14:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s what sets the DZ apart from other games.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 20:15:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agent? Yes. Man? Sure. Wise? Meh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 20:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 20:23:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes this is a good point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 20:50:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice. I usually only extract in DZ4, 5 and 6. I feel I have the advantage with the multi tier extract points.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 20:58:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is a sight to see two factions having at it. It #8217;s quite hilarious. Once I did lose track of time of extracting cause I was watching cleaners and rikers have a massive battle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 21:04:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>It does start slow. I think the writers tried to bring in new audiences when it went to Netflix and introduce the main characters. However, I felt it got better a few episodes in. Still doesn #8217;t hold a candle to the first three seasons though. Especially the third. That #8217;s when they pulled all the stops.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 21:05:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>By far my favorite TV series of all time. I #8217;ve seen all seasons at least five times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 21:07:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha. Yea I #8217;ll do that sometimes as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 21:16:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m down for high-risk-high-reward. That #8217;s what the DZ lacks. It should be like back in the day when going rogue and dying you #8217;d lose a shit ton of DZ XP but that #8217;s still not enough. It should be more like if you go rogue and you die then you lose all your gear including what you #8217;re using. That #8217;s right. Weapons and gear. If not then at least a 10 min cooldown from entering the DZ cause you #8217;re being interrogated by Lau for disobedience. She #8217;s just keep whining cause her body can #8217;t seem to heal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 21:17:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Touch #233;. There #8217;s always money in the first three seasons.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 23:27:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I run 6 piece Sex Predator.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 23:28:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. 90 secs to wait then 60 secs for the liftoff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 23:29:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s exactly it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 03:02:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It always is satisfying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 15:55:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m saying it #8217;s an optical illusion. It #8217;s the pattern in my pants.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If all the movies in the history of cinema shared the same universe, New York City would be the most uninhabitable place on earth due to it #8217;s destructive attraction.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 13:05:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 14:25:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tru dat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 04:15:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hats off to you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 04:15:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll shall check this out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 04:15:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 04:21:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well since it #8217;s a looter and RNG can be quite unfair, you just have to stick with it. I enjoy this game. Probably because I can slap on different gear set and play differently so it keeps it fresh. I #8217;ve grinded my ass off every GE and in right now I have: 6 piece classy Nomad 6 piece classy D3 6 piece classy Alpha 6 piece classy Hunters 6 piece classy Banshee 6 piece classy FireCrest 6 piece classy Tac Almost all the sets but yet again RNG can be a bitch. And it can get you down and be very frustrating. I only need a Predator backpack to complete my set and it just won #8217;t drop. Lucky for us all, looks like they might tweak the drop rates on classy gear on the next update. At least that #8217;s the rumor. Bottom line, if you enjoy the game then I #8217;d just keep playing and eventually the pieces will fall for you. Also, try farming Resistance. That #8217;s what I #8217;ve been doing lately. Pretty reliable. EDIT: drop And farm LZ bosses</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 04:29:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha. I took a break for 6 months I wonder how high it would be if I didn #8217;t take a hiatus.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 04:32:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>When the Commendations started I was surprised with how many I haven #8217;t unlocked. Like NPC kills. I surely thought I had maxed it out three times over but I just barely finished it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 05:00:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>The DZ isn #8217;t that much better in your favor. I would run the LZ bosses every four hours; if you have four characters then that #8217;s 60 chances for exotics and classys in two hours. Also, run Pier 93 for one or two chances at a loot box. This is by far your safest bet. Don #8217;t worry about the DZ. Cause if you don #8217;t have a group to run the DZ and you happened to get a gear to extract your chances of getting out alive is slim. But stick with it. It #8217;s a pain in the ass but this is grinding.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 05:01:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>No shit?! Well that explains a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 05:01:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>God bless you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 17:03:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s insane man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 18:15:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s dedication dude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 03:57:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh shit my bad. I meant Skulls. You #8217;re right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 03:58:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>So you #8217;re saying out getting the 3 out of 4.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 03:58:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn #8217;t know this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is your favorite scene from Twin Peaks?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 18:33:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my favorites is when Coop and Ed go in disguise to One Eyed Jacks as oral surgeons in Realization Time. Ed blows his cover by telling Blackie that he #8217;s a gas station owner and she tells him  #8220;I #8217;ve got a car out back with a serious root canal problem #8221;. Ed quickly responds with  #8220;I was hopin #8217; you #8217;d need a little gum work,  #8217;cause I #8217;d sure like to take a look under your hood. #8221; Blackie is pleased and tells Coop she likes Ed. And Coop is disgusted/stunned with Ed #8217;s reply and says  #8220;He #8217;s a prince. #8221; Has me rolling everytime!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 18:37:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha yes!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 20:02:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Beautiful scene.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 20:38:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>There really are so many.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 01:15:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree. I was expecting Bobby to explode on him but he actually listened and was thankful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 04:16:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea you #8217;re right. I guess watching it on Netflix for some reason screws with my mind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>RIP Don Carter, You will be missed in Dallas</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 20:37:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pulling off the price tag from an expensive purchase feels like pulling the pin from a grenade.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 13:38:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 17:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 04:30:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha. I hope not. I #8217;m not asking for a nerf in terms of bleed but maybe changing 9k stam to 9k firearms. It seems more reasonable to be a glass cannon with that kind of power.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 04:31:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 12:32:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very nice. I took out a four man Manhunt group solo with this build.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 12:33:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>My understanding is to get the extra percentages for chance I #8217;ll have to get through weapon talents like vicious?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 12:35:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dropping a box and running in and out is what I do and I understand it #8217;s not a great counter but still viable. Also the best counter is to make them bleed first. Like I said, toning down the bleed would be ok with me. Or at least make the 9k threshold Firearms so you #8217;re a true glass cannon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ELI5: was The Brady Bill effective towards homicides with firearms?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 15:47:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most of the research and articles I have found show numbers relating the blocking of felons and criminals from purchasing firearms; also suicide rates by firearms. I feel most of the  #8220;news #8221; articles are skewed by bias. Is there any definitive proof with black and white numbers to back up the bill?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 16:12:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s exactly what I #8217;m looking for. The things that happened and recorded. Like did the number of homicides from firearms go down?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 16:23:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for your input.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 15:29:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Their annoyance is my pleasure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 14:50:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m on my fourth iPhone. I pretty much use all google apps. The only iOS related app I use is iMessage. To sum up, iMessage is the only reason I have a +$600 phone...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 19:11:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. If Android would have something similar to iMessage I #8217;d be on board. I like the devices by Google and was a click away from switching to the Pixel 2XL AND carrier for it but a friend iMessaged me and I folded.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New Plastic</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 20:17:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 17:59:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hands down my favorite movie of all time. I have to watch it at least once a month. Line by line, quotable. Memorable characters, every single one. Made me fall in love with White Russians.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 17:54:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Raw was delicious but I don #8217;t know if I consider it a Horror flick. More like Indie-Drama with a splash of blood. Then again I #8217;m not a movie critic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 20:15:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess I will be placing Mute in that category then.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Gal Gadot doppelganger</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 04:29:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, I just rewatched Bring It On on Netflix, haven't seen it in like 17 years, and there is a character named Darcy. She is a brunette, quite fit with distinct eye brows and my immediate reaction was "holy shit, Gal was in Bring It On!" But a quick IMDB search proves wrong. Darcy is played by Tsianina Joelson. Wow, to me at least, the similarity is uncanny. Please, someone back me up on this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 04:33:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re probably right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ReviewBrah is savage</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 19:03:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 00:08:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just choked on my beer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In Seven, Somerset (played by Freeman) is confounded by the glassware Mills (Pitt) used to pour wine into.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 03:01:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 15:39:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Punch Drunk Love - PTA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 15:10:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favorite PTA film.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 00:22:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 00:30:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe the super paranoid. Out of habit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 00:30:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s the only way to dip.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 00:38:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I usually double dip in front of my friends just to let them know I #8217;m disease free.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Water Fountain at a Dallas Bar</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 19:30:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 19:33:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Barley House off of SMU BLVD. Decent little spot. Nice area for food.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 20:31:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re close. It #8217;s actually Michelob Ultra. These folks count cals like money.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 23:39:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>You got screwed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 00:16:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Genius.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dallas drivers, why is your driving so damn shitty? No, seriously...why so shitty?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 22:27:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 22:30:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has to be. Look how they drafted in the NBA this year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 22:31:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d have to fly. I wouldn #8217;t make it in a car.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 22:31:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>People in Houston are allowed to drive?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 22:31:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wear it proudly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 22:33:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 22:34:08</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8216; #8216;Tis true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 22:35:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the most asinine answer I #8217;ve ever heard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 01:41:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am a native Dallasite. I guess that makes me a terrible driver too then.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ant-Man Inspired drink menu at The Alamo Draft Dallas</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 00:30:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I was at a BBQ on Saturday. We live in North Texas. One citronella candle was out yet I still got bit 18 times. What are some tips and tricks to keep these blood-sucking demons at bay?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 05:03:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 05:06:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh come on...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 05:06:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mint eh? Will do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 05:07:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess the attraction from mosquitos boosts my ego a slight bit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 05:08:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Interesting! I will purchase these. This actually is quite helpful. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 05:09:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>They seem to keep all plants in pots. Maybe a couple of pots of mint wouldn #8217;t hurt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 05:09:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>No lakes, ponds, reservoirs, watersheds, seas, oceans within sight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 05:10:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your view of Texas is askew.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 05:12:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll let the fellow Aryan neighbors underground we #8217;re not celebrating anything special.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 05:12:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fairly dry. Sprinkled a couple of days ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 05:25:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>These actually work?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 05:26:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good tips. Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 15:08:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dallas is a dark tour zone?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 15:13:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>My place.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just Bacon It</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 15:19:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 15:30:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol. I guess it #8217;s not as obvious as it was for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 19:59:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>They do. At the very least dickbutt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 04:56:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>My title could be better. Nike #8217;s slogan is Just Do It.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:24:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah yea thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Took a screenshot of my cracked screen</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 00:34:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 00:21:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have a friend whose uncle is wealthy. Owns several Mercedes but would rather drive his Hyundai Equus. He loves that car.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What the hell is going on with the reddit app on iOS?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 04:40:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 04:42:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gifs won #8217;t load. Scrolling is laggy. Am I alone on this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 04:42:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will do this. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 04:43:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gifs won #8217;t load. Scrolling is laggy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 04:44:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I maintain the background fairly well. WiFi is solid. If I feel it #8217;s the WiFi then I go to LTE. Problem persists.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 04:48:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok. I #8217;ll do that. Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What was the best service you ever experienced that absolutely blew you away?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 18:09:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 18:15:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sad to say I haven #8217;t had the same experience.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 18:15:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was waiting for this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 18:23:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s what she said.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 06:50:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Solid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>LPT: Whenever someone had a bad day and they #8217;re being cathartic, just listen. Don #8217;t speak. Don #8217;t give advice. Don #8217;t interrupt. Don #8217;t pretend to listen. Be a pal and be a sponge. This is the most good you can do.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:58:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:17:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve lived and learned.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>