<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject9652</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2006-09-12 10:06:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Joel, the privacy issue is huge and what we've spent the most time working on. I just posted some thoughts about it here: http://www.techcrunch.com/2006/09/11/loopt-to-make-mobile-presence-usable/#comment-187067</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2006-09-13 01:46:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>we agree. keep an eye out...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I am Sam Altman, lead investor in reddit's new round and President of Y Combinator. AMA!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 19:50:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>**EDIT:** I have to go do my class at Stanford (http://startupclass.subject9652.com; Paul Graham is speaking today), but will try to answer more questions later this afternoon! **EDIT 2:** Back. **EDIT 3:** Ok, I have to go to five hours of non-stop meetings, so I'm going to sign off. Thanks for reading! I put up a blog post here: http://blog.subject9652.com/reddit **TL;DR:** I'm investing (along with many others) in reddit. We're working on a way to give 10% of our shares from this round to the reddit community. I hope we can increase community ownership over time--I've always thought communities like reddit should mostly own themselves, and that it's time for some innovation around corporate structure here. I'm giving the company a voting proxy on my shares. Also, I'm the President of Y Combinator (though this was a personal investment, not a YC one). Startups like Airbnb, Dropbox, Stripe, and many others (including reddit itself!) have gone through our program. I'm happy to answer questions about startups in general. Excited to be along for the journey! Proof: https://twitter.com/sama/status/517008116857061376 and Leaving the reddit office after our first meeting: https://twitter.com/sama/status/489593535083999232</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 19:59:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm willing to be very patient. I don't have any particular timeframe in mind. I believe that the community is very valuable and that the value will continue to increase. Up to the company if they want to share cashflow details, but they run the company efficiently :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:00:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, there was, and i think they're going to announce what they're working on soon :) More generally, though, great tools are important and programming is especially important. I'd invest in tools that I believe will help hundreds of millions of new people create software even if I was sure I'd never make any money on the investment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:02:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can do some really creative stuff with LLCs, but why bother? It's clean and simple to create a new one, and the challenges of setting up a company (which YC helps with anyway) pale in comparison to everything else a startup has to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:05:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who knows. Maybe there will be a better option than an IPO. It's up to the reddit team, not me, but I think they should do whatever is in the best long-term interest of the company.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:09:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just a user--whatever the company wants to do. I used to HATE it when investors told me what to do with my product :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:16:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>PR comes and goes. I think the more important (and harder) question is how should reddit best protect what it stands for. Yishan is far more thoughtful and intelligent about this than I am, and I trust that he'll get it right. Free speech is both great and awful, but it's difficult to figure out how to limit it without cutting off something potentially very important. There are hurtful things that are still important to allow to be said--someday, the ability to speak up will be really important. But, like almost anyone else, I hope that the community can find a way to push out more of the bad and highlight more of the good. The shock subreddits are just a sideshow, I think. You can't find them unless you look for them--the community generally works as designed, and most of the stuff that bubbles up is great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:16:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>as a user, my number one feature request is a really great mobile app.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:17:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>when i invested in stripe, i left the "to:" field of the check blank--patrick didn't have a real name or a corporation yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:18:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sure hope not! Yes. Anything that is both 1) interesting 2) makes me think something I haven't thought before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:20:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have a checklist of what companies need to do when they start (I'm actually working on a new one for companies when they get to the ~50 employee mark--founders are often very busy and forget to do important thing). We can't force them to get everything right, but we sure try...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:22:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. I think it's somewhat overstated (i.e., the great majority of startups don't fall into the brogrammer category) but that we have real work to do in making the valley a place where everyone feels welcome. I think that less arrogance from the valley would be a very welcome change--we should let what we build impress people instead of talking about how great we are. 2. Absolutely! We did a Startup School in Europe (London, actually) this summer and were blown away by the quality of the founders. One of my partners just returned from back-to-back trips to Asia. About 40% of the founders in our last batch were born outside the US.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:24:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Founders should never expect employees to work as hard and care as much as they do, but still, if you join an early-stage startup, expect to work very hard. Most people at Facebook still seem to work very hard. Generally, I think companies should hold off the transition to feeling "corporate" as long as possible, but transition to something with better work-life balance after a few years--no one can work around the clock forever. All of that said, I do think most startups need to get some basic HR in place sooner than they usually do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:25:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you not remember this? I voted you guys number one in the poll!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:25:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi Joshua!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:28:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>YC no longer owns any of reddit :( Conde Nast bought our shares, and we didn't get new ones in the spinout. This is not at the stage/valuation level where I have any concerns about signaling (and reddit went through YC 9 years ago...presumably any information advantage we have is long gone). Instead of a lot of personal early-stage investments, where there would be big signaling problems, I'm planning on infrequent late-stage ones. And in this specific case, some of the nontraditional things I think are important for reddit in this round (community ownership, voting proxy on the shares) are terms that would be tough for a VC to set--it's easier for someone like me to say "this is what's happening" and then they can sign on to that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>1) People take care of what they own. 2) It just seems fair--users create the value, they should get to capture some of it. 3) I do think more sites could benefit from this, and honestly I'm somewhat surprised others haven't tried it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:40:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will help whenever the company asks me, and otherwise I will stay out of their way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:42:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a user, I'm excited because it means reddit will be able to grow and do things. I'm also excited because I think online communities are one of the most powerful applications of the Internet. As an investor (along with many redditors soon :) ), I'm excited because I think communities are some of the most defensible businesses out there. It's not a lock, of course--plenty have faltered--but it's at least a good bet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:42:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Passion, clarity of vision, and deep insights.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:43:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is correct.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:43:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>The IQ of the position went down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:46:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I dropped out of college to start a company in 2005. In 2010 I started investing (small amounts and only 4 companies that year) and I've steadily ramped it up since. I've really tried to study how to be a good early-stage investor--here are some thoughts: http://blog.subject9652.com/black-swan-seed-rounds</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:46:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think any are that good, but Twitter is probably best in my case.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:46:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I expect to be at YC for a very long time. We have a lot of plans about the future for YC that are very exciting, but given my normal advice about not hyping yourself, I'll hold off on sharing them until they're ready :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:48:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have two amazing in-house attorney and standard documents. Most of our startups also use Clerky which really helps. We are generally able to take care of this very quickly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:49:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should work on whatever you want--there is no shame in a web service. But I disagree that the days where a small team can have a huge impact are gone. Every great startup begins with a very small team. It's worked in the past and it will work again. For example, both of the nuclear energy companies in this summer's batch began YC with less than 5 people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:51:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>We know what we want to do, but we have to get regulatory sign-off (and if we can't we have a backup idea). I probably shouldn't say too much, but my one-word hint is "blockchain". Also, the company will be handling this, not me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:52:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>They went through YC in the Summer of 2007. Incidentally, Drew previously applied with an idea for an SAT prep company that we rejected.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:53:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cinnamon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:58:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, anyone who tells you they can do it precisely is lying. I made a few models but ended up using them only for very rough guidance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 20:59:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>No implicit preference towards US applicants. We don't break out the acceptance rate, but my guess is it's about the same. The number of non-US applicants keeps going up, and thus so does the number we accept.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:00:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>(Also, as an indication of how long ago that was, it was a literal check, and perhaps is the last time i have written one.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:02:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>We can't share the details until we get it no-actioned, but no, if we can get plan A done, it won't be symbolic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:11:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, a lot of founders have told me they've put some or all of this into practice at their companies!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:11:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am fairly shy in big groups and terrible at conferences. I probably don't have great advice here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>We help founders get visas as much as we can. It's a headache, and I think turning away people who want to start companies and create jobs here is one of the dumbest positions taken in the name of politics in a long time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:21:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will answer this, but you first--I think the reddit-in-YC story is a great one you should tell here:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:22:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>If people start posting there, I'll check it out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:23:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>It gets revoked in cases of fraud and similar situation. I think that, most of the time, investors destroy their own value when they try to get creative and force a sale or whatever. I also wanted to be sure the community didn't worry I was going to this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:24:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't mean this to be glib, but have a good company. It's tough to hack our application process. Being a solo founder definitely sets the bar higher, but it's not impossible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:25:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once, and sadly I can't tell the story publicly. I got it on the first try :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks Peter!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:26:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's both. We are very fortunate that we get amazing people to apply, and we work very hard to help them. I think the single biggest "secret" is the strength of alumni community.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:26:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>For a very small value of "tiger".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:27:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Subreddits. One of the most brilliant moves in the history of online communities.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:34:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Addressed elsewhere, probably can't add a lot more detail :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:34:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>He is. I've read his talk and it's great (sadly, I have to go to my class in about half an hour and take a break from doing this)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:35:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it's what you most want to do it, then you should do it. What's stopping you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:36:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm certainly supportive of whatever the company wants to disclose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>That doesn't always happen. Often, funding makes a company far greater.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Focus on getting a small number of super-engaged users that love you, and them spread the community. If you're building it for an exit, you will probably be disappointed. That's not a specific statement about a community site but a general comment about startups.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:44:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>1) Less than half. 2) It's very hard to say what is going to baffle in the good way and what is going to baffle in the bad way. What we're doing seems to be working in aggregate, but of course there will be a lot of failures. 3) Take another look in 5 years :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 21:48:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi RWTH Aachen! Thanks for watching the class; I hope you enjoy it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 23:31:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are a lot of good answers to this, but one I think is particularly interesting is healthcare.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 23:33:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I think a good financial outcome is generally indicative of having made a big impact. However, you can make a big impact without having a big financial outcome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 23:36:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of the things I like most about the reddit team is that they understand this and take it seriously. In many ways, the relative slowness of the product evolution is a feature, not a bug.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 23:37:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure, but he can beat me in a game of chess in 30-40 seconds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 23:38:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>On a bet with another redditor, I once got the word "petrichor" printed in the NYT.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 23:38:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>So much has been written on the Internet about this I'm not sure if I can add much in a short response. It's pretty simple--as the landscape evolves, smart people focus on new areas. We let them lead us to what to fund.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 23:39:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't they are particularly close competitors, though there is clearly some overlap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 23:39:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's cool!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 23:40:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>1) The thing that bums me out most about hackatons is people get started on really cool projects and then totally abandon them. 2) Other than fast cars and wine, I mostly waste my money.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 23:49:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>A severe lack of time :( I do feel bad that I take more than I get from the community. I'll try to contribute more, but work doesn't seem to be letting up...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 23:50:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>askscience and askreddit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 23:51:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope that it will be funding companies that transform the world in great ways. I think startups are a very good way to do new things, and I think YC is a very good platform for helping startups.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 23:55:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-01 00:33:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Peter is speaking at the class next Tues. We're going to let him cover that part :) We do talk about it during YC, but one thing we tell early startups is that they are unlikely to get killed by competitors; it's much more likely they'll kill themselves. In the early days, you should focus more on creating a product people love. Later, you have to worry about how to not have competitors (though a strategy for this is a component of many great ideas).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-01 01:05:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>So happy you're part of this round :) Long-time fan! Also, you should come visit YC sometime.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-01 03:10:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>We try to give away as much knowledge as we can, but 1:1 advice is still irreplaceable, and I think the YC partners are some of the best people in the world for advising early-stage startups. Also, the YC alumni network is becoming one of the most helpful groups in the startup world--there is a strong cultural value of helping other YC startups.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-07 21:45:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>no, that's a job post from a company we funded. they are building a bank, though :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-06 08:52:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>sure, I'll do one. this week is a bit busy but I'll find a time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-08 08:18:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>sorry--this week crazier than expected, probably will have to wait until next :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An old team at reddit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-10 23:14:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ellen Pao resigned from reddit today by mutual agreement. I'm delighted to announce that Steve Huffman, founder and the original reddit CEO, is returning as CEO. We are thankful for Ellen #8217;s many contributions to reddit and the technology industry generally. She brought focus to chaos, recruited a world-class team of executives, and drove growth. She brought a face to reddit that changed perceptions, and is a pioneer for women in the tech industry. She will remain as an advisor to the board through the end of 2015. I look forward to seeing the great things she does beyond that. We #8217;re very happy to have Steve back. Product and community are the two legs of reddit, and the board was very focused on finding a candidate who excels at both (truthfully, community is harder), which Steve does. He has the added bonus of being a founder with ten years of reddit history in his head. Steve is rejoining Alexis, who will work alongside Steve with the new title of  #8220;cofounder #8221;. A few other points. Mods, you are what makes reddit great. The reddit team, now with Steve, wants to do more for you. You deserve better moderation tools and better communication from the admins. Second, redditors, you deserve clarity about what the content policy of reddit is going to be. The team will create guidelines to both preserve the integrity of reddit and to maintain reddit as the place where the most open and honest conversations with the entire world can happen. Third, as a redditor, I #8217;m particularly happy that Steve is so passionate about mobile. I #8217;m very excited to use reddit more on my phone. As a closing note, it was sickening to see some of the things redditors wrote about Ellen. [1] The reduction in compassion that happens when we #8217;re all behind computer screens is not good for the world. People are still people even if there is Internet between you. If the reddit community cannot learn to balance authenticity and compassion, it may be a great website but it will never be a truly great community. Steve #8217;s great challenge as CEO [2] will be continuing the work Ellen started to drive this forward. [1] Disagreements are fine. Death threats are not, are not covered under free speech, and will continue to get offending users banned. Ellen asked me to point out that the sweeping majority of redditors didn #8217;t do this, and many were incredibly supportive. Although the incredible power of the Internet is the amplification of voices, unfortunately sometimes those voices are hateful. [2] We were planning to run a CEO search here and talked about how Steve (who we assumed was unavailable) was the benchmark candidate #8212;he has exactly the combination of talent and vision we were looking for. To our delight, it turned out our hypothetical benchmark candidate is the one actually taking the job. NOTE: I am going to let the reddit team answer questions here, and go do an AMA myself now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I am Sam Altman, reddit board member and President of Y Combinator. AMA</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-10 23:20:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>PROOF: https://twitter.com/sama/status/619618151840415744 EDIT: A friend of mine is getting married tonight, and I have to get ready to head to the rehearsal dinner. I will log back in and answer a few more questions in an hour or so when I get on the train. EDIT: Back! EDIT: Ok. Going offline for wedding festivities. Thanks for the questions. I'll do another AMA sometime if you all want!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-10 23:23:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>The best part is constantly being around incredible people working on new ideas. It's hard to think of a more mentally stimulating job. I personally think the most fun part of starting a company is the first part, and so I love that I get to do that all the time. The worst part, by far, is rejecting companies that want funding from us. It sucks :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-10 23:25:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's up to the reddit team and Steve. Part of being a good board member is letting the management team run the company. However, I think this is critical and would not have voted to hire Steve if I didn't believe he will make this a top priority.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-10 23:29:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>The previous CEO resigned on the spot. Ellen said she would do the interim work, and I am very thankful she did. She walked into an incredibly difficult situation and move the ball a good bit down the field for reddit. She made some mistakes, for sure, but I think she did remarkably well in a very tough situation. And Steve is happy to be taking the baton for her here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-10 23:31:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I honestly know almost nothing about that situation, sorry. EDIT: Obviously I know about what happened when she left. I mean that I don't know about any future plans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-10 23:33:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a question for Steve; he is the CEO. Poached!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-10 23:34:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tripel_Karmeliet On a farm in the midwest on a hot summer night.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-10 23:35:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not very much. I think good board members work with the CEO to set strategy and goals for the company, but leave it up to the CEO to implement them. Of course, whenever CEOs ask for help, I try to do anything I can to help. I almost never take board seats, though. The list of things I'd rather do than sit in a board meeting is long. reddit is just special.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-10 23:40:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>She resigned. Thankfully, she did it a thoughtful way that gave us time to hire a successor and have a smooth transition.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-10 23:41:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>No; in fact we agreed as a board not to focus too much on monetization for now. Someday we'll need reddit to be profitable, but we want to do it in a thoughtful way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-10 23:41:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-10 23:45:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most board members? Very little that's helpful :) You could ask Ellen if I've been a good one--I hope so! Your job as a board member is to hire and fire the CEO, approve the annual financial plan, and help the executive team set the strategic direction. Bad members don't do a good job of those things. Very bad board members try to do the CEO's job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-10 23:49:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's simply not true--not sure how to better put it to bed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-10 23:53:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is an incredibly good question. Free speech is great and terrible. We need freedom of expression; we need compassion. Part of the reason I voted to hired Steve is he is one of the most thoughtful people I have ever met on this intersection. I think figuring out how technology can encourage empathy is one of the more interesting and important open research problems in the world right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-10 23:59:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>reddit has more than $50MM in the bank, which will last many many years. At some point the business needs to be profitable. Monetizing AMAs does not seem like the right way to do it to me, but again, Steve's call. Ads will work but it'd be great to figure out something better that actually makes reddit better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 00:17:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I knew there would be a lot, and I was still surprised how much there was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 00:18:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Determination, focus, clarity of vision, ability to hire great talent, and choosing a rapidly-growing market.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 00:23:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>No.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 00:24:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes--in fact, I think that's the major challenge. It's easier with fusion, but it still feels uncomfortable to people. However, I think the appeals of cheap, clean, safe energy will eventually win. It's too important.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 00:25:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Prioritize getting customers. If you start to build a great business, you may attract a great cofounder. Trying to "force" a cofounder almost never works--I'd stay away from cofounder dating stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 00:26:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Elon and I have discussed this many, many times. It's one of the things I think about most. Have some news coming here in a few months...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 00:26:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sort of think it's the best hope for democracy working long term. I don't yet know what the right solution is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 00:27:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I wrote it, so thanks for the complement I guess. My style is generally just say what's going on and to do it before the lawyers and PR people can slow my roll.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 00:28:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I receive about 1200 and send about 200. When people ask me what my job entails I just say "email".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 00:29:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>The company runs +/- breakeven. I think ads will work if necessary, but there are some really cool things reddit may be able to do with for example commerce.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 00:30:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not usually at private companies (and not at reddit, but in my case I own a lot of reddit stock) but usually yes at public companies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 00:30:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I spend almost all of my time running YC. It is an intense job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 00:31:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>buy a beat up old used iPhone and a prepaid SIM.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 00:32:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not very much, honestly. Almost all of my work time is spent on other stuff. I will try to be a sounding board for him if he wants to talk, and warn him if I see a big strategic issue coming.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 00:58:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>A startup because you get to see much more and can gain more responsibility more quickly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 00:59:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>We already fund companies from outside the US, and lots of them. I think there were founders from about 40 different countries in our last batch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 00:59:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Steve and the team will set the plans. I just reallyreally hope they make a mobile app :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 02:39:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>gmail with a lot of labels and filters. i also write extremely short emails, and honestly just spend a lot of time doing it. i'm also quick to forward things to other people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 02:42:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Figuring out how to fund lots of startup per year is really exciting to me. Honestly, the most exciting thing is not any particular startup, but that YC as a sort of meta-company can have such an impact on stuff, and that the YC network is so helpful that companies we fund have a big advantage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 02:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's such a powerful community, and it grows exponentially more powerful with more users. I am most excited for a mobile app. Sure wish I wasted less time here though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 02:45:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the enterprise startup trend will go a lot further. I think this would be a good time to start a new social product that is mobile-focused. I think biotech, AI, and energy are likely to big.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 02:45:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Totally room for the outliers. That's where we make most of our money and have the most fun; we try not to lose sight of that. Related new thing coming soon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 02:46:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes and I loved it! Going back this year (going to try to hold a startup event there too).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 02:47:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>When there is a mobile app I will make some comments. It's just too hard in mobile safari. But I might use an alt account--everything in my life is now so public that it's sort of nice to be not recognized on reddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 02:47:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That if I played an hour of Internet chess a day I could be better than Peter (this is a joke--sometimes we play 5 min/1min games and I still can never win).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 02:49:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not always, but when I do I prefer dos equis.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 02:50:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>A mobile app please please please.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 02:50:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. We are working on some new stuff, but honestly this is high on my list of worries. That's part of the reason I do stuff like the startup class: http://startupclass.subject9652.com</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 02:51:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think this is a good start: http://startupclass.subject9652.com</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 02:54:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Leonardo obviously. Turtle power!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 02:55:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's really hard to make a general statement about this, the specifics matter so much. I think the best advice I have is to start a company with a CEO you really know well and have a trusting relationship with, and then talk frequently about how things are going.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 02:57:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some do for sure. Many live to work and are perfectly happy with that--that's what they love doing, they understand the tradeoffs, and they wouldn't have it any other way. I'm pretty far along the live to work spectrum but nothing like many people I know. I work a lot, but there are a few parts of my life I'm not willing to compromise on or neglect, and that works for me. The rest I let go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 20:38:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, yes, agreed for sure. But also...growth!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 20:45:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool story bro. Except I could never have predicted the part where you resigned on the spot :) Other than that, child's play for me. Thanks for the help. I mean, thanks for your service as CEO.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 22:13:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>true. /u/spez, could I get some site-wide flair? also, /u/yishan, thanks for the gold!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-25 19:13:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's good. the weakest answer is about how you're going to get users, which given the competition in the space is also perhaps the most important.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-25 21:05:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a really good point--I place a huge value on clear, concise answers when I read applications.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-25 21:06:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not true; we still prefer teams.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-26 00:11:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes--we will be more open to it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-17 02:54:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw this happen once and honestly thought I'd gone crazy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-05 05:17:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>HODL!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-05 05:19:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>To the Lagrange L2 point!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-16 08:54:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I in fact just bought some!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-27 22:04:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>