<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject6668</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 21:30:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are we some kinda suicide pod??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 07:30:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It has multiple definitions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 15:10:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mmmm true</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 21:15:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Grammatical Pedantry Syndrome. Look it up. I'm not saying every grammar freak has it. I'm just saying it exists.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 21:21:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eh. They're alright. They're one of the go-to hated vegetables in kids books. For some reason.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 21:23:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Store-bought cupcakes have the most disgusting icing on them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 08:00:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Both of you are pathetic. You're the ones that need to seek help. I'm not a snowflake for having OCD.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>iPhone 5 keeps dropping wifi when I access the internet.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 19:32:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have an iPhone 5. Every time I open an app that uses internet, it drops the wifi. Otherwise, it's fine. This is extremely annoying. Does anybody have any tips? Things I've tried: -turning off the wifi, powering off the device completely, then turning it back on and reconnecting. -forgetting the network -resetting network settings Thanks in advance!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 03:23:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw this accounts on Instagram where literally every post was dedicated to the user's sexuality. Being  #128079; gay  #128079; doesn't  #128079; make  #128079; you  #128079; special  #128079; or  #128079; superior  #128079;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 18:14:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>How tho! I am TERRIBLE at singing in front of people</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 01:56:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Female</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm angry with the way my body looks and I take it out on my skin. My best friend gets uncomfortable when I ask her for help (and I don't blame her) so I decided maybe I'll try here.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 07:52:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 07:58:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>-There's an app called Calm Harm that I used for a bit...really helped. -use a washable marker and draw a butterfly (or another animal you like) on your skin where you feel urged to harm yourself. Don't scrub it off, let it fade away naturally. -get up and take a walk or go on a run. The exercise is healthy and the fresh air will make you feel better. It may seem cheesy or stupid, but this has helped me quite a bit. If you feel urges a lot, you'll find yourself in very good shape, which is always a plus. You're beautiful, inside and out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>