<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject5112</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 05:50:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>my bf and i have showered together once after sex, and for us it was more of just a "hanging out and being dumb, but we're also naked" kind of thing. we didnt do anything sexual. we washed like parts of eachother, but it was mostly just splashing eachother and me making him smell my soaps. shower sex doesnt really work that well anyways, water dries out vaginas reaaaaal bad, so it's really unpleasant for both parties. but for fun soapy foreplay that has no genital contact i could see it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 22:25:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>nah, i dont think she would care. as long as it's not anything kinda grossish like anti dandruff shampoo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 17:57:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>all of these comments are super positive, and i hate to be a negative nancy, but for me it's an absolute no. even the idea of it repulses me, i've tried the absolute minimum before and felt nothing sexual whatsoever, it just felt clinical. i just think it's gross. and a lot of work, you cant just have spontaneous anal like you can with piv, and i hate planned sex. (and it seems kinda pointless when there's a perfectly good vagina like right there) but to each their own i guess  #175;\_( #12484;)_/ #175;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 06:01:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>every cat i've ever had has LOVED cat dancers. it's literally just a slightly curved wire with little bits of cardboard on the end, but it drives them CRAZY. they're super cheap too. you can find them at most pet stores, or on amazon [here](https://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/B0006N9I68/ref=mp_s_a_1_3?ie=UTF8 amp;qid=1495511885 amp;sr=8-3 amp;keywords=cat+dancer)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 21:31:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>this makes me wonder, what makes them different? why is luke more powerful than leia if they're the twin children of the chosen one? i know luke received training but he was still relatively powerful before that, and there's no reason leia couldn't have been trained either. did the ~force choose him~ or something?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-26 02:19:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>my dad fast forwarding past the part in A New Hope where it shows Luke's aunt and uncle's flaming bodies because it was to scary for a 5 or so year old. i remember feeling really rebellious the first time i actually watched that scene.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Leaving tank light on overnight?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 18:01:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>i have 3 serpae tetras in a 10 gallon tank in my bedroom. i usually turn the light off before i go to bed, but sometimes i forget and fall asleep with it on. is occasionally leaving my tank light on overnight bad for my fish?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 19:50:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>the sims 4 and its relentless release of payed dlc</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 23:29:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>id say that's possible. you just have to have a loading screen between lots, and i dont think that would stop you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>my beautiful little blind boy Stevie, after Stevie Wonder (get it?)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 00:26:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>cat.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 01:12:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>i cant eat, how harmful is it?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 03:33:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>for the last two weeks since my boyfriend left me, i havent been able to eat very much or at all. for the first weekish i couldnt eat anything at all, but now im able to eat one small meal a day. im not doing it on purpose/to hurt myself, i just have 0 appetite and when i do manage to eat i feel really nauseous after. i've lost a little more than 10 pounds and i weigh about 87 pounds. i know that not eating isn't healthy, but what could this be doing to my body?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 03:48:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>pull a kylo ren and tell him that he's my hero and that i love him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 19:01:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>try not to use your hands as toys, like wiggling them around for her to attack, that'll get her into the habit of attacking them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 19:20:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>indoor all the way. not only would letting your cat be outside be unsafe for your cat, they also kill a lot of birds/small animals that they dont need to eat or even eat at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 21:49:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>is she fed exclusively a plant based diet? or does the cat food she gets contain meat?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 22:07:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>okay cool, just checking. i had a cat that loved broccoli and carrots!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>my beautiful fluffy boy, captain fuzzy pants.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 22:08:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 22:42:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>no id say it's bears</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 23:07:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>you could always try leash training him! harnesses for small dogs usually work pretty well, not all cats like them but it's worth a shot. that way you could take him outside and he could be completely supervised.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>i have no idea who this guy is, he apparently lives in my town though. pretty much everything he says makes as much since as this. he also thinks the earth is flat, and believes in ancient aliens. also: liked his own post.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 05:10:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 05:11:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>he has a little white spot on the tip of one of his feet- we call it his french manicure lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 06:15:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>i think he mentioned one time that he's schizophrenic but he doesnt take his meds for it because he cant get high when he does and he thinks that it's the government poisoning him. poor dude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why can't Russia ever seem to catch a break?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 06:32:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>So far everything I know about Russian history seems really negative. They had the invasion of the Mongols, they were cut off from the rest of the West and still had feudalism for longer than a lot of other places in Europe, they had a bunch of shitty Tzars, and once they did overthrow the monarchy they got communism. The only positive thing I can think of off the top of my head is Peter the Great. So my questions are, why is Russia so unlucky, and what are some positive events in Russian history?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 23:07:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>as a person from wisconsin who isn't good at spelling i relate to this greatly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 18:01:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>any rare meat is absolutely disgusting to me, the texture is so gross and the concept of eating under cooked meat makes me feel sick. i always get my steaks medium well, they're so much better that way. if any meat is pink at all, i wont eat it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 03:08:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>i've had that same box set since i was really really little. pretty sure we still have them somewhere, and a special addition of episode one. childhood :,)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 07:13:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>i really hope we get more vacation worlds. i want my sims to be able to go on trips, but going camping over and over again gets kind of boring. i'd like to see a tropical/beach world, and maybe a ski resort.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 18:21:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>im not a parent and this isnt about my parents, but it still works i think my uncle has been married before and his adult children have no idea but the rest of the family does (including me, and im younger than them). he and his ex still remained friends and stayed in contact, and when she passed away a few months ago he had to go to her funeral in secret. every time i see his kids i want to tell them so bad, but i dont.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 22:54:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>dreams do come true</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 02:48:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>i dont mean this in a "im not like my generation im cool and unique" way, but im 16 and i remember like 90% of these things, most of them were still around and being used when i was little. like we used a vcr until around 2009, i had a walkman as a kid, etc. older technology doesnt just completely disappear when new stuff comes out. maybe the people who dont know this stuff are just dumb. or rich.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 10:26:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>the pool item she put underneath is just so that it looks like there's a platform under the bed so it isnt just floating. it's just for decoration, you could definitely raise a bed without it, there just cant be anything underneath the pillow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Homemade] Lomo Saltado for a project in Spanish Class!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-05 01:11:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-05 05:12:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>if i have individual or very few cuts, i blame them on my cats scratching me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>