<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject9039</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Obsessed with therapy (always fantasize about it)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-17 11:15:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I started therapy 4 weeks ago, it's been 4 sessions now. I went for my anxiety in social situations, that limited and stopped me during an apprenticeship with university. I don't have a diagnosis of social anxiety yet, i mean my therapist never talked about it, never give me some hints. she is using cbt and exposure therapy. I had my last session 3 days ago. Now i always think about it, i see images in my mind of various sessions, i repeat in my mind phrases that my t said to me, or that i said...or i fantasize, for example i have scenarios where my t is comforting me, or where i start to cry (i never did this in therapy, i can't cry in front of people). And i feel anxious. Yesterday i was in a panic state, because i have some homework she assigned to me. I have to write my thoughts, my emotions, in which situations they are present, my behaviour, and some alternative ways of thinking instead of my warped thoughts. I'm anxious about it, sometimes i can't find a specific situation, for example when i think "i'm no good enough, im stupid" nothing happened, im at home, i don't have a situation. And i start to think that maybe i'm doing it wrong, maybe my T is expecting more from me. Another example i have: last session my T arrived late. I was waiting for her, i started shaking, i thought "she hates me, she isn't coming because she's bored, or i'm annoying..." and i felt the need to cry. I'm anxious because maybe she'll get mad at me for not doing things right, or for not doing my homeworks right.... I don't know if this post makes sense...i want to know if some of you experienced this during therapy. Maybe it's like a sort of transfert? .___.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-17 12:10:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok :) thanks. I already told her, two sessions ago, that i was anxious before and during therapy. I said that i had the fear of being judged or criticized by her. She was very nice and supporting - she always is- and reassured me. My anxiety is...irrational! She is always nice, gentle, caring, supporting....i don't have to be afraid of her. But I'm so embarassed to tell her again ._.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Social anxiety + fear of abandonment?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-21 20:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Today i had therapy. My T finally told to me that i have social anxiety (she wasnt so explicit, but she mentioned it)...so i told to her the story of it...i didnt have sa in elementary and secondary school. In secondary school (at the age of 11-12) i had two best friends, i was shy but my shyness didnt bother me, i was able to talk in class etc...so at the end of the third and last year, i had a problem with my best friend. She said to me in an unexpected way "you talk only to me and x girl, i think you'll have problems to find friends without us", and then she never talked to me again. I felt very sad, anxious, i felt like a loss...i had lost her. So my t said: maybe you had this fear of abandonment, but it turn into the fear of being criticized? Her point is: during social situations, i think that people are criticizing me, or wil do it, i feel i'm being judged. I think that i have to appear perfect, because if they see my flaws, they will judge me -- gt;and then leave me. So this comes fear of abandonment. Please i want to ask you if this makes sense. I'm not sure...but i have this doubt. Maybe i have this fear, and its linked to social anxiety?? I'm a bit confused...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-22 16:34:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>sometimes i think like this...at least with bipolar you are more able to socialize, to have friends...i know, it's not right to say that. But for me social anxiety is like living hell and somedays i think "i wish i didnt have anxiety but another thing"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-22 16:41:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really don't know. I'm stuck in the same situation. I think i am boring with others, because i'm not able to show my emotions, or even to change my tone of voice! When i was in highschool a girl told me something like "are you human?" because i didn't show nothing about me, my emotions etc... Only when i'm drunk, or tipsy, i'm able to show more of myself, i'm cheerful, happy, i speak more...but i can't be drunk everytime. I think you have to try, and try again...to find people with your same interests, or hobbies maybe it's easier to open up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SA + distress?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-23 21:24:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have sa and it's been a while that i feel a sense of distress...i don't know how to explain this, and if it's the right name. For example, today i felt a feeling similar to anxiety, but a bit different from it...i felt a heavy sensation in my stomach (a sharp feeling), a sense of emptiness, of boredom, i was tired...sometimes i cry a little or i feel the need to do it. and i stayed at home all day. Does anyone else with sa have this thing? How do you call it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-23 22:43:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I noticed that im feeling like this after a therapy session. Therapy sessions drain me...i have anxiety before and during, even if my therapist is really nice, gentle and calm. The sessions are on thursday, so during the weekend i feel really tired and i think about therapy all day. And then this sensation usually fade away during the week.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-24 11:30:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes i do! Fo example, some days i woke up really tired. I noticed that during those days i care more about people because i'm sleepy... i have this thing not only when i'm sleepy, but when i'm very hungry too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why I can't be happy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-24 20:37:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was at home during the weekend. But i felt like i was drained, tired, with negative thinking, thoughts of self harm again (but i didnt do it), i felt the need to cry....i didnt have anxiety. I wasnt in social situations...nothing happened. I feel i'm empty, nothing interests me. i don't know if im fine or not, because im not even sad. Last week was way better...during the week i was a bit tired but i felt happy too. So this thursday i have another appointment with my therapist. I'm really anxious because every session she asks me "How are you?" then i say "fine" and i explain the reasons. Or i will say "i'm ok, i had anxiety during this and that but im ok"...im afraid that this feeling will last. I dont want to tell my therapist that my mood dropped...i know it's sound stupid, because you may say "the therapist is here to help you!" but i feel that if i tell her that i'm not fine, that i feel empty, maybe she will think bad about me, or she will think "you don't have to swallow in your emotion..." Or she may be worried. I feel embarassed....i want to tell her that i had anxiety but i'm fine too, i'm recovering....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-25 16:31:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same. I try to appear as calm as possible, sometimes i "copy" other people behaviours...i can't be truly myself, or act like i do when i'm alone. I think that sometimes i give an image of an emotionless person, in the past some people told me if i was human, or if i felt emotions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-25 16:32:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not before sleep because it gives me anxiety. Sometimes when i do a mistake, or i say\do something that bothered me i think about it all day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-26 16:46:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, me too! When i'm at home, alone, i'm more confident, i dont have problems with taking photos if i want. When i go out...i think i started to compare myself with others (like "that girl is so beautiful\cute\i want to be like her) and i dont want to look at my reflection because i always find more flaws. Even more when i go to dress stores, i cant face my image on the mirror. I feel so uncomfortable to try clothes on, i think because im so aware of other people presence, and i compare myself to them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-28 21:50:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you i'm going to try the app!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thinking about my therapist</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-29 21:31:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's been 4 weeks that i started therapy for my SA (1 session per week). At the beginning i didnt like her at all. I found her irritating, even if she didn't do anything. In fact she was - and always is- gentle, caring, supportive.... but I didnt want her to be my therapist. I started to have feelings of both love and hate. Due to my SA i was really anxious that she would judge me. After some sessions, one time she was 20 mins late (it was the first time). I panicked, i wanted to cry and started to think "ok, she hates me, she don't want to see me again!". (she arrived and apologized). i was afraid she would leave me. And now, i think i "love" her. I don't hate her, i like her. Last session i feel like i was able to connect more, talk more to her. I thought about flirting with her (im bisexual so i think its because of that), its like im starting to have a crush on her (she is young too, 35 years old). Today i thought about her all day. Im thinking that i dont want to quit therapy, but one day it will happen...and i feel like crying because i don't want to "lose" her, to never see her again...it's painful. Im so ashamed to tell her all of this. I told her a bit of it, only that after therapy i feel drained, and that im really anxious before and after. Do you felt like this during therapy?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-30 18:40:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same with me...but for example, some days ago i went out to a party with 2 "friends" of my university. I drank way too much, next morning i felt like shit! I dont want to rely too much on alcohol! Maybe a bit, but i don't want to feel like shit again...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-30 19:10:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought it was love because i wanted to flirt with her. It's like when i have a crush on someone, it's a different feeling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-30 21:12:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, i have to tell her. I'm so scared and ashamed...but she's a therapist, maybe she's used to it, she have other clients, i'm not the only one! Anyway, today i felt anxious and at the point of crying of the thought of her leaving me. I don't know how to tell her this...maybe it's childish...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-01 11:19:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in Italy. It depends on the person. When i was in high school there were some people who judged me for my SA, but only during those years. But usually people will treat me and my problem (if they know about it or if they "see" it) in a gentle way. Nobody laughed at me or criticized me, in front of me. Maybe they talked behind me (like during high school) but they didnt criticized me in an explicit way. I think if you live in a big city or in a small town , it's different. In a small town you are more judged or criticized, everyone know everything about the others ( i live in a small country, near a city, so this is my experience). In a big city you dont know anyone, nobody cares about you unless they know you in person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scared by the future</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-02 14:56:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm at my third and last year of university. I have many doubts regarding my future and i really don't know what will be next. I'm so scared of the thought of leaving university, leaving that city, i don't know what to do. I'm studying to become a social worker (this was the intention) but now i changed my idea and i think more about the profession of "social" educator (i don't know if it's the right name in english). And i have to do my thesis, i sent an email to one of my professors, and i have to do research for an argument, and im anxious, i only want to cry and do nothing, stay at home. The idea of working scares me. I did two apprenticeships with university which were mandatory and my anxiety blocked me. Last summer I worked a few weeks in a pizzeria but i quit because of my anxiety. I talked about this to my therapist, and she said that it's normal and many students don't know what to do next, they don't have an idea or a path to follow. She wants to "normalize" everything but i'm confused and i think i should have a clear idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-02 15:06:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think nobody can save you. But you can. I spent many years of my life with this problem, and i never searched for help. During my teenage years i didnt know that i had SA, i couldn't find a solution to my problem. I became more aware after high school, and now i found the courage and started therapy. I found a very gentle person, and i like her. So i think you should find the courage, seek help, this step worked for me. But the therapist alone can't help you. She can support and encourage you, but I have to put effort, somedays it's really hard. But if i'm not motivated, i can't solve my problem. So i think that a therapist (or other people) can encourage you, but you have to do the work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-03 17:58:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for your answer :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scared my therapist will leave me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-03 18:07:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm in therapy for my social anxiety, and i did 5 sessions. At the beginning I didn't like my therapist so much, i found her irritating, without a reason. Then after 2 sessions, one day she arrived 20 mins late. And then i panicked, i started to think "ok, this means she hates me\ she doesnt want to see me!". In that moment, i realized that i was afraid that she will leave me. I was afraid she would judge\criticize me, then leave me. And now i think i have like a crush on her, this week i spent the day with this thought in mind "i dont want to stop therapy, how can i live without it, what if i will have a relapse?" and i cried thinking that one day i won't see my T anymore. I realized this is a common pattern of me. I have this fear that other people will criticize me or they won't accept me, and this means that they will leave. I really want to tell my T about that, about me having "feelings" for her and about my irrational fear. I'm so scared, i think maybe i will say a stupid thing, i feel ashamed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-04 14:01:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you tell him about that? What was the reaction?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-05 08:38:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok thanks ;) I'm going to tell mine today...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-05 17:19:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I told her! Today I was really anxious at the point of shaking! She didn't judge me I told her some details and at the end I said that I hope I don't think too much about therapy (and her) during the week. It's an obsession. She told me pretty much the same, that first we are going to work on my social anxiety. And then in the future about this second thing , only if I want (what does she means,of course I want to work trough this transference, because I felt bad and anxious!)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-05 17:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Italy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-06 21:13:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I felt like this. It sucks. You don't have to stay like this forever! I think you should make a step, and try to reach for help...i started therapy 1 month ago and it was the best decision i ever made! even if my SA isn't improved a lot...but you have to start with small steps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Therapist doesn't talk about medication</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-07 20:22:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I started therapy 1 month ago and we are doing cbt and now exposure exercises. My therapist (a private one) told me that I have SA but she never mentioned any type of medications. Is it normal?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-07 23:45:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a bit worried about medication...don't know why. Maybe i think i'll feel less "normal"...i think that cbt is working, but it's very hard. I have to repeat and repeat the exercises, because i always tend to return to my warped thoughts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-08 15:02:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to wait and see if cbt alone works.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are you anxious before or during therapy?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-08 15:05:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm really anxious when I have therapy. It's not the therapist, I like her and now I feel love towards her too! But I'm always afraid that she will judge or get mad /disappointed at me if I'm not doing well. . At the end of our appointment last week I told her and she wanted to know how much I was anxious with her. I gave my anxiety an 8. How can you cope with this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-08 21:17:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thans. I told her during the last session, and during another one. I think that when i first started therapy, i had anxiety because i felt uncomfortable of sharing some of my problems. Now i have a sort of transference towards her, i feel love, and i think the anxiety is here (and so strong) because of this love i'm feeling. I like and love her, and i fear that she may leave me, if i do something wrong...so thats why im afraid of her "judgements" even if i know they are not real, and she isn't here to judge and criticize me! She told me that first we are working on my SA. And in the future, we will work on this transference (she didn't tell the name, i think she is waiting for me to open up more, and be more explicit).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-09 20:57:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm curious about it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-10 17:25:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm curious! I'll try the app....this is a common pattern for me too. I'm afraid that others will find me boring, annoying, and so that's why i tend to isolate myself. But at the same point i really crave the connection with others.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>what if you fail at exposure exercises?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-10 17:33:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>With my therapist i started to do exposure exercises. She gave me this homework for this week, where i have to talk to a girl, she was a friend of mine during my first year of university. Then we lost contact, for no reason. And so i'm afraid that she left me beacuse i was annoying, boring, shy...as a consequence i'm not able to talk to her, i see her during classes but i always feel anxious. So my task is to talk to her about random things, or to simply say "Hello how are you?..." I want to try. I'll see her on thursday. But what if i'm not able to do this? I'm afraid that my therapist will be "mad" at me, or i'll disappoint her. I know this is not true, she's a therapist, maybe she's used to it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-11 15:03:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>But if you don't do the action (for ex. talk to that girl) you can't collect "proofs" or evidences...my therapist said to me..you may remain with the idea of "she thinks i'm boring etc.."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-12 15:33:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't do it.. I saw the girl only one time today but lessons already started... I could sit with her but I couldn't do it. Great. Let's see what my therapist will tell me...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-12 17:10:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same. I don't care so much about other people. And when I'm hungry too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-12 17:11:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too. I think maybe other people will say "what the f is she doing"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-12 17:18:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why I'm feeling so hurt? I want to cry and I think she doesn't give a fuck about me. Maybe she was annoyed because I wasn't talking so much? I felt fine today until now... Now I'll think about it this evening and tonight too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-12 17:23:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes during high school. I was shy and didn't speak, so I spent 5 years alone in the class.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What a shitty therapist appointment</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-12 17:52:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know I'm disappointed. I go to therapy for my social anxiety, I did 6 sessions. We did the ABC exercise with some situations that gives me anxiety. Then I told her I wasn't able to do my first exposure exercise... She said that it's ok but I have to try again. And then I felt like she didn't care about me, she stayed silent a lot, she asked me stupid questions like "what's your day usually, what do you do, about my future and student life..." what the f ... Are you serious? I was anxious, because I love her (transference lol) and it gives me anxiety... I don't know she felt distant. Like she was questioning me! Not in a caring way! She told me if I wanted to talk about something... I wanted to tell her about other stuff like suicide (I thought about it in the past) but I wasn't able to. I feel like she doesn't want me and I want to cry I feel bad. Why I'm feeling so hurt? I think she doesn't give a fuck about me and maybe she was annoyed because I wasn't talking so much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-12 21:02:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wrote a letter before. I talked about this, about my transference, my love for her, how i felt after the session etc...and i really want to give her the letter next week. I have to do it! I'm not able to say this to her...i feel too embarassed. So, i was thinking....at the end of the session, i can give the letter to her...and say something like "i wrote this, i want you to read this when i leave the session." And we can talk about it during the next appointment! I'll die of shame...._.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can i give a letter to my therapist</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-12 21:11:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Today i felt bad after the session, because i had thoughts like "i love my therapist, but i'm so anxious because i fear she doesn't care\she finds me boring\i'm afraid i'll lose her....". I feel like i love her...and today she asked me some questions that i didnt like, or that gave me anxiety (for ex. talking about my future...). So i wrote a letter, and it's very explicit. I wrote about my anger for her too! Now i want to give that to her, at the end of the next session. I don't want to be there when she reads the letter...so i'll give her the letter, i'll say something like "take it, read it when i leave!". Does it seems like a good idea?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-12 22:26:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>for example...i wrote: "then she asked me some things like "how do you feel about your future, or what do you do during the day" which i found superficial and irritated me...like, are you serious?" or "when i leave therapy, i feel bad...how the fuck i'm supposed to face another week on my own?".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-12 22:27:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>or i wrote "I'm sure i feel 'love' for her...i idealize her... etc"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-12 22:28:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>i can't read it with her ._. it's embarassing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-12 22:31:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, her office isn't where i live. I'll give it to her next week...of course i'll be really anxious. But i think i'm able to manage it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My therapist suggested me to search for volunteering groups</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-13 10:51:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean...she diagnosed me with social anxiety, she wasn't so explicit, but she said it. Now, we are doing a first exposure exercise. I told her that i'm really scared to talk to an ex friend of mine. And also that i'm scared to go out with my classroom group for dinner. I dropped an apprenticeship i was doing for my anxiety... And at one point in session she told me "you can search for volunteering groups during the summer, you can do a work experience..." So how i'm supposed to do volunteer? To work?? She knows that my anxiety is that bad, i'm not even able to talk to that girl! She told me that we have to make small steps...ok, but for me searching for a work\volunteering is a huge step! My anxiety is so bad! I wanted to tell her, but i was afraid she would think "wow, you can't do nothing..." things like that. .___.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-13 10:53:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, it helps me to feel less alone with my problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-13 12:13:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>When i was in high school it was a common situation! My classmates treated me like a child, because i didn't talk, i appeared insecure, quiet. And i have a "cute" face for others too...i mean, it's not necessarily a bad thing. But SA can block and limit you, so it's a problem. You could tell that you have SA. I really want to be honest with people, and tell them "i act like this because i have SA!". I'm too embarassed to do it...but i think it will be a good idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-13 12:36:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. Is it normal that im feeling so bad after that session, like i'm hurt? I thought about cutting myself yesterday to not feel like this...i don't want to eat today, i want to cry,i think i'm a burden, and i'm afraid to lose my T.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm so mad at my therapist and i feel guilty about it</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-13 22:43:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because she is a good therapist. I mean, i started to see her 7 sessions ago. She handled well some of my problems. She was gentle and caring. I started to think about her after sessions...i started to feel a sort of love. I know this is a normal process in therapy...But. Due to my anxiety i always fear i'll say something stupid, or that she finds me boring, and i'm scared of the thought of her leaving me. Last session..i felt that she stayed silent for a long time than usual, she didnt asked me insightful questions. I found myself very irritated because she asked me pointless things like "what's your usual day\how do you see your future?". What the...I didnt know how to respond. I don't know, this irritated me! I felt like she was questioning me, and then she stayed silent. I left the session and felt really bad. Like i wasn't able to speak, or to connect with her! I thought "ok, maybe she hates me\i didnt say something meaningful.." then i felt anger towards her. Why did you ask me those questions? I thought about the session all day, i felt really sad, i didnt want to eat, i cried. I feel anger! I want to get mad at her, to yell at her! I'm scared. I had the impression she didnt care about me. Why? I don't want my week end to be ruined by this stupid session!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-13 23:09:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks :) My therapist never talked about medications...but i want to tell her all of this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-14 11:44:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, but this isn't the first or second time i see her. It was my 7 session. Or maybe i'm expecting too much?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Silence in therapy made me angry</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-14 16:59:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wrote some post about how i was feeling bad, and hurt after my therapist session. I had the impression that my T didn't care about me, found me annoying or boring, and i was scared (and i am right now) that she didn't want me. I'm terrified she will leave me. So i felt anger towards her. Great. Now i think that all of this came up because she stayed silent more than usual. I hate silences in therapy...i didn't know what i was supposed to say, maybe she wanted me to break the silence? So, i associated the fact of her being silent, with the thought "she hates me\i'm boring etc". I want to write about it because i was obsessed with it, i felt bad, but now i'm feeling a bit better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-14 20:44:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, maybe she wanted me to take the initiative, because usually she always start first and asks me questions. Because i don't know where to start :D Or maybe she was simply tired.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-14 20:46:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to tell her. I have the right to do it, but i'm scared of her reaction. I think all of this is connected with my transference with her. She doesn't know, i dropped some hints during our conversations, but i have to be explicit. I don't know if she will focus on transference, she does cbt, i heard that cbt therapist don't focus so much on tranference and feelings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-15 14:26:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the root of my anxiety might be my fear of abandonment, of making connection with others and i'm scared they will leave. I was thinking this...maybe my anxiety is like a defense, if i'm anxious around people i won't stay with them, so it may prevent them from leaving (?). But it's too complicated!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-15 20:26:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm thinking that for me it depens on the behaviours of other people too. For example, if i (an introvert with social anxiety) talk to a person similar to me (introvert, shy) i have more problems, i can't open up, because the other person is like me too, maybe he\she doesn't know what to say, and me neither! But, if i talk to an extrovert, or a person who is funny, or who talks with everyone, i feel less judged and i'm more able to open up. Because that person always knows what to say, and i tend to "imitate" her\his behaviour (so i'll talk more, or be more funny, or laugh...).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-16 11:57:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I have the same impression! And i find that when i'm able to speak more naturally with others (like i do when i'm alone or with family) i act more spontaneously! It's a bit difficult but i'll try more this week!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-17 15:24:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>It can be a good exposure exercise! If you have friends or anyone in your family you can ask them and go to the gym together. Maybe with someone that give you a sense of safety. Or you can go when it's very early or one hour before the closure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fear of abandonment and SA</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-17 15:34:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought about the connection with those two. In therapy I feel this fear with my T... Im afraid I will say something that will bother, annoy, or disappoint her. And that she will "leave" me. I mean, I fear her leaving physically, but also her not supporting me, or that she won't understand me anymore. That's why I'm super anxious with her. This though left me depressed all week, I wasn't able to function! I didn't felt anxious but depressed. This is a common pattern... In every relation I fear that the other will leave. I was thinking that maybe SA is like a defense? Because if I have SA I can't form a connection with people so nobody will leave me. It's me leaving others. I left on purpose some people because of this way of thinking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I can't tell my therapist how I feel</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-19 14:03:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>When she said to me how I'm doing, I can't tell her that I feel bad. I think I feel exposed... Or I feel shame. But I'm no fine. Today I'll try to tell her... It's so difficult.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm so embarrassed with my T now</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-19 17:39:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>So today I told her that I think the root to my anxiety is my fear of abandonment. I noticed that in my relationships I'm afraid of this. I realized this with my T, because I'm attached to her and I always fear that I might disappoint her or whatever, and then she will detach from me, leave me. I didn't tell her about my transference I only said that I'm sad every time I leave therapy. And that I'm afraid of deluding her. And now I'm feeling so embarrassed, I want to hide under a blanket! :) Do you think I did it right? I'm thinking oh why I said that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-19 22:42:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>But sometimes I think she is watching me with a strange look in her eyes...like "what is she saying... I know maybe I'm thinking too much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-20 11:04:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for your answers! Lol I thought that maybe this attachment is too much and exaggerated,maybe she thought I have some problems ._.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-20 14:05:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you shouldn't stop going but face this problem.. Maybe tell your therapist about it... Like "Im not really able to open up with some things/problems ... The best way is always to be honest. Unfortunately I can't be totally honest... But she notice it when I'm not telling the truth, and so at the end I always tell her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-20 14:13:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not English too, I'm Italian! But I want to write here because it's anonymous and because I need to know that there's always someone who is like me, who has the same problems! I feel less alone :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-20 14:19:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to say that you shouldn't worry about that! I mean it's anonymous and nobody know you in person. If you are not mean with others I don't see a problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-20 14:23:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Watch your phone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-20 16:52:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I noticed that some of my relationship patterns shows up with her too. For example my fear of losing people. It show up in therapy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-20 19:45:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can relate. I thought about suicide 3 times in my life, now i'm 21. My recent thoughts were present two months ago. I never had the courage to do it. I thought, what about my parents? And my family, my sister, my cousins, everyone? I was afraid of them worrying about me. I think suicide will devastate and ruin others lives! You think that nobody cares, but someone cares about you (family, even some friends). I was also afraid of failed attempts. If i survive an attempt, how can i explain to them my act, my ideation? I will feel embarassed, full of shame. But sometimes i start to think "I regret to not had the courage to kill myself".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I want to change my carrier because of my SA?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-20 20:01:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm an italian university student. 3 years ago i had to choose a university. I decided to do social work, which is 3 years long. During the 2nd year we had to do two apprenticeships. During my second one, i started to have serious problems because of my SA. I felt blocked, i wasn't able to speak, i was really anxious, to the point of shaking, of not wanting to live...In the end i was able to pass all of them, but i think that the second one didn't went well, as i was expecting. Then this 3d year i did another apprenticeship, but i quit it because of my SA. I started to think that maybe i don't like very much social work, the profession itself. I wanted to choose another "path" after this university, which is social educator. I really want to do a work where i will help people with their problems. For me social educator was different from social worker. During my last session with my therapist, we spoke about that. I said to her "I'm scared about my future, i don't know what to do anymore!" and I also said this sentence:" If i were extroverted, i'd become a social worker!". So my therapist said to me "This sentence is important, because it's like you think that you can't do this work because you have SA, or you are shy...But if you didnt have this problem, you would do that without doubts!". That's true. She told me to see if i want to change carrier only because of my SA. I don't know if i'm making sense. ._. I don't know how to explain this properly. But any of you felt like this? Its like i want to run from this work, to escape from it because i think i can't stand it if i have SA.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-20 21:40:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you said "that cost is the pain caused by your SA" it makes me thing about the fact that i can't tolerate my SA. It's not only limited to anxiety, but to other emotions (sadness, rage...). when i feel those emotions, i feel pain, because i'm not able to tolerate them, they are too intense. I couldn't tolerate to feel so anxious at the point of shaking when i had to do some tasks during my apprenticeship. Today i felt another thing. I was more able to accept my SA, i thought "ok, now i feel anxious, but i don't care, i have to talk with this person etc..." so i did it anyway. And by staying with my emotion, i was able to reduce my anxiety! That's great, and it makes me think that if i can tolerate this "pain" i will be more able to do things anyway. So i think that's it's negative because it makes me feel in pain, and also i think : "I, as a future social worker, can't be so anxious when speaking with people! If i'm anxious i can't be a good social worker".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-21 11:28:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>With my therapist we talked about this too. I think that maybe my fear of abandonment is the cause of SA...but it's so strange and difficult. Before therapy, i never think about it...i mean, i didn't felt this fear so much. Then, i started to felt it with my T, and i noticed that in all of my previous relatinoships i had it. ._.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-21 21:46:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I find that after a while i feel drained when i socialize with people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-22 17:59:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only during high school i hide in the bathroom during the morning break which was of 15 min. I felt very embarassed, but i didn't like to stay with my classmates, because i was the only one who didn't speak, i felt out of place.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-22 21:08:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It depends. I think without social anxiety, i would be more extrovert. I like people, i feel good when i'm able to talk more, or to enjoy myself with others! But then sometimes i need to stay alone, and i feel drained when i socialize more than I usally do. But here I am, with anxiety. I think it's a part of me. I don't know if anxiety can be seen as a part of our personality. Because there are people who said that you can resolve SA, and be anxiety free. I don't know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-25 22:16:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm 21 and I thought about suicide 3 times in my life. The third one was two months ago, and during that period I started therapy because I was scared of my thoughts. And yes, it was connected with my SA. I don't know if I'm really fine now. I'm not suicidal and im working on my SA and I notice some progress! But I can't talk about suicide, my therapist doesn't know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I don't know if i'm fine</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 17:40:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>So in the last week i found that my SA decreased during social situations, i was more confident and tried exposure exercises (decided with my therapist). My SA is here, but it's a bit decreased. Yesterday i went to therapy, and i said that i was fine, i was feeling good, because one hour before i went out with some of my classmates from university. She said that i was looking good, that she saw my happiness. But i really don't know if i'm fine. Sometimes i feel sad, sometimes happy, and excited, sometimes even hyperactive. There's always a reason, mostly because i think about something. And my emotions could change during the day. I don't know if in an hour i will be sad. Or happy. I don't know if this makes sense...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 23:15:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, it could be that i'm feeling more emotions than usual! I remember when i started therapy i only felt anxiety, sadness, and somedays i felt emptiness. Now i don't feel empty anymore, but different emotions. I think that maybe these emotions are too much, it's strange for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-28 15:20:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I went to different parties this year, usually with a friend of mine because I feel more safe, less anxious by her side. Some parties I was able to talk more, ok mostly because I drank a few. And others I didn't talk to anyone only to my friend. But that's OK! I think I was brave because I went to the party instead of avoiding it so it was a big step. You have to make small steps, it's great you went to that party! And even if you didn't talk a lot it doesn't means it was bad. If you have a friend it's good to go with them because at least you can talk to someone that makes you feel safe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-28 15:32:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same with me! I think it's like a suppressed part in ourselves, because of SA. I think it's important to acknowledge it and give it expression but we have to learn how to regulate our emotions because it isn't always the right thing to yell at people, in my opinion. For example in some situations I noticed that I felt an intense anger to the point I wanted to treat really bad a person, I started to have aggressive ideas, like scenarios in my mind. I think it's a part of me that was suppressed by SA. But I can't act on the impulse I have to learn how to regulate my anger. I think a good solution is to learn assertivity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-28 15:39:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, it's true that I'm really hyper aware of changes in my emotions. And then I freak out because I think I don't feel I'm in control. Anyway I think I'll try to feel my emotions more, as you said it's normal, and an emotion have to make its course. Thank you :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Painful feeling in my chest when i'm sad?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-28 21:16:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have this feeling during the day, if i think about a painful memory, or when i feel sad. I feel a painful feeling in my chest. It's like a tingling sensation, i think there's some adrenaline but not too much, that "goes" around that area. It's a mix of sadness + anxiety, i don't know how to describe it! It's connected with sadness and when i think about something that makes me sad, even a small thing... i find that i have this sensation when i think about the fact that a person important to me could leave me, even if it's not going to happen, its only in my mind. Is it involved loneliness maybe?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 12:14:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>i want those glasses!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tatoo idea</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-02 21:32:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really want to tatoo "peace will win, fear will lose" on my wrist. I give it my own meaning, and importance. At first i wanted to tatoo the entire lyric. But then i had this idea to give it a symbol, because someone said "if you tatoo lyrics\names\quotes maybe in ten years you will read them and find that you don't want them anymore, because maybe you change or aren't so connected with the original meaning". So instead there's this idea where i can create a symbol or image to represent that lyric. As time pass i can reinterpret it in different ways. I'm asking for some advice. I'm thinking about a small image, or something more stylized. I will think about it. Maybe some of you can give me some inspirations.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-03 21:45:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>english isn't my mother language</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-04 22:11:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I went to a therapist one month ago, for the first time in my life(i'm 21)! Obviously for SA. At first i was terrified, scared, anxious. But she was very supportive, caring, gentle, she alway treated me well...to the point that now i'm having transference towards her! I like her so much! I want to say that i love her, but this is only due to my transference. :) I'm more able to open up, it takes time. And - most important thing - i had success! We are doing CBT to work on my warped thoughts, and we did three exposure exercises that went well for me! I think my anxiety is decreased...i have it, i mean, it's not disappeared, but it's better now! I really hope this will last...i'm scared of relapses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My SA is decreased but</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-04 22:35:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't feel well. In fact, i feel sad, don't know if it's depression. I feel sad, somedays really tired. I wake up well, but then during the day i feel more tired. I feel i want to cry everyday, and i have this horrible sensation of being "stab" in the chest by this sadness. But there are reasons for this. I think i feel like this because i feel lonely. I i really want to hang out with friends, i want to laugh with them, to spend the time in company. But i can't because i dont have a large group of friends where i live. I made some friends during my 3 years of university, but now i've finished the year and i don't see them because we live in different cities. And when i think about it, i feel the sadness "stab". I feel this stab when i think about my therapist too. And this make me feel confused, like i'm weird. I'm experiencing transference towards her, i feel a platonic love. And this week i didnt see her so i miss her. So maybe i feel this sadness because of my therapist too. I want to see her, during the dsy i think about her (she doesn't know this, i've shared with her only a little of my feelings). I feel weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-04 22:40:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>She works in a private service associated with my university. I didn't choose her, i only ask for an appointment and they "assigned" me her. She mostly work with CBT, she recommended it, i did some researches and i found that CBT have positive effects on those with anxiety. So many therapist use this on their work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 14:34:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too! Maybe it's because of summer...during the year i had university, so i had to go out, i went out with friends\classmates. But now that's summer i won't see them often, and where i live i have one close friend. And i think "what if i do nothing on this summer? i don't want to stay at home all day". I have to get out of the routine. To motivate myself i think that i'm going to do one or two different activities during the week. I'll start with simple things, like play a sport that i love, or go for a walk, or meet with my close friend, and stay in contact with her!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Transference toward my therapist: the need to be in a relationship with a significant other</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-07 17:02:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Before therapy i thought i wanted to be alone,it wasn't a problem, i didn't think about being in a relationship with someone (as a friend or as a lover). Now that i'm experiencing transference with my T i feel the need to have a strong connection with someone, to love someone (both boys or girls, it's indifferent to me, but my T is a girl, and i really want to be in love with a girl, more than a boy. Could it be that this transference has reawakened my need to have a meaningful relationship?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I should tell this to my therapist but i don't have the courage</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-10 11:26:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yesterday my T asked me if there are things i'm not able to tell her, and that i avoid. I said yes, in fact there is one thing, about my past suicidal thoughts. I thought about it 3 times in my life, when i was a teenager in high school , 2 years ago and 2 month ago (the thoughts only lasted some weeks) There were reasons behind these thoughts, i found myself in situations where i felt trapped, and it was connected with my social anxiety. I think it's an important topic, and i don't know if i'm really "free", i don't know if in the future i will think about it again, who knows. But everytime i think about it, i start to cry because it's a strong and triggering topic for me. I didn't want to think about suicide, i wish i didn't have these thoughts i feel weird. So i think that next week she will ask me again, and i want to be ready and talk to her. I think i'll start to cry and i never cry during therapy! How should i tell her? She said that i can write too if i'm not able to talk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-12 18:35:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think next session I'm going to tell her. I wrote my thoughts so if I'm not able to speak I will show her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-12 18:50:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wrote something, I'll show her because it's important and im paying so if I lie with her it's like a waste of precious time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Transference and I'm afraid to see my therapist everywhere</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-13 10:30:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some days I think about my T, for my transference issues. I like her because she is the only person that cares for me, and I think I have the need to be taken care of. It's like a sort of love, but it's not love, I don't know her as a person. I like her as a therapist. So I'm afraid to meet her outside therapy. She doesn't live near me, but in another city very far from mine. But when I go to therapy I'm afraid too see her outside the building. And sometimes I see strangers and if someone is similar to her I feel very anxious. For example right now Im seeing a person in distance who looks like her and I thought "what if it's her oh i don't want to be seen" Anyone else had this fear? How can I cope with it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-13 14:52:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some days more than others. But I don't feel confident, I always tend to compare myself with others, I think everyone is better than me, or more beautiful than me, I'm very judgmental with myself. I also feel I'm not enough. For example I have to write my thesis but Im not able to start because I'm afraid what I write won't be enough. I have low self esteem in general regarding my skills and aspect too (I feel I'm less cute or beautiful than others, and recently even less skinny and this is very stupid because that's not true at all). I don't know how to resolve this sometimes I fake it and think I'm good and capable enough, even if I don't feel like that, I do stuff or meet people pretending to be confident. And that's why sometimes I act like a "snob" person, but in reality I'm faking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are your parents hyper protective?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-13 19:41:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm 21 and they treats me like a child. Maybe there is a connection with SA. What do you think?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-13 22:49:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do wat I want and on my own but they are still hyper protective, but I tend to don't listen to them and do what I want.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-14 09:40:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe it's because they tend to be anxious too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anguish?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-14 10:20:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every day I feel a weight on my stomach, and I think it's anguish or maybe it's connected with depression? It's very painful and sad. I told my therapist and she wrote down on her notes but didn't say it's depression.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-14 15:00:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>DAE feel like this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-14 16:14:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>For me there isn't a reason, I don't feel guilty. I feel very lonely in my family, with friends, with people, and uncertain about the future, I don't know what to do after University because of my social anxiety... I can't manage a work, I'm scared.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to cope with old sh scars</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-14 16:20:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm at the sea right now with parents. I have 4 scars on my left arm, and right leg, they have 4 years or more. I don't do self harm anymore, it's been 2 month I think even more. I'm really embarrassed, I don't know how to reply and sometimes my parents point out my scars and I think it's disrespectful but they don't know I had issues. They think my scars are ugly to see and im even more embarrassed and feel bad. My therapist said that I don't have to feel that way because my scars are old, when I was a teenager but now I'm better and that's the important thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>