<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject501</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-03 16:54:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Promotional nights are great. They generally have enough for everyone, but it is "while supplies last." Sometimes they pass items out before the games, but have since adjusted to distributing items after the games at the exits. They do this to avoid any chance of everyone throwing their bobble head into the ice for some odd reason (See other clubs' giveaway nights.) As for your tickets... It doesn't matter where you but them, as long as they are valid you're good to go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-12 04:05:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>You posted this a long time ago, but I once found a ladybug in my pancakes. No big deal to me, kept eating. Mom complained. Manager came over and said, "sorry, we don't usually put ladybugs in our pancakes. Your meal is on us." Ate around the thing and enjoyed. Could only imagine someone losing their mind and asking for god knows what. Some things aren't a big deal... I respect you for keeping your cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-27 00:53:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Take the time to watch as many games as you can. Additionally, there is valuable information (most of the time) in the intermission/post game reports. Also, if you have the means, try to go to some games. The experience is completely different than that of watching it at home. Lastly, partner up with an existing hockey fan, who hopefully won't mind explaining the game while it's happening. I love getting to teach people about the sport, and have been able to make new fans out of most. There are a few good apps that can also keep you abreast of current league happenings. Start by reading up on icing and offsides... These are always the first two things people ask about, and happen more often than other "whistled plays." Have fun!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-29 23:28:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a picture out there where a kid used "Everything is life has purpose. You, Chickens, a midget at a circus." But it was edited to be more PC Other favorites are: "Let me get your cat girl, no Hathaway" "I ain't parking unless the meter's green, homie" "I got seven shots in me, three condoms on me and immeasurable hope" There's the ex boyfriend song with the line "he was plus 8 like John and Kate" but, you could totally slide something in under the radar with "I'm plus 8 like John and Kate." Have fun! There's plenty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What happened the first time you got drunk?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 10:01:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 10:16:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something tells me you can't say that and not actually deliver.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 10:17:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>How are you doing with that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 10:17:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Goodnight. Sleep tight. Don't let the j #228;ger bombs bite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 10:18:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jeff?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 10:19:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you end up finding it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 10:21:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's great man! My sister just hit 200 days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 10:23:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn't even need to read past 4 Lokos before I felt immediate empathy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 10:23:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like a midget strangling you. (Dane cook joke. Yeah, he sucks)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 10:26:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>The worst kind of bean dip.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 10:30:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You get a punch in the face! You get a punch in the face! EVERYONE GETS A PUNCH IN THE FAAAAAAAAAACE!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 11:30:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, it worked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 11:31:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Accused and folded? Or straight up "it was me!"?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 20:38:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>INBD it's my BFF Jill FTFY Edit: I was mistaken.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-02 23:51:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know, you're correct. She says "INBD" earlier in the conversation. Apologies. Link for fun: http://youtu.be/4nIUcRJX9-o</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-03 03:52:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great cake! Congratulations.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-11 17:25:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone have this with audio? It's so low, and I love these things.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-14 00:58:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Currently on vacation in Cabo San Lucas. Can confirm, those dudes are HUGE!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What was your all-time favorite movie as a kid?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-26 06:11:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-26 06:12:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>A Goofy Movie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-19 18:28:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just be cool. If someone razzes you, go along with it. Most times you get to enjoy it like any other game. Don't be "that out of town fan" that creates a scene. The worst thing to happen to me when seeing the Duck's play at another arena was a guy faking me out of a high five. Have fun! Hockey fans are the best fans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 00:46:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that sarcasm? IMO, she's terrible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 01:08:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excellent point. I think the unfortunate case is she's hired by the network for perspective/marketing. Her bench interviews and between period interviews are written for her and offer no creative leeway. There isn't really ever any substance to her interviews, as they seem forced and directed. I appreciate your insight though. This may be more of a case of poor network writing than personal performance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-22 21:53:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very satisfying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-22 23:16:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sheriffs Office (it's an indoor firing range) just south east of the Santa Ana River. $10, never full.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What was/is THE rumor at your high school?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-10 00:47:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-26 00:31:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so tired but can't get enough time for a few weeks of the best way for the next two days</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-26 18:49:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll be there as well! Have fun, dude!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>There was an angle I didn't get to see when ordering my new work boots...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 19:46:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 21:17:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>My struggle is proper "punnage".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 21:17:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Polar Fox</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 21:18:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 21:35:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>As luck would have it... Rainy day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 21:35:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Polar Fox</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 00:01:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally just needed for field walks. I'm not in construction. I needed something that "looked nice" but could take a better beating than dress shoes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 00:39:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone would need to explain my olive skin, and year round tan to the other "antifas" in their daily briefing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 00:40:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>They fit true to size. Pretty warm. Definitely more a fashion pair, but subjected to ones taste.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 00:45:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure if that's something I want to take credit for. Hahaha, but thank you for keeping others honest with their use of the picture I took.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 00:48:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never thought this was a thing or that I'd be in this sub... Thank you for the credit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 02:29:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>As I am not in politics, and have a dick, I'm afraid I am not Gloria Johnson.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 04:19:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I kampf believe it! Great job everyone!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 23:57:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh hello! That was due to my post yesterday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 03:08:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well would you look at that!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 03:11:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIFU by not posting on /r/TIFU quick enough. ....... #175;\_( #12484;)_/ #175;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 03:13:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Yeah, go ahead and leave that out..."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 03:14:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 03:16:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least they're fresh!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Photo Credit Question</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 03:22:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I recently posted a picture of an unfortunate happening regarding some "work boots" I purchased. Since posting, things escalated quickly and multiple sources have posted stories. My question is, since the picture is original content from me, and these multiple "news" sources are using it in articles, that have ads, am I entitled to any compensation from potential revenue? I just want to know what my rights are, as my photo is being used, yet I was never asked for permission. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 05:08:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yh, fck tht ns. Ths s nt n f ths "nd smtms 'y'" thngs"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 05:10:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the thorough response! This situation is definitely the first of the two options, as they are just reporting. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 05:11:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why does it fall off? Formatting thing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 05:11:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 16:02:34</DATE>
    <TEXT> #175;\\_( #12484;)_/ #175;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 20:01:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bad ass, man! I'd love to have something like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 02:26:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>418 here. Not planning on changing seats, as we have had them for quite some time. Parking passes are not included, but that's really not all that bad with the wealth of parking in the area. I haven't parked on site in years. Mentioned in another comment, benefits are 10% off team store purchases. There's additional benefits with fan appreciation events (ice skating, early admission to the 10year celebration, priority for additional seats in playoffs and others.) There are different packages, so you can start slim and work your way up. I love having them, a chunk of change at first, but totally worth it. As far as selling, it really depends on the game. Kings, easy (mentioned by another user) Cane's "who cares!" Something they've changed with ticketing is the face price. You basically pay one fee for all games (ex: mine run about $45 per ticket), but depending on the game, you'll see different face prices (kings: $108, canes: $52) All in all, season seats are awesome. I say pull the trigger. Good luck!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 18:10:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely love it. Ducks shoot towards us twice, and we are out of the way of the safety net's bar for the goal on the other side. We used to sit in the same row in 420, but when they instituted the nets, the bar at the top goes right through the other goal/crease. In my opinion, the corners lend a better vantage point up and down the boards. But, I will say, section 421 seams too always have a lot of fun. They're so rowdy and spirited. Love it. You really can't go wrong, but I'd definitely recommend picking the Zamboni side regardless, that way your have the ducks coming towards you twice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 18:11:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whattup!! Welcome! Make sure to say hi to Teri on the way in! She's a blast, and if you're nice, she hooks you up with pins and coupons and such. Cheers!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 03:06:59</DATE>
    <TEXT> #161;Orale! Vamanos Los Patos!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 03:10:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ex Dick's Sporting Goods manager here. If you asked nicely, and were cool, we would totally give you one. The displays change seasonally.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 19:27:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lodge (the department it's in) sets usually shift right at Memorial Day to make way for easy ups and chairs. You can ask then, or at Labor Day, when the department shifts out of the summer set. It also depends on if the store receives new tents. Dollars to donuts they have a couple in the back because they never all fit on the shelves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 22:59:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>IIRC it is not hunter orange, as that is far brighter. The orange they use is "Harvest Orange."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 09:32:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>None. Because that's petty and terrible sportsmanship. Fans need to support their team and accept the outcome no matter what. Yes, I hate to see the ducks lose, but a comeback should celebrate hard work, not the other teams shortfall.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 00:39:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for reminding of this movie. It has always been a staple of my childhood. "Compliance"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 20:43:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>*N*othing *B*ut *C*onnor *S*ports *N*etwork</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-08 06:43:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good sportsmanship should never be relegated to a time or place. Especially when it's as sincere as /u/bigsteve27 's was. We should be as kind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 07:20:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>418 Checking In!!! The terrace is always the loudest!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-12 05:18:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm with you. I haven't done anything to earn the right. I had dinner at Selanne's Steak House, and they offered to let me wear his gold medals... I politely said no thank you, and continued to marvel visually.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-13 23:22:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I worked for a company that insisted on BPROYG. So weird the first time remerchandising an apparel wall.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 04:48:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's part of this "floor is lava" thing going around. That's why you see everyone try to get their feet up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 04:49:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the "The Floor Is Lava" thing/meme?/trend happening right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 04:49:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>"The floor is lava" thing going around right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 05:58:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 07:55:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Shoot for the moon, something something something" - Every Third Grade Classroom Poster</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 08:04:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I think it piggy backed on the "andy's coming" fad. For the uninformed, it was this viral thing where someone would yell "andy's coming" and everyone would drop to the floor like the toys in Toy Story.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 08:08:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Super late response to your post. But I can relate. I relocated for work, and while working at that location I had a boss say, "if you ever want to go home to your family, you better do what I say!" Needless to say, I was out and back home within 3 months. Couldn't be happier. Good on you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 19:07:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Much like the rest of the world, I too played this game. I was referring to the "fad" and people posting it on social media. The rock I lived under was consumed by the lava.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-09 19:14:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depending on the use, this building is probably served by one or two 3-phase transformers. I would not anticipate the load being more than an elevator motor. What helps keep the overall demand down is having it remain constantly moving. Flicker (which generally refers to the surge in power when an AC unit, or Elevator motor kicks on) is a lot less here. My guess is that it's no more than 277/480v 3-phase service, which is your "typical" commercial building service voltage. An electrical panel schedule would answer your question thoroughly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-14 07:24:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been to the one in Moon (right by the airport)! It's a great place!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How much gold bond medicated powder would it take to cover a Shaq?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-14 08:25:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-14 08:26:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>And what does that equate to?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-14 08:26:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shaq from the gold bond commercial Shaq.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-14 08:28:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>A yes 1=1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-14 08:29:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Right Leg 2. Left Leg 3. Shaq Torso 4. Right Arm 5. Left Arm We've got 2 heads left...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-14 08:30:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stocks UP Wetness DOWN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My wife ordered a burrito with avocado for dinner this evening.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-15 06:51:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-15 07:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everyone has that *one* Mexican drive thru that usually puts ALL THE CHEESE on one side. We thought this was the circumstance, two bites, still avocado. Was not expecting all avocado.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-15 07:58:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still wanted avocado slices</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-15 07:59:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was delicious intent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-15 08:01:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sent the picture to a family text group, and my dad responded with, "I've seen that in a diaper before"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-15 08:03:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I would have offered to share, but my wife horked it down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 18:44:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can Confirm. http://imgur.com/wxPxuAn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If a country were a store, which store would it be?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-20 05:13:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-20 05:16:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would say Target. We can be a mess, but mostly have our shit together.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-20 05:21:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can respect that viewpoint.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-20 05:22:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sweden would be IKEA.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 04:24:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>"The unexamined life is not worth living." It reminds me to constantly push, and earn every day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 04:26:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I place various pictures of me throughout their house, leave an outfit or two in the closet, leave a toothbrush followed by shampoo/wash. Then I leave 1 drinking cup.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 04:28:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm guessing you're not in CA, but thanks for giving me a sunset to look forward to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 04:30:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Flameboy, 1 of the 2 'brand characters' of World Industries.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 00:34:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Less than lethal is the term used where I live.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 07:27:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>My wife and I were just reading your comment (I know it's late) but she was reading over me standing next to the bed, and literally spit on my face and hers from the burst into laughter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 18:55:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know, not as weird as the Internet/Reddit makes it sound. We have interests that overlap one another, and sometimes it's fun seeing some funny/uplifting things together before bed. I subscribe to the more "comical" subreddits for mindless perusing. It's not very frequent, but I do say. "look at this!" fairly often and show her a pic/gif. Example: She saw the "IT" trailer on TV and it freaked her out, (she's deathly afraidnofmclowns) so I introduced her to /r/eyebleach. Some threads are too good to keep telling her, "listen to this comment/post!" Plus, that's why alternate accounts exist.  #128521;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>People who are afraid to go into the ocean, why?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 06:07:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 06:07:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Godzilla lives in there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 22:57:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Testicular Torsion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-02 05:11:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>What am I missing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-02 05:24:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck, this is cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Redditors who have successfully ran from the police, how did you get away?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 04:02:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 09:05:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would have made McDonalds serve breakfast from the get go. Why? Motha Fuckin' McGriddle!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 09:07:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>This one for total browsing, the other for just my hockey subs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 09:20:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>An elderly man sitting at a desk, with a large book that contains all of the answers to life's questions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 09:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not seeing anyone who had actually had this happen. Hired an associate who participated in photographic pornography, and it was brought to my attention by an associate. A "did you know" kind of thing. I didn't. She was a sweet girl and a hard worker. It was never an issue, and never would be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 08:03:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why things are called what they are called. Fork. Crayon. Orange (Fruit and Color). Also, saying those words over and over. Roooooaaaadss.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 08:06:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Define "alone". Like, NOT one another person around? Movie Marathon at home. No known friends or acquaintances? Head to Vegas and walk the strip and Casinos. It's more fun than it sounds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 08:07:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Knee High. How choco are you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 08:11:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Get up because of a spider behind me, laugh, then ask me to grab something "while I was up".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 08:17:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Making tomorrow's chocolate?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 08:19:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Space Suit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 08:22:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trust, but verify.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 08:31:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>HR is NOT there to protect you. Get EVERY offer in writing. Always have a witness for disciplinary conversations, and write them down. Even if it's just notes. (Managers) Always triple knock before entering the opposite sex's restroom before entering for maintenance (public settings). Always ask for a copy of your offer letter, review, etc. Understand that you DONT have to sign a write up. If you're a manager, don't take it personally, but make note that the associate opted to not sign the write up. Don't think you can get away with stealing from the safe. Always stand your ground on ethical issues. If you catch flack, do you really want to be there? Remain above reproach at all times. Everyone has a target on their back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 08:37:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have always been a fan of "Inspect what you expect" too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 08:40:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be fair, I know a lot of people who can answer that with a yes. Hahaha Milk Chocolate? Or are you one of those freaks that prefers dark?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 08:42:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Said it too many times, and am now weirded out. AND I just remembered it's the same word as a dish, and a verb for a sport.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 08:48:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>All they would need to do is pop the hinges out. Also, I know nothing about lock picking, but that doesn't look like an actual lock. It it actually were, I'd imagine it wouldn't be hard to pick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mid conversation, I just heard my phone "ding".</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 09:03:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 06:47:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>What gets wetter as it dries off?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 18:21:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Huevos Rancheros</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 18:32:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was very scary at first. I had only lived at my parents until then, and I was ready for an adventure. The opportunity was great, so I took the chance. I would have monthly breakdowns over missing my family and friends, but it got easier. I made some new friends and really started to enjoy myself. I always knew I'd get back home, and when the opportunity presented itself, I changed industries and moved home. I am so grateful for the experiences I had while I was away, as it reminded me just how valuable family and friends are. Not to mention, I moved away with my then girlfriend, got a crash course in cohabitation and personal space, but grew closer and closer. We are now married just over a year. If this is an opportunity for you, I'd recommend taking it. Results may vary, but nothing varies if you don't take chances.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 18:34:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Zebra Sarasa .07, in blue. Always.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 18:38:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>The fact that it's 2017 and not all carriers let you FUCKING HIT "1" to skip ones outgoing greeting on their voicemail. Even worse when it starts the process over! Lastly, has anyone ever used the "for more options" feature! Just let me leave my fucking voicemail.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 18:41:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>The new Death From Above 1979</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 18:45:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sat in the back of the classroom, and there was a whiteboard (6'x8') behind me. I liked to rest my head in the whiteboard, but the pen/eraser tray would jab my neck. I managed to remove the entire tray (8' long), with some help, slide it along the floor towards the door, then asked to be excused. Picked it up just outside and walked it to the back of the school where I ditched it under a bungalow. Maximum comfort there on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 18:48:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd go to my nearest booming beach hotel, offer to sweep the sand off the deck, then start running bags, and other odd jobs. I'd eventually team up with the sheriff and later on become a deputy sheriff when I was older. I think thereafter, I'd get into politics and eventually run for city treasurer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 02:05:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still ring doorbells too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 03:34:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unless you have a source I have never seen, this couldn't be more wrong. The "usual" layer of pavement ranges from 2-4 inches thick (in cases wear the base already exists). Racetracks pavement are typically 6.7" thick) They most certainly scrape and repave. Clearly the picture indicates this was not always the case, but technology changes. Racetrack paving guidelines are far to stringent to allow for it to simply add another layer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 03:35:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>They scrape then repave. Racetracks are extremely regulated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 05:46:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're not a robot. Allow yourself to feel each emotion, and talk to your friends. It's ok to be upset. Process your feelings, and find a learning lesson in all of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 05:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Buy a suit, interview for a job, get a job. Make money, live in a hostel, or tent when I could afford one. Save and grow. Might as well put the abundance of new time to good use.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 05:50:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lookin good, Barry'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 05:54:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stubbed Toe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 05:56:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Coldstone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 00:19:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>The number 2 as the first digit in their age.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 00:24:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had a troublesome associate, who was scheduled to close, come to me and say he needed to leave early. The reason? He had a softball game that night (about 2.5hrs before closing). When I asked if I missed a time off request, he said no, and that he just forgot. I didn't allow him to leave, as it was imperative he stayed and helped recover. Not to mention, this company writes managers up if there's any lapse in coverage in the Golf Department. He called HR, and I was "reprimanded" for not being more sensitive to his request and needs. Neato.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 00:27:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even if you go to college full time, still have a job. A lot of employers will discount your application for a lack of job experience, or a 4 year gap. Keep working. You can volunteer, intern, anything. Just maintain work experience continuity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 00:29:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chili Cheese Dog, Chili Cheese Burger, Chili Cheese Fries. Wienerschniztel is a great hangover food. Wrecked my stomach and arteries the last time i had it though. Might rethink my choice next time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 06:18:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>How were they late when they "gained" an hour?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 20:05:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>He understands he gained an hour, right? I'm truly interested in what happened here. Hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 04:38:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe she means she uses the auto for the morning, and feeds the cat herself when she gets home(?)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 05:47:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Get there at 6:00 and you're stylin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 18:03:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Going to the movies alone is the shit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Serious] Redditors who have won a "lifetime" or "year" supply of something, what was it, and how did it go?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 03:46:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 21:43:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>People see him and pray to meet him. People see you and "periscope" because they don't want you to see them. Or it refers to "you periscoping" which would mean you are below the surface, while LD is above in total view.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 19:46:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Be 23.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 05:31:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have to agree, this is actually why I asked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 05:35:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aside from being on their period, there are very few ways a girl can enjoy sexual gratification. No tongue, no digits, no penetration. Sounds awful. (And before any one says anything, I know there are other options. ie: Butt, giving oral, feet, hand, neck, hair bun, ear, eye, back of knee, armpit, double chin, or gauged ear piercings)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 05:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I applaud your open mindedness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 06:36:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Real question... What was the problem with them raising the net?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 04:11:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, it's still good. Just watched it again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 15:18:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sad to hear about Flight of the Navigator. I made the same mistake with The Saint.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 18:26:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Name and numbers out. Always. Get yourself some frames too!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 06:27:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Two Brothers Pizza. Fountain Valley, CA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 05:19:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chicken Period</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 07:07:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whoops</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 07:08:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought we #8217;d see some amazing west coast hockey.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 07:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know, whole heartedly agree with you. Our series was just surprisingly unsatisfactory hockey.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 06:13:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone counted, and I think it #8217;s like 2:32 CB and 0:52 LD. Something around that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 02:11:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shit! You #8217;re right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 05:34:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/atbge</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 06:59:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry to say, this is far from good. BPM =/= visual cohesion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 05:44:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>*LIAR* is really weird to read spelled out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 23:44:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>No shit, I thought the same thing. Dont know where it came from though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 07:25:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rented a bounce house for ever Birthday up to 28. Just got one for my niece this past weekend, and you know I was in there jumping around. Some places actually have some designed for adults. Timeless fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 08:22:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a myth, and 100% not true. There has to be proof that you had operated the vehicle. If you #8217;re still worried, Sleep in the passenger seat, or back seat if you have one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 08:37:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Real Question: What is with all the gifs with that watermark lately?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 08:08:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gif1 Gif2 Gif3 Best chat rooms for this. I remember when Gif1 would be at capacity, and you #8217;d have to scramble to the others, but still wanted to get into Gif1. I hope I #8217;m not the only one who remembers this. Man I loved AOL at midnight. So long my gray floppy in the bowl of my trophy on top of my bed. Goodbye.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 00:02:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Moroccan Oil FTW</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 07:46:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bikey!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 07:49:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>The more you toot the better you feel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 07:51:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which side of the mirror are you actually on?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 07:54:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>The shade of crayon you #8217;d like to use.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 07:55:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wake up. Grababrushandputonalittlemakeup.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 07:58:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>He really dislikes you hugging anyone else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>For those of you with siblings who are twins, and you yourself are not a twin, what was the overall dynamic growing up with your siblings?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 05:57:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 07:16:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s almost exactly why I asked. My wife and I wondered if that would be tough due to the connection twins tend to have with one another. Thanks for replying, even though you #8217;re the only one. Cheers! Edit: Well their response *was* the only one at the time. Glad to see all the responses now. It #8217;s all so interesting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 08:52:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a great perspective. Thanks for sharing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 08:59:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems like there is a substantial gap between those of you commenting. It #8217;s interesting to hear. I met someone who has triplets that are substantially older than there younger brother. Now in this case, they are fraternal twins, all girls. The age gap is due to conceiving in vitro, where all three eggs were fertilized. From what I #8217;ve heard elsewhere, there seems to be many cases where a family has a tough time conceiving naturally (no offense, just don #8217;t know what the appropriate term is here). Then after the first  #8220;batch #8221; it seems like they conceive again down the road, when it was thought impossible otherwise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 09:06:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>So if it #8217;s not being left out by your twin siblings, what #8217;s gotcha all grumpy? Good to hear it was normal for ya.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 09:08:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lightning McQueen better fix that road, or he #8217;ll never make it to the Piston Cup.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 09:11:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/uselessredcircle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 09:14:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>When Doom lagged.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 09:20:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know, I thought about this the other day. I spent an exorbitant amount of time bashing my, then, current company and supervisor. Didn #8217;t understand why I didn #8217;t get the job for a while. Lesson learned. Don #8217;t shit talk your current employer to a potentially new one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 09:28:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Start working as soon as it is legal to do so. Start with a job where you can work Friday/Saturday nights, and go from there. Restrictions will be different depending on where you live, but get to work. It builds discipline and responsibility. Also, working weekends still let #8217;s you focus on school. Keep up on your school work, but keep working. Experience goes a lot further in some industries, but school is still important to build a strong foundation. I started as a host working 8 hours a week. I loved the ~$50 checks, and still had a lot of time to do other things. Find something fun. Boomers, hosting, movie theater, bowling alley, etc...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 09:30:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Highly dependent on how old you are...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 09:34:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Find another person who shares the same desire. Hold each other accountable. Baby steps. Start with diet, I know people will say I #8217;m wrong, but cut every meal you would normally eat in half. Then start to adjust what you are actually eating. Start going for walks, then work up to a jog. Don #8217;t eat past 8pm, and work to an earlier time from there. It #8217;s all about creating a foundation, and growing from there. Recognize your accomplishments, but continue to grow on them. It all starts with that first step. I #8217;m sorry your parents seem to not care. Do this for yourself, and realize it all has to start somewhere. Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 09:37:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Korn - Blind</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 09:40:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where #8217;s that one with the little kids? Also, when did we enter the age where almost everything is staged? This ones not even remotely believable. What does one gain from something like this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 09:45:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>You just watch The Interview or something?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 09:46:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dozens of us!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 09:48:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s subjective, but my personal vote is for Bome Thugs - Crossroads. Edit: Leaving It.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 09:49:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go on...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 09:57:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lists. Lists. Lists. Don #8217;t preoccupy yourself trying to remember everything the day of. Write it down! Then remember, while some people say  #8220;it #8217;s her day #8221;, its also your day. It #8217;s both of YOUR days. Don #8217;t let anything or anyone take away from that. Slow down, breathe, and enjoy it. It will go by in a flash, but that #8217;s ok. Just relax and build a memory. Rely on your wedding party to help out, and assign duties. That #8217;s what they are there for, and *should* be more than willing to help. If you have a coordinator, or day of coordinator, stay in touch with them, and let them know if you need anything. EAT! Stay hydrated. Have fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:10:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Take a step back, or reach back with your hand. That #8217;s the best I got with a serious tag.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:13:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>There #8217;s so much that comes with humility too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:18:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love a good panoramic shot where something/someone moves in the middle of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:22:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be an interesting proficiency on the SAT #8217;s...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:23:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re on reddit via phone or computer. There are far quicker ways to get what you are looking for...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:24:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m here friend. I can hear you, but I can #8217;t see you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:28:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brushing your teeth with the opposite hand. Reversing the order in which you shower. Brush teeth THEN drink OJ. Parting your hair the other direction. Carry car to work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:30:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn #8217;t hire them. Not related, but I was told they OD #8217;d soon thereafter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:31:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Arby #8217;s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:33:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll be down in the basement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:35:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that a young Obama?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:36:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maniac McGee</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:41:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fiddy and Game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:41:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you behind me? I #8217;m not allowed to look.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:42:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, friend!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:44:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Isn #8217;t that the premise for that one Lohan movie?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 16:48:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m so sorry to hear that. To me, twins are simply two separate people who happen to look the same, or come at the same time, or both. While it #8217;s  #8220;neat #8221; because it #8217;s not *that* common, (I #8217;m not saying it never happens, in fact, I #8217;d love to know the stats on frequency) I don #8217;t understand the fascination, let alone the propensity to focus all of ones attention on twins. If I were the sibling of twins, I #8217;d take pride in knowing I looked like me, and only me, and maybe one other person in the world that I #8217;d someday see on an airplane and take a picture with them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 16:50:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fraternal is the word you #8217;re looking for, but, that #8217;s fascinating how things change simply because of looking alike. It seems so superficial.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 17:15:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>But did you ever stop to think how Ron felt? We #8217;ve got a lot of Ron #8217;s in this thread.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 17:15:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s great!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>