<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject9242</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIFU by being so retarded that I can't use Google Maps</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 08:21:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just got home after all this mess, I'm tired as fuuuck. My family just went camping for the past three days, for this trip it was just one of my older brothers, mom, dad, me and my dog Mac. Then my bf would be joining us on the second day(he had work and Sunday was his free day, then he was suppose to work tonight). We live in the potato state and took a 3 hour drive to our yurt we rented, near the City of Rocks. First night was chill, except my dumbass brother being an asshole in general, making everyone mad and screeching like the dick he is. He has ADD and is always being an annoying shit like it's his job. Its understandable but it's too much sometimes. Just the usual, so we ignored him like always. Everyone goes to bed everything is chill, my brother wakes me up in the middle of the night with his HOT mp-15 point at my damn brains (it was upright, but fell over when he moved around). Whatever. Go back to sleep and wake up around 7 because bf is finally here. We feast like kings and plan to go hike around for like 6 hours around on some trails. Fun shit, dad pushes me off a rock and jumps on me, nothing out of the ordinary. Later that night we have campfire pizzas for dinner, using crescent dough for our crust. Bf gobbles 4, 2 sausages and some little smokies while I ate like 3. 1st one was fucking raw, but I ate it anyways. Food is like heaven and I have an iron stomach, nothing can fuck me up. Wrong. 3rd day was the worst fucking day ever. Family decided to go on one last fishing trip before going home, I went with bf because he has limited data while I have unlimited(We also brought our little Macaroni). I get from my bf, him from my dad, dad from mom to drive to Lake Walcott. What I didn't hear is that I needed to go to Lake Walcott STATE PARK. In Google maps there is Lake Walcott and Lake Walcott State Park, the 1st having like a .3 mile difference so I thought nothing of it and picked that one to ensure quality traveling. We take separate cars and drive (it's also part of our trip home). We start driving and we are ahead of my parents, they call saying that they're getting coffee and will be a little behind. Cool, GPS has my back. Were flying down roads and before you know it, some dirt roads. No biggie, they are smooth and bf is driving his Baja Subaru, all wheels. Everything this is chill, but before you know it we turn down some super off road paths. Once again, being young and out camping, thought nothing of it. Cue like 30 min of just straight rocky, unmaintained, car jumping straight into rock piles, underbelly being cut open with t h i c c rocks and the tire being bent inwards from our shit job of a GPS route. Bf is calm but obviously stressed and I get mad ass road anxiety so I'm thinking we're gonna die by some dukes of hazard jumps and flipping the car over. We some how live, my crybaby dog didn't cry once and the car is in worse shape then it looks. Smells like burnt rubber and the car has an awful pull because of the bent ass tire. We pull into the state park visitor center to check the damage and I couldn't believe wtf just happened. Now, I'm an unapologetic cunt, but I sat the next 30 min bawling my eyes out because my bf loves his car and I felt like I singled handily murder his baby. He was very calm and understood, called my dad and he helped up through it. By then it had began to snow uncontrollably, it was cold, wet and our fishing trip was over. Towtruck wanted $900 (even after coverage), and my dad was like fuck no. The park rangers were super chill with leaving the car there for a long as we need, as this wasn't the first time something like this has happened before. We leave his car there because my dad offered to drive back with a trailer to get his car and fix it for him. Here begins another tifu story. We moved stuff around to fit everyone in and hauled everyone back home, 1 1/2 hours away. We decided to grab bk on the way to make us happy( mom thinks fast food is the devil so this is a treat to us). My parents own a 2004 pathfinder armada and the handle is a hook shape. I locked my seatbelt and began to push it back to unlock, my dog began to cry so my brother was saying "Hey" or "sit" in this super cringy deep voice to be "dominant." I get distracted and I manage to hook the still locked seatbelt around the door handle, cause the door to stay open. I freak out and after like 20 min of trying to fix it, its stuck like that and we don't have bolts to remove the seatbelt. I say fuck it because I just want to go home. I lock the door so it won't open randomly on the freeway, all while trying to lean on my poor bf being crushed by my fatass thighs and my fucking 500+ 6'3" brother so I don't cause the door to open up just in case. Now my dad, bf and I are finally feeling the effects of the raw dough and greasy burgers, oh fuck. Thankfully no hershey squirts erupted from any of us, but I sure did stank up the Maverick toilet with my garbo ass. The rest of the way was peaceful and my dad explained how the car was in better shape than it looked. Bf called boss saying that his car got into an accident and told him to call someone else to cover him. My bf just got this job and its not his problem anyways, basically tells her to fuck off (she was mad because she couldn't understand him and thought he was skipping on working, she understood him later). We get home, things were starting to look better, thank fuck. Butttt. The trailer needs to be pulled out, but my oldest brother has to move his truck out of the way, nice. Micraciously, he doesn't have work at that time and does so. Mom points out the trailer has expired tags, fuckk. Mom goes on the phone to register, dad is out pumping the tires back up while bf and I go on a coffee run to prepare us for another 6 hour trip. We come back and everything is good to go, registering was hell for my mom tho (the real mvp). With everything unpacked, dad, bf and I drive 3 hours back to Lake Walcott. Along the way, the flat tire sign came on and the trailer lights were coming off. So we pull into town and grab the last trailer lights and surprisingly the rest of the way was pretty smooth. We grab bf's car and load it up, got on fine and we strapped it in. I looked at the car and realized that there was not a single scratch on it. Wth. Now we drive back the rest of the 3 hour trip and just unloaded everything. Too easy. Everyone is too fucking tired and just bailed. All we have left is too really see the damage and get it fixed, which will be this Friday. TLDR Went camping, ate raw dough, trashed my bf baja, locked a seatbelt to my dad's car door, got Hershey squirts, had to deal with trailer issues, and drove a totally of 12 hours over something I could've avoided if I clicked a route with a similar name.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 20:41:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't hate my brother because of his ADD, he has constantly tried to get me in trouble since we were kids. He also just yells at anyone in general and tries to fight with anyone. He also is extremely self centered and thinks he is hot shit. I just mentioned it because it plays a factor in it. My uncle is redarted and I love him and I don't think he is annoying at all. I love it when he calls to tell us about his job or how his day is going. Of course I love my brother, I just think he is annoying. We just don't get along well because of our personalities, he isn't unlikable. I don't think my bf is a pussy for having anxiety and I don't think my dad is a bad father for having ADHD. I never said people with autism were annoying, anon. Hating on people with disabilities is a shitty thing to do. I tried to keep it short and probably ended up coming off that way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>At trying to spell</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 02:07:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This sprinkler sprays all over the parking lot instead of watering the grass</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 03:57:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 11:24:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't worry about it, my boyfriend was 21 when he lost his virginity and didn't have a girlfriend until he met me. I consider him lucky for not dealing with all the bs that comes with a bad relationship.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 11:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>T</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 02:37:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Help! My sister's _____ is bleeding!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 22:56:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 23:00:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First time cosplayer-need help with making these goggles/wondering what good materials that you find are a must have in general!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 12:10:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 03:24:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/SneakyBackgroundFeet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 03:31:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/pareidolia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 10:48:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/trashy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Help] Never done cosplay before and I was wondering how I could go about the patches on Kaneda's (Akira) jacket. I plan on making the entire costume 99% from scratch and if you have tips for beginners that's a +1 too.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 06:47:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 07:59:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/SneakyBackgroundFeet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 19:49:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/KidsAreFuckingStupid</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 05:58:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/Triggered</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My full grown good boy that will be a forever puppy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 23:45:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 02:41:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only thing I really see right off the bat are the skinny ankles that the kid sitting down has and the standing man has a skinny wrist but that's about it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The very first fish my bf caught and he managed to skewered it</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 05:30:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 06:11:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL as I said my bf is new so he doesn't know much I wasn't watching him when he did it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #128064; tell me all the spoilers in the movie I have yet to see it</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 13:16:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 13:18:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahhh that's what I thought I didn't like the new actor for this spiderman so that makes me happy lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 05:39:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good bot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 09:20:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>OOF</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 09:22:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is no one going to mention that Indiana Jones crystal skull headed mother fucker?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 09:27:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bad bot I've only Oofed once</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 06:38:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/SneakBackgroundFeet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 07:39:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Came for the pop, stayed for the walk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 08:01:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/aww</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 08:29:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/awwwtf</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Maybe Maybe Maybe</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 17:47:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 03:05:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Face says ugly hipster, glasses say you rape little kids.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 06:31:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oof</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 17:25:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since when does someone stating their opinion become a creepy pm? Plus op you make yourself look like an asshole with you "entitled male" bs. It just looks like you cant handle someone else opinion so you threw a fit. This is embarrassing to people who actually support minorities and equality. Oh and I'm not a white male so you can pull that card on me too sweetie ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 17:30:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me a nazi cause I said you're a baby? Oof, I dont believe in what he said and neither in yours. You're the one who sounds like a nazi because people aren't forming to your idea of perfect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #128064;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 09:16:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I might break up with my boyfriend</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 09:57:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just to start off-heyy and I'm typing from my phone. Also this will be messy as I'm just typing it along the way and I know this isnt the worse thing to happen to someone. I don't have any friend so I haven't told anyone about this-hopefully it qualifies as a confession. Sorry if it isn't and I hope this doesnt break rule 4(I'm not really looking for relationship advice). I've been with my boyfriend for 1 1/2 years and I've been living with him for most of that time as well. I love him very much, but there are some days where I just can't stand him. I've been in several abusive relationships so I think I know what a bad relationship is lol. He isnt anything like those past guys tho. Going back to me being a whiny girlfriend, I just cant stand when he complains about something. He really makes a mountain out of a molehill and its driving me insane. I understand everyone takes life differently and we all have issues, but he even treats things that have fucked me up (before I've met him) as his own life issue. Not long before our relationship, I was taken advantage by an older man. I told him this and my past relationships because I feel like he should know these things. Almost 2 years later and he has crying fits about how I ruined HIS life with what "I" did. How he wish I never told him such things. Recently I loaned him $1000 to help him pay for classes and I told my mom this. My mom is a CFO so she handles her money well and she was curious about how I was doing in regards to money and us. I tell my bf when I got home and he just gets really upset. Going on about why I shouldn't have told her and asking what I said (literally "I loaned him some money so he can get by, he will pay me back soon). That was like 8 hours ago and he is still mad at me as I type this. Everytime he throws his fit he always asks me if I'M done being upset "for no reason". (At the end of typing this he just asked me if I was done for being "mad at him") Going back to relationships, I have a really hard time talking about how I really feel. In my childhood I was always pushed to the side because "my cuts weren't as deep as so-and-so." Most of my life people never cared about me, I never has friends to talk to or anything like that. Sometimes I just have bad days and when I try to reach out to him he seems to question why. I'm thinking I might have depression/bpd/fucked up brain lol something, but I'm too afraid to go to therapy because of my constant rejection. I know therapist are helpful and they dont reject people but ya know. So I try to talk it out with my boyfriend, he usually says something like "why are you depressed? You aren't the one constantly worrying about money" (I worked every since 16 and saved up money-I hardly spent it). It's just throws me off because he's my boyfriend and I do all in my power to help him and listen to him but he doesnt really do the same for me. The only reason why I'm not really going forward with breaking up with him is because a lot of my things are at his house and I'm not sure if I really want to deal with all of that right now, maybe slowly over time. These are just a few of my conflicts with this boy. I generalized the whole thing for you guys. If you need more context just ask and I'll tell to the best of my ability. I know I painted my boyfriend as a bad guy, I love him a lot but I'm honestly considering breaking up with him. I've been in relationships where I can think I can fix my partner only to be thrown under the bus so I'm wondering if this is the same thing again for me. He tells me how he wants to marry me and this and that but it seems like he gets mad at me for such little things. I'm sorry if this isnt a confession, I just needed to get this off my chest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 10:29:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks that makes me feel a little more hopeful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 17:28:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol it's like you read my mind with that last comment. I rarely ever loan out my money, I was kinda tired of hearing him complain (I know I'm a jerk). He is actually giving the money back with some interest in the next few days. Thank you input, I'll try to talk about it with him today.  #129303;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 17:30:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I needed that lol thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why are you filming?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 22:53:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 00:03:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Smh more like the Protector of Virginity with those crocs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 07:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/awwwtf</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 18:09:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/SneakyBackgroundFeet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 06:40:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>You misspelled girlfriend</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I was just as happy as this little guy when I got my headphones!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 06:58:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Good boi does a good boi fit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 21:16:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>NSFW. Oof. Penis inside of bottle with wasps. Oof.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 00:09:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>HmMmM??</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 18:57:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 02:15:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>What an absolute unit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mom's special!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 06:11:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 06:56:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>To repost? Yeah</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 08:55:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/OSHA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 09:41:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bruh, you have to tell us this story.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Oof, this sub in a nutshell right here.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 09:46:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 07:02:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/WTF</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 05:12:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is true I was the thunder</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 18:50:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is true I was the mall</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 18:53:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/ChargeYourPhone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Selfie boye</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 10:25:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>WCGW when you jump down some stairs on a scooter.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 07:59:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>