<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject3883</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-26 09:03:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>i think this probably goes under [plot]</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-26 09:15:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe she's just really damn depressed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-26 09:27:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>i think that the necessary knowledge was literally encoded in their food when they were grubs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-26 09:38:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who is the loneliest character in Homestuck?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-14 10:09:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Circumstantial simultaneity or whatever it was the good Doctor called it, I believe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-12 12:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Write a strong character who happens to not be male. Problem solved.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-25 07:09:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>an item that gives you damage reduction but only allows you to move in a direction perpendicular to the direction you're firing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-25 07:12:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>a quick-charge item that teleports you to the opposite position in the room (i.e. if you're in the nw corner you move to the se corner, etc)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-25 07:14:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>a powerful damage-up item that makes your tear hitboxes very small</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-25 07:18:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>an item that gives tears down and gives your tears miniature clones of your orbitals</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-25 07:21:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>a bomb item that causes your bombs to spawn 3-4 spiders when they blow up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-25 07:29:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>a familiar that seeks out the closest nonboss enemy and "possesses" (charms) them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-25 07:30:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>already exists, 2 for 1 though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-25 07:40:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>a bomb upgrade that creates a brimstone/technology-style beam connecting it to isaac and causes your bombs to take twice as long to blow up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-25 07:46:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>a shop item that increases the proc rate on all status effect tears/loki's horns/etc</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-25 07:53:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>an item that blindfolds isaac; all enemies in the room with isaac take chip damage over time based off of isaac's tear stats</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-25 08:01:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>an item that tanks your luck and boosts everything else</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What are the current recommended quality of life mods for this game?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-14 18:48:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My gnomad monks are dying of thirst.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-16 05:04:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Two of them have keeled over. I have plenty of yak's milk, orange wine, and well water. What gives? Are they just training themselves to death?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-16 07:20:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah, they had access to all of the above.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-11 10:30:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>i would like this, if only for the increased survivability of allies. why must you suicide unnecessarily, my monkey friends :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-11 10:38:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>today i learned that if you quaff-id levitation you better wait for it to wear off before quaffing the rest of your stuff if you're hoping to use water/mud nearby in case of accidental incineration</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-11 11:17:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>ran into a wraith at the start of depth 7, tried polymorphing it, which turned it into a dar blademaster, threw a potion of confusion at it, nearly got away before it slowed me and i was overtaken by the cloud, then a vampire bat got me i had not yet fully ided the spear of quietus, regardless of its enchantment it didn't save me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's your general starting M.O.?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-12 13:26:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is to say, how do you tend to play your first few levels? I generally hoard items until Depth 3, then ID all my potions in the hope of getting detect magic. From there, I try to guide my play based on what I've got for equipment, but I think I might be making that decision too early. I don't generally get very far in this game, that's for sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-28 10:25:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>once had a gnome pick up another gnome's severed head and beat their murderer to death with it, it was metal as fuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>does a texture pack need to be up-to-date in order to work? what happens if it isn't</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-30 22:25:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>i want something other than the default, maybe something darker or more wintery. far as i can tell the texture scene has been kind of cold for a while though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-30 09:20:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>fucking brutal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-18 13:02:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>heh ahahaha somebody hasn't read gunnerkrigg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>came back to find wiki apparently defunct</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 18:27:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>what's the best resource for this game these days?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-06 15:44:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>i don't specifically got any questions right now, usually the kind of info i'm looking for is the sort of thing i'd pull off a game's wiki. wondering if anything at all like that still exists</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Worlds Adrift Unofficial Sort Of Official Discord is an inclusive, welcoming, chill place where all can feel welcome</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 02:44:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 02:46:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>seriously tho, i know half of the mods here mod there. adjust your fuckin shit, dudes, this is pitiful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 09:33:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>that i could take that screenshot speaks to issues here far more important than me getting kicked out. i don't care that much about getting kicked out, but this kind of shit is the kind of shit you really don't want to see in your only technically unofficial community for a game. it looks really bad. it is really bad in itself, and really bad for pr. in conclusion, eat my entire ass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 10:08:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>it'd be like if i said "white nationalism" and somebody posted a picture of their totally ironic swastika armband in response. and it goes entirely without comment or rebuke. at a certain point you have to back up and ask yourself how you got from point a to such a horrid point b. is this when that happens? or will it keep festering?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 21:21:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>the lesson to be learned here is level 12 dudes at the very least at all times</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 14:16:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>assuming i didnt lose some of the essence of myself w the mi+causes, sure. idk if thats even possible tho</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>