<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject269</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-16 21:47:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>As recomenda #231; #245;es da ONU n #227;o s #227;o fontes materiais de direito, mas tem dois prop #243;sitos muito importante: um pol #237;tico e outro jur #237;dico. Politicamente,  #233; uma forma de press #227;o da comunidade internacional sobre um Estado; as recomenda #231; #245;es podem ir se acumulando at #233; que todos os outros pa #237;ses resolvam dizer que aquilo  #233; uma viola #231; #227;o de Direitos Humanos e sancionem o Brasil por isso (pode ser economicamente, pois muitos pa #237;ses adotam barreiras comerciais contra Estados que violam Direitos Humanos, ou politicamente excluindo o Brasil de confer #234;ncias e n #227;o negociando tratados nesse campo). Juridicamente as recomenda #231; #245;es servem como ind #237;cio de Direito, ou *soft law*, n #227;o sendo regras por si, mas indicando uma regra costumeira caso uma disputa relacionada ao tema apare #231;a em um julgamento, digamos, na Corte Interamericana de Direitos Humanos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Catedral (Olympus Stylus Epic (mju II) // Fujicolor Superia X-tra 400, expired since 2007)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-27 04:18:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-28 16:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT> #201; uma sa #237;da, mas me parece que s #243; faria sentido se fosse proposto outro programa pra combater o analfabetismo. Coisa que n #227;o vi anunciada nem proposta pelo MEC. E mesmo assim, cortar um programa s #243; se justifica se a falta de efic #225;cia for intr #237;nseca ao funcionamento do programa, o que tamb #233;m n #227;o parece ser o caso. O MEC poderia muito bem ter repensado o programa e se reorganizado pra garantir que ele funcionasse, sobretudo porque falta de efic #225;cia costuma ser mais um problema de desenho institucional do que de recursos, o que poderia ser consertado s #243; com uma dedica #231; #227;o maior e melhor do tempo do MEC pra o programa, sem ou quase sem custos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-28 16:44:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eu espero que seja isso mesmo! Mas o ministro n #227;o se pronunciou sobre a reconsidera #231; #227;o do programa, ent #227;o n #227;o tenho muitas esperan #231;as :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-28 17:48:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>This depends on the lenses/film. Although F. Zuiko lenses for the Olympus are brilliant, you can mount a lot of different lenses on the Praktica because of the M42 mount, many of which are just as brilliant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-28 17:51:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never used the Olympus, but the Praktica is quite a heavy monster, difficult to load and mine has a very very hard film advance and shutter speed/ASA dial. The shutter button is also in a weird place (you press it with the middle instead of the index finger). That said, it feels as solid as a beast and it's M42 (screw) mount so you can get a looot of lenses for it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Making a political statement (Olympus Stylus Epic (mju II) // Fujicolor Superia X-tra 400, expired in 2007)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-29 20:20:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-29 22:06:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just like food, film has an expiration date, after which it may or may not perform as it is supposed to. Sometimes things will work out just fine (as is the case of this picture), but others there might be A LOT OF grain or weird colour casts - in this roll some pictures ended up too green in the shadows. It is a fun thing to shoot expired film because of the unpredictability. By the way, 9 years is really not that long, I've seen people around shooting stuff expired for 50+ years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-30 00:49:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can just do it normally, but you can also push it for extra grainy weirdness. Or develop it yourself with some different chemicals. All in all, expired film works exactly like regular film, only more unpredictable and most likely with loss on IQ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-31 19:14:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>N #227;o, mas t #225; rolando no TSE um processo que pode cassar a chapa Dilma/Temer. O Gilmar Mendes  #233; o presidente por #233;m, e t #225; sentando em cima do processo tem muito tempo, mas agora em setembro o Toffoli assume e deve poder o processo pra correr. Se condenado, o Temer perde o cargo. Se for esse ano ainda ocorrem novas elei #231; #245;es, se for ano que vem (o que provavelmente vai acontecer), o congresso elege indiretamente o novo presidente.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>People at McDonalds (Olympus Stylus Epic (mju II) // Fujicolor Superia X-tra 400)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-01 21:58:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-08 03:50:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pesquise em partidos que voc #234; goste, depois corte desses os que tem coliga #231; #245;es com legendas demais ou com legendas que voc #234; desgosta (porque  #233; muito prov #225;vel inclusive que seu candidato n #227;o ganhe e seu voto se dissipe na coliga #231; #227;o). V #227;o sobrar provavelmente poucos partidos, a #237; fica f #225;cil de passar pente fino candidato a candidato. Se gostar de v #225;rios que sobraram, vote na legenda, se n #227;o gostar de nenhum, nulo/branco.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Took a short road trip to Rio with one camera and one film (Olympus Stylus Epic (mju II) // Acros 100)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-16 01:34:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The creases from this napkin turned out like that</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-17 21:48:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-24 22:00:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm new to vinyl and just found out my grandfather has a working Akai AP-Q55. Though not listed in "Turntables to avoid" list, I could barely find any resource on it. I've looked the sub and it matches all the criteria for a nice turntable, but I would like to know if it is really any good. Has anyone better resources on it or ever used one?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 02:14:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boa parte das escolas ocupadas, se n #227;o todas, est #227;o tendo aulas dentro durante a ocupa #231; #227;o.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 12:08:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Couldn't you use a quantum entaglement based technology? If you entangle two particles, they will do exactaly the opposite of one another with no time delay wherever they are in space. I don't know a lot about quantum physics but sci-fi sold me on that one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thanks God For Lens Flare (Mju II // Superia 400)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 21:56:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Brutalism (Mju II // Superia 400)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 21:58:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 23:24:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not an architect so I believe in you, plain concrete buildings it is. Can't change the title tho :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-24 03:15:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-24 03:15:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks :3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-24 14:24:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not really, there was only a dim light under the cross illuminating it, I never thought it would be enough to create lens flare.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-24 15:08:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-24 20:08:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's in focus, but a little camera shake. This bugged me too, but although not technically perfect it ended up nicely, so I posted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 01:43:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>My Akai LP-Q55 doesn't work with my grandfather's old Sony LBT-20 receiver. The receiver, however, works perfectly with his TT (a Sony PS-LX23C). The problem is that when playing the Akai, there's little to no sound, it's only barely audible when you come close to the speakers. As I searched for the Sony receiver on the internet, I started thinking it was a TT/Receiver/Speakers bundle (they're all Sony) and it might be that they only work paired with each other and the Akai "intruder" messed up the system. Do you think buying another "independent" receiver/speaker may solve the problem or is there something wrong with the turntable?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ELI5: Why is fish mest dark near the skin/spine?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 18:09:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 18:33:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Biology</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Trees by a lake near Belo Horizonte, Brazil [2932x3664][OC]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 15:11:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Trees by a lake near Belo Horizonte, Brazil [2932x3664][OC]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 15:22:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 22:45:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that's just black in japanese</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 00:40:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even if they did not pay anything directly or indirectly to the government - which they do as explained -, free basic education is a human right guaranteed by the International Covenant on Social and Economical Rights, to which the USA is a party. It must be provided to anyone within the territory or jurisdiction of the USA, irrespective of the person's legal status as that would violate the non-discrimination principle. This is an international obligation which is also appliable to the domestic law as interpreted by the Supreme Court.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 13:50:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is indeed, but since it's a human right it cannot be denied to anyone for political convenience. Human rights standards are the limit to policy-making. Besides, if it were denied that would be unfair to children, because their parents took the decision to emmigrate, not them. Furthermore, undocumented immigrant status is already a gigantic hassle, specially in the US, so I'm also not sure whether denying them access to public services would be an effective deterrent to undocumented immigration, I think it would rather worsen the life of people who already have it really difficult.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-14 17:39:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any recommendations for a receiver with a phono input under $200? (preferably new, or mint used)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 23:09:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anny suggestion for standalone pre-amps under $200? I live in Brazil, so there's hardly anything available apart from the most popular models.... Also, can I plug low-impedance headphones directly to a pre-amp or will I need a headphone amplifier regardless of the headphone?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 03:29:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anny suggestion for standalone pre-amps under $200? I live in Brazil, so there's hardly anything available apart from the most popular models.... Also, can I plug low-impedance headphones directly to a pre-amp or will I need a headphone amplifier regardless of the headphone?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 17:20:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I usually buy at mercadolivre.com (which is pretty much the Latin America e-Bay equivalent). What are some good pre-amps with volume control you know of? Since price may vary greatly between the US and South America, there's a small chance I can afford a more expensive one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 02:00:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks a lot!! Oddly enough, double the US price is quite the bargain, audio equipment is almost always imported and duties and taxes here are abusively high.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Brazilian Supreme Court Justice dead in a plane crash</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-19 21:12:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-22 20:20:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm traveling to Europe (Portugal) next week and I intend to buy some new headphones for at home listening. Naturally, I want the highest possible quality within my budget, but the problem is I live in an apartment at the centre of a big city in Brazil, so I always keep my bedroom windows open, which means there's often some ambient noise. Budget:  #8364;200 (for headphone + integrated DAC/AMP if needed) Prefered sound signature: Neutral Purpose: at home listening Need for isolation: may need a little, not sure though Need for portability: none Prefered fit: over-ear I was thinking of getting the Sennheiser's 598s with a Fiio e10k amp, but will the lack of isolation be a nuisance even though there's only some sound coming from a relatively busy street about 150ft below my room?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Need a USB mic for a podcast</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 01:56:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm starting a podcast for a college project and I need a USB mic, since I figure the regular mic + usb interface would be too expensive and I'm on a tight budget (need something around $100 in the US market). What are some good options? If it's of any help I live in Brazil. Also, what should I look for in a mic for podcasts? I'll probably be conducting interviews and holding talks with 3 to 5 people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-05 10:35:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>My RHA Ma750i's are lacking mid- and sub-bass response on the right ear, which is making everything sound weird and very annoying. It happened while I was on the plane and I feel it's a problem with the driver. Is there any solution to this? The warranty expired, but could I take it nevertheless to a repair shop?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pra #231;a de Gomes Teixeira, Porto, Portugal (Olympus MJU II // Fuji C200)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 01:20:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ELI5: Why do we often mess up time-related greetings (like saying good evening when it's morning), even though we use them all the time ever since we were little?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 17:41:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>This comes from a non-english native speaker, but I'm guessing it's the same all around</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 18:18:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Other</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tejo River (Mju II // Fuji C200)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 21:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Turists in Porto (Canonet QL17 // Fuji C200)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-11 15:05:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-11 16:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have the non-gIII version, which is bigger and heavier, but I don't mind it, it feels like it's built for a war, really solid. The rangefinder is exceptionally bright and the lens is as sharp as you can get for anything under 1000USD (the 1.7 aperture also gets beautiful bokeh). The lightmeter is quirky and often times a little off, so I always set it one stop down (this way if it gets right, it'll overexpose by only one stop and if it goes a little wrong it'll either get exposition right or overexpose by two stops, which is no big deal with C-41/B amp;W film). Canon's quickload mechanism works a treat, you basically can't mess up the film and it gets you 38 exposures in a normal roll!! I found mine for a little over 100USD (in Brazil), but the lens was in a deplorable state, so I paid extra 40USD for a complete CLA and it looks as good as new. Worth every penny. 100 to 150 pounds seems a little on the expensive end, but it's worth it if you're paying for a mint camera.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 01:45:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're absolutely right, but sanctioning a country shouldn't mean severing diplomatic ties with it. On the contrary, keeping a representative to mediate negotiations between one country (or the international community) and other, is absolutely essential to make sure it complies with human rights standards. Not only because you can only achieve it with negotiation - what good are sanctions if there aren't any ways to suspend them? -, but mainly because without diplomatic relations there's no reliable way to observe, investigate and control the policies implemented in the direction of achieving human rights' standards. Really, sanctions are just a kind of "coercive negotiation".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 15:54:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>So... You're Monet? (is this a meme? I don't get the meme)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 16:07:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the one! Thanks a lot!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-13 18:44:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>About six years ago, my grandparents gave me this lovely Breitling Windrider for my 15th birthday (it is sort of a tradition to receive jewelry for the 15th birthday where I live). Since then, I'd wear it only to very special occasions and use random cheap quartz watches daily. Recently, my father came back from a trip and he brought a Tissot quartz perpetual with him, I was immediately fascinated and decided to dive into the timepieces world. Not long ago, I made my first "real" addition to the collection, the Seiko 5 SNZG15 field watch. I intend to expand my collection slowly and my eye is already fixed on the SNZF17 Sea Urchin, since I really want a diver style jubilee bracelet to wear around. I'm also looking into straps now, mainly because the nylon in my Seiko seems quite flimsy and I'd like some good NATO alternatives. If you've any suggestions or comments, I'm all ears!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 18:53:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I looked into the entry-level (mainly Seiko and Orient) diver line-up! The SKX007 looks great but I can't really get along with the jubilee bracelet and I think it is somewhat busy-looking. I was also interested in the SNZH55, which would look amazing in a thicker nylon strap, but the smaller case profile and Oyster bracelet in the Sea Urchin are really what grew to me the most.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Advice] Good watch retailers in Washington, D.C.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 23:59:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm traveling this week to D.C., and it's a great opportunity I have to get me a new piece.I live in Latin America, so watches are usually overprice (I saw a SKX007 retailing for 600USD). The problem is I won't have a lot of time. I don't want to risk buying it online, since I may not be able to get it when it arrives. I also cannot pointlessly stroll around the city, so it'd be best if it's at an obvious place downtown. As for money, I have around $200, so reputed Seiko, Orient or Citizen retailers recommendations would be nice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 03:21:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I will! Haven't really thought about duty free, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 03:22:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the advice! Maybe I'll find some time to go there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 15:42:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-01 19:46:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>They speak dutch in Suriname, and english in Guiana, other than that every other country (except, of course, Brazil) in south america speaks spanish. Slight exception to Paraguay, where Guarany is also an official language. The fench Guiana belongs to France, so they're politically Europe. Other countries like Trinadad and Tobago, Haiti, etc, are in the Caribean islands, which is not south america. Mexico, Canada and the US are in north america, which is a geographical distinction (South, North, Central and Caribean). Anything between Mexico and Colombia within the mainland is central america. Other than that, there's also a linguistical-cultural distinction, in which Canada and the US are part of the anglo-saxon american and the rest is latin america (even if english, dutch or french speaking, like Haiti, Jamaica or Barbados). By the way, although Haiti's official language is French, they speak Cr #233;ole, which is borderline incomprehensible to francophones.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-06 16:31:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wore a friend's [F-91W](https://imgur.com/gallery/hE58S) and felt why such a cheap piece of horlogerie is indeed a classic! Looks awesome!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Question] Is the Nomos Tangente an acceptable homage?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 21:23:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know it is one of the most beloved watches out here and a beautiful piece of horology with its in-house movement and staggering attention to detail ...but It's pretty much identical to a Stowa Antea, which came before it. Nomos also does not reference Stowa in their description of the Tangente. The question is: why should a Tangente be more acceptable than a Invicta? Both are homages to other well-known watches, and have their own level of craftsmanship and also their own movements.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 21:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get it, but the design of them both is basically identical. You can still go bauhaus and not use the exact same design (see: junghans max bill, all of the other nomos' watches - except perhaps the ludwig).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 22:13:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh! I was thinking Stowa came back with the original dial and then Nomos went on with it. But if it's a rediscovery thing, then I definitely can appreciate it more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 22:20:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I can definitely relate to and appreciate re-discoveries.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 23:05:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a law student and usa a Seiko SNZG15 daily. When I have to dress up for an event, a meeting or a judgement, then I put on my uncommon Breitling Windrider (ref a49350) I got from my grandparents for my 15th birthday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-14 18:34:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look out for vintage omegas on ebay and chrono24</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 18:19:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>The owner may or may not be entitled to claim the watch depending on whether 2 years under the shop's care meant that he waived his right to claim it back. If he did, well, then it's yours; but if he didn't then he may claim it back directly from you BUT you should be able to petition against the watch shop (or the owners, or whover legally answers for it after it closed down) and retrieve your 500 bucks, unless they prove you bought it with knowledge that the owner could show up and retrieve the watch (prepare yourself against this allegation just in case). Disclaimer: my point is not totally valid, it's subject to change depending on your local and national laws. I'm a brazilian law student, but I tried to keep it as close as possible to general rules of private law that are more or less universally applicable. Edit: all of this sounds too convenient. The shop closing down, the owner randomly showing up the downscaled price... If I were you I would also search for a lawyer and prepare against frauds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-17 17:14:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>My new [A-158wa](https://imgur.com/gallery/uvBd6) because I fell in love with the design and I think this piece has a fantastic history for a ridiculous price.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-17 20:50:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Orient Mako or Seiko SKX (007, 009, 013) are the most recommended around here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-17 20:59:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, they're perfect for everyday beaters. If you're usually in business atire, though, you might want to avoid divers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-18 17:45:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seiko Spirit SCVE series (001/003/005/007) because of their crazy beautiful design with the misplaced bold-colored power-reserve sub-dial and matching second hand. The only downside is I think the bracelet looks really ugly, but you can change that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-18 18:33:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Christopher Ward divers fit your criteria real tightly, but I'd also recommend the Sinn 104, which really is a pilot watch but does everything a diver does, looks a lot like a diver, and is so nicely put together that at 1000$ it's a bargain (some say it's just as good as some breitlings/omegas).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-18 21:21:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've stumbled across some japanese websites which still sell them for reasonable (~$200) prices, though I'm not sure whether they were discontinued.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-18 21:26:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tudor Black Bay or Pelagos (in blue or black), great alternative to something like a submariner. Perfect for everyday and a charming faux-pas for formal attire. Edit: the tudor black bay 36 is a smaller size that goes along the lines of the original explorer, which is also great for formal and casual attire.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 04:27:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks legit to me, but you should check whether there is a wave-pattern in the dial to be sure (it can't be seen from the photos). Aside from that, everything looks all-right. If you're in doubt check yourself for official photos and compare them. What's most important, though, is that it feels real. By the weight alone you should have an idea. Also, make sure to check the smoothness of the sweep (it should be pretty smooth albeit a little tiny bit tickly), make daily measurements to make sure it's accurate (if it deviates more than +/- 15s a day you should double-check), and finally inspect closer - preferably with a magnifying glass - and check for any quality-control flaws, everything should be absolutely impecable if it's a real omega. If after all that checking and double-checking you still have any doubts, find a trustworthy watchmaker to remove the caseback, take pictures of the movement and check the authenticity yourself or send a picture of the movement here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Identify] This Grand Seiko from the WUS forums</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-20 02:58:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-20 03:01:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was browsing for small watches at watchuseek and I came across this beautiful Grand Seiko. It is perfect since I was looking into white-dial watches with interesting patterns like the Snowflake (SBGA011), but I wanted it to be on the small side of things. Although the hefty-ish 41mm of the Snowflake would fit my wrist, I enjoy watches that don't take all of my wrist with the case.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-21 14:27:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wearing my gifted [Breitling Windrider Cockpit refA49350](https://imgur.com/gallery/yih3Y) today. Beautiful underrated watch with a big date complication.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 02:48:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm looking for a small to regular watch, preferably 36 to 38mm, that is sleek and minimal looking and great for both formal and casual settings. Water-resistance greater than 30m is not necessary but desirable (it'd be cool to use it in the beach ever so often). The price range is anything below $5000. I know Nomos is the obvious choice (I was thinking the Ahoi Neomatik in white), but is there anything else out there?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 04:16:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>How limited is the SBGR251 actually? I was looking into the SBGR253 but I'm afraid they'll sell out before I collect my funds and end my research...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 04:17:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great suggestion! How would you say it compares to the Tudor Black Bay 36?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 04:20:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>True! I had my eyes on the models with the sunburst blue dial, no numerals and oyster bracelet. But if I am to go used I guess the Tudor prince oysterdate with the linen off-white dial would suit me better, the problem is finding one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 15:55:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much! I mistook the sbgr251 for the sbgw253 because reference numbers make me confused. On the Aqua Terra: is there any rumor about when the new Railmaster (non limited edition) will come out? Perhaps I should wait, because I fell in love with that one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 19:02:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Half lumed [Seiko 5 Sports SNZG15](https://imgur.com/gallery/knWwo)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 21:25:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seiko 5 Spurrts SNZG15 f(ur)ield watch on a nyanto strap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-25 23:23:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't get the Daniel Wellington, they're hated on this sub for a reason, the quality is dreadful and they're usually overpriced rebranded chinese watches. For $300 you can get a Seiko SARB033 or SARB035, which are very minimal looking and beautifully finished, if you don't like the metal bracelet you can buy another one, everything looks nice on those beasts, just search the sub for pics. For even less than half your budget you can get an Orient Bambino, which is very Bauhaus (minimal) inspired and features a nice Seiko automatic movement and really nice finishing and is also quite though for a dress watch. There are many other great options, check the sidebar if you want to know more!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-25 23:25:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks tacky in a nice way, rock it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-25 23:31:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go for it! Timex is a respectable brand with a very rich and interesting history, you can't go wrong with them. In any way I'd still recommend the Seikos, they're automatics and very elegant and minimal while still being a little out of the ordinary.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-26 01:15:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't know this brand, but the review was very positive so I guess it's a good go. But it didn't seem like much out of the minimal fashion watch fad for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-29 04:57:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Assuming you'd be your everyday regular gun-for-hire, I'd say a G-shock of some kind, waterproof to the bone, unbreakable, reliable, functional and sweats practicality. Now, if you're talking high-profile international hitman you should be able to blend in well within the elite environment of your targets. No G-shocks on cocktail parties with CEOs and drug lords, please! In this case, you'd ideally have a different watch for each job, but if you were to need an all-rounder (for whichever reason), there should be some requirements: 1. It must be tough, you may be at a cocktail at a given time and then fleeing in the jungle right after. 2. It must be subdued, you don't want anyone noticing you too much, so no all-gold yacht-masters. 3. It has to be classy, you will be meeting REALLY important people (and perhaps killing them). 4. Ideally it'd be a conversation starter so you'd blend in along the *connoisseurs* in the circle. 5. It requires reliability because, well, it can't break. 6. You need to be able to wear it with a tuxedo or casual attire - no one knows whether your next target is at the French Riviera or at the Vienna Opera. 7. Yet it needs to be somewhat flashy so people will know you belong there - no obscure brands, few people will ever know your $100k vintage 1920s Vacheron Constantin is any better than your grandfather's beaten up Timex. IMO the Rolex Explorer 1 fits all the boxes, it's reliable, precise, tough, subdued, classy yet sporty and has a very interesting story behind it, you can also dress it up or down with different straps. Other options are the Submariner, Seamaster 300, or pretty much anything any Bond has ever worn (with the exception of the awkward digital Omegas and Seikos).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-30 03:25:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, kind redditor, for the gold!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 00:49:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you post pictures of your watch? Do you have budget? Luxury watches can go all the way up to six/seven-house sums.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 06:05:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lots of Nichijou visual cues, but they actually managed to make them work. Visuals on the show are not boring, the animation keeps lots of interest all the way through. I mean, it's far from perfect, some gags didn't land, fan service is sometimes oddly placed, the student council president had an odd chemistry with the duo, soundtrack is just ok, etc. But the absurd duo, the nice use of visual gags and great voice acting and sound effects really made it for me. So far this and Kakegurui are the only animes I'll be looking into this season.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 18:19:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I find it really bizarre that the child gets punished for not being vaccinated. Refusing to vaccinate is the parent's fault! Why limit the child right to education when the parents are the stupid ones? There should be a fine for the parents who don't vaccinate their children, but restricting the access to education is just dumb.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 18:39:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok I get that not vaccinating your child is bad and stupid and should be punished but do you honestly think it amounts to child neglect?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 18:45:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not all vaccines are against contagious diseases, and even so, a child infected with a contagious disease should be granted leave from school for as long as the doctors reccomend, not outright lose its right to education. Besides, it doesn't make sense to punish children because they may (or may not) be infected in the future.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 19:15:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good point, though I'm still not sure whether the number of unvaccinated children is large enough to undermine herd immunity...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 19:17:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Geez, people</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 19:23:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a good point right there. Nevertheless I still think there are preventive ways to avoid denial of vaccination that do not deprive children of their rights. If there were fines against the parents, with high interest in case they don't get paid, then children would still go to school while the parents would, in a short timespan, have no way other than vaccinate the child.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 20:45:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow I didn't expect it to be so drastic! Perhaps there's still a less damaging alternative, but while I don't find one I can't help but agree with you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-06 05:06:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure about the watch but the IEMs are shure a beauty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 04:04:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really liked it at first because of the intro scene with the progressive and emotional soundtrack, mainly because it had very interesting location shots that established the ambient of the show nicely. It honestly reminded me of some Ghibili movies like castle in the sky, pony or spirited away. Then it came the introductory dialogue: "this is where our story begins" - and where my interested ended. It was followed by a poor OP with boring music and no animation but random shots scattered throughout the show that have no relevance. When the show started I was already so bored I didn't bother to look at the screen, but the few glances I gave showed bland backgrounds, little to no animation effort and generic character designs. There were some positives points, though. Besides the intro scene, I enjoyed when the blonde guy pretty much declared to the class rep (ok her char design is actually really really cute with the braids and whatnot). Also, the establishing shots kept their high level, but were mostly used to cover up for the lack of quality in animation. BUT WAIT I'M NOT OVER THERE'S STILL THE SHITTIEST PART What. The. Fuck. Happened. When the blonde guy was speaking in the background about meeting in the convenience store while RANDOM SHOTS OF OTHER UNKNOWN PEOPLE WERE SHOWING??? I think this lasted for a good minute or two and had NO REASON. I don't know who those people are, I'm sure they'll never show up again so WHY GOD WHY? Also, the class rep and the main girl in the library speaking in the background while random shots of the rep reading manga in the aisle from EVERY. ANGLE. POSSIBLE. Pointless. Tl;dr: mostly bland, the intro scene was interesting, as was the last one, they tried too hard to cover up for the bad animation, two garbage scenes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 04:54:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think Tomo and Yoichi are that close to Victor and Yuri. If you look into it, what made the relantionship between Victor and Yuri so great is that Yuri never thought he could actually reach Victor. Yuri had already abandoned any hope in light of his recent failure at Sochi. At 25 he could never hope to be anything in the ice-skating carreer and then BANG his idol appears naked at his inn' hot spring and what a ~~butt~~ scene. On the other hand, Tomo and Yoichi have also an endearing relationship, but it comes from a completely different place. Yes, Yoichi is Tomo's idol almost as much as Victor is for Yuri, but the fact that Tomo is just starting makes all the difference. There is no hopelessness to be overcome, nor any adult-to-adult relationship. It's rather a senpai-to-kouhai supporting thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 04:58:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great review, now that you say it, I didn't realize how *to the olympics* is such a bold statement. Most sports anime never dare get this far, let alone from square one! ok, it's diving, which is not that popular of a sport, but yeah yeah...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 03:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think it's tuesday anywhere, but who cares, this watch is gorgeous!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 03:46:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ugh... Do you have better pics? I want to help you here but it's really hard to believe that this is actually diamond and white gold. Actually it is hard to believe that's any better than a cheap chinese watch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 03:54:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well it wouldn't eventually happen, wouldn't it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 05:47:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Audemars Piguet watches with the calibre 2120/2808 movement have it. There's also the [Krayon Everywhere](https://www.google.com.au/amp/www.ablogtowatch.com/krayon-everywhere-sunrise-sunset-watch/amp/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-09 21:46:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>1) I wear it behind the wrist bone, centered, otherwise it's uncomfortable. But comfort is the only rule here. 2) Nylon straps (NATO, Perlon or Cordura) are strictly casual, they're a good wear when it's hot because of breathability - they can also handle water. Bracelets are also breathable, handle water well, and can also be worn formally (though that's a slight faux-pas). Leather is the most formal, specially textured leather, contrast stitching dresses it down a bit, but keep it out of the water and heat. 3) Definitely. President Putin wears Fliegers, for example. The strict dress watch etiquette is not much of a thing, mainly since Bond rocked a submariner with a tuxedo - on a NATO no less. Just keep it to simple tool watches, you can't dress up a Navitimer. 4) No, I keep them on display at my desk. 5) Not really, just keep it simple and wear whichever way you like it. Edit: just realized you meant night, not evening, as a non-native speaker I frequently forget the difference.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-09 23:23:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>By all means go for yout grail watch first! The Seiko you own should be great for formal situations of you throw a black/brown leather strap on it. I think the Navi works in the picture you sent me, but mostly because it's paired with jeans and a navy blazer, if we're talking full-suited formal attire, I don't think it would. By the way, which model is your Seiko? I really dig it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 00:21:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>The bezel faded so beautifully, the patina on the lume is so nice... I get why Rolex gets so much love, it looks better with age.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 23:25:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Indeed](http://i0.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/facebook/000/916/071/aa6.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 04:45:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>No minute markers, so I guess the correct reference is the IW371713</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 04:49:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks a little bit too playful for a Skagen, I'd say Swatch, the exact model is really difficult to find out, though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 04:54:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, the crown also looks a little too flat and large, could be a replica.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 04:55:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfortunately we do not support replica watches on this sub, whoever you could check the buying guide at the sidebar for flieger/pilot style watches, there should be some within your budget! Edit: my personal favorite under $1000 would be the [Stowa Flieger](https://c8.staticflickr.com/9/8207/29281162855_ff75aae5d0_b.jpg), there are also cheaper options at the sidebar for the same style.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 00:49:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a tough tell. Everything looks correct. Can we have movement pics?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 05:14:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also, even if it were fake, it'd be at least a $300 one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 05:15:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Life is a box of chocolates.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Identify] Former president of Brazil's lawyer, Cristiano Zanin's watch.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 21:32:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 21:34:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Remove</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 00:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>At the point in which it is explained how the abyss curse works and it is thus hinted how massive it actually is, all I could remember was the dark continent from Hunter x Hunter and the never ending city from the Blame! Manga. Such an endless feel to this show's worldbuilding is goddamn beautiful. There is little chance this won't be AOTS or even AOTY.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 15:20:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like the steel better, and I think the blue sunburst dial is not only the most gorgeous thing on earth, as I believe it's just enough to stand out from the crowd. The everose goes a little bit too far, but I still believe it's subtle and a safe bet if you want something a little more different. Sure, it isn't as traditional as steel/white-gold, and you might see it going out of fashion - rose gold is all the hype after apple started releasing things in that color -, but it still looks cool, and being a Rolex I doubt it will ever stop being that way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 15:24:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a Casio A-158, it's one of my favorite watches, has a ton of tradition, works a treat, it's pretty much unbreakable, it's a classy everyday watch with its small profile and all stainless-steel case/bracelet, ridiculously easy to read, and all for 15 dollars.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 15:35:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you go to the used market, there are lots of vintage omegas under $500. The ones under 33mm are specially cheap, since there's not much demand for them. Unfortunately they do not have a sapphire caseback, but you can rest assured the movements are amazing. Just be extra careful when buying, it's the used market.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 06:30:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great one! I'd get the Rolex Explorer I. Such a timeless, rough design! Also a strap monster, can work perfectly with formal or casual attire!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 23:04:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Sinn 104 is an aviation watch (although it technically qualifies for diver status). It's well under the $2000 range, but there are few worthy competitors until that range. Bu really, anything Sinn does will fit your question, except for their not-so-sough-after dress pieces.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 23:20:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>So beautiful! The Nomos two-piece perlon strap is also amazing. How does it wear on your wrist? I'll be living in Germany starting this September and I just might be lucky enough to get one of these (it's been on my list for a while), but I'm really scared with sizing issues due to the long lugs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 01:09:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>could you send a pic of the watch with the minute hand at twelve? (for easier perception of the misalignment)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 01:27:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, it's small but noticeable. Hamilton's, however, are not high-grade watches, so I suppose that misalignment could be something common given the grade of quality control. However, I'm not a Hamilton owner, they could speak better of quality control than me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 15:27:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look for [Jochen Benzinger](http://www.jochenbenzinger.de/en#news) , he's a german independent watchmaker with a tiny workshop in Baden-Baden who I believe used to do skeletonization for Patek Phillippe. I usually hate skeletonized watches, but his work is indeed admirable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 21:03:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be fair with OP, he has posted most legit checks in rep subs, which is in fact a good way to ensure something bought on the grey market is the real deal, as the replica subs are REALLY nitpicky. Now, I do have serious doubts that a 1.1 million dollar watch limited to 30 pieces would randomly show up as a trade with friend. Even if OP's AP were real that'd be stupid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 05:26:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>If he's a begginer in buying vintage than I don't think it's recommendable. Too easy to get scammed and turn out with a replica / re-dial / frankenstein piece.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 05:28:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hamilton Jazzmaster Edit: there's also the Intra-matic line, with slimmer and smaller (at 38mm) pieces, as well as cleaner dials</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 14:26:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>And that water would just make it burn more</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 03:55:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks like a real rolex but fake rolexes also look like real ones so agreed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 02:10:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that /r/watchescirclejerk ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 03:25:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>You'd have a hard time finding this watch even at the $5000 mark. Or get a G-shock.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 03:28:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like to</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 03:32:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>What you're looking for is basically a Patek Nautilus / AP Royal Oak with an annual calendar. That wouldn't cost less than $20.000, with a lot of luck you might get an used rolex / omega with the features you're asking for around $10.000. I really hope I were commenting on the wrong post, and that it'd be possible to get something like what you want at under $600, but it just isn't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 03:53:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was dead honest with you, as all of the comments above said, if you wanted to get your whole list of requirements that'd be stupidly costly. The Oceanus is a valid choice, as is a G-Shock, which I openly suggested to you. The thing is you came here making a gigantic and unreal list of requirements for under $600, it's only natural I made a light hearted joke. You have absolutely no right calling me an asshole when all I did was being honest towards you immediately after you commented on my dad joke. Besides, you should do your own tiny bit of research before commenting on a sub looking for reccomendations. Even if you just looked at the sidebar guides you'd know you're asking for too much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[qUESTION] what is the best movement ever?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 04:53:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>is it the 7s26 or the 7s36?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 00:23:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bet you spend half a day just staring at those hands and those applied romans. I'd do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 00:36:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>That Bezel! Fantastic find, OP!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 01:41:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>this makes me sad :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 04:56:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not only is it an awful SKX replica, it's on this non-NATO crap you call a "strap". Get yourself a Seiko, will you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 05:46:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>IMHO this is not good skeletonization, as the movement shown underneath is totally undecorated. If you care to compare with [other](https://www.definewatches.com.au/wp-content/uploads/images/products/p-52015-Habring-Benzinger-Engine-No03.jpg) skeletonized watches, then you'll get what I mean. However, skeletonization is a purely aesthetic choice. If you like the way it looks, fine! The Oris Artelier is an exceptional piece.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 15:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>The one I linked is a Jochen Benzinger piece, he makes the most affordable ornate skeletonized pieces and still they go for around 8000EUR. If you want something that won't break your bank and still has mechanics showing, I suggest the Bulova Accutron or the Swatch jellyfish. They're not ornate skeletonized pieces, but their see-through design has a purpose and a coll history behind it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 16:24:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very nice looking, OP! The off-white dial and neon-orange hands look a lot like the Nomos' Neomatik line. What do you have to say about build quality? Also, what was the price?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 16:30:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are many different reactor watches, specifying would be useful, however, they all roam around the big, busy-looking, military, "manly" aesthetic. In this sense, I could recommend the Seiko Monster line, Marathon watches (if you have higher budget), or even some Breitlings like the Avenger or the Chronomat (now we're talking luxury watches).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 16:37:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oris and Christopher ward are definitely under $3k, Panerai and IWC are at the luxury price points. Couldn't emphasize more the Nomos' basic models (Orion, Tangente and Ludwig).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 15:13:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>But it can't look really good because it's not a SEIKO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 00:09:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you feel weird because of the price, you can keep it until you don't. For me, I was gifted a Breitling by my grandparents at my 15th birthday, until a couple months ago (that is, 6 years later) I only wore it for marriages and other sorts o cocktail parties (it's a dressy-ish kind of Breitling). Now I kind of rediscovered it and it's on my wrist almost everyday. The anxiety of wearing an expensive timepiece wears off, and once it does you'll realize almost no one knows how much it's worth so even in public it's kind of a dirty little secret, which is cool to keep. If you're really afraid of getting it stolen, then by all means insure it! In my case, though, I like to think thieves are just like everyone else and don't know what watches are actually worth. Being a Rolex you might be a little bit more on the spot, but still one would have to get real close to find out the brand (and most would think it's a fake, because "no one spends that much on watches"). By the way, I live in Brazil and still wear it almost daily although robbery is not that uncommon here, as you might guess. (It's bad, but not  #732;that #732; bad really, I was never robbed tbh).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 00:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Beautiful find, OP, congrats! Care to share the ref. number?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 16:06:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Both fit, the 45mm because of the noticeably shorter lugs. I prefer the look on the 40mm nevertheless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 04:39:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>They kind of tried to decorate the movement, but still a million miles away from any real Vacheron. Nice try, replica guys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 04:41:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now that's a rare find. How'd say those hold up? That's a popular band in Brazil, might get me one eventually, but they're nowhere to be found on most forums.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 04:44:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I passed by an Omega dealer today and saw this exact Seamaster in exhibition. I have never been a great enthusiast of Seamasters, but when I looked through the window at various angles to check the light play on those hands and indices I gasped out of excitement. Beautiful, beautiful piece, OP, congrats!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 00:28:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>These are really great pieces! I'd also suggest the beloved Seiko SARB033/035, absolutely fantastic, and a bargain at this price!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 02:29:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow! Great advice! I think we have serious contenders against the Sinn 556i now!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 02:33:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're pretty common, but I'm never bored of seeing one. The same is true for all the other watches I listed, even the ubiquitous SARB033. I can only seriously consider spending this much money on a timepiece if I'm sure I'll never get bored of looking at it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 03:01:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since you said nothing about sticking to one strap for the rest of my life, I'd choose the Rolex 1016 hands-down, because I'm an uncomplicated person. You get it? You get the pun?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 03:19:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're willing to settle for arabics, there's the [Junkers Dessau 1926 Flatline](https://www.amazon.com/JUNKERS-Watches-Junkers-Dessau-Flatline/dp/B002XCIENI/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 amp;qid=1501204457 amp;sr=8-1 amp;keywords=junkers+open+heart). However, I don't know how much you intend to get into the watch hobby. If you do want to go deeper down the hole there's a chance you'll eventually regret choosing an open-heart design, as they're usually frowned upon in the community you might get the same ickiness in the long run. If you want to go safe I suggest the Seiko SARB033/035, which you'll end up wearing everyday until it eventually breaks after intense wear 300 years from now. In any event, any watch that marks this moment for you will be priceless, so whatever ends up being in your choice, make sure to wear it in good health!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 04:59:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like a fashion watch in the likes of Daniel Wellington or Tommy Hilfiger. If you like the look and want something with more quality for the price, look into the [Tissot Everytime](http://us.tissotshop.com/tissot-everytime-big-quartz-4.html) or the [Timex Fairfield](http://global.timex.com/node/102056). For a more refined (and much more expensive) purchase, the [Nomos Tangente](http://www.nomos-store.com/en/Watches/Model-series/Tangente/Watches-with-manual-winding/Tangente-stainless-steel-back.html) is almost as good as it gets. There are also lots of choices in between.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 19:20:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually most vintage models are around 34mm, 36mm was already considered a "big watch" until somewhere around the 80s. If you investigate a little on the history of rolexes, you'll find that the original Air King was an aviation (thus: big) watch at 34mm in the 1940s.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 20:50:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Traveling with my trusted friend [Casio a158-w](https://imgur.com/gallery/dQb9W) today!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 15:31:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the advice, unfortonately at 43mm it won't fit my wrist :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 16:14:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was really hepful! Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-02 21:55:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amazing dial</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 23:25:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd say this is just a cheap Speedmaster homage but typing does not allow any sort of ironic intonation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 03:59:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Two-tone datejusts with diamond indices and mother-of-pearl dial don't go for 4000 bucks, that's the base price for no-frills all steel ones. Also, the two links at the end of the bracelet are in steel, which I believe should not happen (but I'm no expert, so I'm not sure). The gold also seems a little too white for 18k, which should be used. I'd say it's a fake, but you should run to an AD as soon as possible to be sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 04:24:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you think of the Rolex Explorer? It's has an incredible history and the newer ones are at 39mm. Other than that, I'd look into Tudor. The Black Bay Black is beautiful with its hints of red and gold. I'm also an enormous fan of the new Seamaster 300, it's so slim and the fake patina on the lume is oh so great. There's the Breitling Super Ocean Heritage too! Many great divers at your price point, including your alternatives (which I think are great). I'm personally not a huge fan of the Seamaster Bond, I just don't think the bracelet and the skeleton hands do it for me, the case shape is also a little weird. In terms of the Submariner, it's one of my all-time favourites, and it is significantly different from the CW so as not to be redundant IMO. Last but not least, if you're a vintage guy, check the Tudor Snowflakes, many of the marketed ones have aged to a glorious patina and bezel/dial fade.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 06:08:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>In your tank top rainbow Stalin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 22:28:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anything up to 40mm will fit most women's wrists. You have a really great budget with lots of options in that range. My all-time favourite, however, is the Rolex Explorer I (preferably the older reference at 36mm instead of the newer 39mm, but both are fine). The new Seamaster 300 and the soon-to-come Railmaster are also really great watches. Datejusts are also really great choices that retain their values!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 23:31:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's a regular tachymeter, that's why it says "base 1000"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 23:15:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice episode, I really enjoy the romance between Tatara and Mako, but I honestly fear she's there just for the romance filler before Tatara actually gets to be with Hanaoka. I hope that doesn't happen, but the support messages she speaks to him at the telephone are more or less the same "believe more in yourself" stuff Ram said to Barusu in RE:Zero. I'm really fearing the "but I actually love Emilia"-effect here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 23:18:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>The head-pushing bit was one-on-one with Yuri On Ice's Yuri goes hug berserk scene for the most fujoshi bait bit in modern anime.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 23:19:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>The second best [Mako](http://media.tumblr.com/e2f174115654637b7990fd9dae64a104/tumblr_inline_nbgawpi7w71rohgu0.jpg) in the history of anime</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 18:16:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>If he isn't then I am</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 02:14:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know why OP is getting so many downvotes. It's his choice whether or not to open the box, different people have different ways of enjoying the same hobby, I don't see why storing instead of wearing would be a bad thing, it's not bothering anyone. That said, OP, I believe you're wrong to say it'll increase in value, all things considered the watch industry is very perfidious and even timeless pieces like the Nautilus can decrease value over time, even if never worn. If that's your only reason for storing it, don't bother. Anyways, ~~wear~~ store it in good health.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 03:57:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh. Wow. When I read the post all I thought was "here we go on the dirt-cheap fake Patke Philip thread again"... But those watches are legit. You have inherited one hell of a collection. If you don't bother me asking, what line of work was your dad in? He has to be some high-ranking executive in a big company to be able to spend around $100,000 on watches he didn't even know anything about. Anyways, I don't know in which line of work it is 'just expected' to wear Pateks and Vacherons.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 06:42:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's the ref number? Loved it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 14:44:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think so, it ranges from 0-100 with three subdials from 0-10, each one with a 1k, 10k and 100k mark. I'm not sure what it does but it ain't measuring time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 03:11:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a GMT bezel on a submariner. Although the bezel mod is easy, I'm not sure why someone would do this kind of mod to a Rolex, nor why the new bezel would be so scratched and faded. Odd. That said, it's an obvious fake, the index at 9 o'clock is misaligned with the minute track and there's not enough magnification on the cyclop. Sorry to be the bearer of bad news, though :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 04:42:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>He could have received it as a gift or maybe he was deceived by some random street seller, which would be odd since this isn't the worst of replicas. He might have gotten it out of a garage sale and didn't bother checking too, this kind of stuff happens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 23:37:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you safely tie it around your wrist without risking have the blood-flow to your hands cut off? Then yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 05:52:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Misaligned indices, Submariner on a Coke elapsed time bezel (I don't think Rolex ever made those), lack of date magnification, probably something wrong with the font - there's always something wrong with the font. Edit: weird yellow gooey lume on the lume peep, also: definitely something wrong with the font, the "R" in "Rolex" is too thick and there's lack of clear edges on the serifs, especially in the "L". There's always something wrong with the font.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 05:10:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something with a urushi dial, a crystal caseback displaying a beautifully decorated seiko 9r01 spring drive movement, platinum highly polished case, 38mm with slightly curved modern shaped lugs, slightly domed crystal with dual AR coating, highly polished steel dauphine hands for the hours and minutes, applied no-numeral trapezoid(ish) white gold unobtrusive indices (with two of them together at 12 and a slightly smaller one at 6), hand-painted minute track, seconds on black concentric-circle finished 6 o'clock subdial with high-polish steel leaf-hand, white-gold applied logo between 12 o'clock and the center. No. Date. Pretty much a SBGR305 with some patek 5196 and Nomos Tangente cues. Oh, and with a darker-than-black dial.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 05:51:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I'm biased for the Explorer, as I believe it is one of the most flawless watch designs in the history of watchmaking. It simply works well with everything, from trunks and a tank top to a smoking (although that's a slight faux-pas, but whatever). It is also no nonsense and a rugged beast. That said, I have a gigantic crush for Grand Seikos, their finishing is, I believe, even better that what Rolex offers and they are responsible for the most technologically advanced watches in the industry. To be honest, though, I wouldn't get a hi-beat spring-drive, but rather one of their quartz pieces. What Seiko does to a simple quartz movement to up its quality is simply unbelievable, their stable and precise tic-tacking makes me shiver. My favourite is the SBGX093, with the anti-magnetic shielding and touches of red on the dial.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 19:45:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm shocked that this is actually a speedmaster and not a "watch with dial and hands". Seriously, what director would bother to have the 3D team model and animate an actual speedmaster for an anime?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 20:53:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love when they do that, but a Makoto Shinkai movie and Fate/Zero UBW are definetely in a completely different level of production work</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 23:05:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That watch fits you like a glove. I really wanted a samurai but am afraid it just isn't gonna fit me. How big are your wrists?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 06:33:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh wait it's Prisma Ilya, I read the comment real fast then just looked at the pic so I thought it was Fate Unlimited Blade Works, I also directly associated Shinkai with a movie because yeah that happens, but granted 5cm/s is a TV anime. Anyway, I meant production work, not necessarily value. Although some anime might be better budgeted than others, which depends a lot on the studio, the franchise (if applicable) and the estimated sales; even similarly budgeted anime can have a different approach to production. Shinkai's care for photorrealistic frames with a lot of attention to detail, which is more or less the same *ethos* adopted by the production in the later adaptations of the Fate franchise (though granted I'm not a fan of the franchise so I didn't really bother watching much of it), and in the case of OP, Akyuki Shinbo being who Akyuki Shinbo is, means that the work put toward details in the character's design will strive to be realistic rather than focus on, say, high-profile 2D animation, like most of Trigger stuff, or background art and character reactions like what KyoAni does best. My god I'm discussing anime on a watch subreddit where has the world gone. That said: Monogatari and Speedmasters are really two things I though I'd never see together. My god do I love Omega and Shinbo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 06:49:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Rolex Explorer I](https://m.rolex.com/de/watches/explorer/m214270-0003.html) The new [Omega Railmaster](https://www.hodinkee.com/articles/the-new-omega-railmaster-collection-and-a-contestant-for-the-surprise-favorite-of-the-show-live-pics) (black dial on the bracelet) [Grand Seiko SBGX093](https://www.google.com.au/amp/www.ablogtowatch.com/grand-seiko-sbgx093-quartz-watch-review/amp/) And, more realistically, the darling [SARB033](https://www.seiyajapan.com/products/s-sarb033)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 22:26:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm really fond of the guilloch #233; in the new Montblanc models. It's very hard to make it assymetric and still look good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 22:29:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly as expected of a japanese PM</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 03:35:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone got any reccomendation for a sub $600, dressy sport / sporty dress watch,  lt;41mm, black face, no date and on an oyster-like bracelet that is neither a homage nor the SARB033? I love the Explorer I, Omega Railmaster (new) and the Grand Seiko SBGX093 for a reference; but my collecting philosophy is mostly against homages and although I love the SARB033 I've heard the bracelet is real poor quality.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 04:13:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought about that too. What are some nice bracelets that fit a SARB?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 00:08:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, as an enthusiast I believe there can be a lot of amazinng craftsmanship in quartz, even to the point of exceeding mechanical movements. The quartz Grand Seikos and other classics like the Rolex Oysterquartz are IMO on par with the excellence of the mechanical version of their watches. That said, I'm unaware of the quality of Heuer quartz movements, or how they compare to their mechanical counterparts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 06:21:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey OP I think it's wonderful you shared such deep and personal issues with all of us and I wholeheartedly empathize with you in much of your experience. Sex is definetely something weird for me too although I'm not really repulsed by it and believe I could do it to please a significant other. I understand particularly how you feel towards porn, and that's what creeped me out the most about sex as soon as I came in contact with it. For many years I couldn't stand the idea of sex because in my mind it was supposed to be abusive in order to be pleasant, however recently I came accross many alossexual friends - specially feminists - who deeply criticized the idea of sex as portraied in pornography. With this new contact, I managed to figure out it can actually be something pleasant for some (most?) people. From there on I started being more open towards the idea of having sex, albeit it didn't change at all my (lack of) will to seek it. I think that in this particular point your experience says a lot about the intersections between sexuality and gender violence. The way sex is sold, as a male dominated market that reiterates th subjagation of women, makes many of us very uncomfortable and unable to develop a healthy way of understanding sexuality. This is not to say, of course, that assexuality is caused by direct or indirect exposition to sex, but rather that this kind of exposition makes many of us assexuals unable to understand alossexual desires and it is very challenging to overcome it since the idea of sex as a kind of violence is aggressively marketed mainly towards us, the male audience.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 22:13:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just because you don't want to have children yourself, don't force your life choices into others whether ace or not, I thought that was just common decency</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 21:37:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not even that, Canada has actual Human Rights issues, mainly violations towards native canadians.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 21:39:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brazilian here. Many drug problems around for years with a repression policy (not so harsh as the ones in Phillipines though). Drug trade has probably increased due to such policies. It is well known that police forces and government officials actually take part in drug related crimes, increasing the repression thus increases criminality.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 21:41:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ponzi schemes?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 22:35:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not to mention the interests of rich landowners and mining/oil industries</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 11:59:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that an argument for epistocracy and foreign interventionism? We had that. Believe me it was worse than it is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 12:00:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even the economy part is arguable, although granted that's the only part which is still within democratic possibilities.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 12:06:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not really, hardly ever elected presidents get less than 40% approval in Brazil. Mr. Temer was not elected, and Dilma got really low at around 20-30% before she was impeached. This and Mr. Collor in 1992 are probably the only instances where elected presidents got below the 40% threshold.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 23:41:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Palestine's independence, I'd guess - except the bullets they'd get there wouldn't be rubber ones</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 23:17:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can find people attractive just as you find artworks attractive. Take a look at Botticelli's Birth of Venus and you'll most likely be in awe and want to stare at it for a good time. The same with people. Of course, that attraction may be different in weight for each person. The same way some people are more attracted to sculptures than paintings, some will be more attracted to people. The same way some people are more attracted to baroque than classic, some will prefer, say, women to other genres. And it goes on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 13:36:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because colonial rule is really not a pretty thing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Berlin-based photographers, where do you develop/scan/print your film?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 18:35:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello guys, I just moved to Potsdam a month ago and I was wondering where I could go to develop my film. If any of you know a place in Potsdam, I'd appreciate it immensely, however Berlin is only 30min away so it's also no big deal to go there. Thanks in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Question from a cis white male ace.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 18:43:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello guys, I was talking to a friend of mine recently and the topic diverged to whether I am or am not part of an oppressed community. Now, don't get her wrong, she was very respectful and all and it didn't go in the "you're not oppressed enough" talk. Rather, she argued that as a cis white male who so far only had relationships with women, I am not perceived as a member of the queer community, thus I'm not oppressed. Although of course aces are frequently subjected to corrective rapes, correction therapies and sorts of exclusions, I started to think she might have a point. The thing is, I have never *personally* suffered any kind of violence. My friends and family are very respectful and compassionate about my sexuality, and even with strangers I never felt much more than slightly bothered by their denial of assexuality. However, I know my experiences are not necessarily universal. That's why I'd like to know from this community whether any of you know of or have suffered any kind of discrimination or violence agains cis white male assexuals. Thanks in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 19:22:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>The thing is when it comes to actual acts of violence against assexual people, I do have a feeling that women and trans people are targets to corrective rapes due to their assexuality (although I don't think there's any data to back that up). That's why I asked the question. Is the violence against cis male white aces just people bothering us or is it something else?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 19:30:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think that was my friend's point. It's rather that the *seen as* is what constitutes oppression from a social and objective standpoint, not individually but rather as a collective. If I am to further my question, it'd be: what exactly constitutes the *seen as* in the assexual community? If nothing, than is it possible to exist a kind of oppression that relies necessarily on intersection? The answer to the second one would be obviously be yes, since for assexual women and trans people corrective rape is a thing, and for non-heteroromantic assexuals, invasive corrective therapy is also a thing. But I'm not 100% sure about the first one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 19:33:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>That makes a lot of sense, I didn't think through this point of view. I can take corrective sexual activity as being a thing (especially given the conditions for male socialization).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 01:13:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, but I'm also politically defined by some categories. This does not rid me of me individuality, but rather allows me to see myself as part of a bigger group.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 10:06:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nuclear waste, people. It's baaaaad. This is in no way a support to the actions carried out by the activists.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 22:56:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, but I believe that from a non-lawyer/politologist/sociologist perspective, the terms law, state, civil society and organized groups might be very similar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 23:05:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tbh I think this decision and this ending is perfect. The whole show is not about individual heroism, but reflects on the need of a collectivity to cause change in a system. Akane knew that. She saw with her own eyes what happened to Kogami when he tried to do it. I differ from digi, where I believe Akane is a true revolutionary for that. Her choice was to not get rid of sybyl, as it'd only bring chaos and take society to it's primal state, from which it would take centuries to reorganize in a no less oppressive state. But it was also to not merge with it and keep the status quo. By walking back Akane realized herself was not enough, that she needed the help with others to bring society to a brighter and more human future. I only loathe that the second season was not at all about this collective effort both within and against sybyl.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 08:14:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Except for the market competition it'll create. So far as I'm aware the japanese market is overcrowded with animators. Although you might be able (and probably will) to get more money for overtime, this also means everybody will overtime, and the ones who don't will be underproductive and fired to be substituted with new animators who will.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 08:05:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>International law in a nutshell</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 10:28:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow $800 for a slave, sounds honest</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 10:33:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lybia was a complete disaster from the national AND international standpoint. It's silly to blame it all on Gadaffi, even though he had a part in the first place, it's not out of the question that the lybian spring was supported by west governments, nor that the NATO intervention was *surprise* a complete wreck. The point here is, although authoritarian in nature, Gadaffi kept the country *a country*. One could easily argue that North Korea is better off than Somalia. Authoritarian regimes are still regimes of some kind, and far better than failed states. Besides, during Gadaffi Lybia had one of the highest HDIs in Africa and well sustained health care and education systems, now it's just nobody's land.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 10:39:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those guys with cannons come at your coast and say they won't let you off the hook and storm your whole empire unless you sell them some slaves. You conquer some tribes and do. 400 years latter some dude on the internet is saying it was your fault.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 10:44:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get what you mean, I'm just not sure who much the "refugees welcome" campaign has affected more than the overall anti-immigration propaganda by most western states. I tend to think the guys would try to flee anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 10:47:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>But wouldn't shutting the routes actually cause smugglers (who don't care anyway whether the others get there) to keep doing their thing, but with a higher return rating? (Thus, more "sunken cost" being sold as slaves)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 11:02:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe you're correct, my point is that you shouldn't make such a strict analysis of a complex phenomenon. Western powers and arab states were also at fault here. To a point that trying to say who started what is almost impossible, and would greatly vary depending who much one weights certain factors against others. The fact remains that Lybia was better off while Gadaffi was ruling as it is right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 10:45:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>First, Human Rights are not ideals, they're norms, law, legally binding. The phillipines are a contracting state on the international covenant on civil and political rights, and even if they weren't, the prohibition of extrajudicial killing is a rule for every single country in the world. Far from every moral argument, Duterte's drug policy is *straight up illegal*. Second, if processing and jailing drug users and traffickers would be a problem (as it is a problem in Latin America, btw I'm brazilian so I know it first hand), then why not legalization? It doesn't have to happen from day to night, but it's a path recommended internationally and with high rates of success, yes, even in developing countries - see how uruguay reduced drastically the number of prisoners and drug-related offenses processes after only marijuana legalization. Of course the policy would jave to be adapted to south-east asian reality, but it's tried and tested.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 17:56:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>If your whole argument is based on rampant corruption and system inneficiency, I don't see what actually impedes you from standing for solutions of this problem rather than just giving up and accepting mass executions of unjudged presumed drug traffickers as the only way out. It's true I don't understand much of the history of south east asia, but all of the problems you ennumerated as the starting point of your analysis (drug abuse, corruption, and system inneficiency), are also present in latin america.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 19:06:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm still not comviced it's the only way for developing countries. Once again, look at Uruguay, they solved the drug problem without having to resort to any kind of extrajudicial executions. Portugal is also a good example after the decriminalization and shift from crime to health policy, although maybe not the best for comparisons, as a membership to the EU has a lot to do with that. Still, public policies are challenging, even if it is necessary to adapt to the east-asian context, that's something that can be done. Of course it would take a long time but it's possible to preserve the rights of *everyone* and get rid of drugs. Policies should aim for that, not taking the easy way out (for some, because it certainly isn't easy for drug users, alleged traffickers and their families). Politics is no Occam's Razor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 13:48:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not everybody who lives under isis is a isis member I thought that was obvious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 13:50:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfornately, but all steps should be taken to assure the number of deaths is the least possible. Transparence and conducting independent and imparcial ground investigations on the damage of an attack is one of those. Seems the US hasn't being doing it so well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 08:09:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or your bureaucracy is a pain in the ass hell I'm trying to get a 6 month student permit in germany and it takes me at least 3 months of filing papers. Edit: I don't even know why I'm getting so many downvotes for clarifying a factor that plays a major role.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 18:04:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wouldn't care about a "small fortune" if it is to be used in a wrecked country with no prospect of wellfare.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 01:02:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>For non-international actors such as ISIS you might be right, hardcore authoritarian regimes are also not caring that much, but drmocratic states come under A LOT of scrutiny for violating the laws of war. Military operations are usually planned keeping those in mind and everything is always triple-checked to avoid unnecessary damage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 01:33:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Non-state actors are hardly ever concern of the UN, as they're considered a problem of the state in which they are acting, only in extreme circumstances will the UN intervene and even so while keeping the interests of the affected state in mind. As for third-world countries you're right, but I wasn't mentioning the UN as the sole interstate actors. The US and Russia come frequently under scrutiny of the media for their attacks in Syria. In their case of course the permanent seat in the UNSC helps alleviate the consequences, and in the case of Russia the authoritarian regime allows it to not give much of a fuck either. The thing is substantially different for countries like Japan, Germany and most NATO members, for example, that don't have the UNSC curtain nor the authoritarian rule to keep public opinion at bay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 09:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed! Just want to make a remark on the taliban, which is a de facto state actor. Even though it lacks recognition, the exercize of authority over Afghanistan has legal consequences in war (ex: POW treatment for Taliban detainees), which have been observed at the least to be circumvented, and even so most states don't even circumvent it and even the US has to accept a great hinderance for its military operations when denying the status of combatant to Taliban forces, namely that US combatants are to wear uniforms at all times or be treated as illegal combatants by the detaining power.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 18:35:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is pointless. Twelve year-olds will keep being raped unless effective policies are implemented to secure women's and children rights. What really is needed is a significant reform on the indian police system, with strategical budgetary increases in sectors dedicated to specialized treatment against sexual violence. A nation-wide plan to restructure police offices and give adequate training to officers, specially in the affected regions is imperative! Commuting death sentences is just a scapegoat to a serious and systemical problem, which will likely result in a more expensive and less human justice system that does not respect the rights of the alleged offender. No punishment is preventive, specially if you cannot reasonably expect for it to be carried out, as is the case in India. Tl;dr: no point in death sentences, specially when the offenders are not even getting caught.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 11:04:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Clearly dutch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 11:34:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I'm just trying to specify</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 23:03:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone knows any good low to mid-tier (nordic) minimalist brands like COS or Samsoe  amp; Samsoe? Those are my favorite go-to stores, and I'd like to open my catalogue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 23:56:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Although the style is high on point, and as much as I love those brands, it's just not within my budget, they're significantly more expensive than the ones I listed and make up for only one or maybe two purchases a year for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 21:30:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hard to say, what it means is less foreign intervention in syria, so syria's matter will be left a little bit more at their own hands. Violence from other rebel anti-asad as well as government violence might scale up significantly, or it just might end with a sure win on either side (probably asad's). Russia's step out of the country means it perceive a less likely threat to the deposition of asad's government. If it is true, it might mean the government is more likely right now to take matters at their own hands and solve it more or less quickly. But I am certainly downplaying many other factors here (for example, how rebel groups might feel encouraged to engage in more direct violence with the government's greatest military ally stepping back). There is no short answer, but whatever comes next will be crucial.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 09:08:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably, I'd also wait for more detailed analysis from political scientists, but if my guesses are correct even they might diverge on the prognose here. It's a subtle subject, depending on how much you emphasize a certain factor, results may drastically differ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 09:19:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably, I'd also wait for more detailed analysis from political scientists, but if my guesses are correct even they might diverge on the prognose here. It's a subtle subject, depending on how much you emphasize a certain factor, results may drastically differ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 09:27:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a pretty solid argument you have there fella, indeed it is</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 09:30:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>It has succesfully avoided large scale total wars for over 70 years, take it is you may</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 21:43:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pax americana without expansionist tendencies and worlwide brute force colonization is only possible trough the existence of a worldwide forum of states led by the single most relevant rule of prohibiting wars. Your "pax americana" is only stopped of being a barbaric roman/british empire through the mediation of the UN. Not denying the factor of the existence of a hegemonic power as a possible means to the achievement of peace, but even that is debatable under current realistic political theories.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 15:27:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's called suicide, look it up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 01:53:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great news, you just discovered that there are really shitty people in the world and you use that to derail a whole political movement. Yeah, there are shitty women, but it's hard to believe 4 out of 10 in a research conducted in proper methods are mostly lying because of one very unfortunate example you happen to know of. Btw, I'm also brazilian, and I'd go as far as to say the number might be higher, as most woman friends of mine have reported being groped, catcalled or even sexually threatened in public environments.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 01:57:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Guys, sexual harrassment is not necessarily the same as rape, catcalling or groping in public transportation, for example, is a serious and common issue in Brazil most women did in fact went through, probably even more than 40% as many don't even recognize it as sexual violence. Stop trying framing it on feminism when the problem is a sexist society. Btw I'm also brazilian, most of my women friends have reported being harrassed at least once, either by gropers, aggressive (threatening) catcallers or even bosses/colleagues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 19:57:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly I think we should just stop blaming things on the "worst" people - as if there was something like that - and recognize that the only steps takrn towards praceful coexistence in the region (UN Resolution 171 and the Oslo Agreements) are being shattered by an american policy that overprotects one side of the conflict. An arab (palestinian) ruled west bank is the only way to peace, as is a coadministered jerusalem!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 20:08:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think OP is theoretically correct, but this downplays the many ways of restricting citizenship within a country. It's naive to believe that after Israel became a single state in the region the government would grant all palestinian/arab residents citizenship. Israel could, for example, restrict citizenship to sons of original israeli decent (jus sanguini), which would significantly impair most papestinians of acquiring citizenship. On another example, it could adopt an ethno-national citizenship policy, where only members of certain ethnicities are allowed citizenship (see what Myanmar is doing with the Rohingya). Also possible would be the treatment of palestinians as jordanian migrants, with no right to citizenship under strict immigration laws. Tl;dr: there are endless ways to restrict citizenship, israel would somehow manage to not grant it to palestinians.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 10:34:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well yeah, in theory you're right, but that's assuming Israel and Palestine would manage to draft a treaty in equal grounding, which is hard given Israel's superior military power and their harsh unilateral stance in international stance. But even if such a treaty were to be drafted, then a political consensus on the structure of a new state would likely envisage power distribution between jews and arabs in a way very near to the Lebanese political compromise. If so, the situation would just further unstabilize given the rapidly growing arab population in contrast to the declining jewish. Anyway, best-case scenario the one state solution would end up just turning the oppression scale in medium to long term.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 11:17:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is true, but you still get two more or less stable states where people fully exercize their right to self-determination. The tensions arising from the conflicts between the states themselves can be solved through international politics afterwards and as long as no war breaks out, the damage to each people would be minimal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 00:19:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are goddamn brilliant, please never stop making comics, you got everything to be really big, I honestly enjoyed those comics as much if not more than I do my personal favourites webcomics.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 13:55:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sources? Also keep in mind that under brazilian law indigenous reservations are NOT a property title, it #8217;s a collective right of common use of the land, land within a reservation CANNOT legally be sold to third parties. If they are donated by a private NGO than that #8217;s different, but we #8217;re not talking about a reservation in this case, regular property laws (including the right to sell) applies. Besides, if they got the donated property and sold it afterwards its their problem, just like if someone gave you a house for free and then you sold it it #8217;d be yours.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 14:04:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, George Soros and Bill Gates also do it, guess what they are. Edit: hell, even Bono Vox</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 09:09:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, but what about the benefit of the doubt? This is approach of taking first to give back later is a clear violation of any democratic country criminal law. Of course the proof standard for confiscating a jacket is probably no that right nowhere, but implying it can be done without any proof at all is arbitrary.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 09:29:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>But that #8217;s not how the benefit of the doubt works, it #8217;s not a tool to be used based on the individual but on the alleged crime commited. Even a known sex offender has the same benefit of the doubt as everyone if accused of yet another sex crime for example. Suspicion does not preclude this right, exactly because suspicion is highly subjective and based on the individual and not on the criminal act. Doing so undermines equality before the law.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 16:47:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve been living in Germany for a while now and: 1. Nazism is something very sensitive for germans, even light-hearted Hitler jokes are a no-no unless you know the person is ok with it. 2. The Nazi Police (the SS) was the most horrendous organ within the whole nazi system, they carried out the exterminations and organized the public humilitions strategies and did ideological policing. Calling a german a nazi is bad, calling a german cop a nazi is so fucked up you #8217;d be better straight up hitting him/her. 3. Free Speech in Germany is NOT the same as it is in the US, legal limitations concerning hate speech and specially nazism allusions are really strict. Tl;dr: you #8217;re in someone #8217;s house, you better respect the rules.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 17:46:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Free speech doesn #8217;t mean saying what you want, there #8217;s no place in the world that doesn #8217;t establish some sort of barrier to the exercize of this right. Also, it #8217;s always bilateral, if you #8217;re free to speak, others are free to hear and those are free to be offended. What the law does is recognize certain things as offensive and make those punishable. In democratic states those are really few strong insults, like calling a german officer a nazi. In autocratic states, criticizing the government itself gets you jailtime. The difficulty is where to draw the line on what is free speech and what is not. Different cultures do that differently. But there is no question that there should be a line somewhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 17:54:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>The SS was the paramilitary before the regime then it became the regular police and army after a certain point. The Gestapo was the secret police, they didn #8217;t even have that many people really (around 4,000 employees) and were closer to being a NSA sort of thing. All of them were under the coordination of the SD. Please anyone correct me if I #8217;m wrong, but pretty dure it was something like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 18:20:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Free speech means you CAN say anything, but you #8217;ll be held responsible for what you say. If it damaged anyone in a significant way or presents a threat to the security of others, then you #8217;ll be in trouble. It doesn #8217;t mean you SHOULD say anything you want. The difficult point is what constitutes  #8220;damage #8221; and  #8220;threat #8221; in the sentence above. Germany is more strict with it than the US.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 18:25:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I have friends here who do joke about it too (both german and foreigner). It #8217;s usually ok with anyone under 30, but even so I #8217;d be sure to know the person #8217;s sense of humour firsthand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 18:28:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>The government doesn #8217;t decide the words that are or aren #8217;t prohibited. The circumstance and context is absolutely fundamental to assess whether a) there is an offence and b) whether the offence is punishable. You can say  #8220;Nazi #8221; in Germany, and hell you should say  #8220;Nazi #8221; to someone doing a Sieg Heil with red arm bands on a protest for white supremacy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 18:33:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed, but that is not the issue. Nor did you disaggree with me that yoo should be held accountable for what you say. By the way, with maybe the exception o violent crime-encouranging public speeches, the punishment is private in nature, the judge will only confirm or deny the right and settle the amount of reparation for the victim.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 18:48:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, it #8217;s not like that at all, of course if she somehow knew they were nazis, then she wouldn #8217;t be punished. That #8217;s how the law works. And it #8217;s true she might have know that somehow, but it seems just a casual encounter between a woman and a police officer. Even if he is privately a nazi, or even somewhat publicly, it has to be established whether SHE knows or could #8217;ve reasonavly known it. Otherwise it #8217;s just offensive, she did it to purposely hurt the officer, not only in a subjective manner, but a very objective one with clear reference to the common past of the nation he belongs too and one could hardly say this was not her intention when calling him a nazi.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 18:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are everywhere, though. For the same reason punching someone is: it hurts. Edit: from circumstance to circumstance you #8217;ll get different answers on what hurts and whether it hurts enough to make someone liable for it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 00:22:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reasonable redditor comment award 2k18, thank you! I don #8217;t know why this is turning into a heated debate on what is free speech, where my argument is that there are many conceptions. That #8217;s all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 00:27:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unless you #8217;re implying free speech only exists in the US the way US laws govern it, then yeah. I #8217;m saying it #8217;s different. Not that that isn #8217;t nor that it #8217;s better. Btw you can obviously get punished by insulting someone in the US either, it #8217;s just that it #8217;s stricter in Germany.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 00:29:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hate speech is a very difficult term to define precisely, it is illegal everywhere I #8217;m aware of, but countries differ on its precise definition. To an extent, that #8217;s ok.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 00:32:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You punish someone for calling a law-abiding working class citizen a genocidal, the worst insult possible in his culture, therefore you are a nazi. Yeah, right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 00:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>1) those are not my laws, I just happen to live here, not a citizen; 2) insult leads to legal consequences in every democratic country, whether fines, reparations or jail time (in severe cases). Either every democracy is authoritarian or no one is, except a potential one where you can insult anyone (and anyone can insult you - and mind yourself, insults can get REALLY dark).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 00:41:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m still astounded about how many people still think it #8217;s nazi to punish someone who calls a person nazi. I mean, back on the reich this would be a hell of a compliment. Also, there are the eventual comentors like you who abuse the nazi insult and at the same time seem to comdemn it #8217;s use by the SJW. You either like it or leave it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 00:47:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I also think german laws are a little on the strict side of free speech too. The Nazi thing is historical and well-grounded, I believe, but they could be more lenient on the rest. Still, can #8217;t criticize them that much, it #8217;s their decision as a democratic nation and I believe it #8217;s well withing general human rights parameters. It doesn #8217;t bother me to play by their rules.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 00:51:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even the right to life can be limited in war situations or with the death penalty in the US, why couldn #8217;t free speech? It #8217;s your right (free speech) as long as its exercize doesn #8217;t infringe the right of others (privacy and dignity).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 01:05:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mind games: imagine you #8217;re a 50 year old suburban guy who had his daughter raped and killed by your brother. He goes to jail, years pass and he gets out. Later on he comes back to your town and everyday religiously goes to your porch and screams  #8220;how #8217;s your daughter? #8221;. Now, repeat to me what you just said.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 01:23:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a brazilian I think they #8217;re really really well-prepared. And I #8217;m not that much of a police guy, for the good or for the bad their job is to exercize violence. The Polizei guys always keep it as a last resort and usually work around non-violent measures until they are absolutely exhausted. Well, of course there are problems like the racial profiling we saw in K #246;ln a couple years ago, but that #8217;s more of an exception than a rule. And not every cop is always well prepared. But even for the exceptions I think police laws here offer a great deal of remedies for the victims. In my personal experience officers have always been really helpful and open to everyday inquiring like  #8220;is there a toilet here? #8221;, even the high-tech armed guys at Berlin Hbf. Now, I #8217;m comparing them to the brazilian police, which is likely one of the most brutal and arbitrary in the world. Not saying this for every individual officer, personally they #8217;re also usually nice hard-working honest people, but the whole police system lacks a gigantic amount of safeguards and there #8217;s little attention to human rights and tactical training for operations in densely populated areas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 09:11:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>They were run by the SS also Mengele was a SS officer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 09:17:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>It means you #8217;ll be held responsible for what you say. There is a line between free speech and respect for dignity, so that one right ends were the other begins. What I #8217;m saying is there #8217;s a cultural difference on where this line is drawn, and this is acceptable to a certain extent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hrollaugr, Dane Baron of the Kitchenware</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 00:32:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 13:33:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excelent reply! I #8217;d like to add a little bit on more internal political aspects. Myanmar is now a transitional democracy after long years of a junta led military government who are the ones manipulating the militias and paramilitaries and in fact conducting the genocide. The population is also majorly favourable as the extremist buddhists have gained gargantous influence over the past months. Even though the current president is a peace nobel winning leader and I believe is fully commited to achieving democratical peace in Myanmar, the constant threats of the army make the Rohingya situation a untouchable one, to the point that even using the word Rohingya is a political tabu. In such a tense environment, I believe that even if an intervention was politically possible, the military component might lead to a failure as it did in post Gadaffi Lybia, Iraq and arguably Kosovo. The population would likely gather around strong military autocratic leaders against the perceived menace of international troops. Worst case scenario this could lead to a proxy war between NATO/UN and perhaps China and Russia on the other side. Best case scenario democracy will be overthrown and all hopes for a peaceful resolution will be gone once the junta is back in power.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 17:29:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>They can be called back anytime by the sending state (US) and be declared persona non grata at anytime by the receiving state (Canada) and losing immunity if staying longer than the deadline. The decision is unilateral and doesn #8217;t have to be grounded on anything, but most countries choose to do so for reasons of good offices. Anyway those are politically harsh decisions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 17:34:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes and no. On the one hand, the immunity extends way further when you deal with the country, since it might gain diplomatic premisse status (which is absolutely inviolable, even for functionally unrelated claims). On the other hand, depending on the country you #8217;re dealing with they #8217;ll make the effort to pay and not get bad rep.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 17:57:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a hard time believing the judge #8217;s decision will hold up. All in all this is a short analysis on why you SHOULDN #8217;T make contracts with diplomats (unless in their country of origin). Article 31 (a) on the Convention on Diplomatic relations states that diplomats are not immune  #8220;To real actions relating to private immovable properties situated in the territory of the receiving State, UNLESS he holds it (...) FOR THE PURPOSES OF THE MISSION #8221; It #8217;s very well settled in International Law that the house of a diplomat is a place that also serves the purpose of the mission. This is because it #8217;s a place where diplomatic reunions and dinners may take place, as well a place where privacy should be granted for the diplomat to freely communicate with its staff while outside the premises (this is essential in case of diplomatic emergencies for example). Also, systematically speaking, art. 30 of the same Convention makes the house of a diplomat enjoy  #8220;the same inviolability (...) as the premisses of the mission #8221;. Which is further argument on why its considered to be a place for uses of the mission. All things taken, art. 31 (a) also excludes inviolabiloty in the case of REAL claims. Real claims involve property, so diplomats are not inviolable to claims regarding the status of proprietary of real-state. Obviously, rent claims do not consist real claims, but rather contractual ones, to which there are no exceptions on immunnity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 03:13:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well considering territorial sea extends 12 sea miles away frim the coast baseline I can #8217;t see how that map #8217;s accurate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 23:40:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brazilian here: the shittier 25% are very real.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 00:35:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well there #8217;s one guy who #8217;s maybe juuuuuuust maybe not corrupt. But yeah he #8217;s a populist, right-wing extremist scumbag who is openly pro-torture and pro-dictatorship.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 00:41:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>He #8217;s the first in the polls after former president Lula got arrested.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This man #8217;s name</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 01:14:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 01:17:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Over at the website of the Police Department of the State of Goi #225;s, Brazil, you can find a list with their former directors. There you can see Hitler Mussoline Domingues Pacheco (his name was slightly misspelled - for more comic effect - in a interview back in the 90s) [Relevant Page](http://www.policiacivil.go.gov.br/ex-diretores/) Edit: slight additions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 13:38:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you intend to travel there you'll probably be fine, policing and security in high end touristic parts of town is quite good. I strongly advise you to know exactly where you're going and which route you're taking before going out. Also, using the public transportation or staying on the streets past 21h is discouraged. Having a brazilian guide/friend nearby will also help, we know our way through.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 16:53:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm starting to think that Carnival in Brazil is like a special event raid with extra 2.5x drop rate every year. So many bosses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A pretty gurrrl in a muted background with neutral colours (Mju II // Portra 400)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 19:45:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Second pic of my friend during a trip to Potsdam (Mju II / Portra 400)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 03:07:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I live in my house.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 02:21:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 02:26:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like the place I live in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 14:24:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where I live.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 13:28:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. I just don #8217;t see how OP implied their asexuality has anything to do with anhedonia. They used  #8220;in addition to #8221; in the post title and psychiatric drugs and anhedonia may as well be  #8220;partially to blame #8221; in one #8217;s perceived sexuality.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Night at the Spree (Mju II // Portra 400)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 23:56:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Berlin Television Tower (Canonet QL17 // Portra 400)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 23:57:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 15:17:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh thanks! I know it #8217;s technically a  #8220;bad shot #8221; but I misfocused and misaligned intentionally. I really like the dreamy and blurry feel of the result, the colors also complemented it very well IMO. I #8217;ve been living im Berlin for the past 6 months and the television tower is so heavily photographed and has such a heavy feel to it that I thought I should somehow soften it with my pictures.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 21:06:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it #8217;s quite clever tbh. Sounds really cheesy but it #8217;s not crappy design, it #8217;s clearly intended to be like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 17:06:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the context but most people came here without none so it #8217;s understandable to complain.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 17:49:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m a vegetarian and asexual. Whenever people come up with any made up facts on either I just look at them with a  #8220;I don #8217;t even know why you bother #8221; face and proceed to whatever I was talking before or completely change the subject. Usually works, but there #8217;s the eventual asshole that just insists on asking. Now, even those assholes are often not ill-intended, people just can #8217;t really empathize with our identity, which is understandable. My tip is: stay strong, be calm, and most people will eventually understand. Whoever maliciously pokes on you for that doesn #8217;t really deserve your respect and attention. If it #8217;s unavoidable, then keep contact to a minimum and gather with people who give you respect. But do not hide. Be loud, be proud. You #8217;ll feel much freer and you #8217;ll realize that many people love you regardless of your identity and life choices.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 17:52:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you lack sexual attraction</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 22:53:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fun fact: the Berlin television tower (Fernseherturm) was actuall a Stasi-sponsored  #8220;tourist attraction #8221; with various caf #233;s and shops in the former Eastern Germany. It is said that ALL of the employees working there were Stasi undercover agents. It also broadcasted government propaganda and fake news from state-run media, as expected in a dictatorship. So this is a true evil building.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 22:54:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Isn #8217;t that straight up nazi architecture?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 12:21:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you seen the live action movie? Is the book any better? I watched it on a plane and really it just felt like a boring manic pixie dream girl thing. It kind of got to my nerves how the main girl is construed in a way that feels meticulously tailored to fit the likes of the MC. Even the conflicts were solved so as it excuse the MC of his shitty behaviour.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 18:13:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>The fact that taiwan is colored might make some people angry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 23:39:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Legally speaking you can recruit anyone above the age of 15 (or more in some countries). Under that line it is a war crime, but all countries are nevertheless reccomended to not recruit anyone under the age of 18, although this is not really binding. However, sending children under the age of 18 to a battlefield might still be a legal problem, since the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child doesn #8217;t cease to apply in those situations.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 21:01:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>The introduction of Frederica in this episode was brilliant. I #8217;ve only seen the OVA quite a long time ago and don #8217;t remember if it was the same or slightly different, but it comes to show that if one criticism can be made on LotGA #8217;s writing it is the lack of female characters, but it makes up for introducing the most amazing and well constructed ones. Take for instance Yang #8217;s slight discompusure when she comes into the room and presents herself (which is shoved away immediately after she asked if there was something unusual). This minimal facial expression does two things. First, it builds up on Yang #8217;s character as this praxis-oriented admiral fascinated with history that on the one hand is alien to the perspective of women in battlefield, but on the other understanding that this doesn #8217;t change anythig at all given that she was put there on her accolades alone. Second, it shows Frederica #8217;s grounded compusure and firm treatment, who doesn #8217;t care about putting her superior in a tight and akward situation, if it is to stand her ground. The second part is further explored on the Rosenritter HQ scene, but this doesn #8217;t mean that this scene was without purpose. It strikingly poses a comparison between the treatment of women in the FPA and the Empire. Wherein on the first case the more progressive ideals allowed then to get a military carreer and strive for political activism, the old and conservative Rudolphean institutions treats them as  #8220;marriage commodities #8221; (see Annerose and, more interestingly, Hildegard on the OVA). Certainly former Empire citizens do cater to more sexist and harrassing atitudes, besides of course totaling disrespecting the rank and position of Frederica. This is just one perspective to read those two scenes of course, which manage to tell so much in very little. Writing and directing like this gives not only more depth to the charaters but also builds a world which resonates much more with our own. The way LotGA in general, and new adaptation in particular, manages to bring so many larger-than-life themes in such a tight and natural package is what makes it a widely acclaimed series.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 22:22:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>From Trump #8217;s perspective this sound very logic. Peace talks in Korea have been smooth sailing and it #8217;s clear enough that Trump had very little to do with that. President Moo Jae In is leading all the talks and Trump is pretty much out of the game for now, so he can #8217;t really claim it as a political victory. Since the Israel-Palestinian conflict doesn #8217;t show much of a good perspective at the moment, and other conflicts (Syria, Ukraine) have been dwindling down or don #8217;t present a very strategic benefit for US intervention, then Trump clearly wanted to reactivate an old one. This will bring much more attention to the US in the Iranian nuclear program and prove as a new Battleground for Trump #8217;s Big Ham Policies. This serves the benefit of keeping his image and support from conservatives in the US by once again playing to his  #8220;preserver of national interest #8221; character and creating a new enemy that everyone can join to fight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 08:46:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah of course, that on the beggining was meant to be only mild criticism. The show is pretty ahed of its time, it certainly could be  #8220;aheader #8221;, but it was pretty great nevertheless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 14:22:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>But isn #8217;t wearing something a private display of religion? I know this is a hard debate but I believes what someone chooses to wear is their own business, the same of course would go for cross/david star necklaces. It seems quite abusive that an institution dictates what you should(n #8217;t) wear. Of course it #8217;a another thing for crosses in classrooms etc, that #8217;s not private.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 14:44:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes but the guideline being that state is secular means IMO that it respects religion plurality and allows private clothing and accessories without distinction. I know the discussion is a hard one, but that #8217;s also why I think it should always weigh to individual freedom as far as possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 15:19:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course! The discussion is whether religion neutrality means prohibiting certain indumentaries or allowing all of them. A state which allows Hijabs, Cross and David Star necklaces to be worn by their servants is no less secular than one who doesn #8217;t. Certainly civil servants are representatives of the state, but they #8217;re also individuals with their own beliefs. Celebrating religious diversity is, in my opinion, representing secularism as a form of respect towards all religions and not a refusal to represent any altogether.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 15:29:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I just believe the state #8217;s interest is celebrating religious diversity more than shying aqay from religious diplays.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 15:33:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactaly because it should be separated, that the state should not interfere or restrict anyone #8217;s liberty. Is a secular state one that rejects all religions or that accepts all of them? I #8217;d argue for the latter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 15:42:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Certainly, I believe neutrality in this sense means accepting all forms display of faith, not enforcing the lack of it. Yes it #8217;s a tough debate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 15:46:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Put it simply, both being being represented by people of ALL religious expressions and by people with NO religious expression is, in fact, neutral. My point being that the former allows the individual more liberty and should be preferred. Secularism isn #8217;t shown on the individual sense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 15:48:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, it #8217;s a different thing though discriminating by formality (undisputed in the workplace) and by religion (quite a hard discussion). You can be formal with a Hijab or a cross necklace.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 16:52:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you can sign up most american countries with that kind of interpretation on religious freedom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 22:52:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who are people supposed to prove they are not turkish citizens? This is devil #8217;s proof, if it #8217;s really like that this court case seems like a witch hunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 14:23:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok, that #8217;s a complicated law. Surely sex without consent is rape by any moral or societal standards, but legally this is a very complicated situation. In criminal law, as a matter of principle and justice, the Court has to assume the accused is innocent, unless proven otherwise. In this case, it means the initial assumption is: there was consent. How is it possible for prosecutors then to prove that there wasn #8217;t? You can blindly trust on the alleged victim #8217;s word, of course, and have the alleged perpetrator prove that there was consent, but isn #8217;t that the same thing as destroying the innocence principle altogether? I might be deadly wrong, and the law might be more precise and well written than what I could assume from reading the article, but if it is like that, any judge faced with a rape case will be forced to take one of the two routes: 1) destroy the innocence principle and assume whatever the alleged victim is saying is true without further proof or 2) simply disregard the accusation because consent is presumed and can #8217;t be possibly disproved (this is devil #8217;s proof, namely to allege that something didn #8217;t happen). Aggression and coercion on the other hand would have ne proven existent on a given case by the prosecutor, which actually makes it easier to the accusation. This law is either a violation of the right #8217;s of the accused or a way less effective mean of punishing rape. In either case bad, [trump] VERY BAD [/trump]</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 01:25:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I liked the former one though, the  #8220;oh shit they #8217;re almost here but I just barely made it #8221; feel made it awesome. I don #8217;t know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 10:26:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get your point, some people did read it like that but I think it was much more a kind of meta humour, like actually poking fun at ace exclusionary people. I mean you can #8217;t deny that the original post does indeed accept ace people. The final line IMO reproduces the exclusionary discourse in a comedic manner, it shows how stupid it actually is. That #8217;s why it was funny.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 19:03:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>On a legal perspective is an interesting decision, but both the ECJ and the ECHR have recognised implicitly in numerous cases that homossexual marriage is barely a contended issue within european space anymore. The ECHR for example has regonised Italy #8217;s duty to regulate it, although only reiterating the Corte de Cassazione #8217;s judgement (and pushing italian congress further). I #8217;m not sure how much different this judgement is in terms of judicial policy, specially given that the decision has a very specific and generally uncontroverted legal groundig. It might seem like a step further, but for me it only shows how the courts are still too stuck up with the idea of pissing off member states.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 20:00:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>For this matter certainly, because more and more states have been recognizing same sex marriage. I #8217;m just not so sure wheter the margin of appreciation doctrine as a whole has lost influence, on the contrary, I have the feeling the european courts have never been as strict in safeguarding state interest as they are today.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 09:46:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make germany two again!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 22:59:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>(translator #8217;s note: keikaku means plan)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 14:18:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>If all is fine with your body, not having sexual desire is ok and there #8217;s no need to panic. Asexuals are out there, as I am one. My whole life I was really attracted to girls and dated some but never had I ever wanted nor had anything sexual with them. And that #8217;s fine. I #8217;ve lived so far a healthy and happy life regardless, as many asexuals also do. If you really think there #8217;s still something wrong with you and you wanna fix it, then go on ahead, but I assure you there #8217;s nothing wrong, abnormal, vicious or hurtful about not having sexual desire. No one needs sex to be happy. Live your life the way you want to, no one should judge you, just be honest to yourself and happy :) If you wanna talk about asexuality feel free to hop onto my DMs I #8217;ll ba glad to help as much as I can. Otherwise visit r/asexuality or the AVEN forum, they #8217;ll surely have lots of material for you. Disclaimer: I don #8217;t wanna force asexuality into you, that #8217;s a label you should decide if you want for yourself or not, just want you to know that lack of sexual desire is healthy and normal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 17:24:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I guess that comes along with having and etnostate. Nothing against the right of existence of Israel, I understand and approve the idea that jews should have a place to live together, celebrate their culture and live free of oppression and persecution. But when this state is acceptant of jews only and promote those same things against arab minorities, then the state functioning should be reviewed from the ground up. It is possible to keep a nation within a state while promoting tolerance of others and human rights. Most western european countries do that (with the inherent flaws of walking on this often very tight rope). If Israel claims to be democratic, it better start opening up to diversity, which comes hand in hand with it; otherwise people like this congressman might just get stronger. This said, all Israel = nazis comments are stupid and overlook the very base of the historic institution of nazism. Moreover, this is just one congressman, and I guess all democracies have those weirdos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 07:55:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>The fact that norway hasn #8217;t done anything like it since WWII and the long lasting political stabilization of nordic countries. This points to a reestructuring of geopolitical military power in the european space.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 12:19:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you look into this list, the US is only better off than New Zealand in the developed world. All countries under number 41 are not developed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 11:00:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hope his audio files will be all LOSSless</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 11:50:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>:(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 13:00:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Responding with force would be a very dumb move. Spying and meddling in political affairs are a very grey zone in international law and governments can do it freely without attracting much attention. In fact, in terms of international relations it is way more lucrative to let it be done to you so you can do it back to them. Spy games are the norm in international affairs, some just happen to be more public than others, and often in purpose. Using this or other further espionage incidents as a ground for the use of force puts america on the wrong side of thing, because you can #8217;t use force for other reason than to impair the illegitimate use of force against yourself. Putting america in the wrong side of things and russia in the right one (as they #8217;d legimatelly defend themselves) turns all the factors in favor of russia. It #8217;d be hard if not impossible to justify any NATO action on the grounds of illegal use of force by the US, and Russia could rely on allied countries to retaliate, for example.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 15:31:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>The NATO acts accordingly to legal mechanisms subject to judicial review in each of the member states #8217; justice system. France, for example, wouldn #8217;t be able to send its troops even if the president wanted unless the action was due to collective self-defence. If it tried, the french judiciary could and possibly would just bar the sending of troops in lack of a legal ground for action. The same for most if not all NATO member states, they would see themselves inactive unless self-defence was sufficiently proved.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 01:47:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tales of Curitiba (besides the abusive customs delay on international orders I never had any problems though)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 10:29:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>No last panel is mirrored</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 17:34:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Transgender is not necessarily about body dysmorphia, which IS a mental disorder. Wherein transgender people often feel dysmorphia, some are completely comfortable with their own bodies or not uncomfortable enough to the point of being unhealthly obsessed with body change (such as in anorexia). It is more about the displacement in relation to expected social gender roles than to the body per se.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 17:39:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Playing videogames to the point of damaging obsession might as well be a mental disorder, also the number of suicides with homossexual people is also significantly bigger than in the straight community without meaning homossexuality is a disease. You might as well argue trans people are suiciding because they are being treated as sick anomalies. I don #8217;t know where you want to get with this argument.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 17:41:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>But are they emotionally unwell because they are transgender or because they are treated badly for being transgender? Certainly trans people who have been treated with love and acceptance are not unstable, much on the contrary.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 17:45:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do them? The left-wing argument I #8217;m for is that men and women (and trans and cis) are equal, but the different treatment each get in society is different. Brainwise I think it #8217;s pretty clear there #8217;s no difference (in the biological organ that is, maybe in its functioning, but it #8217;s also pretty unclear how much of the brain functioning is socially determined).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 17:47:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s an interesting argument, but even those lucky trans people are not living in isolation from an overall transphobic society, which in its turn impacts their mental well-being. It #8217;s not so much transsexuality #8217;s fault as it is transphobia #8217;s.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 17:49:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most certainly, I #8217;m not challeging the statistics, but the causality. Transexuality is not the cause of the mental unwelness in trans people, but rather the outside treatment they receive for being trans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 17:53:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also that #8217;s some shady edit. Still doesn #8217;t unprove my point, after all, isn #8217;t the lack of acceptance the cause of chemical imbalance? And going on a tangent, it #8217;s still pretty damn unclear whether depression is even related to any brain chemical imbalance, as it has been shown that many individuals with perfectly balanced brain chemistry still may show symptons of depression.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 22:38:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well all those factors come often paired with body dysphoria which is an actual mental health condition, but not to be reduced to transexuality itself (many trans do not have it and live well with their bodies, just not their social roles). Besides it #8217;s been pretty clear over the years in the transexual movement that they themselves do not want it to be considered and a disease and regard the  #8220;treatments #8221; for it highly inadequate. Treating transexuality as a disease puts the blame on the individual for being trans and doesn #8217;t focus on actual problems, such as body dysphoria or depression. Also, even if trans people are met sometimes woth acceptance by their close family, friend and colleagues, this does not mean they are being well treated overall. Transphobia is rampant and a trans person is well more likely to be poorly treated by other if not most people outside their close social circles, which put them still in a more sensible mental health condition. Tl;dr: the problem is not transexuality itself, but other things that come associated with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 22:40:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Transphobia doesn #8217;t mean being scared of trans people, but treating them in a bad and damaging manner for what they are. I don #8217;t know where you wanna get with this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 23:07:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can #8217;t seriously think homophobics are afraid of gays and xenophobics of strangers can you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 07:06:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Given the comments on this thread I wonder what would the reaction be like if Canada were to do the same with US families instead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 17:21:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It don #8217;t think they can force you either, nor that anyone except for some stupid individuals are trying to force that on any kind of political agenda. Of course of you misgender someone just because you might come off as a jerk given that it #8217;s quite a petty thing to do. Also I don #8217;t know how the brain chemistry in cis and trans persons is different, I #8217;m not a neurologist, but remember that the extent of the influence of social experience in brain chemistry is highly debatable. So even if it is different, that doesn #8217;t mean one would be able to differentiate trans people by their brain chemistry alone, and self identification would remain as the main and most useful factor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:52:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wherein I don #8217;t think  #8220;modern art #8221; is lesser art by any standard, having to write a book to explain it points to the inability of the artwork to communicate by itself, and makes it lose in meaning. What I can #8217;t stand are those attacks on the viewer for not understanding the piece, when it is supposed to communicate something. Good art, and also good  #8220;modern #8221; art (although modern is a umbrella that says nothing at all) is supposed to portray a zeitgeist, inspire an emotion, open new paths to the very understanding of the human condition. If you have to explain it, you failed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 00:52:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, that #8217;s why it doesn #8217;t distract me. It #8217; so bland and boring and repetitive that I just take it as background noise. That way I don #8217;t get excited and overly concentrated on the fully layered details or jaw dropping arrangements or anythig of the sort.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 09:36:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not sure how it goes in the US but usually changes in official documents are publicaly notified, so this wouldn #8217;t be an issue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 10:06:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wtf man this is kinda interesting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 10:08:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>But australia doesn #8217;t exist didn #8217;t we settle for that a long time ago?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 01:18:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactaly, my gut feeling is some people in this thread don #8217;t really understand research. That would probably be the worst thing you #8217;d find.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 13:05:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was about to add that to my tinder profile but it #8217;d be too much r/niceguys</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 03:29:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>It would, most countries abide by the so called "active personality principle" meaning that they have criminal jurisdiction over nationals who commited a crime anywhere. So if a US citizen kills someone on a raft in international waters he can be liable under US law. As I said: most countries, however I do not know of a single one that does not abide by this rule. The funny situation would be that of a stateless person commiting a crime against another stateless person in outer space, that'd maybe be left unpunishable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 03:34:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>If your rover is unregistered, it'd probably escape US jurisdiction in outer space, as the "flagged ship rule" applies only to vessels registered within a state. Not OP though, OP would be liable for any violation of FAA rules.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 21:00:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Too packed with the presidential run, but there was some minimal air time. Honestly there should be much more, Brazil is the country that most kills human rights activists in the americas and his is pobably the highest profile murder since Marielle. A shame a great part of politicians and people alike believe they are a nuisance that should be dealt with. Edit: wrong data, check thread.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 01:10:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://brazilian.report/society/2017/12/05/brazilian-human-rights-defenders-killed/ The worst in the americas* will correct original comment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 01:15:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s a hard number to get, specially because of forced disappearances and covered up reports, but for the accountable killings, Brazil does kill more (in absolute, not relative numbers) than any other. Bottom line is: we kill A LOT regardless</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Portuguese] Rio #8217;s 200 year old national museum caught on fire</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 01:30:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:18:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a research assistant myself this image will never leave my head. First they cut all scholarships and now they destroy our history and culture. It makes me wanna puke, and some candidates are even speaking of cutting off the ministry of culture and the ministry of research  amp; technology. It #8217;s just plain rotten.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rio #8217;s 200 year old national museum hit by massive fire</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:22:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:28:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>All because of a complete lack of funding for cultural heritage and public research. Some candidates for the forthcoming elections even have the guts of saying they want to get rid of the ministry of culture. Despicable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:56:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even they came back in this decision a little later. It is and always was criminally underfunded, but getting rid of it as a proposition for the candidacy is a new low.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:17:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thankfully nobody got hurt, there were only 4 security guards on duty that escaped before the fire went berserk and the museum closed for visitations a couple hours before. However, firefighters are having a hard time finding extra water supplies so they #8217;re currently only doing the fasade to try and save the structure, but the fire is stil spreading along the sides of the building. Due to severe underfunding the museum couldn #8217;t install fire prevention and control mechanisms that were necessary.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:23:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>They didn #8217;t fail, they planned it. I #8217;ve been working as a research assistant in Brazil ever since I got into college. The underfunding of public research and cultural instutions is planned and often times even cheered and regarded as a bad use of public funds. Well, this is what happens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>