<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7262</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 20:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a clinician in a residential program for children ages 6-12. I currently am getting my doctorate in psychology. Even though most of my kids are in state custody, some are returning to their parents homes and we do family therapy. At the start of my first family session the mom, who had just apologized to me for forgetting her teeth, informed me that one day she would be qualified to be my boss because she was getting her masters from Phoenix University.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-04 19:35:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>As SM you can't get wrapped up in it. Unless it is going to directly effect you just stay out of it. My husband's youngest was 15 when he and I started dating and for awhile I lived for the teen daughter drama. But I learned that for me and my family, I needed to just let their dad handle things like what OP is talking about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-04 02:41:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>By accident. I thought it was by-accidentally. On like, my 30th birthday I said it correctly and my mom was like why did you say that?! I was like because by-accidentally is wrong! She was like Nooo! Who told you? It was so cute! Thanks Mom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-04 02:46:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love friends!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 05:35:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was little I would get pains in my legs. My mom said they were growing pains. I'm 32 and still get them consistently. They keep me from sleeping. The only things that help are a combo of pain killers and heat. I wish they would stop. It gets worse when I'm tired or cold. My dr growing up had no explanation and I stopped asking for help around 7 years ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-15 00:44:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wenham here- Beverly really isn't trash!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>People of Reddit who have unhealthy/not positive relationships with your parents, how have you been able to cope as an adult?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 14:02:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can you help my dad deal with HIS dad?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 14:12:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm asking (32f) because my dad (62m) has never had a good relationship with his parents. My grandpa is narcissistic and controlling and has been all my dad's life. His mom is a nicer person, however was easily manipulated and controlled by her husband and now has early stages of Alzheimer's. There has always been tension and awkwardness in the family, but we would spend holidays together despite my grandpa's clear disdain for my mom (she's Irish and apparently that equals trash). When me and my brothers were in our teens our parents decided to give us the option to have a relationship w our grAndparents and we decided no, mostly due to the way he treats our mom. My dad's 2 siblings are divorced (due mostly to their dad's meddling and belief that "family blood" is stronger than non family) my dad has never seemed especially bothered by this divide in the family, and does try to have a positive relationship with his parents and siblings, but doesn't seek them out to spend time with them. He just found out that this thanksgiving they will all be together and didn't even bother to invite him and for the first time expressed to my mom that it made him feel really bad that he wasn't invited. My dad is one of the kindest, most generous, intelligent men I know, and he's not one to talk about feelings so I know this is bothering him. I was hoping to hear from people who have had similar experiences and how you handled it, especially as they approach old age/death. Did you have regrets once your parents were no longer here? Thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 23:02:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!!! He is a really good person. I think the only reason he survived that family is because they sent him away to school at the age of 12 because my grandfather couldn't "handle him". It's a tough situation the he's been dealing with his whole life. I just hate that he's sad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 00:54:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>(I made this a post before I saw this post.) I'm asking (32f) because my dad (62m) has never had a good relationship with his parents. My grandpa is narcissistic and controlling and has been all my dad's life. His mom is a nicer person, however was easily manipulated and controlled by her husband and now has early stages of Alzheimer's. There has always been tension and awkwardness in the family, but we would spend holidays together despite my grandpa's clear disdain for my mom (she's Irish and apparently that equals trash). When me and my brothers were in our teens our parents decided to give us the option to have a relationship w our grAndparents and we decided no, mostly due to the way he treats our mom. My dad's 2 siblings are divorced (due mostly to their dad's meddling and belief that "family blood" is stronger than non family) my dad has never seemed especially bothered by this divide in the family, and does try to have a positive relationship with his parents and siblings, but doesn't seek them out to spend time with them. He just found out that this thanksgiving they will all be together and didn't even bother to invite him and for the first time expressed to my mom that it made him feel really bad that he wasn't invited. My dad is one of the kindest, most generous, intelligent men I know, and he's not one to talk about feelings so I know this is bothering him. I was hoping to hear from people who have had similar experiences and how you handled it, especially as they approach old age/death. Did you have regrets once your parents were no longer here? Thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-22 00:54:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg this! I have it on my hands and feet. The number of times I get "Have you tried x y or z? It helped my friend who has dry skin." Ok... but I have psoriasis and use lasers and uv rays to treat it so your over the counter bullshit probably isn't going to work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 17:35:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Constance after a relative. Thank God they changed their mind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 17:36:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love, actually. I just love it. I'm not even sorry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 17:36:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Theatre- because I want to be unemployable!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 17:39:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>On my birthday in 6th grade I was feeling a little gassy. We were taking a test. I bent down to get something out of my bag (maybe a new pen...) and I farted SO LOUD! It was the worst. Sometimes I tell myself it didn't happen, and that's what I said to the other kids in my class who all definitely noticed... but I know it definitely did happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 00:17:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's pretty much what love, actually is...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 16:46:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I moved from north of Boston to western ma and everyone out here says grinder. No- it's a sub!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-28 00:41:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holyoke, first Springfield for grad school</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-28 14:44:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>On the NorthShore it's a sub.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Could I have RLS?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 04:46:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi! 32f here. Ever since I've been little, maybe 2 or 3, my mom reported I would complain of pain in my legs "growing pains". There pains occur most when I'm tired, and when I was younger usually late at night. It was just a pain, and I would take Tylenol and use a heating pad and it would go away. As I got older and stopped growing I still suffered from these pains. Now at 32, not only is it a dull pain in one or both legs, but also a numb or tingling feeling, and a tightness. I never feel like I HAVE to move my legs, but moving them, in the moment seems to help. I'm going to see my doctor soon but wanted to see what people who know they suffer from RLS think about these symptoms compared to your own. Thanks!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 17:44:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to the doctors today. This has been an annoyance most of my life but lately has become unbearable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 02:14:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>The doctor I saw thinks it's shin splints. I had shin splints in high school. This is def not shin splints. I'm going to keep a log of the pain, which leg, when it starts, the intensity, when/if it ends, water intake and level of activity. Then I'm going to go to PT in 3 months and show them everything. I asked him if it would be normal to have shin splints for 30 years and he was like well, maybe. I'm not buying it. He didn't think it was RLS because I'm not restless. But all the other symptoms line up! I don't think I'd even take RLS meds, I just want to know what this is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 01:00:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>If his name was Dudley I would have had the same story!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-13 00:45:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had a guy in his 60's come up to me in Boston common when I was in between classes at Emerson. He asked me if I had a boyfriend. I did, and told him I did. He said "too bad, because if you were single I would take you out tonight and make you fall in love with me"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I need help with a clue!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 02:13:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got my husband an auto car starter for Christmas. I was just going to print out the slip to give him, but then started thinking, is there something else cute he could open and would then have to guess? I need something automatic, and something that means starter. Does anyone have any ideas????</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 13:08:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>It does not happen often, I'm 32 and it's maybe happened 2 or 3 times in my life total. But every time it's annoying. I'm assuming that what happens is they have my number but didn't save it, so that's why they don't know who it is. I just never would randomly text someone if I didn't know who it was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 13:40:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>My doctor said I have shin splints. I was like oh, I e had that before, is it normal that the pain would come and go during the day and that I've had it for like 20 years? He was like umm?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 14:54:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>My SD's were 19 and 22 when my son was born. The 19 year old loved him from the second she found out I was pregnant. The older one hated that I was pregnant and was quite frankly a little brat the entire time. However, she is a great big sister to her little brother now. She doesn't live at home with us so my son is definitely closer with the 19 year old, but I think your 12 year old will be fine! I would just recommend making sure that there's still something fun/special that you guys do with your SS, even if it's just once a month, so he knows he's still loved and important.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 15:29:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's been mad that we rehomed the dog. This was 6 months ago. I could see if it was a dog from when she was little and she was like "oh gosh I miss that dog, what ended up happening to him?" But this was clearly not a memory issue, more of a "I know it really bugs you to think about the dog so let's bring this issue into the spotlight."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 15:33:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! This is great advice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 15:35:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. My husband did and she wants nothing to do with it. She definitely has a lot of anger that she needs to deal with when she's ready to. I did restrict her today, so she is limited in only seeing something if she's tagged in it. That should help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 15:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh I had the baby! Haha he's great. He's 19 months now. This is all great advice. My husband is really great but you definitely nailed him in his relationship with his oldest. I can tell he's torn because he wants to defend me but doesn't want to get into it with her. However, he did say he was going to say something to her which I do appreciate, but it's also hard because she's a master at starting a conflict and then disappearing until it blows over. And especially with the holidays I can see him wanting to put it off until Christmas is over. So we'll see!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 15:42:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I think it's easy to place blame on the bio parent, but I cannot imagine how he feels. I know if she ever did anything blatantly disrespectful he would call her on it immediately. But she's a good manipulator and that's where it's tricky and hard for him. He also would much rather ignore all drama in his life and I tend to leap into the drama. I really try with this stuff with her to pick my battles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 15:53:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>And "don't set yourself on fire to keep others warm" is one of my favorite sayings. You definitely understand this situation. My husband has said that it's unfortunate that she's forcing him to choose between us because he doesn't think she's going to like his decision. I know back when I was first pregnant he felt a lot more sympathy for her, but as time has gone on he gets more and more frustrated with her and her lack of respect. I have a feeling in the next 6 months something is going to snap and he's going to have it out with her. We'll see.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 16:28:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perfect!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 16:30:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that's great advice. I agree. I just needed to vent and hear that I'm not alone. I think the hardest part is she and I used to be really close, but seeing this mean side of her has made me realize we can never have the relationship back. I do think I initially jump on my husband to act, but I need to live my life and not let her get to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 19:32:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed! Well said.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-06 20:05:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That you only use 10% of your brain. You don't. You use pretty much 100%</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-08 17:49:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok that's what I was thinking too. At this point I'm so over her and her nonsense, but I hold professional licenses and I'm not jeopardizing them because she wants to get high. I was fairly certain if she was not on our property or in our cars we would be fine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 20:31:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>You've obviously never been on the corner of Boylston St and Tremont St on a windy snowy day. Trust me. It's cold. https://www.currentresults.com/Weather-Extremes/US/windiest-cities.php</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 01:14:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am so sorry this happened to you. And proud of you for speaking out about it, especially after receiving back lash!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-04 10:53:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>He handles the financials?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 00:53:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got a puppy earlier than I had told my best friend I was planning on getting it. She lost her mind. We're 32 and 36 year old moms. It was weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 18:49:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or just be the best parent you can be. I work full time, but I'm in a school I pick my son up at 3 everyday and have Summers off. Do I wish I was with him all day everyday, of course. Am I grateful that because of my job I can enjoy my time w him and not stress over bills? You bet!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 01:20:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 01:07:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Genius!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-19 00:45:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>So nice!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 01:23:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I went through a super religious/judgey phase in middle school/early high school. Than balanced it out with the always classy slutty/easy phase late high school-20's. Now I'm married and have a 2year old and can't stand thinking of those times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-14 00:19:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chomping on my split ends. It's so gross and yet satisfying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 18:23:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I spill water all the time. My husband can't stand it. I can't even explain it. It seems like it's only water, not other liquids.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 18:27:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait can you explain? I'm just not understanding</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 18:28:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>This might take more than a minute, but now when we do our grocery list we also fill out a meal planning sheet for the week, including when to take things out to defrost them. It makes week nights with a toddler so much more manageable when there's a plan!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 18:31:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was driving through a not great part of the city I lived in and a woman jumped in front of my car. I swerved and did not hit her but she claimed I did. Luckily, because my car hadn't been washed in months, the cops were quickly able to verify that the sheen of dirt coating my car was not disturbed and I did not hit her. Apparently this is how that woman gets money, trying to get ppl to hit her. I was never charged with a crime, but definitely could have been!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 18:31:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ooh ok that makes sense!!! I have to try this thanks!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 00:10:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know right?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 00:12:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was such a pain because she did end up getting $1000 from my insurance company. I was all pumped up to go to court but they were like the money we'd spend on a lawyer etc is far greater than just giving her $1000 and saying that she can never ask for more money no matter what. I get it, but I was still so mad. I would have killed it in court too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 02:15:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, luckily my insurance company was awesome. They were like there's no code for not hitting someone haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 01:22:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have to say, I came here half way done w chapter 4 fully aware that there could possibly be spoilers. I understand and appreciate the sub not wanting to ruin it, but let's use common sense and assume that any discussion might contain spoilers and it was your choice to come here. ( I may be taking some anger I have towards Gilmore Girl fans who didn't want the discussion of the new episodes to include spoilers color my comment here. )</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 23:06:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the luckiest person</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-01 01:37:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mom always told me to say sorry no matter what (even if you did nothing wrong.) now she's always impressed when I tell her about times when ppl(wrongfully) demanded apologies and I don't give them. I'm a school psychologist and deal with a lot of angry parents.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 02:34:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>No that's what I think too! I just wanted to check because 6 years later... it's crazy!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 02:34:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed!!! Thank you for the validation!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 13:13:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg tell me about it. Daddy can sleep all day but if I even get cozy under a blanket my son loses his mind. Tears, tantrum... the works! Apparently mama doesn't need sleep. Ever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 01:39:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dcf? File on them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 01:18:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also wash it with soap and water if it's scratched, but don't rinse off the soap!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 01:21:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>LPT: All makeup should be shimmery, glittery or frosted. Preferably all three.  #9757; #65039; This sooo much !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 01:32:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're not overreacting. Get out now. I wasted a year on someone who made comments just like this in the beginning and he is a huge racist. I am still so ashamed 7 years later.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 01:32:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yessss!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 18:47:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dad has one blue eye, and one eye that is 2/3 blue and 1/3 brown!  #128065;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 18:48:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oooh I hate my grandparents too!!! My dad's dad did something similar, but less intense, to him in West Virginia in the late 60's!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 18:49:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also use it only your nipples if they're sore from breastfeeding!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 01:00:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know where you're located but some therapists do financial counseling and can help you get things straightened out. Idk if you went to a college/college in the states... but if you did you always can access the career center and they have resources too!!! You are doing awesome!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 00:52:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>My hair sometimes will still smell like my perfume several days after application, after I've showered. I believe you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-06 19:04:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would have more faith in myself and do a lot less "stuff with boys" to make myself feel like I had value. And I wouldn't have dated Dan. Or Eric.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-07 01:24:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was w someone for 4 years, 19-23. We did get engaged but he was wrong for me. I did feel the same way as you at first, not wanting to waste that time. I would be divorced now though, and worse off. I met my husband when I was 27. We'll be married 4 years in November and have a 2 year old. Don't settle!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 18:16:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>My husband works in a hospital. Parents came to ED with their daughter, Felony.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-12 23:14:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>"They prefer to work rather than parent, and will focus on vocational success. " This point right here, no. At least for me, I am a semester away from being done with a doctorate in education. I love my career and my education, however I LIVE for being a mom and would never choose my career over my child.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-26 01:19:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>How is it "roughly 140"? I give the IQ test every day. That's not how it works.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-26 01:26:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a school psychologist. That is correct- some type of disability impacting their performance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 16:53:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>NAL but... as a therapist I have experience working w DCF (mass). In my experience they do NOT want/nor have the resources to take children, especially newborns, and place them away from parents. Assuming pot is the only substance you would test positive for they may open a case... but unless Oregon has an abundance of foster families I really wouldn't worry. I've worked w parents w babies born addicted to meth/crack etc and the parents have taken the babies home w Dcf. Please don't stress.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 01:34:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! Sorry it's one of those things where once you know it you forget most people don't. That's great that there's no other drugs! Like others have said, and I said too, these state agencies really don't like to/have the resources to split up families. Think of it from their perspective, if you DID test positive for marijuana: the worker would have to tell their supervisor who would have to explain to their manager why they were taking a new born baby and paying money they don't have to a foster family because a mom found out she was pregnant and stopped smoking marijuana. It doesn't make sense. You are going to be a great mom. I really wouldn't worry about it!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 01:34:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! Good point haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 03:17:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could call hospital and ask to speak to the human rights person. IANAL- I'm a psychologist, so I don't know the time frame for these things.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 19:14:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was a great episode!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 01:10:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am the owner of the most adorable rag doll cat. I got him because when he was a baby (less than 6 weeks!) he was wandering the streets in my town. We looked for the owner but no one claimed him. When I brought him to the vet they scanned him for a microchip. If I were you, I would imagine the first time you bring him to the vet they'll scan him, and you can ask if you want. No microchip, no owner. My cat is now microchipped. We did it when we got him fixed and it was like $20 additional. I think any decent owner would do that. So if he has no microchip and no other way to identity the owner you're good! (IANAL) (and I live in mass)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 17:27:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have. I got my MEd in clinical mental health counseling and am a LMHC. I am one dissertation away from completing my EdD. It worked out great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 01:02:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll be done with my doctorate in May! I almost dropped out of high school 14 years ago...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 12:30:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Step 1. Ask someone out that I'm really into and taking a big risk asking. Step 2. Sit at home and think of only the person I asked out and did I make a mistake?? Step 3. Diarrhea</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 14:06:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have to say- I am a school psych and administer IQ tests daily. You can probably study for about 1/3 of it- but of the different activities you're doing, only 2 are verbal and the rest are looking at memory, fluid reasoning and visual spatial. Some portions you just can't study for.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 14:07:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh and you can only take it once every 18 months for it to be considered valid (there's obviously a retest advantage, so if you take it Monday and tank it, then take it Wednesday it's not surprising you'll do better)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 02:32:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mostly administer the first 10 sections of the WISC V, and there is no section like that on there. There are 5 more sections, that are optional that I typically don't administer, and it may be in one of those. However, to get you FSIQ (full scale IQ) you only use the scores from the first 10. There are other "iq" tests, but the WISC V is thought to be the gold standard. The WAIS IV is the adult version and I administer that as well, to the kids older than 16, and there is no section like that on the mandatory sections either. I'll check on Monday though and let you know!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 14:20:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do testing for students with suspected learning disabilities. I administer 2 assessments. One is achievement- looking at their abilities in reading, writing and math. The second is intelligence- the IQ test. The reason we give both is to compare and make sure the student is functioning within their abilities. If you get a kid who's IQ is in the average or above average range, but their achievement scores are really low, you would probably say, this may have more to do with the fact that this student was home schooled grades 1-3 and missed a lot of the foundations that would help them now. So instead of putting them on an ed plan, you could do some remedial work and get them caught up. The IQ scores aren't for everyone to see and I find it really does help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 19:34:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's a speech/language test.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 03:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not the one I'm thinking of, but there could be one that is, for sure!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What was a gift you got that really showed you how much someone appreciated you?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 17:33:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 14:28:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I schedule things into my planner, even leisure activities. That way when I pull out my planner ppl can't say "oh you're free at 2p on Tuesday, cause it says gym, or just meeting or appointment. Now that I'm a mom with a toddler this has been more of a struggle, but things are starting to settle down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 19:29:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I was pumping gas with my son in the car in his car seat. He was around 1 year old. This woman, in her 20's, tried calling me over to "help her". I'm looking at her just thinking, something isn't right. She said "I need help pumping?" I just said "I can't help my son's in the car... try taking off the gas cap." I immediately got in my car and drove away. I don't know what her deal was, Im thinking maybe a car jacking team...but me and my baby definitely always SSDGM.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 03:20:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>What?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 02:27:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>My story is different because I became one (sort of) by accident. My original goal was to be a therapist. I went to grad school, got my masters and my counseling license. 2 years later, still feeling unfulfilled, I went back to school for a doctorate in education in educational psychology with a clinical track. But I discovered I loved the assessment aspect and switched to school psych. Now I'm in my second year at a great district and finishing my dissertation. The important qualities are definitely being organized and being able to deal with angry parents. I've never had a problem with a student, but the parents and sometimes teachers are a pain!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 02:35:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work in a relatively small district with about 100 students a grade. I'm the school psych for grades 6-12 and I also am the sped coordinator, which means I track and schedule all annuals and 3 years, and request the testing. Because we are such a small district they can't afford ETL's. Last year was my first year. I rarely took work home, and if I did it was because I overextended myself. Now that I'm in my second year and have a better grasp of things I don't anticipate that happening. I had some men in my program but it was primarily women.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 03:19:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.radiolab.org/story/invisible-girl/ Idk if anyone posted this already, but this girl went through the same thing! Maybe you could get some ideas from this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 03:42:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>IANAL and I don't work for Dcf, but I have worked closely with them. They ALWAYS want the child to be with the parent if it's a safe, possible option. Show up, present your case, admit any mistakes, say what your plan is for the future and be honest. If you want your daughter and you have a safe home and don't use/abuse substances, there's no reason you would lose her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>School Psychs of reddit, how do you get parents to attend meetings????</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 17:11:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi all, This is my second years as a school psych in a relatively small district. I am one of 2 school psychs. Because the district is so small (around 100 kids a grade), the other school psych and I are also the coordinators of the sped meetings (3 years, annuals, rejected ieps and transfer ieps, we don't attend them all, but we schedule them). I work with grades 6-12, and the parents who were fighting for their kids IEPs in elementary school seem to stop caring once they get to high school and they no call/no show ALL THE TIME. Because the coordinator position is not my main job, I do not call parents to set up the meetings. I schedule the meetings based on due dates and the sped office sends home the meeting notice with at least 2 weeks notice. The parent can they call (or email) to reschedule if they need to( all this information is provided with the meeting notice). But they never call or email, they just don't show up. Even when they get reminder emails from the SPED teacher 2 weeks, 1 week and 1 day before the meeting they don't reply and they don't show up. Has anyone found a system that works on getting parents to come in, or at least contact the school to reschedule????</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 20:01:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think part of the struggle is not having the ETL's.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 20:04:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand your point. However, I would be unable to do my main job- school psychologist, if I had to call every single parent to set up meetings. Since we don't have ETL's in my district, the school psychs and sped teachers share the roll. So I set the meetings up and then the sped teachers follow up with a call or email. If the parent is unable to make the scheduled meeting then I 100% have no problem rescheduling it. But most of the time the parents no show and then when I do call to find a time to reschedule they don't answer or call back, and because of sped law and timelines I need to reschedule it so the whole process repeats.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 20:19:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've never worked with a mobster or been a psychiatrist, but I did feel like some of the therapy sessions in The Sopranos were pretty realistic, especially when she would get so frustrated with him!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 22:40:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a good idea to involve the student more! I know some sped teachers do have them run their meetings, but not all. That's definitely a good idea! Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 22:49:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just hate that they can't even bother to call or email if they can't make it and need to reschedule. Especially because of the message it sends to the kids.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 22:54:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone else asked this question and this is what i said: https://www.reddit.com/r/schoolpsych/comments/6y0u17/comment/dnltma8?st=J86D8XOX amp;sh=0caebc80</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 22:57:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>This all seems incredibly normal to me. What makes you feel that it's inappropriate and/or unprofessional.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 00:57:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like we have a good amount of overly involved parents with advocates who micromanage their ieps and then we do have a decent amount of good, dependable responsible parents. But we also have a pretty decent amount of parents who just don't show up. On the third no call no show our sped director has the sped teachers hold the meeting anyway and update the iep, but the parent still has to sign off on it when it comes in the mail and return it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 01:37:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what I do too! Documentation is key.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 01:38:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also I don't think it's a requirement, but I think it's best practice to try to keep the iep current.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 16:19:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only problem would be if you #8217;re on an IEP. After 10 suspensions in an academic year you would be entitled to a manifestation hearing to see if the suspensions were a result of your disability. IMO it sounds like you were purposefully instigating your teachers, and there #8217;s no disability for that. NAL- school psych</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 02:54:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agree. Once a month, once every 3 months even.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 20:18:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed! Especially someone like Tony.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 14:04:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed! This was going to be my suggestion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 03:33:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would have loved that. I work in a high school now and they have a financial lit class and it sounds amazing. I want to audit it for personal reasons lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 04:43:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I only bring work home if I am super slammed and need to write a report that I couldn #8217;t get done in school. I make my own schedule in terms of scheduling my meetings etc. I #8217;ve probably brought work home 2-4 times a year, and honestly it #8217;s work I could have gotten done at school but didn #8217;t.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 05:35:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had a situation where I discovered I was working with a clients much younger half sibling and had to terminate the newer relationship but obviously to keep confidentiality had to be vague. This sounds similar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 04:41:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ignition remix!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 04:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 20:11:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>My family give each other so many Christmas presents it takes us almost all day to open them!  #128580;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 02:26:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good work mama!!! I felt just like you- my husband was killing it and I was drowning. It definitely got better after 4 weeks- and SOOOO much better at 12 weeks. He #8217;s 2.5 years now and it #8217;s sooo much more fun. You can do this girl!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 02:28:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Etsy has the cutest bracelet that I got for my mentor: https://www.etsy.com/listing/527211459/psychology-psychology-gifts-schoolhttps://www.etsy.com/listing/527211459/psychology-psychology-gifts-school She loved it!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 02:36:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think if it #8217;s not distracting or noticeable than go for it. I #8217;m a DD at least and since having my son and breastfeeding my nipples stick out even with A decent bra on and no one has ever said anything, I just feel embarrassed when I notice them and have been getting wicked padded bras to help with this. Lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 20:45:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to be an in home therapist. There are programs, free- covered by insurance- that will help you advocate for what you need, and especially around Christmas they usually have a lot of donations/support. I would either google in home therapy/support single moms or call your insurance and ask what services they cover for infants/single moms!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 03:32:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg when my son was a new born I was convinced our keueig broke because it leaked coffee all over the counter. Turns out- if you don #8217;t put the cup there that #8217;s what happens when you brew coffee in a keurig. You got this mama!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 03:33:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did this with my keurig!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 13:42:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>One time I got up to change him and I sure did take his dirty diaper off but forgot to put the new one on. Luckily my husband discovered this before he actually needed a diaper! I also nursed my son, and I would sort of doze off during the nighttime feedings. I can #8217;t tell you how many times I woke up thinking I #8217;d dropped him on the floor, but really he was safely in his bed(where I #8217;d put him) and I #8217;d gone back to sleep. Sleep deprivation is the worst.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 16:40:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Education team lead. In bigger districts they #8217;re the people who run the iep meetings, sent out the requests for testing and basically coordinate the ieps. My district is too small to warrant paying someone to do this full time, so the school psychs get paid a stipend to set up the meetings and send out the consents for testing etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Because Swifties are never extra....</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 01:19:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I realized I never got my pre order email from Apple about reputation. And I need as many boosts as I can get yo! So I emailed Apple support and received an email back from Gerald, and in the email he said he too was a fan. Well once I knew that I knew what I had to do. Below is my letter. (Spoiler alert, I got the code!!!) Hi Gerald! Ok.... Are You Ready For It? So what happened, and the End Game of all this is that I Did Something Bad and now that I #8217;ve looked into it, I discovered that all my Apple email went to my aol account, because that was my iCloud email. I want to say Don #8217;t Blame Me, but really who else is there to blame? Since I don #8217;t use that account I just have all mail go to spam, and then that gets deleted after some amount of time, it #8217;s a Delicate operation. When I bought the album I wasn #8217;t super aware of the boost code, now that I know, Look What You Made Me Do, going through my aol spam searching for the boost code lol. So It Goes...as  #8234;12/5 #8236; gets closer I clearly am aware, and obvi want to get further up the line(and work on getting some Gorgeous merch), and this is when I started investigating what had happened to the email. If only I had a Getaway Car and I could try to snag all the boost codes! You are the King Of My Heart for responding to my email. I know this may be a situation where you #8217;re Dancing With Your Hands tied- I get it. I haven #8217;t bought a Dress for the show yet, It #8217;s 100% my fault, so if there is no way to resend it i understand-This Is Why We Can #8217;t Have Nice Things. If there is a way to resend it #160;I will be sure to tell everyone that you made my 2017, when we recap the year on New Years Day. All the best Gerald!! Xoxo subject7262 Edit: weird spelling/word choice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 01:38:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I went to this link: https://getsupport.apple.com/?caller=cups amp;PRKEYS= And then filled out the required fields and they got back to me pretty quickly!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 01:39:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!!! I was like well, if he #8217;s a fan then I should definitely take advantage of this situation! Because it definitely was my fault that I lost the code to begin with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 03:24:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the best thing ever!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 03:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 03:31:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol thanks. I started writing him back just a regular email and then I was like wait- and The spirit of Taylor entered me and I knew what to do  #128514; #128514; I mean let #8217;s be serious, I was probably getting the code regardless, but this was more fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 03:46:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 03:47:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love you!!! Lol. Thanks!!!  #10084; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 07:40:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg. I missed it. I can #8217;t believe it!!!! Ahh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 15:19:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg love that!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 03:34:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>When they just sort of take over  #8220;helping #8221;, especially when it #8217;s something where their  #8220;help #8221; makes you look incompetent. I have a friend who does this, she #8217;ll come to parties at my house and start acting like the host. Before I had my son it really made me mad, but now I just roll my eyes and go with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 03:35:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes!!!! Good work!!! I HATED breastfeeding and pumping so much, pumped until he was 1 and BF until 26 months. I LOVED when my son would find other ways to self sooth. I can imagine exactly how you felt!!! It gets sooo much better the older they get. You got this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 16:54:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg thank you!! And a few months of pumping is still awesome! I used the rubber band trick, because I wasn #8217;t spending $100 on a pumping bra. https://kellymom.com/bf/pumpingmoms/pumping/hands-free-pumping/ This made it easier to pump and get work done at work. Honestly, if my mom guilt for working full time wasn #8217;t so strong (and if we could have afforded formula) I would have stopped pumping/nursing way sooner. As he got older and nurses for shorter periods and less frequently it got better, but I couldn #8217;t believe it when he was 2 and still not interested in weaning. Now I have summers off and it was a little easier to stop over the summer. You can message me anytime if you want motivation when you try pumping again, and congrats on #2!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 21:56:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly! Omg I remember my second night home being exhausted googling  #8220;I hate breastfeeding #8221;, and honestly reading how other ppl hated it made me feel better.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 03:00:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m sorry your experience was so terrible! I was a Girl Scout in the 90 #8217;s, my mom was my leader and I LOVED it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 03:08:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just came here to say I went to Springfield College and live in Holyoke!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nap time hell</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 19:55:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>My son is 2.5. He has always napped great at daycare, but fights it so hard at home. Today I had a half day at work so I picked him up right after lunch. We get home and he #8217;s rubbing his eyes, so tired. (And he #8217;s a kiddo who is a bear when he doesn #8217;t nap) I bring him up to nap time and get him all settled. 32 minutes later, 3 times in to  #8220;retuck  #8220; him and he #8217;s up there  #8220;crying #8221; saying  #8220;mama I done #8221;. I usually cave in way sooner, but today I #8217;m trying to wait him out. I #8217;m going up in 6 minutes though if he #8217;s still crying. This is one of the parts of being a mom I hate!!! Just nap little guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 20:04:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds pretty much like what we do, but I don #8217;t stick with the limit of no screen time always, that #8217;s probably where this all falls apart. Now that he #8217;s sleeping better at night I #8217;m less frustrated with him during the day so that does help. It just stinks that the evenings are so grumpy on the days he doesn #8217;t have daycare. Over the summer he was napping for me after running around all day, but that hasn #8217;t transitioned into the fall. Do you think your son understands the  #8220;no screen time #8221; time? I feel like right now mine won #8217;t understand but maybe at 3 he would. Thank you!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 21:00:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s what I want too!!!! Ok well that #8217;s good to know!!! Thank you!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 21:11:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll go in at the beginning closer to 5 minutes, then I #8217;ll wait 15-20. He #8217;s super stubborn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 16:00:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats!!! I got my dream job a year after having my son and it has made me a much more relaxed and fun mama!!!!!! You are going to do awesome!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 04:07:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Listen- he agreed. That #8217;s it. You #8217;re in this together. And if you think that he isn #8217;t leave now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 04:08:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is everything. You said what you wanted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 20:08:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>This girl posted on Facebook that she was having homicidal ideation against co workers, after getting in trouble for recording a patient and texting it out to a bunch of other employees. She got fired.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 23:05:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats!!!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 04:03:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my relatives on my dAds side was John Adams</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 00:15:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has he had social/emotional or executive functioning assessments done by the school district? I would put that request in writing and give to sped office. They #8217;ll have valid, Normed surveys for him, you and his teachers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 00:17:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also depends what grid it #8217;s in. A grid is consult between the sped teacher and the other teachers. B grid is services in the classroom and depending on what level of support is needed it can be sped teacher, sped staff or gen ed teacher. C grid is direct service delivery and should be from either the sped teacher or another licensed specialist- adjustment counselor, SLP, specialized reading etc. this is how it is in Mass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 00:39:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>The phone we had In our kitchen was olive green and rented from the phone company. I can #8217;t even remember their name. It was like a globe?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 00:41:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wine Anything cozy Sleep More wine Take me out Wine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 00:47:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>We LOVE our sons daycare. He #8217;s been going since he was was 12 weeks old, he #8217;s 2 1/2 now. He LOVES his day care provider, loves the other kiddos- I have a school job now and have summers off so he only went once or twice a week this summer so I could get stuff done and he was bummed. By Sunday night he would be asking when he was going back. I was really nervous about it first and cried dropping him off. But he has had such a wonderful experience.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 02:14:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had a similar but very different situation with my husbands daughter. (And please, I understand the difference between a biological child and a sibling, but i felt very similar to OP.) my SD mom kicked her out her senior year of high school and she moved in with us full time. Fine, makes sense, she was 18, planning to go to community college and the would move out. 3 years later and she had dropped out of school, did nothing to contribute to the household, wasn #8217;t working full time, left a mess everywhere and on top of that we have a 2 year old. This summer was terrible. I was constantly stressed, walking on pins and needles, fighting with my husband constantly. He kept saying he #8217;d talk to her but wasn #8217;t. Finally I made an ultimatum for myself: if he didn #8217;t talk to her by October 1st about new rules and expectations for living here, I would start looking for alternative housing for me and our son. I never told him this and he talked to her by the end of August and Labor Day weekend she moved out in a fit of rage (I guess my husband telling her she needed to clean up her own messes and that he and I would try to help her pay off her defaulted school loans was unacceptable  #128580;) my life is sooooo much better now, and my husband was fed up with being a maid for a 21 year old too. Reading your story brought back all those feelings of stress and anxiety. I will never live like that again. Good luck !!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 02:31:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s definitely hard!!! I don #8217;t think OP is avoiding  #8220;no #8221; just for fun- it really is hard when you #8217;ve been basically trained to always say yes. I say  #8220;sorry #8221; at the drop of a hat because that #8217;s basically what I was trained to do by my mom. Over the past 5 years (I #8217;m 33) I #8217;ve really been trying hard to say no and to not say  #8220;sorry #8221; and man is it hard!!!! Obviously if OP was comfortable  #8220;just saying no #8221; she would have. Some comments make it seem like it #8217;s the simplest act in the world and in theory- yes it sure is. But in practice it is very difficult.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 03:16:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work in a school and have summers off and my son goes to daycare which is perfect for us. My mom was a SAHM to me and my brothers. Once we were all in school she did little things like substitute teaching. When I was probably in middle school, so my youngest brother was in 4th grade, she started working 10 hours a week at our church as the director of Christian education. I think overall it was great having her home. Of course as a mischievous teen I wanted her gone so I could do whatever I wanted, but honestly it was nice that she was always around. Of course I know a lot of families can #8217;t swing that, but growing up it was nice. So if you can afford it and don #8217;t have career goals than you #8217;re passionate about I would keep on doing the SAHM route.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 02:26:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 17:03:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>My SD (21) moved out, of her own accord, over Labor Day. Brought zero belongings w her and lived with her sister until she moved into an apartment the middle of November. During that time her room was completely full of her stuff, and she came occasionally to pack what she needed. Finally the end of October we packed up the room and turned it into a playroom for our son (2). We put her boxes on the 3 season porch so she could get them to her car easier than if they were in the basement. Last night she came by to pick up a package she had delivered and yelled at her dad when he asked her to either take the boxes or put them in the basement because  #8220;we packed up her stuff so fast #8221; and she was  #8220;homeless #8221; and it #8217;s our fault. Im just so done and needed to rant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 23:49:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s awesome!!!! Don #8217;t you love it when you #8217;re like yup- I definitely picked the right person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 21:54:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work at a high school that has a financial literacy class offered. It sounds so great, they basically have a budget (fake), bills, learn about paying taxes- I wish it was a requirement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 21:55:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t post anything about my relationship with my husband for this very reason! He #8217;s a great guy and we have a great and healthy relationship, but I know if I posted anything (sleeps through the baby crying etc) I #8217;d get  #8220;leave him #8221; responses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 22:01:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly!!! It #8217;s just like anything, when you don #8217;t know about it it #8217;s super scared.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 22:30:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a therapist, that is an extreme form of treatment, typically used for bipolar patients, or schizophrenia. I would never recommend that on someone with depression based on a conversation with a parent, especially when they #8217;re not a minor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 00:32:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. And even if you write it, reread it, make some changes and think  #8220;a reasonable person would get what I #8217;m saying.... #8221; you still get the  #8220;you need to leave him #8221; response. I feel like if there is abuse- yes, no question. But if he sometimes takes you for granted and you sometimes don #8217;t communicate well, the first option should not be  #8220;divorce! #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 15:08:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have to disagree with the person saying after 3 years if it #8217;s a good relationship it shouldn #8217;t fail. I do think the young age plays a huge role. I was w an ex from 18-22. We got engaged even. I was 6 years younger than him which definitely played a huge role too. What I wanted when I was 19 changed sooo much 4 years later. I do think the age gap played a role too, being 6 years older he was in a different stage of his life. Ultimately he just wasn #8217;t the right person for me. Relationships fail after much longer together than 3 years. To play devils advocate though, my aunt and uncle have been married for 50 years, they got married when they were 19 and 20. I wonder if being closer in age helps?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 18:24:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>U/Cooper720 I was agreeing w you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 04:03:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>My LO is 2.5 years old but when he was a baby he would growl at people  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 14:41:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>IANAL, but my elderly next door neighbor had a similar incident happen, and due to the severity of her injuries she is going to need plastic surgery on her hand. Initially the bad dog's owners offered to pay, but now they are not. Additionally, I would recommend taking a legal route in order to make sure that law enforcement/the community knows about this dangers ABD, and hopefully something can be done to insure that the dog is properly secured.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 20:40:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>People who say  #8220;well that #8217;s just how I roll #8221; after doing something shitty, as an excuse for their bad behavior. Additionally, people who say  #8220;well, that #8217;s just how X is, there #8217;s no reasoning with him. #8221; And then let them get away with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 14:18:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can #8217;t remember which episode, but he said it was Selena. I know Georgia did it at one point so maybe it was that episode</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-26 15:53:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>The boy who was raised as a dog by Bruce perry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 22:03:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could dad call the school and find out how his behavior is there? Sometimes kiddos are totally well behaved at school and fall apart at home, but from the extremes that you are reporting I would be surprised if they #8217;d never seen ANY type of aggression when he doesn #8217;t get his way. Unfortunately schools can recommend outside of school treatment (or they could be held responsible for it financially), but they could recommend in school counseling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 22:24:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would have to say, if I was a college professor and someone contacted me to say one of my students was doing heroin, I would be pretty confused and would most likely just go to the student and ask them what was going on, especially because, since you don #8217;t do heroin, I doubt you would even be on the radar in terms of concerns. And if the person calling was my students boyfriends mom I would pretty much know that there was some type of BS going on. I work in a public high school and we are not allowed to confirm or deny if students attend, I #8217;m guessing college would have similar rules.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 04:02:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get these intense pains in my lower legs(knee to ankle), it #8217;s happened randomly since I was little. My mom said it #8217;s growing pains but I #8217;m 33... so no. My little brother gets them too. Doctor said shin splints... it #8217;s not. Mostly happens at night, and more when I #8217;m cold and/or tired. I #8217;ve question RLS but I don #8217;t think it is. I have hashimotos but no other medical issues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 04:06:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m a school psych. I would recommend requesting an evaluation through the school. They will send a Consent to both parents. Make sure you request attentional assessment and social emotional. Edit: weird formatting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 04:16:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 04:27:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also, based on my work with CPS, they often under estimate timelines so as not to turn off potential foster parents. If you said you could keep her permanently I #8217;m sure they #8217;d be thrilled.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 13:51:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 13:57:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe so... I think your best bet might be contacting the student services/sped office for your district (well, probably have your husband do it) and explain the situation and provide them with the custody agreement. In most cases the district wants the kiddo tested as much as the parent does- they have their own lawyer they can consult with too. I know it #8217;s really frustrating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 04:17:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>If an event starts at a certain time, don #8217;t show up 50 minutes early!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 14:50:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mountain lions!!! When I was maybe 5 we went to the Boston science museum and I saw a stuffed mountain lion and I was PETRIFIED. There are no mountain lions near where I live but it didn #8217;t matter. Finally after months of not sleeping my dad made a sigh  #8220;mountain lions, please don #8217;t eat u/subject7262 #8221; and it worked!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 15:05:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friend #8217;s husband.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 15:07:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is spot on. I #8217;m very ambitious but I also love being a parent. However, I also only have 1 child. I think that if I had more it would be difficult to make progress in my career and be a good parent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Best smart lightbulbs that don #8217;t need a hub?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 21:49:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have an echo dot and an echo- I want to get some smart lightbulbs. Im wondering if anyone can recommend smart lightbulbs that don #8217;t require a smart hub or gateway? Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 14:01:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wasn #8217;t it the one called The Finch, episode 89</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 14:24:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was very good friends with someone exactly like this. She was in my wedding party and everything. I knew she was judge mental and outspoken, but I tend to be easy going and less aggressive and she never was judgmental of me (at least to my face  #128580;) so I would just sort of chuckle when she was being crazy. However; 8 years into our friendship she turned her crazy on me and I was done. I tried to resolve it but she could not hear/accept that just because a thought crosses her brain it may not be her place to say it. (Basically she got mad at me because we got a puppy in the winter but I had said we were going to get one in the summer. We=me and my husband, she lives 100 miles away, this would have zero effect on her) we #8217;re both moms in our 30 #8217;s. I couldn #8217;t handle it. I wish I #8217;d paid attention to her red flags sooner. OP- I don #8217;t see a promising future here, I #8217;m sorry!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 14:26:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>My husband is 45- when he #8217;s 55 our son will be 12. His mom had him at 41, she #8217;s 86 right now so.... she definitely saw her son through his 30 #8217;s and I #8217;m guessing will still see him into his 50 #8217;s. Just to the point that it #8217;s selfish to have a child later in life. Edit- I was commenting on a deleted comment where the user said (paraphrasing) that it was selfish for people to have a child later in life, that due to obesity in the United States an older parent wouldn #8217;t make it to see their child live to be in their 30 #8217;s. My point was that that is not necessarily the case. I DO not think it #8217;s selfish to parent a child in your 40 #8217;s- my husband was 43 when we had our son.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 14:53:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m just making the point that your experience may be true but it isn #8217;t the only possibility.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 18:13:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>U/pm_me_some_dessert I #8217;m so sorry for your loss. I agree- you can never predict the future!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 19:31:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 01:00:18</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;At 15, why aren't you just leaving them alone at home and NOT deal with it?  gt;We have been letting the boys stay at home alone since they were 8  amp; 10. Two years later and they can now stay home the entire day by themselves, make all meals by themselves, laundry, etc.  gt;Is there a reason you can't leave a teen alone at home? Speaking for myself- my SD lived with us until she was 21 and I hated when she was home alone. Her strategy was to basically make a huge mess, eat all the food and then disappear for 2-3 weeks. She #8217;d crash at her sister #8217;s place. By the time she came back there might be a cursory conversation but at 21, what can you really do? She had a job, her own car... luckily she moved out and things have been much better in our relationship with her and she seems happier. Before becoming a step mom I may have thought OP was being unreasonable, but I definitely understand where she #8217;s coming from. If it was my SK #8217;s I would tell my husband they need to go back to mom #8217;s if he can #8217;t be home.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 01:30:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>You had a hard choice to make. I totally get it. I think it #8217;s important to know yourself enough to know that you wouldn #8217;t be able to enjoy the time because you #8217;d be worrying about your baby. I was the same way. And even when my husband encouraged me to do things I still would choose to stay with our son because I knew he #8217;s all I #8217;d be thinking about anyway. He #8217;s 2.5 now and things get soooo much better. He nursed until August, so 27 months. By the last 8 months or so he was just nursing at bedtime for like 5 minutes, but it took him FOREVER to give that up. My husband and I are going to Cabo for a week in a few months and my parents are going to watch our son. I feel a lot of guilt about leaving him, but I also know my husband and I will really enjoy this time together, and that my son will have a blast with his grandparents (he tells me his grandpa is his best friend) but I never would have agreed to this trip if I thought I was going to be miserable missing my son, because that #8217;s a wasted trip. You #8217;ll know when you #8217;re ready.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 02:18:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work for a school district in mass and all I do is test, write reports and then report the reports in the meetings. We don #8217;t have anything to do with writing the IEPs or coming up with plans or providing services. Is this just your district or is it all of your state?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 03:38:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi, sorry for misunderstanding! In my district it works a couple different ways. I #8217;m in the high school, grades 7-12, so there #8217;s less initials to begin with. I would say the majority of my cases are re-Evals. Then I get initials either through parent request, which we have to do even if there #8217;s pretty much no reason to asses, or they referred through the SAT (student assistance team), where teachers fill out forms and then the counselors, me, the principals, the SRO, the nurse... we all meet and discuss students. I have some input in that, looking to make sure they hadn #8217;t been tested or on a plan before, checking their grades (we have an admin who wants every  #8220;bad kid #8221; on a plan even if they are getting straight A #8217;s and really aren #8217;t a discipline issue overall). We also just found out that we have too many kids on plans based on percentages across the state so I #8217;m hoping that will stop all the pointless referrals.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 04:23:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>My husband is 45, I #8217;m 33. We met when I was 27 and he was 39. He has 2 daughters. They #8217;re now 24 and 21. When we met he said he hadn #8217;t wanted more kids, but if I did then he would have more. Our son is 2.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 01:15:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed!!!!!!! It was a dance. So perfect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 17:02:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can knit. I cannot pearl. I just can #8217;t.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 17:21:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, my husband was never a hard NO with me. When we started dating I honestly thought we were just going to be casual, but he said I love you 2 weeks in and we just were so perfect for each other it all worked out. (That's not to say that his 2 daughters haven't been little bitches along the way, but that's another story, and I do get where they're coming from to an extent but OMG you're 24 and 21....). I knew from the beginning I wanted to have at leats one kid and while he wasn't super sure if he wanted more he said that he would be open to talking about it. When we got engaged we had a more serious discussion about our future, as you do, and he said he would definitely be open to having 1 or 2 kids.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 03:52:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was Amazing. I read it to my husband and we were nothing DYING laughing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 04:38:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>IANAL but I am a school psychologist. This is what I would recommend: - email/contact I #8217;m writing your district #8217;s SPED director. -request that you would like to discuss placement; state he is not safe in his current placement and he is unable to access the curriculum. -request his 3 year evaluation be conducted now (put this in writing) -any disciplinary action save documentation from -do not pick him up from school unless he #8217;s sick or suspended (after 10 days suspended they need to hold a manifestation hearing to discuss placement- many schools try to avoid this but just asking the parent to pick up the student.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:38:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait is that avocado on your pizza??? Do we get that I. America cause I #8217;ve been DIYing that my whole life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 00:37:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is such a good and smart idea! When I first started dating my husband his 2 teen daughters did not want me to have anything to do with disciplining them. Fair enough, I had no interest in disciplining them. However, when my now husband and I moved in together the status quo was if I had a problem with a mess they made or chores they wouldn #8217;t do I had to talk to my husband and he would talk to them. 6 years later, not being able (just mostly because of the resistance from my SD) to even say hey, pick up after yourself 21 year old, got old. I wish the second (first month) of living together, DH and I had sat down with them and said,  #8220;while subject7262 has no intention or desire to be your mom, now that we are all living in the same space if there is an issue and she is the adult home she will address it with you. #8221; I also wish I had just said to them,  #8220;I don #8217;t want to be your mom #8221; their mom is alive and very present in their lives. I was 27 when I met their dad. I had no interest in being a mom to a 17 and 15 year old. I know it #8217;s a little different with 10, 8 and 3... but I think just being clear about boundaries and rules from the beginning, and talking about it when a rule changes. Congrats on your upcoming wedding!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 03:47:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is what mine did too. I turned 18 at the end of my junior year and I think I left early once to vote. And then came back  #128580;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 16:07:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I totally understand wanting to spoil them and wanting to be liked! I think it would be an awesome idea to do little monthly "date nights" with each of them, where maybe you do an activity and a bite to eat or something. And then if during the month you see something you want to get them or see something you want to do with them, you can save it for the date night. That way it's more of an occasion, so they aren't just expecting you to get them things all the time. And that will give their mom to have some 1 on 2 time with the other 2. When I was growing up we would have family meetings on Sundays and then go on a mystery ride or do a fun activity after it. I hated the family meetings but loved the surprise after it haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:35:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>How did she get meds if she isn #8217;t in therapy? If she #8217;s not in therapy then she doesn #8217;t have a diagnosis. If her PCP diagnosed her, it most likely won #8217;t be accurate. I am a therapist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:41:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope she does the CBT, it #8217;s a really good treatment modality!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 03:59:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine undergrad is a BFA in theatre management. I #8217;m finishing my school psych doctorate and have a masters in clinical mental health counseling</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 20:36:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a toddler and a dog. They never leave their poop on the counter. Get out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 16:33:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Up until the cheating part my situation was fairly similar to yours. I had someone I  #8220;loved #8221;- very unhealthy, dramatic passionate relationship. I ended up moving across my state for a school program to end things with him. My now husband is amazing- and while our passion may not be at the intoxicating level it was with my ex bf, we have an amazing relationship, he treats me respectfully and I trust him. If I #8217;d stayed with my ex I would most likely be divorced right now. But now that you #8217;ve cheated I think you need to come clean with your gf, cut contact with your ex and find a new woman(when you #8217;re definitely over your ex.) (I #8217;m assuming your gf will break up with you- sorry but it #8217;s definitely what I would do.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 16:42:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could definitely try to have an honest talk with your girlfriend and let her know EVERYTHING. I can imagine it being too hard for her to trust you, but you also don #8217;t want to make the decision for her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 00:16:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are an amazing dad. You #8217;re doing everything you can for her and that #8217;s all thAt matters. Be there. Listen. Be kind. I am a therapist and wish all my clients had dad #8217;s like you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 01:40:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love this!! And love the person who took it. This would look great in a frame!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 04:37:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>There #8217;s a sears house in my parents neighborhood! I #8217;ll see if my mom will send me a pic in the morning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 22:00:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>We trained our dog to this! I highly recommend. It #8217;s so much better than barking or whining.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 22:24:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good for you!!! I have a borderline abusive relationship with my brother and I totally understand and am sooo proud of you!! I wish I had been as brave as you. I #8217;m 33 now, my brother is 31, and right now I deal with him very superficially because that #8217;s what works. It is so hard when the person who abused you is also a family member. I am so proud of you!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 18:52:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree. I #8217;m in an interesting situation because my school isn #8217;t NASP accredited but some of my teachers are and NASP/my states licensure board counted my program as a NASP program when I applied for my initial school psych license. In my state for the professional license if you went to a NASP school you don #8217;t need to take the praxis, but since I didn #8217;t go I #8217;ll have to. I lucked out, I would definitely recommend just going to a NASP school.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 00:34:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>My program has been good and honestly I #8217;m a good test taker so I #8217;m not too worried. Just ready to be done. I #8217;m procrastinating on my dissertation and I need to just sit down and do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 03:42:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could you tell her you think someone made an account using his pictures? Just play dumb?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 03:50:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>All I have to say is it #8217;s a game changer when you have a kid with someone else. At least for me. My husband of 4 years has 2 daughters, 21 and 23, from a previous relationship. I 100% trust my husband but I snoop on his ex sometimes just to see if she #8217;s talking about me. (There #8217;s been some conflict). Rationally, I know it doesn #8217;t matter what she says about me. Or what the girls say. But I #8217;m a nosy bitch and I want to know. Since having my son I definitely care less. Unless you date someone with kids you will never know how hard it it. And yes it #8217;s your choice. But still. So hard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 04:37:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>If he didn #8217;t want to get better he wouldn #8217;t have told you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 04:44:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you #8217;re in mass I #8217;ll send you my brother  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 16:55:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hated the baby stage too!!! Some people just love it. My son will be 3 this May and I love doing puzzles, playing pretend and chatting. If someone could hand me an 18 month old child that was biologically mine that would be ideal. Otherwise I #8217;m done  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 15:42:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Talking about Tom Brady, the GOAT!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 15:21:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you me???? 1 semester away from being done with my doctorate. It #8217;s been hard- especially because I had a baby in the middle of it all (planned- but still), but sooo worth it for my dream job and comfortable living!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 17:11:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I already have my dream job- I #8217;m a school psychologist. In Massachusetts for your initial licensed you don #8217;t need the doctorate if you went through a NASP approved program and completed the Practicum.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 00:19:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>He was abused by his sister, and she most likely was abused by someone because most 7 year olds don #8217;t engage in sexualized behaviors unless they #8217;ve been exposed to it. Maybe as he got older he felt he was choosing to engage in sex/sexual acts with her, but she #8217;s been ABUSING him since he was 5. He doesn #8217;t know anything else, this has been his life. Coming to terms with this is scary and traumatizing and basically shaking up his entire life. If that #8217;s too much for you to (understandably) handle that #8217;s totally fine and you need to take some time to figure that out. But please realize that this abuse is not the same as some ex girlfriend he #8217;s had that he #8217;s continuing to have contact with. Source: psychologist</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 03:12:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>School psychologist. Love it. Summers off, all the school vacations- can #8217;t go wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 14:36:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Best!!!! Congrats!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 00:03:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did a google search for #1 and based on a tweet that came up I #8217;m 99% positive it #8217;s episode 77[MFM77](https://imgur.com/gallery/B06lH)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 00:32:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s what I was thinking too!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>He just wants his keys</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 00:54:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 00:54:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>My husband works in an emergency room and sent me this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 01:49:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Soooo accurate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 19:44:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could put a request, in writing, to the superintendent stating that since they will not provide safe transportation for your son based on these repeated incidents that have not been addressed you would like to know how they will be getting him to school?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 14:05:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that #8217;s the biggest component to a successful IDWHL post. When I was a teen/early 20 #8217;s there were plenty of times at the mall when someone would mistake me for a Gap/Limited/express employee. But when I said  #8220;oops, don #8217;t work here! #8221; They #8217;d accept it and go on to find an actual employee. It #8217;s what the people refuse to believe you that you get these stories. So rude!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 19:14:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gimp!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 23:56:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed 100% My mom wanted my son, her first grandchild, to call her wren (I can #8217;t even...). I was like  #8220;mom, I #8217;m pretty sure whatever he wants to call you is going to be your name, and you have to be ok with that. #8221; My parents are GrammyGramp (he says it like one word lol)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 04:38:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>So my mom loves birds (wrens) and wanted to be a  #8220;cool grandma #8221;. She #8217;s sooo fine with Grammy now though lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 17:04:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>True love. It's not dramatic, it's not difficult, it's not fighting, yelling and backstabbing. It's not flowers and fancy dinners every night. It's your life being a little bit better every day because you're with/married to your best friend. it's butterflies in your stomach on your way home from work because you can't wait to see them, even after 7 years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 21:33:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have my bachelors of fine arts in theatre management, my master of education in clinical mental health counseling and I almost done with my doctor of education in educational psychology. I #8217;m a school psychologist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 04:29:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tell my husband he needs to tell me if he wants me to respond as his wife, or as a step parent. We were getting in a lot of disagreements because he would vent about his SDs (24 and 21), but then I would join in venting and he would get annoyed. So I finally said I need you to explicitly tell me what kind of response you #8217;re looking for. I think it more so helped him understand where I #8217;m coming from. Also SD21 finally moved out so it #8217;s just us and our 2 yr old. That helped a ton!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 18:01:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/gallery/XBtQL 107 is solidly in the average range. This is the bell curve from the IQ test I give every day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 07:29:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>It sure is. Massachusetts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 19:52:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh he #8217;s on masshealth for sure- so just the taxpayers are paying his bill.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 05:19:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>The dream!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 18:28:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the natural consequence of broken legs is sufficient. You could tell him for sneaking out at night he #8217;s not allowed to go anywhere besides school/activities (sports) for 2 weeks. And you could explain that if this does happen again, regardless of injuries he will have a severe consequence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 18:43:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Patient rights advocate is who you ask for. On a practical note, I doubt the health insurance will cover her for 10 days if she is only endorsing vague SI with no plan and panic attacks. The utilization reviewer meets with the doctors every week day to get a patient update and then they contact insurance. When I worked inpatient we had patients who were endorsing suicide with a plan and insurance would deny them. She should get an FMLA and work on getting outside therapy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 19:19:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It doesn #8217;t matter if she has good insurance, there are certain criteria for level of care that you need to meet. To be inpatient LOC (level of care) you need to be an immediate risk to yourself or others, you need to not be able to care for yourself safely and/or going through med changes that NEEDs to be monitored 24/7 by a psychiatrist. There are so many levels of care, there #8217;s partial hospitalization where you go from like 9-5p m-f and it #8217;s basically run the same way as inpatient but you sleep at home. Then there #8217;s intensive outpatient which is similar to partial but you may go 3 days a week or do 1/2 days. There #8217;s outpatient therapy, med providers, specific groups- and this is all covered by insurance (for the most part, and if you meet level of care). It #8217;s very expensive to have someone inpatient for the insurance companies, so if someone doesn #8217;t need to be there they aren #8217;t going to cover them. If she has insurance then the most she would have to pay is whatever her copay is and if she has deductibles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 20:20:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I broke up with my borderline abusive long distance ex over the phone too. It obviously would have been  #8220;the right thing #8221; to break up face to face, but I only saw him once a month and it didn #8217;t seem right to string him along when I knew I was done. He also treated me like shit and had apparently been cheating on me so I didn #8217;t feel too bad about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 20:27:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wouldn #8217;t this be up to the landlord or town ordnance #8217;s to mandate? I 100% agree that it #8217;s important to be environmentally conscious but A. 10 minutes seems pretty reasonable and B. If there is no law about it/or regs in the lease even if her neighbor feels she is being inconsiderate she #8217;s not doing anything wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 21:32:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>So tough!!! But definitely the right way to do it in this case!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 21:46:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Best of luck to you!!! Even though break ups are hard and being alone can get tiring, it #8217;s definitely better than being with the wrong person!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 21:54:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to be an in home therapist and a trap we saw a lot of parents falling into is taking away everything and then the kid is like well, I have nothing else to lose and they amp up even more. Something we would recommend is earning more time. So you #8217;d tell your son and your SS, you each get x amount of time on your tablet/screen a week, your bedtime is this time. However, if you want to do these chores or we see you being helpful and listening you can earn points. You cN turn these points in for more screen time, a later bed time, more one on one time with a parent, choosing a meal, choosing a dessert etc. obviously identify  #8220;prizes #8221; that work for your family and budget. Make it very clear, you can even write on a poster board how many points each task/request would earn and then how many points they need for each prize. Hopefully SS will but into it, especially if he see your son earning things!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 22:29:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m 5 #8217;9 #8221;, female. Married. But if I #8217;d been on a dating app and someone made a big deal about their height I would be turned off. Girls who are obsessed with 6 #8221; and up aren #8217;t the ones you want anyway. Being a taller female I def would have felt a little self conscious if my partner was like5 #8217;, but my husband is 5 #8217;10 #8221; and when I wear heels I #8217;m taller than him. My mom is 6 #8217; and my dad is 5 #8217;8 and 3/4 #8221;(  #128514;) and they #8217;re very happy. B Just list your height if it asks for it and then don #8217;t stress it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 22:36:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know sometimes it #8217;s hard because it feels like you should be punishing. But I think the kids feel some respect because they know they #8217;ll get their 45 minutes or whatever (unless they do something totally crazy and dangerous or whatever you all decide) and then can earn more! You got this!! And the more detailed you are about it in the beginning the less work for you in the long run!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 22:49:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is what I was going to say, can she just call the police and ask them what to do?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 23:26:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn #8217;t see what subreddit this was and I thought this said your brother died, and I thought maybe he killed him self after his bird died. Soooo glad I was wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 22:49:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am not a lawyer but I have my masters and am almost done with my doctorate and I really rarely looked on rate my professor. I don #8217;t think anyone really uses it as a reliable way to pick a professor. I think, OP, you and your family/friends are spending way more time worrying about this than any student would. I totally get that having mean and untrue things about you on the internet is upsetting and concerning but I think most people would consider the source and understand that anyone can write anything on there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 00:26:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too. 1 day before his due date. On MY birthday.  #128580;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 00:35:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would reach out to agencies in the area, I used to work for an in home therapy team that worked with single moms. They help you find a job, child care etc. another possibility is to call DCF and tell them tour situation. I know this can sound scary, but in general they just want to help. You would get a caseworker and they could help you w vouchers for formula etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 23:12:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just growing up and growing into myself. Being in an amazing, healthy relationship didn #8217;t hurt either. But just knowing that I #8217;m a good human being doing my best helped.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 23:48:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I dated someone from when I was 19 to 23 and he was 6 years older than me. We got engaged. I knew it was wrong for me. If I #8217;d married him I would be divorced now. At 33 I am such a different person than I was at 23, and scientifically your brain is still developing into your mid 20 #8217;s. If you #8217;re positive this guy is right for you than have a long engagement, get your business started, travel with him, travel with friends, travel alone- and see how you feel in 2-4 years about marrying him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 14:53:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>The sims!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 15:02:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could probably just call your insurance and they #8217;d give you a list of actual psychologists/therapists you should go see. I was with someone for 4 years (19-23) and at the end when I was deciding if I should break up with him I kept thinking  #8220;but I #8217;ll have wasted 4 years... #8221; but I so glad I did break up with him. If I #8217;d stayed I #8217;d be miserable and divorced now. But I #8217;m 33, married to a wonderful man and we have a son.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 17:14:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>If OP tagged their workplace then anyone can see the post who has a connection with that workplace.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 17:17:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>There #8217;s also school based counseling, at least in my state was have social workers in schools. Meeting with the counselor doesn #8217;t cost any money and they are under the same confidentiality as they would be in a clinic- only breaking it if the student says they #8217;re going to hurt themselves or someone else. (At leader in my state).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 17:32:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>When my son was a newborn we had a terrible dachshund who loved running around the yard yapping, but it was more 1 minute of barking, 5 minutes of silence, 30 seconds of barking, 4 minutes of silence etc. on my 3rd day home w my newborn our neighbors, known to me only as  #8220;mean man #8221; came over and yelled in my face that he would run his lawn mower all day if I didn #8217;t take care of the dog barking. A few days later I called animal control to ask them what was allowed in terms of barking (this was all happening during the day in the summer and there are tons of dogs in our neighborhood.) animal control said a. I should file a compliant with the police about the man threatening me and B. It would need to be at least 10 minutes of non stop barking to be considered a noise violation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 22:42:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>How is she with your sister?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 00:07:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mom wrote this in the 70 #8217;s, totally forgot and her friend texted it to her yesterday. They postponed it until 2022.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 23:45:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love that one!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hashimotos and psoriasis</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 23:33:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi all! Does anyone else suffer from psoriasis too? I have scales on the palms of my hands and soles of my feet. I went gluten free for about a year and had success. However, after I gave birth to my son gluten free didn #8217;t seem to help anymore. Then I did UV light treatments which helped but I had to stop because it was too far to travel to 2 days a week. They #8217;re getting bad again and I #8217;m wondering if anyone else has experienced this and had advice? I #8217;m going to try the UV lights again I think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 04:51:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>My husband #8217;s ex is like this. She is just selfish human being who doesn #8217;t care about her kids *unless it brings her sympathies* . Luckily (maybe) for me, my husband #8217;s daughters are in their 20 #8217;s now, so I only had a few years of dealing with helping them get appointments. My husband had no problems with keeping up with their health, however at 19 and 17 they had questions about safe sex etc that they weren #8217;t always comfy talking to their dad about (while he had no problem with them learning safe sex v abstinence it #8217;s def awkward as a daughter to talk about with your dad.) I think, as long as SO shows that NOW he is involved and will continue to be, you need to focus on that and not worry about BM. Edit: a word</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 13:51:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 02:47:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>How are the people you adopted from able to see you pictures? I would just unfollow/unfriend whatever and move on with your life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 03:00:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry! I missed that. Is there any other way they #8217;d be able to get info on you now? (I have an ex friend who used to volunteer w a shelter and she was CRAZY about stalking ppl on social media. But if she didn #8217;t have access to that she would usually forget about them.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 14:24:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love Karen so much and I get 100% that they are not doctors/cops/psychologists etc. I #8217;m a licensed mental health counselor and a school psychologist. Normally if they kind of bungle something related to mental health it doesn #8217;t bother me, but this week when Karen said multiple personality disorder isn #8217;t even real anymore, I was so annoyed. I #8217;m hoping she #8217;s talking about how multiple personality disorder was removed from the DSM IV and replaced with dissociative identity disorder in the DSM 5, but I don #8217;t think that #8217;s what she meant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 02:29:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, she could have meant  #8220;they got rid of MPD and replaced it with DID #8221;, but to me it really sounded like she was saying  #8220;they proved MPD isn #8217;t real #8221;. Only 2% of the population have DID, so the chances of anyone who listens having it, or encountering someone with it, is slim. But still, you don #8217;t want to misinform people! Thanks for letting me know you #8217;ll let your SO know he was right!!  #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 04:12:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>NAL but I am a licensed mental health counselor and have worked on inpatient units with suicidal adults as a clinician (therapist). There is no reason that a competent (I understand that a suicide attempt shows decreased decision making skills, but not competent would be floridly schizophrenic, intellectually disabled etc) able bodied, physically healthy adult would be discharged into the care of another adult (again, unless they had a legal guardian). The psychiatrist may have wanted a family session before releasing him (which you definitely can say no to, especially if you #8217;re separating/divorcing), but that #8217;s probably the extent of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 04:39:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a former 14 year old girl (now 33 lol) I can tell you if she #8217;s not saying  #8220;I hate you #8221; when you say  #8220;I love you #8221; , you #8217;re in pretty good shape. It #8217;s not ideal, and not what you want, but any 14 year old girl who sits there with a parent figure, talks to that person honestly and openly, and is respectful an age appropriate amount of time, is telling you she loves you with her actions. As a current therapist (licensed mental health counselor) I can tell you that from her past she most liked has post traumatic stress disorder (PTSD) and due to disrupted placements and traumatic relationships (a pattern of them!) with father figures, she will have a very hard time being able to express love to anyone. She could benefit from trauma informed therapy to work through her past, in order to help her future familial, platonic and romantic (way more in the future) relationships. She also probably has resentment to mom. Mom is the  #8220;adult in charge #8221; and through SD #8217;s eyes she may think  #8220;mom picked all these bad men who ruined our lives and now we #8217;re here and I don #8217;t want to like anything she does. #8221; (Or something along these lines.) she #8217;s 14! Her brain still has 11 more years to grow and develop until it #8217;s finished, so she isn #8217;t able to see the big picture like you and I can. I #8217;m a SM to 2 SD #8217;s, now in their 20 #8217;s, and I get it 100% that not getting that feedback when you show love makes you want to pull back. I can PROMISE you that by what you #8217;ve described she is showing you that she trusts you and feels love for you. You are doing an AMAZING job for this family. As long as you can remain caring, kind, consistent and compassionate, your SD will only find more love for you. Sorry if this was cheesy but I just feel like you have a really great dynamic here that will develop into something wonderful as everyone grows up, as long as people remain consistent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 18:59:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>But they have no obligation to release him to anyone, unless he #8217;s someone that has a legal guardian. OP- think about it this way. What would a single person living in an area with no one they knew do in this situation? The hospital would set up whatever aftercare supports they felt were needed and then the person would be discharged home. There is NO reason that anyone else needs to be responsible for them. If there is a reason, then they shouldn #8217;t be released.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 19:21:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most Insurances will cover sessions you go to. However, if you miss a session then the insurance obviously won #8217;t pay, since no service was provided. However, the therapist still needs to make money, so they put in place a cancellation fee. Different providers will do different amounts, it sounds like this one is just doing the full amount covered by insurance. If there #8217;s no fee for missing there #8217;s no incentive for people to cancel in a timely fashion, or at all. As a therapist myself, when I worked outpatient, if I knew someone was canceling, with enough notice I could fill their spot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 03:15:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agree!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 03:42:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was going to say all of this. I got my research approved through IRB at my college for my doctorate in the fall and what I had to provide for a survey was intense. I can #8217;t imagine that this would be something that would be approved.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 21:59:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something you could do, maybe on a slower shift, is compile a list of all the homeless shelters (with address and contact info) in your area. Then when they come, if you turn them away you can hand them the list. In my experience, people who do want to better their life, get in a better situation, will be appreciative. Those who want to continue to use etc won #8217;t be, because they aren #8217;t allowed to use in shelters and are forced out during the day to look for work. If you were feeling super generous you could put the pamphlet of shelters in a ziplock bag with some granola bars and crackers, but you def don #8217;t need to do any of this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 22:54:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a reverse problem. I work at a high school and frequently use the restrooms in the nurses suite. The doors have that occupied/available sign that is connected to the lock. At the end of last year I opened the door of a bathroom that said  #8220;available #8221; and terrified a student. I made it my personal rule that I ALWAYS knock even if it says available. This fall went in there, both bathrooms say  #8220;available #8221; knock on the door, wait, no response, open the door.... and there #8217;s a freaking kid in there! WTF?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 00:19:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 01:02:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes!!!! My younger brother tortured me growing up but it was always my fault.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 13:21:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!!! This is what I came here to say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Academic] Grandparents raising grandchildren (grandparents raising grandchildren in mass)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 20:10:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 04:42:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude. You don #8217;t look 50. Get it!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 00:29:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>This. I mean I comment on lighter stuff, but if anything is slightly controversial I don #8217;t want to deal with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 20:28:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>My husbands ex and I get along great! To be fair I met my husband when his daughters were 15 and 17. It seems like, as the kids get older, there #8217;s less drama (this is just from what I #8217;ve seen, and based on my relationships). The biggest thing for me was learning to take a step back. I know it can be so hard, because even though they #8217;re not your monkeys, at times is IS your circus and you just want to do what you want to do. I used to spend so much energy getting annoyed at BM (even though we get along I def would get frustrated with her.) but at the end of the day, they #8217;re my husbands daughters and he needs to figure it out. Now they #8217;re both in their 20 #8217;s and live on their own. So. Much. Better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 00:21:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got married 5 years ago but it still seems recent to me. If any of my bridesmaids had been feeling the way you #8217;re feeling I would have hoped they #8217;d approach me to express their concerns. I would never ever have wanted this for them. My bff was my MOH and she lived in Cali, so I knew she #8217;d have to pay to fly back, but otherwise the dress was $120 and I shared a room w my MOH and my cousin the night before the wedding and paid for it. Seriously, talk to the bride.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 13:51:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking that too! Especially if he always goes there and always pays- I would have definitely given him the benefit of the doubt that something happened and there was an oversight!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 13:52:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oooh good call!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 13:55:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone suggested maybe it was a customer who called, that makes a little more sense. Still weird though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 15:21:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol true</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 03:08:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dad has a similar eye!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 18:00:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your boyfriend may be an anxious guy, maybe he was cheated on in the past- However, if someone is engaging in behavior they shouldn #8217;t be (cheating) they sometimes project their guilt into the person they #8217;re cheating on. I dated a Guy who lived 2 hours away and from as convinced I was cheating. I wasn #8217;t. I was in grad school and was in class or studying. Found out after I broke up with him that he was cheating on me. Just something to think about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 18:25:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly no. But it was a pretty bad relationship, and I lived 2 hours away and he never visited. I guess maybe he was always on his phone, always talked about how he #8217;d been cheated on before so it made him paranoid, and always accusing me of cheating. I never let Him go through my phone or anything. He was the worst, I #8217;m so glad I #8217;m done with that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 23:47:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was terrified to give birth but it wasn #8217;t that bad. I mean- it was terrible, but I survived and you can too. I breastfed for 25 months which was hell- but honestly the effects to my body were pretty limited.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 23:54:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have to agreed- I #8217;m not on meds but I am an anxious person. However, I #8217;m ok with a nap being missed or a bedtime being a little late. I really thing if it #8217;s affecting you this much you should see a doctor or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 00:21:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never lock my phone. If my husband went through my phone then I would know our relationship is over (not because of what he would find, but because he didn #8217;t trust me enough to communicate that he was worried about something. )</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 00:28:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve been married for 5 years and that #8217;s exactly how it #8217;s worked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 01:18:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m a woman. Married to a man. I guess my relationship is just awesome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 15:32:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work at a high school. There is a designated student drop off area. When parents drop their kids right in front of the school- blocking all traffic from moving, disobeying posted signs etc, and then frantically try to pull back out, I don #8217;t let them. The parents who pull up the 10 extra feet to the designated area- I always let them pull out in front of me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 15:46:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean that #8217;s how I see it, but I #8217;m sure they don #8217;t think they #8217;re doing anything wrong. Thank you though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 04:57:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m an LMHC but I #8217;m also almost done with my doctorate in education. 2 years ago I became a school psych. I only do testing. I. Love. It.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 05:03:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>IANAL- I am a licensed mental health counselor in MA. All inpatient hospitals have a human rights persons. Ask for that person. They are there for the patients. Make a compliant. This was not right. None of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 13:56:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly that #8217;s just going to take time. My personal stance when I #8217;ve ended relationships has been to cut all contact with that person. It sounds like you guys go to school together, so there #8217;s bound to be some contact. But I would stop engaging in social media, stop responding to texts, etc. if he wants to post pictures of you from a year ago- oh well. I know it #8217;s super annoying. But unless you can delete these pictures there #8217;s really nothing you can do (unless they #8217;re inappropriate and then I would report them.) You can only control yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 13:57:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>This!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 16:14:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn #8217;t read all the comments yet- but couldn #8217;t you just say it #8217;s for religious reasons? I get that that may not be telling the truth- but if you were a Jehovah #8217;s Witness you wouldn #8217;t celebrate your birthday- or any holiday- and wouldn #8217;t they need to respect that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 04:22:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I came here to post this!!!! SSDGM!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 00:20:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love it!!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 21:51:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not OP but it #8217;s common in my district. In my experience, in smaller districts (like mine) psychs do ed/achievement testing. In bigger districts around me, teachers do the ed/achievement testing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 02:35:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m a school psych. She should request an evaluation for 504- and ask for accommodations for field trips- however they don #8217;t HAVE to accommodate. (An example I learned in a sped law legal issues seminar was, if a school was going on a field trip to learn about bee hives etc, it would not be reasonable to bring a student with a 504 for bee stings because you really couldn #8217;t keep them safe. Or a 504 for a peanut allergy and a a peanut factory- however the student wouldn #8217;t be penalized for not attending. I #8217;m a little surprised that they aren #8217;t allowing them to go- and that a nurse isn #8217;t going on the trip. My school does 3 nights in DC and a nurse has to go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 22:25:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>My Favorite!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 20:40:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely treehouse. Also depending on the line there #8217;s no way you #8217;ll only be there for 15 minutes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 02:57:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got my first fillings ever about a month ago. I almost fell asleep during the procedure- an uninterrupted hour with out my very active 2 year old!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 14:32:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to work at a residential program in my state (Mass), and worked closely with DCF. It is ALWAYS easier for DCF to leave a child with its mother if possible. If conditions are safe, mom is fit and able to care for the kids, then they do not want to spend time and money relocating babies that have a safe place to live. They can #8217;t remove the babies without investigating- and it seems like their investigation isn #8217;t going to lead to them finding anything that would warrant a removal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 02:46:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m in western mass and I will drive to the top of the cape if I have to I need to know!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 02:55:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahhhhtbat would have been amazing!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 04:02:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in the US. If you qualify for Medicaid in mass (you don #8217;t even have to have Medicaid, just qualify for it )you are not financially responsible for any services you get medically. My husband works at the ED in our area and he sees people using ambulances as taxis to get downtown because they don #8217;t have to pay for it. It #8217;s ridiculous.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 02:10:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agree 100%!!! I found the sub after I had finished the hardest part of my breast feeding journey, but it #8217;s been a life saver and a support for so much more than that. Like u/tinysmommy says, it can be painfully hard at first, but all of it is amazing and parts of it are just breathtakingly wonderful. We #8217;re here for you mama!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 02:13:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just read your update and I #8217;m super proud of you!!! That must have been so hard and uncomfortable, but I #8217;m so glad you did it. I was hoping you would update!!! Good luck with the therapist and psychiatrist search!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 02:30:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, since that episode MFM has kind of left a bad taste in my mouth. I DID write them, and was hopeful that they would read my correction, or if someone else wrote in read their correction, but they didn #8217;t. As much as I get that this is a free podcast that I, and many others, choose to listen to- if you know that people are looking to you for guidance on mental health issues, wouldn #8217;t you want to be as accurate as possible? And honestly all that would mean is saying  #8220;I #8217;m pretty sure about x, but I haven #8217;t researched it, so maybe check it out if it #8217;s something that interests you- but my understanding about x is- blah blah blah. #8221; I #8217;m in my 7th year of grad school right now and I don #8217;t talk as confidently about psychology as they do, (and it #8217;s what I #8217;m getting my doctorate in), and I know what I #8217;m talking about. I just wish they understood how much power they have with their podcast, and how many opportunities they have to educate people!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 16:34:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has anyone recommended posting in r/legaladvice?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 14:25:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had never heard of this. I have hashimotos and I gave birth to my son 3 years ago. No concerns about autism.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 14:03:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ever since I had my son and nursed him for 2+ years my nipples have literally been out of control. The only 2 (incredibly padded) bras I have that do completely keep them from being seen are so uncomfortable that I rarely ever wear them. I try to layer up shirts over my more flimsy bras to keep them at bay, but sometimes at work I notice they #8217;re sticking out and I get embarrassed. But bras are so uncomfortable!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 16:10:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>33f. When I was single, if a guy I was interested in asked me out and I had a conflict- I would definitely offer an alternative option  #8220;shoot- this Saturday I #8217;m working until 11:30, but I #8217;m free the following Saturday! #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 05:39:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>My son started crying because I said he can #8217;t have a Dino as a pet. I quickly amended that to- any Dino you find you may have as a pet. Smooth sailing ever since.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 16:05:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh snap! Good call</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 03:25:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is 100% a HIPAA violation. Sharing that they are in the hospital is information that the people had because OP was in the hospital as a patient. What was OP supposed to do? Drive however many hours to the next closest hospital or assume their co workers could be professional?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 15:07:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m an LMHC, and in some situations it #8217;s not plausible to drive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 23:10:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will die if she plays All Too Well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 14:53:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>And even if she pumps on her lunch she still needs to pump 1 or 2 more times a day. When I went back to work after having my son I would pump at 9a, 12p(on my lunch) and 3p. As he get older I went to 11a and 3p, then just once a day and then at 1 year I stopped.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>May the Fourth be with you treats!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 17:23:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 17:25:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>My husband and I made Han Solo peanut butter dipper in chocolate (much better than carbonite), light saber pretzel rods, Death Star Oreo truffles and Wookiee Cookies (they #8217;re Chewy  #128514; #128514; #128514;) Happy Star Wars day!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 21:53:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Death Star #8217;s- they def need some work!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 03:32:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m a school psychologist and a licensed mental health counselor. In our meetings for students in IEPs we discuss if the student could be the victim of a bully OR if they could be a bully, and what to do in either case. I think part of the problem is that it #8217;s much easier to sensationalize the story of a bullied student, then talk about a bully.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mass- student loan scam</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:18:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I searched reddit to see if I could find the answer to this, but I couldn #8217;t! For the past 6 months I receive a call from  #8220;no caller ID #8221; that rings once and then hangs up, however a message from  #8220;Brenda Green #8221; is left saying to call back 888-227-5324 with the reference number 02065 in reference to my student loan debt. (I know this is a scam because they leave no company name and just are super shady.) I called them on April 18th and left a message that they were harassing me and if they continued to call I would take legal action. They called me again today. When I called back 3 different times 3 different people hung up on before I spoke to someone who confirmed my name and said they #8217;d take me off the list. Before he hung up on me I said if they called again I would take legal action. I #8217;m just wondering though- is there anything I can do legally? Do I call my cities non emergency number and report it just for the documentation? And is it even worth it? Thanks! I #8217;m in Western Ma</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:22:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did block the number that the message is left from. However- when they actually call it shows up as  #8220;no caller ID #8221;. There is no number to block. I #8217;ve blocked every number from them I have but I don #8217;t see a way to block a  #8220;No Caller ID #8221; number. Thank you for the form I #8217;ll do that now!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:48:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will do both thank you! I did the FCC already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 20:52:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>She #8217;s 15. I work w her maternal aunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 01:20:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes!!! We had a holocaust survivor come. She wrote a book. I can #8217;t believe I can #8217;t remember her name!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 00:43:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why can #8217;t that hand be mine?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 03:52:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check how many hours are required for internship in the state you want to relocate to. When I was doing my internship the most required was 900, so I did 1000 just to be safe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 03:48:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That because I #8217;m nice I actually care. Not to say I don #8217;t care- but sometimes I just want to do work and not hear your ten minute story.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 03:59:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed!! I #8217;m slightly concerned about an emerging mental health diagnosis here, so if she doesn #8217;t accept it I would consider asking to go to therapy with her. The therapist would be able to pick up on Amy emerging diagnoses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 14:03:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I worked as a counselor (floor staff) at a local psych hospital.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:58:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean- I guess unless it was in Vegas, in the states you need to get a marriage license- both parties need to be there for that. So without that it wouldn #8217;t be a legal marriage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 01:28:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>My son has been sick a lot at daycare too but now that he #8217;s 3 it #8217;s not as bad. All my friends w older kids say that their kids who were sick in daycare were fine in kindergarten when all the other kiddos were getting sick left and right, so I #8217;m crossing my fingers for that scenario for us too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 01:39:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>In my district the special ed, or student support services office is staffed during the summer, as is the superintendent #8217;s office. I #8217;d start w the supers office, call and say who do you contact to get a copy of your 504 and any testing you had done. They should direct you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 14:30:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>This so much. I was sexually harassed at work, told my supervisor and NOTHING was done about it except to make me feel like I #8217;m starting drama and have no value as a woman. Honestly I don #8217;t think I would report sexual harassment in the work place again unless I had concrete proof that the person would be fired. Luckily, I am at a much better job with people who would hopefully never engage in this behavior. The layers of dealing with sexual harassment and assault as a woman go so far beyond just reporting the assaulter. It is great that this worked out so well for your wife, and your support was great! But this is definitely, unfortunately, not the norm.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 14:35:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is so cool!!! I #8217;ve never heard of this type of seal before. Sooo cute.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 15:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is what I wanted to say. I do not have a great relationship w my two adult SD #8217;s (24 and 22), and I used to be like OP. It WAS ruining my marriage. I had to take a step back and realize that, while so annoying, it #8217;s just a mess and it #8217;s just food. If their dad doesn #8217;t care about them learning how to clean up after themselves or eat healthy then why should I? (I know that sounds terrible, but it wasn #8217;t worth the battle.) SD 22 has moved back in after being gone for about 6 months and I am so much less stressed and annoyed because I really have no expectations for her and don #8217;t care (and also she #8217;s leaving for good August 18  #128588;). For me, the best think you can do as a step parent is- support your partner and spouse, and attempt to have a positive relationship with your SKIDS that doesn #8217;t involve a lot of limit setting/discipline (beyond normal house rules).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 15:07:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just came here to say: My husband has a divorce dad guilt and it annoys me to no end (and his daughters are spoiled adult brats because of it), but I get it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 15:57:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>You nailed it. And for me I #8217;m like  #8220;this is so simple- your ex cheated on you, why do you have guilt? Why do you let this adults treat you like shit? #8221; I was a little worried about having a child with him because of the way he parents his girls, however it #8217;s 100% different with our son, probably because we #8217;re together.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 17:39:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you need to ask yourself why you #8217;re stressing so much about this but their mom and dad clearly aren #8217;t. If it was a situation where you prepared food for you (say for lunch at work etc) and they were eating that- tell them  #8220;I #8217;m going to label my food that I am bringing to work and you may not eat that. #8221; Otherwise, if it doesn #8217;t affect you then don #8217;t stress it. And if husband complains about their unhealthy eating habits, don #8217;t get into it. They #8217;re his kids. If you #8217;re stressing more than BIO parents something is wrong here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 21:38:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>And if he doesn #8217;t- tell him what you need to feel comfortable in your home. For me it #8217;s: 1. No food in rooms (for my husband #8217;s daughters, now that only the 22 y/o is living w us and she is an adult, it #8217;s eating in room but cleaning it up in a timely fashion.) 2. Not making multiple dinners- they can have the dinner or they can make pb and j or a bowl of cereal. 3. Cleaning up messes in a timely manner I feel like these are expectations I would have of anyone staying in my house- not just my step kids. I have talked to my husband about how by not setting certain limits he could be setting his kids up for failure (ie you don #8217;t go in someone house and rearrange their entire kitchen- even if you think you #8217;re being helpful.) but if he doesn #8217;t want to address it it #8217;s his choice. He and I have a 3 year old son together and his parenting is soooo different with our child, much more consistent. The divorce dad guilt is real. You need to decide what #8217;s important to you to be comfortable in your house and express that to your husband.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 04:25:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed! And my point was, tell your husband what rules you need HIM to lay down with the girls so that you can feel comfortable in your home.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 16:26:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was surprised that it was such a low amount. Both of my prom dresses were $400+ (and I had a smaller budget than most of my friends... which typing this now as a 34 year makes me feel so ridiculous)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 19:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most of my friends spent $500-$800. I grew up in a wealthy suburb north of Boston mass. No where like where I live now. It was a different world.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 14:40:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with the first comment as well! I started dating my now husband when his daughters were 17 and 15. They have a mother already. I have no problem being a support for them if they need it but I am not their mother. Sometimes they #8217;ll give me a card or flowers on Mother #8217;s Day and I #8217;m always appreciative, but some years they don #8217;t acknowledge the day and that #8217;s fine too. For an adult man who has only known you for a few years as an adult , it #8217;s insane he would expect a Father #8217;s Day anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 21:22:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you asked for any type of diagnostic residential placement? Have your current providers recommended any in home support? Can you request a respite program where she is able to go on the weekends?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 21:23:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>You cannot diagnose a personality disorder until 18 years old. At 15-17ish you can say  #8220;has x traits #8221; but you cannot diagnose it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 21:44:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m a licensed mental health counselor and a licensed school psychologist. You cannot diagnose a personality disorder until the person is 18, and a good clinician wouldn #8217;t even bring up personality disorders until the client was much closer to 18(in my opinion, and because people get confused)- however insurances are letting more and more people treat with just a masters and no license. I #8217;m guessing OP was confused as well. Edit: what #8217;s in the parentheses</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 21:45:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>A respite program can be 1 night a week doing crafts with peers in the community, or one weekend a month doing an overnight in an actually treatment facility. Combined with in home suppers it can be very effective.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 21:57:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am almost done w my doctorate in psychology and I #8217;m an LMHC too! I just wish people would treat personality disorders with the seriousness the diagnosis demands instead of throwing it around like it #8217;s some kind of run of the mill situational depression.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 22:06:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m a licensed (by Dese) school psych, I #8217;m currently not doing much with my Lmhc but I love working in a school. I cannot wait to be done- this dissertation is killing me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 00:15:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s my struggle too! It was so much easier writing papers etc when my son was immobile. Now that he #8217;s 3 it #8217;s sooo much harder. Luckily I have summers off so my plan is to just pound it all out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 03:17:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right? I live in western ma and for awhile that was what everyone was saying but I found it very hard to believe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 21:47:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes!!! Same. I live in Holyoke and getting off 391 is so depressing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 14:54:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Baby showers/bridal showers that are all women where everyone sits around and watches one person open presents. I know no one who likes it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 20:38:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can #8217;t believe this is the top comment. That does nothing to actually solve the problem of a woman being treated less than men. I don #8217;t know what the right thing for OP to do is- but this isn #8217;t it. I #8217;m glad her boss has her back!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 20:49:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s awesome!!!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 15:02:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I broke up with my super crazy unstable ex boyfriend who has multiple guns and honestly for months I thought he was going to drive to my parents house and shoot them. But then I reminded myself that he #8217;s also a huge stoner and if he couldn #8217;t be motivated to go out and get a job or run errands or come visit me at grad school I doubt he #8217;d put in the effort to go murder my family. HOWEVER- if he had said one threatening thing I would have called the cops. He was licensed to have the guns so I didn #8217;t have a ton I could do. Luckily nothing happened but it #8217;s scary. Guys don #8217;t realize the physical power they have over women.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 15:11:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the point is that it #8217;s not a woman #8217;s responsibility to tell a man what he was doing wrong over the course of an entire relationship/friendship- especially when it could put the woman in real or perceived danger. It #8217;s a lot easier to correct social mishaps (being rude to a server, constantly showing up late etc) than to basically say  #8220;you #8217;re entire self and the way you treat me is not acceptable. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 18:44:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you have a stronger support network before you started dating your BF?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 15:25:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had to get my 3 year old son #8217;s BC recently and it was so easy. I called my city hall, in the city where I lived and asked if they had it (since he was born in a different city than where we live.) they had it, I went down, paid $10 and had it. They didn #8217;t check my ID or anything- so OP I wonder if you could presumably get it? Or if you support her in getting it would be great for her independence!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 15:44:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ask to speak to the human rights representative and make a complaint. They are 100% bound by HIPAA. Also ask for any I take packets/paperwork. If your health insurance is paying for you to be there and/or you are receiving treatment- HIPAA is being broken.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 15:45:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve worked in residential programs before (am a licensed mental health counselor in mass) , they are 100% bound by HIPAA.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 08:46:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look up the teachers pay scale for areas you want to work in. I started at $55k- am up to almost 60k, should max out around $90k. My district is small, some districts that are bigger may pay more, but at least one friend I know who works for more money in a bigger district has way more stress than me. Also remember, if you #8217;re in a district like me you #8217;re only working 180 days a year, vs someone who doesn #8217;t have almost st 4 months off. I love my job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 20:25:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where is this?????</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sometimes... it goes ok</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 05:05:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have 2 SDs (24 and 21). I #8217;ve been with their dad since they were 14 and 16. Their parents had split 10 years prior. Over the years we #8217;ve had a rocky relationship for many reasons, but ultimately I would love to have a positive relationship for the sake of my husband and our son- 3. My SD 21 has been through a lot this year, most recently dealing with a significant mental health diagnosis of her sister (who refuses to treat the diagnosis). Tonight, from her BF #8217;s house she texted me a picture of a suicidal post her friend made on Instagram and said she was going to go over and talk to him. I #8217;m a licensed school psych and a licensed therapist and I convinced her that she needed to call the police as he was threatening to shoot him self and saying he was drunk. When she texted me  #8220;you #8217;re right #8221;, I felt a feeling of calm come over me. For all our battles, for all the disagreements, for all the times she thinks shes in competition w me for her dad #8217;s attention (this is very much a perception on her side- her dad would spend all his free time with her if he could), she was able to trust me as an adult in her life looking out for her best interests. Her friend is luckily ok and not mad at her for calling the police, and my husband contacted his dad, so hopefully he gets the help he needs. Being a step parent is so hard, but moments like this help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 05:08:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe- if it #8217;s possible to make a note on the payment when he submits it, you could ask him to write the dates that the rent is through. I do this on my son #8217;s daycare checks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 05:37:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>He can #8217;t attach a virtual memo to the deposit? Could you get Venmo and have him do it that way. You can #8217;t make the transaction with out a note. He could write rent-  #8220;August 1-October 31st #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 18:16:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s been really hard for me because I #8217;ve really tried to be firm, consistent and loving, but to also have clear boundaries. Sometimes I think to myself  #8220;should I be more flexible? #8221; But her mom is the opposite and she really struggles with not having a clearly defined, predictable relationship with her mom. I know she and I will still have our little bumps in the road, but this interaction felt really good and I wanted other step parents to know that there are good parts of this incredibly hard role too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 18:16:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 18:36:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>This!!! I know as a step parent I get caught up in some of the drama and at times have contacted BM, but really, letting the parents deal with the communication around their kids is the best way to go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 22:14:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gives me chills.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 02:22:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would say she #8217;s definitely emotionally cheating but she does seem to be showing some restraint- not sending pics etc. I would think about how much you want this relationship to work and ask her what changes she wants to see and what you want to see. I #8217;ve found that the flirty stuff does wear off and it can be fun to have that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Taylor killing it at Gillette night 3!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 03:27:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 04:10:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 04:12:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOVE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 04:17:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was 17 I was hospitalized. I was engaging in SIB and they thought I might be bipolar. Turns out I have r/hashimotos and I wasn #8217;t diagnosed properly Anyway- I #8217;m guessing this isn #8217;t the answer you #8217;re looking for, but being in the hospital was super stress relieving. I didn #8217;t have to make any decisions. I didn #8217;t have to worry about anything. It was great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 04:19:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Doesn #8217;t</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 04:19:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 04:19:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Long</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 08:00:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 19:02:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 19:03:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d never seen her live before even though I #8217;ve been a fan forever. We got snake pit tickets from my cousin and it was amazing!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 22:57:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 02:44:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the best song hands down no questions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 14:34:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re amazing!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 17:58:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>It sounds like she has some trust issues. I would ask her what she #8217;s worried about that #8217;s causing her to think you #8217;re not at work/skyping someone else/mad or ignoring her. I #8217;m a naturally anxious person and when I first started dating my now husband I would sometimes get worried he was mad/annoyed when he didn #8217;t text back quickly, but now we #8217;ve been together 7 years- married for 5, and we rarely text during the work day at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 18:02:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so true. I #8217;m a mildly anxious person (like def more anxiety than is  #8220;normal #8221;, but it #8217;s pretty manageable day to day) I know that it #8217;s my problem to deal w if I text my husband during the work day and he doesn #8217;t text back. I also will tell myself (and I haven #8217;t had to do this in years because at this point I #8217;m very solid and comfortable in my relationship)  #8220;ok well he #8217;s done w work at 3:30, so if he #8217;s not home by 4 and I haven #8217;t heard from him then that #8217;s when it #8217;s ok to go crazy. #8221; Lol I #8217;m also an  #8220;anxious they might have died #8221; person vs and  #8220;anxious they #8217;re cheating #8221; person, I trust my husband 100%.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 18:05:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s so funny cause I used to be like this too. I #8217;ve been married to my husband for 5 years now and on a typical day we probably exchange 6 texts total throughout the day. When I was younger I think I thought texting all day and being in constant communication was a sign of a healthy relationship. Now I #8217;m like wow- we have such a positive relationship, I love that I can go to work, focus on my job, and then get home and can talk about my day with him in person. Of course if something big happens during the day we text or call each other, but otherwise it #8217;s usually a quick  #8220;how #8217;s your day going? #8221; At lunch time, then a  #8220;probably going to the store on my way home, need anything? #8221; And maybe one more  #8220;heading home now #8221;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 03:59:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with what pretty much everyone is saying. My son started daycare at 14 weeks because hats what we had to do. He loves it and does well socially. While I was really sad I couldn #8217;t be a SAHM like my mom was. I was happy that my son probably won #8217;t have a lot of the anxiety in social situations that I had- as I was with my mom 25/7 until I went to kindergarten. If you like your daycare I would stay there for sure. My son loves his daycare so much- it #8217;s a small, in home, licensed daycare and it #8217;s been wonderful for him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 04:16:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is everything that I want r/legaladvice to be</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 04:58:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yesss! That #8217;s my thought too. I live in western mass if that helps</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 22:01:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>OP are you my sister? Cause it sounds like we had the same mom growing up!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 22:21:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I totally understand! My mom didn #8217;t want me calling boys because she didn #8217;t think it was  #8220;proper #8221;. She trained me to always say sorry even if it wasn #8217;t my fault. Over the past ten years she #8217;s said she #8217;s been impressed with my ability to stand up for myself, which is so hard because I have to fight all my natural instincts to apologize and take blame for stuff I didn #8217;t do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 00:27:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think for my mom it was 100% to avoid conflict. I don #8217;t think my mom had any ill intentions toward me and wasn #8217;t trying to teach me to be submissive- it #8217;s just how she is as a person it does feel good to have her praise me for being assertive though. I do hate how I apologize for literally everything. I really try not to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 01:37:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>So cute!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 18:15:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>My grandfather is a huge N and I #8217;ve been NC since 2005, with one brief interaction at my parents house in 2012. Despite being NC I know that in the past people would filter back things about our family to them. I HATE the thought that my grandfather will 100% brag about me- I went to a pretty well renown Boston College for communications, I #8217;m getting my doctorate, I have a son now. It drives me crazy that he only contributed stress and unhappiness to my life but gets to take credit for my accomplishments.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 19:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>What?! That #8217;s insane!!! Your wife is awesome, I remember making the baby food and it was time consuming but worth it for sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 21:28:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am a licensed mental health counselor and a school psychologist. Before working in the schools I worked in a residential program as the therapist for kids who have been through trauma and are in the custody of the state. I #8217;m a fairly empathetic person, however I learned to  #8220;shut off #8221; those feelings while at work. It #8217;s not that I was jaded or didn #8217;t care about the kids I was working with, I did care, but I also knew I needed to be professional and deal with my client in the moment. It #8217;s just like when you #8217;re at any job, if your boss reprimands you you may feel like crying but you hold it together because you have to be professional. Having your own therapist to process with after the fact is a very smart, healthy and appropriate thing to do. Good luck to your mom on her masters!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 21:28:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am a licensed mental health counselor and a school psychologist. Before working in the schools, I worked in a residential program as the therapist for kids who have been through trauma and are in the custody of the state. I #8217;m a fairly empathetic person, however I learned to  #8220;shut off #8221; those feelings while at work. It #8217;s not that I was jaded or didn #8217;t care about the kids I was working with, I did care, but I also knew I needed to be professional and deal with my client in the moment. It #8217;s just like when you #8217;re at any job, if your boss reprimands you you may feel like crying but you hold it together because you have to be professional. Having your own therapist to process with after the fact is a very smart, healthy and appropriate thing to do. Good luck to your mom on her masters!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 21:53:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well if she doesn #8217;t like his coldness she can always look for another therapist, sometimes you have to go through a couple! I know that before I went to school for counseling I thought  #8220;of course my clients will want to see my reactions and hear about my experiences too! #8221; (Spoiler - they don #8217;t )- and I learned this through my internships and Practicums. That helps also with keeping your emotions/boundaries in check. As you progress with your client you can shape the relationship, for example I had some clients I needed to maintain iron clad boundaries with. Other clients I knew I could joke around a little bit more and they were appreciative, but at the start you do need to be a blank slate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 05:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 00:01:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I totally get it. I have a slightly different situation where my SDs are older, and were 15 and 17 when their dad and I started dating. They #8217;re now 22 and 24. I never ever felt like a step mom- they have a mom, they were mostly grown by the time I was in their lives. Before stuff got really bad with them (another story involving a bipolar dx), I didn #8217;t mind spending time with them, but I #8217;d prefer not to. I know it sounds awful, but they #8217;re incredibly spoiled, self centered and rude girls. My husband has a lot of divorced dad guilt (even though he would have stayed w his ex until his girls were done w school) and I don #8217;t understand why, he was faithful to their marriage and has been a great dad overall. So anyway, I totally get where your coming from.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 21:10:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s her SO #8217;s sister- so she #8217;s kind of stuck w her in her life to some extent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Harbor Seals off the coast of Rockport</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 04:34:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 05:54:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love this. It #8217;s so true. This time last summer I was nursing my son(2 years and 3 months. ) tonight we #8217;re camping and he had a hot dog and pasta salad. Who cares?! He #8217;s happy and healthy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 05:24:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also, if OP is doing well In school and able to access the curriculum then they most likely wouldn #8217;t be eligible for an IEP anyway. 504 is for sure the way to go!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 12:32:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 04:28:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in Western Mass and we pay $40/day-$800 a month for my son #8217;s licensed, in home daycare. We were lucky, she #8217;s amazing and also one of the cheapest daycares I was quoting in my search (and also the only one with an opening so it worked out). Most of the ones w no openings were $1200 a month. What #8217;s crazy to me too is he #8217;s there from 7am- 3 pm during the school year (I work in a school so have a teachers schedule- I #8217;m a school psych) so she #8217;s earning $5 an hour technically. It #8217;s just crazy to me overall. We #8217;re waiting to have our second child until our first goes to kindergarten.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 13:40:27</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I'm a psychiatrist, not a lawyer, but I was told that 504's don't really force the school to do anything, whereas IEP's do. It sounds like OP needs to force the school to do something and thus needs an IEP. (This comes up often during our child psych rotation.) This is not true. 504 provides accommodations. IEPs provide modifications. Any student with any disability is eligible for a 504 (ie bee sting allergy, peanut allergy, concussions, ADHD, mental health, long term medical issues etc). This also Is regardless of students performance in school. IEP #8217;s are for students who have a disability (autism, sensory-blind deaf, developmental delay, learning disability, communication, social emotional, health etc) and due to the disability they are unable to access the curriculum (evidenced by failing grades, behavioral issues, poor scores on standardized tests etc) 504 is federal and can be enforced at college and at work, as well as school. IEP #8217;s have to be enforced in any public school pk-12 (USA)- but do not have to be enforced beyond that. I #8217;m a school psychologist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 13:55:27</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Many students have both. This is not true. The only time a student would need both would be if a student is on an IEP for a learning disability (for example) and they get a concussion, and the educational team decides it doesn #8217;t make sense to put the support for the concussion in the IEP since it should (hopefully) be short term, so they would create a 504 to support the student while they recover from the concussion. If for some reason the student didn #8217;t recover from the concussion and had lasting effects, then the team would most likely incorporate the concussion into the IEP and dissolve the 504. I understand your confusion because some districts prefer to have students on IEPs and 504 #8217;s- we had an educational lawyer come to our school to present on IEP and 504 and she was very clear that 99% of the time you would not need a student to be on both.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stood up for myself!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 13:38:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last night my husband and I were at a concert. We got pretty cheap $20 lawn seats. About 20 minutes into the first set, a venue employee approached us and asked if we #8217;d like to have a free upgrade. We said sure, and moved from the lawn into almost the floor. It was really cool! We sat down in our seats and suddenly someone is tapping my shoulder. I turn around and an older man is looking at me angrily.  #8220;Are these really your seats? #8221; I said yes, and he said  #8220;really? Well where have you been? Why would you show up almost 2 hours late. #8221; (Now, a few things. It  #8220;started #8221; at 7, but the main bands didn #8217;t go on until 8, and it was 8:30, not 9. Additionally, my mom had trained me growing up to never stand up for myself and always to apologize even if I wasn #8217;t in the wrong. I have to fight this part of my upbringing everyday. ) Instead of apologizing for inconveniencing him, I looked him right in the eyes and said  #8220;I wasn #8217;t aware you and I had an appointment. #8221; He did not like that, ended up moving to several more seats, was blocked by a speaker and eventually left. It felt so good to stand up for myself, even though I know in the grand scheme of things it wasn #8217;t that big of a deal. I just wanted to share with you all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 14:43:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was Live and Counting Crows lol. I think because it was a week night and 2 90 #8217;s bands it wasn #8217;t very well attended.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 14:43:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 14:58:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow!! Thank you! I did not think this story would get these responses! Thank you so much this really means a lot!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 15:19:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hartford!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 15:54:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>