<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject9318</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-01 20:36:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow is my only reaction</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-05 23:10:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cant wait! SNSD never disappoints!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-07 07:20:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>holy shit this is awesome!  #8230;especially when you're high</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-27 02:18:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>WOW Yuri never fails to make ANYONE's jaw drop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-20 06:25:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>damn my Yul never fails to amaze  lt;3 she never lost her hot bod \/ \/ \/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-07 07:45:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>gee gee gee gee baby baby baby</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-13 05:13:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>i generally prefer burnettes but DAMN, Yoona can rock it i say blonde for Yoona</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-19 01:18:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>My new life goal is to marry Kwon Yuri hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-18 07:51:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Enter sandman- Metallica lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 08:10:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>i fucking love this album</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 00:08:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>for me its gotta be Nayeon  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 00:26:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im in that same spot bro i will shoot up anything that will fit in a needle i just had a relapse yesterday and am feeling not only the ill effects off the comedown but the intense obsession of the ritual of injection kills me inside trying to get into rehab (again) and try to address these compulsions, but unfortunately despite all my ideas on getting clean, im truly clueless that however doesnt mean were hopeless, that just suggests to me to follow the guidance of those who have recovered</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 00:37:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>dude im also addicted to IV Heroin, Cocaine, Meth, and all of the above started when i was 17 and i was the only one who slammed in my school(not to sound prideful but just to relate to you) and everyone else smokes or snorts around me as well but back to addiction, i understand the needle fixation is just as strong as the dope itself im struggling to commit myself to recovery, but trying to enter rehab (again) im not the guy to ask about how to get clean, but what i can say is follow the suggestions of those who have succeeded in recovery and no half measures</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 02:23:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>brilliant</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 05:23:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>love this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 22:45:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>i like rusty spoons</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 01:59:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>absolutely beautiful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Candy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 03:04:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 06:16:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I think everyone is artistic and creative in some way especially considering how much we were as kids. But I appreciate it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 06:16:54</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128514; #128514; #128514;You me and everyone else</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 06:17:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks bro. No I actually was just smoking weed and sober during my time drawing it. Not to say it hasnt been a defining role in my life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 06:18:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you i appreciate it! You can too im sure I think we all can</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lady Fent</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 19:57:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 22:12:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. The reason why i use a poppy is because its iconic and recognized. It represents all opiates/opioids. Plus it compliments the drawing more than lets say if i used a molecule of fent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 22:18:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea i feel it haha thanks for the feedback</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 23:39:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>i found god alright</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 23:44:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>bro (i call everyone that so dont be offended) i deal with that all the fucking time, i cant stand going another minute without cutting or getting high. I can relate to your feelings, especially since suicide is out of the question(at least now). i hold on to the hope that i can turn my life around, but it aint gonna happen as long as im fucked up. Cos i believe (at least for me) that no one actually wants to die, but seek a way out of pain. As kids we grew up with hopes, dreams, and optimism. Hold on to that bro. We gotta take baby steps to improve ourselves, but gotta put the footwork in. GOD(Good Orderly Direction) bless you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>