<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject1524</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 05:21:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Zookeeper here, this is a black footed cat kitten but adult males weigh less than 5lbs and females less than 3lbs so indeed the smallest cat species!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Zookeeper here, first time poster, too! Thought our new Sable Antelope calf would be well received here :)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:51:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:09:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! We're all obsessed with him hahaa</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:12:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no the one in the top middle looks so cross eyed. What a good pup  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:17:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's such a good one for sure. Hippotragus all have heart shaped noses  #128525;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:21:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! We're unique in having over 400 acres to give our animals ample room to roam!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:27:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>All zookeepers have a million pictures of their animals, just not many of them are allowed to publish their photos! Rules vary from facility to facility!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:33:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hippotragus all have heart noses  #128525; they're all so cute!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:53:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't know they would be so well received in this subreddit, I might have to!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:03:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yay hoofstock keepers! We're super lucky to have the climate for many African hoofstock species. We have Roan and Sable along with tons of other antelope in mixed species enclosures. What's your favorite hoofstock animal??  #128513;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm apparently going to have to! I'm so glad he's been so popular since I've posted him  #128522; I'll tell him he's famous tomorrow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:08:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahhh! Tapir are my favorite! Specifically Brazilians (South Americans)! I've worked with giraffes and rhinos the whole of my 4 years in zookeeping and they are amazing! Do you work with okapi? So jealous if you do! That's a dream animal for me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:18:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agh! I'm so jealous! What a wonderful time to be expecting for such an amazing species! Are both of your females adults or has your male been a great breeder?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:22:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>They grow up to be "lion killers" ;) pretty hard to manage when adults, take it from me hahaa</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:37:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's amazing but a very hard field to break into. Most places are requiring a 4 year life sciences degree or equivalent experience with exotics. I've been in the field for 4 years and I've loved every second of it but worked so so hard to break in when I was an intern! I'm a lucky woman to be where I am in my career so early in life for sure! It's also lots of back breaking labor, being on your feet for 10 hours a day, and interacting with guests a ton. All part of the job!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:55:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ugh the perfect pairing story for sure! Hopefully all goes well for the first time mom and she bonds right away!!! I have my fingers crossed for you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:16:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not yet, still deciding! All the keepers who work with them get to have a discussion on what to name them. The Sable herd's naming theme is poisonous plants  #128513;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:20:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Almost 2 weeks old now!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:23:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don't always have to have the schooling. Experience is almost as good if not better than education but to break into most facilities you almost have to intern to get the exotic experience which is such a bummer since most are unpaid. If you're able to, look into intern/externships or volunteer work at your local zoo/wildlife park, that on your resume will definitely help</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:34:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>For externships you don't have to be a student. Maybe reach out to the facilities and see if they have programs for people who aren't students, its surprising how many places have those programs but don't advertise them. Even volunteering at facilities is good experience and way to get a foot in the door. It might not be hands on with animals but it's a way to build your credibility. Just be careful to not ask keepers too much about jobs or animal experiences, it's one of the fastest way to get people to write you off. The best thing to do is to keep your head down and do great work. People will notice, I promise!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:48:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahahaa, it kind of looks like it huh? It's just a dead leaf  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:49:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe! My phone has been blowing up from just this post so I might wait a while in between pictures hahaa  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:57:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not to worry, his mama is a very attentive and good mom  #128513;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:01:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I'm a little worried about that hahaa. I'll have to turn off notifications for a minute! Surprised about the amount of negative responses I've gotten but I guess that's just the internet  #129335; #8205; #9792; #65039; can't please everyone!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:03:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll suggest it to the group! I like that name!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:07:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a dead leaf!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:16:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely! I always love talking about my animals  #128513; thank you for asking!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:21:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aren't they such a cool species? They're still sexually dimorphic, the males being much darker than the females (black v. chocolate brown). Their horns (and attitudes!) are what earns them their nickname of "lion killers" since they are curved towards the back of their head and are in a perfect position to spear a predator trying to come down on their neck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:22:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please go ahead!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:24:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a ton of hard work (hauling shit, hay, and grain all day in every type of weather imaginable) but it's so rewarding. Getting to work with these amazing animals is the highlight of my life. I have a degree in ecology and biodiversity and I interned for a while at my first facility which turned into my first keeping job. Now I'm 4 years into my career and couldn't be happier! If you have more specific questions feel free to PM me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:25:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish I could pat/scritch him! His mama wouldn't be too pleased with me hahaa. But I will tell him he is so loved  #128525;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:44:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ugh, I'm so sad about the different policies at different places. I wanna see everyone's cuties! I really like roan kids but sable have a special place in my heart  #128525;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:47:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please feel free to PM me!  #128513; I'm headed to sleep soon but I'll get back to you soon!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:51:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>At my current facility we have regular hours (ish, depending on if days go long or something) I start at 8 and end between 4:30 and 6 most days. But lots of other zoos have overnight shifts and multiple day shifts. Depends on the facility! Obviously if there was an emergency we'd be called in no matter what time!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:52:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I promise he is not sad! Sable antelope are "stashers" when they are young calves. He's just trying to be as still and inconspicuous as possible!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:53:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yayyy! I was worried I wasn't going to find any keepers on here! What species do you work with?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:55:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are born this russet red color for camouflage since they stash as calves and turn darker as they age! When they hit sexual maturity they will range from chocolate brown (females) to black (males)  #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:58:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>All zoos in the United States of America are monitored by the USDA for the size of enclosures they give to their animals. So every animal in the U.S.A is given ample room depending on their species!  #128513;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 08:10:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a dead leaf!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 08:22:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 08:33:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hoof trims aren't super common for antelope but some facilities train their animals to receive voluntary trims!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 08:49:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its just my phone camera hahaa. I have a Samsung galaxy s7</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 09:20:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yay keeper friends! Thank YOU for all that you do! I'm assuming from your username you work with cetaceans??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 09:24:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Their calves kind of look similar but I can assure you this is a Sable Antelope! They are part of the collection I care for as a zookeeper</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 09:29:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pronghorn are so cool, too. I hope I can have the privilege to see or even maybe work with them one day!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 09:46:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! He was just at the perfect angle where I could get a good shot, I'm definitely not a photographer by any means hahaa</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 09:51:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still a good combo of species! My internship was solely with parrots and corvids but for the last 4 years I've worked with large hoofstock and carnivores!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>