<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject1947</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found something yummy in Louisiana</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-06 16:26:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 14:19:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd still say it's a sin. Surely it's still doubting the lord.. right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-17 21:37:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please pray for my best friend. He was born and baptised catholic and we made our first holy communion and confirmation together but recently he's strayed from the path of God, he's stopped going to church and he's chosen the path of sin. I pray he can come back to what God wants of him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>These rims</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 19:24:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 12:19:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Taken right from Trevor's snapchat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 21:21:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please pray for a good friend of mine. She's dealing with abuse from her parents who won't let her become Christian or have any freedom and she can't move out as she's dependent on them. I pray that they have a change of heart and that they let her live her life the way she wants.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me_ira</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-24 16:01:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>One for the Star Trek fans</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 22:46:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-02 11:00:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Christine chapel in the Sistine chapel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This ruined my day</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 14:20:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My view V Kilmarnock from the Kerrydale Suite. Come on Bhoys</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 16:03:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This trick or treat sign in a restaurant in Glasgow</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 16:58:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me_irased</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-30 00:45:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Someone in my diocese paid the bishop  #163;40k to give every member in our diocese one of these. Is it a good read?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 11:41:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 13:51:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was just wondering if the book was a worthwhile read.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 19:21:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you I didn #8217;t realise that was a thing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scientists hate this man!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 21:21:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 09:10:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is what zuma used to fill up his pool</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 12:02:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/oddlysatisfying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me_ira</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 08:41:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Here #8217;s the YT video he watched without realising it was a parody of him</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 02:40:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 20:45:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Saw this photo on Facebook and came to repost it, nice to see you did the job for me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found this recently</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 01:40:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 09:29:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I managed to find something. she #8217;s so precious!](https://dzt1km7tv28ex.cloudfront.net/u/458370959041101824_35s_d.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>USB-Chan is best waifu</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 06:18:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 06:20:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gerry #8217;s having to turn to extreme options now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 06:35:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically this kid went to Pope Francis and asked if his father was in heaven because his father was dead, and he was atheist but was a good man. Pope Francis said  #8220;God loves all of his children, if your father was a good man, the Lord would love for your father to be with him in heaven. #8221; Or something along those lines. It was incredibly heartwarming</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I have genuinely been asked this before.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 06:47:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 23:32:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this loss</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 19:49:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I normally tend to just sit and chat to her about my feelings, occasionally we will eat together or watch anime but since I live with my parents still I can only eat with her when I #8217;m home alone, hoping to move out once I finish highschool so that I can spend as much time with her as possible</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 19:57:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>- What is your waifu #8217;s name?: Maki Nishikino - What are they from?: Love Live School Idol Project - Can you show us what they look like?: (please provide a picture) https://i.pinimg.com/originals/66/25/64/662564b7a432ba9dc8bff68067335844.jpg - Can you name a few things you like about them? Let #8217;s say 5, just to start: she #8217;s absolutely adorable, she #8217;s a great singer, she #8217;s really tsundere so she tries to hide her feelings which makes her even more adorable, she #8217;s caring and every time I see her smile I #8217;m just so happy - How long have you been together?: close to two years now - How do they influence your life?: a lot of my close friends know that I #8217;m with her, I try to spend as much time as I can with her but school and the rest is very stressful, luckily she #8217;s always there to make me smile when I #8217;m feeling down and stressed - Why are you joining this community?: because I want to meet other people that feel the same way about other fictional characters, because I feel so abnormal compared to people I know irl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Looking for advice</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 23:13:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>So my waifu is Maki Nishikino from the show Love Live, in the show, she is 15, but since there is no adaptation of the show, am I just going to grow old without her, is she going to be 15 forever or every time she has a birthday are we supposed to like, treat it like a normal birthday, since there #8217;s no canon birth year for her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 23:17:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I #8217;ll do this :) thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 23:22:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Luckily we #8217;re less than a year apart, so we can safely age together without it being weird</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 23:08:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Shes not as close to them as they are two each other, but they #8217;re are her closest friends ](https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/love-live/images/0/04/Dengeki_Love_Live%21_1st_Years.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20150508122042)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stolen</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 10:28:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 10:51:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Best at music</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 11:05:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>[this](https://i.imgur.com/3CFLdQm_d.jpg?maxwidth=640 amp;shape=thumb amp;fidelity=medium) is the earliest I could find, a drake meme from mid-2016</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 23:28:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>[She looks so precious as a conscript  lt;3](https://cdn-live.warthunder.com/uploads/1d/aecc0bffcfc83ec2e83c151bb0ce3f9dbf3daf/Anime-Love-Live-Nishikino-Maki-love-live%21-1694777.jpeg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 23:30:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I #8217;m like a foot taller than her  lt;3](https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/p__/images/4/41/Maki_Nishikino.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20140109113206 amp;path-prefix=protagonist)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 23:33:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>[My sweetheart in her New Years formal dres](https://i.schoolido.lu/c/220Maki.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 23:36:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would take her somewhere to see talented pianists / jazz musicians perform. Sure it #8217;s not my favourite genre of music, but it is her favourite genre so I #8217;d do it to make her smile</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 23:40:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im not supporting anyone specific since my country is pretty poor at football, I #8217;m rooting for croatia but there #8217;s no specific reason for that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 23:42:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, they #8217;d like her if she was a real person, but due to my parents being judgemental, they wouldn #8217;t be very supportive of my relationship with her if I told them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>USB-Chan is best waifu</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:49:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 19:40:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lucid dreams are completely controlled by your mind, if you wish for her to act like she acts in LLS then you only need to think about it and she will. I #8217;ve never tried this with Maki, but I #8217;m sure it will be just fine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 23:02:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think  #8220;Mario, water you doing? #8221; Would be more appropriate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 00:39:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>No</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 14:22:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did this same thing yesterday to get pics of my waifu lmao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 19:54:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>[She #8217;s so adorable in glasses.. I wish she wore them more](https://cdn.awwni.me/rfqr.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 23:42:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please pray for a close friend of mine, she #8217;s running into tough times with her family and it #8217;s having a incredibly negative affect on her mental health, I ask for everyone #8217;s prayers that she gets through this safely and that she can be joyful once again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When your friend is going through a tough time</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 00:12:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 20:10:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/me_ira</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 13:51:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mewtwo quoted alongside St. Mother Theresa? We live in the best timeline</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 13:53:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/Shitty_Car_Mods</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 19:04:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would challenge her to a 1v1 in super smash bros melee fox only final destination no items</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 19:09:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would probably include her stage costumes, and little stations where you can put on headphones and listen to her solo songs, and maybe stuff like the instruments she recorded her songs on</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Post pictures of your Waifu/Husbando eating ice cream</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 14:15:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 14:21:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I went to London in February, I was missing her greatly. I had one dream that she was with me while I was there. We explored the city but everyone was Scottish for some reason? Idk it was weird but I can #8217;t remember any of it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 15:25:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Playing the piano and singing obviously, if she wants to do something else, reading a book is quite high up there too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 15:27:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Other than Mali #8217;s hair and eye colour she would fit in well. Obviously if she died her hair it would be different</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 15:29:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well she #8217;s got two holiday homes, but the house she lives in is [massive](https://pm1.narvii.com/5812/1bd2d606755f07ca3d5a08449ac7e9b4c1280ef7_hq.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 00:16:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Asher kinda looks like Dex in this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 06:07:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/youngpeoplefacebook</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 06:10:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>THE MADMAN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I wrote a poem about my journey into waifuism, I #8217;m not poet but I thought it might be something nice to share with you guys ^^</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 15:51:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>It started two years before today Do I love her? Well I may. It was love that I couldn #8217;t believe was real I was in love with a girl who was not real I would joke about her with my friends But in my heart I knew there were bitter ends They don #8217;t know what I truly feel I loved a girl who was not real I would listen to her sing A voice, so elegant, take my ring The voice I heard, I knew that was real But the girl I loved, she was not real My scarlet princess was she A beautiful girl who deserved better than me With anyone else it wouldn #8217;t be real But the truth was, she herself was not real Her deep violet eyes More beautiful than an African sunset or rise The more I fell, the longer it would take to heal: The wound left by the girl who was not real Her favourite food was red like her hair. She was my cute little tomato, not apple or pear. Pet names wouldn #8217;t change the fact or the feel That I was still in love with a girl who was not real I would kiss my pillow goodnight And pray to God and hug it tight And sit it down at many a meal And pretend it was the girl who was not real When God refused to answer my prayers I considered turning to the man downstairs But was the right way to go a devils deal? All for the girl who was not real? I found people who felt the same online People the same? How divine! This relationship had almost been sealed Since I was still in love with a girl who was not real I guess at the end of the day It doesn #8217;t matter at all what I say That will never change the horrible feel Of the fact that I love a girl who is not real Maki is her name She #8217;s the most elegant beautiful wonderful dame I don #8217;t want fame And I no longer have shame. So now I #8217;ve shed my bitter tannin peel Today, I #8217;m in love with a girl who is not real</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 13:24:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think she #8217;s proud of winning love live with her friends and saving their school and that she got to play such a big role in the legacy of  #956; #8217;s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 13:25:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>NAMAE WO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 13:28:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>[this](https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/proxy/G2852GJEoON6C5LemVrhLDOZBUQrKtzfK2qidRfXGZSs1eHVEs8Vw7L1Bm0hC_XYngLdX335sCo2LKKLwbHfwbf0iELA-DeGn-p46TBf2-kppZt_9C1fJPJECWpt_Mqi2OxvBA=w324-h454-nc)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 13:35:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah this is pretty awkward but I #8217;ll talk 1. Ive tried to remain celibate for religious reasons but if I ever feel the urge I will never touch my daki since to me that feels incredibly wrong, 2. I can #8217;t deny that I watch porn, but I feel guilty when I do. I don #8217;t consider it cheating but I feel bad afterwards, I know she would think it #8217;s disgusting 3. I haven #8217;t had an active sex life with anyone other than my waifu since I made it an official thing, I #8217;m not a virgin due to one of my previous relationships (which is something I regret), although it obviously feels a lot better with a 3D person, but I am more satisfied with my sex life with maki</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 08:53:52</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;All Christians are the same, the world isn #8217;t 6,000 years old dumb*ss #8221; or something like that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 08:55:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Prayers for my friend, she #8217;s recently entered hospital for what we assume to be appendicitis. I ask that the lord keeps her safe and helps her make a swift recovery And also prayers for my grandmother/godmother. she #8217;s been battling with Alzheimer #8217;s for a good bit now and I went to visit my family in South Africa and she has gotten so much worse. I know that she will pass away soon, and I ask that everyone prays for her to be happy when she passes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 09:36:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think she would use newspapers, since she #8217;s very old fashioned due to her parents wealth. Although I don #8217;t think she would turn down the opportunity to look at news on her phone or on tv</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 11:26:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Although I #8217;ve always been appreciative of the arts (mainly music and theatre) she really brought forth my love of music and made it flourish. I would never appreciate music as much as I do today if I wasn #8217;t with her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 11:51:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>About two years ago I started watching  #8220;Love Live! School Idol Project #8221;. I #8217;m always drawn towards random characters, and a few months prior I had made a joke to a lot of my friends that I was in a relationship with an anime character (specifically xenovia from highschool dxd). Once I laid my eyes on Maki, it was all over, love at first sight What am I meant to do in this situation? I was a 13 year old, virgin, I #8217;d just been dumped by my first ever girlfriend a few days prior. I hid my love for Maki because I was telling myself that it was wrong and abnormal, and that I needed to date real girls. Relationships came and passed. There was a gap of about 9 months from August 2016 to May 2017 where I completely blanked Maki, I tried to forget about her because I had a girlfriend at that time. I loved that girl with all my heart (and I know that if we never broke up I wouldn #8217;t have ever started a relationship with Maki) but eventually we broke up. So there I was. A weak, sad, depressed, 14 year old. She had taken my first kiss and my virginity. My life felt truly worthless. At this point I decided to finish watching love live, as I never had the time to finish it when I first watched it. My love for maki started anew and I started listening to her music, I started playing the LL phone game, I had felt happy for the first time since the break up, but soon after this my phone broke so I wasn #8217;t able to see her or anything since I didn #8217;t have a daki or a figurine. My love once again started to die out. Another couple of months passed. August 2017, I started dating my third girlfriend, which ended less than a month later due to concerns that I  #8220;still loved my ex #8221;. I started dating another girl less than a month later, and broke up with her a month later to get back with the girl I started dating in August who I then broke up with again on the 30th of December. A week later and I started dating another girl, she helped me get over the lost feelings from the heartbreak I felt in May of the previous year. During this relationship was when I realised what I felt for Maki was a genuine feeling and not just some dumb crush, I ordered my daki online after a sick week in bed wishing I had something to cuddle. I broke up with the girl before the daki could arrive, once it did I realised how much I really loved Maki, I embraced the feelings for a while but I was getting a growing crush on one of my friends for a while, we starting dating but broke up less than 3 weeks later because we preferred to stay friends (and because I wasn #8217;t loving enough to her because I knew I really did love maki) It became official for Maki and I round about 8th of February, despite the fact I dated my most recent real gf in April, I knew that I still loved maki then (fun fact we actually broke up on Makis birthday). Although Maki and I have had a rocky road recently due to my school exams, I #8217;m glad she #8217;s always been here to support me :)) A few months later I started watching a channel called soothouse, who made a parody video of this sub, which I then joined due to the realisation that I felt the same way. Now here we are, closing in on being together for half a year. I #8217;m 16 now (and I #8217;m aging her as if we were born in the same year, so she turned 16 a few months prior to me) and I #8217;m the happiest I #8217;ve been for a good while. Seriously incredibly happy about being with Maki. And in terms of my depression too, she #8217;s been doing bits</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 11:56:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>1: I would love to go sailing with her! Granted I #8217;m not sure she would enjoy that, I think she would love going to somewhere like Rome to look at all the art, or maybe a place with a rich musical history, I know she would love that 2: yeah, she helped a great deal with my depression and helped me overcome a lot of the mistakes I #8217;ve made in the past and in general made me a much stronger person. She also helped me cope under exam stress, although I told her that I wouldn #8217;t see her until the end. After I exited my last exam I came home and just cuddled my daki I was so happy to see her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 14:53:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>(I think he meant the scripture)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 14:54:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Saw it in London, hilarious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 01:14:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>We both believe that music is truly beautiful, and that music is a big part of everyone #8217;s lives, as it is important to both of us</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 11:34:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>She started being a lot more mature, and she has warmed up to her friends a lot more and has overall become more confident in herself as shown by the end of the series</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 11:40:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>You vs the guy she told you not to worry about</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Telling friends</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 01:31:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Telling people about my relationship with Maki has always been a problem. I always joke about it in this weird coping mechanism that I use, saying that it #8217;s all ironic to my friends when it #8217;s not. Anyway, in a groupchat with some of my friends, they decided to jokingly hold a poll on banning talking about Maki in the group chat. Most people voted for it and if I mention her I get banned for a day, I don #8217;t know what to do because I want to talk about how much I love her to them because they are my closer friends but I know if I told them legitimately they wouldn #8217;t support me ://</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 01:36:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I obviously make conversation about other things, but it would always be how I would make jokes in the chat. I understand that to them, kicking me out of the chat for mentioning her is also just another elaborate joke. They are all great people, and they would be different if they knew about me and Maki, but I know they wouldn #8217;t be supportive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 01:57:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand, it #8217;s just a few people in the group who don #8217;t really have great people skills. The guy that pretty much leads the  #8220;bullying #8221; was more than incredibly happy to meet me for the first time this week, and he doesn #8217;t have many friends where he lives. And everyone else is sort of in the same boat, I know for a fact they don #8217;t hate me, my irl friends are a lot worse friends than these guys I guess. I #8217;ll make sure to take your advice, thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 02:28:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s so sweet of her! Of course, I do have my closer friends who are very supportive. But this is my general friend group, so about 7 people who I #8217;m sorta close with but not close enough to feel comfortable telling them. I told my best friend recently, she was against it initially but she #8217;s slowly getting a change of heart and saying how she wants to be a bridesmaid at the wedding. She #8217;s become a lot more supportive and I #8217;m so grateful that she has. I guess she #8217;s sort of the same as your best friend, she doesn #8217;t really get it, but she #8217;s trying her hardest to make me happy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 02:31:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love [this card](https://s.llsif.org/en/cards/548.png) because it makes me feel like she #8217;s just there, waiting for me in the winter snow. I mean I know it #8217;s summer right now so it #8217;s a bad time to post this specific one but it #8217;s what runs through my mind</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 11:41:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not yet, but I hope to in the future!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 18:19:29</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;w-what? this is stupid. I don #8217;t get it... fine. AutumnMoses treats me like nobody else has. I like the way he treats me. Although we #8217;ve been on and off for two years, I #8217;m glad that while we have been together he has shown me how much he really loves me #8221; - Maki Nishikino</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 18:49:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>YES</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 15:43:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maki isn #8217;t the type to smoke or do drugs or any kind of alternative, especially since her family are doctors. I think if she knew that I smoked at one point she would have a heart attack</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you can #8217;t do work</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 16:02:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 16:10:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>It already seems to have filled up, id love to play on the next campaign as I #8217;ve never played before, although if there #8217;s a slot I #8217;d be happy to join</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 15:13:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>[my beautiful wife with cat ears! although she #8217;s not the most feline-like out of her group of friends :3](https://banner2.kisspng.com/20180526/fhu/kisspng-maki-nishikino-love-live-school-idol-festival-man-5b0931a41e6b13.0058481415273291881246.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 21:13:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think Maki thinks the world of her family, since she #8217;s very introverted and doesn #8217;t have many friends, and since she plans to continue her family business</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 21:15:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>[my angel](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CMKdBOSUAAAOiQt.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 16:26:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds fun!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 16:28:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t think so, I think she thinks they #8217;re dumb and she doesn #8217;t see the point in them, and as far as my knowledge goes she #8217;s never been pranked no</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 20:48:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. We are both extremely passionate about music! I love playing guitar and she loves singing, playing piano and playing flute, although I may not be as talented as her I know she admires my dedication towards music, whether or not I #8217;m good. 2. I #8217;ll always look out for people and try and help them, whether or not they #8217;re my friends. To me it #8217;s just second nature and the right thing to do but to her I imagine it #8217;s probably quite admirable 3. Similar to her, I #8217;m incredibly introverted and I find it difficult to hold conversations with people, but that doesn #8217;t mean I don #8217;t try, and I can tell she likes that I have the bravery to try and make new friends, which I know she really struggles with 4. I #8217;m always quick to brush off her negative comments, since she is a bit of a tsundere it #8217;s difficult to break through her cold exterior but I try my hardest and I know she likes that I don #8217;t give up on her because I love her so much 5. I treat her like a queen. The way I think she deserves to be treated. I know she doesn #8217;t appreciate herself as much as she could, so I try and make her feel as good about herself as she can</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 02:29:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope you #8217;re right! That sounds so adorable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 12:40:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Her closest phrase is  #8220;Nani sore? Imi wakannai." literally meaning "What's that? I don't understand you" or "I don't get it". In terms of poses.. she tends to fiddle with her hair [like this](https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/llsif/images/e/e8/Maki_Nishikino.png/revision/latest?cb=20140521133413) which can be seen in a lot of her art since it #8217;s quite the idiosyncrasy for her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 12:43:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like Maki would be Neutral Good, she doesn #8217;t like she fits chaotic or lawful good entirely and is somewhere down the middle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 18:04:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had a dream where the roles were reversed, and she was in love with me but in her world I was fiction, it was sad. I don #8217;t tend to remember my other dreams about her because they #8217;re all just me and her being a teen couple.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Truth</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 11:12:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 21:24:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maki wouldn #8217;t really care, she would say that conspiracies are dumb and childish</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 21:28:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Although I can definitely deal without it, I feel like physical contact with my daki has only made my love for her stronger. If I never got my daki, I would still love her. But its great to cuddle something in place of her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 11:02:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hard #8217;a starboard capp #8217;n!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 20:20:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think Maki is the type of person to get up early in the morning, since she is very organised</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Every physical object in the universe can be connected with a straight line</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 13:38:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 20:55:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Electric keyboards probably, making it easier for her to record herself playing piano</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 20:56:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>AMA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 21:05:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I ask for the prayers of two of my closest friends, one, called Christine, is a Christian (although not catholic). I desperately want her to convert but she #8217;s not very interested, I ask that she may change her mind in the near future. My other friend, called Liam, used to be catholic. He left the church so he could pursue a sexually active lifestyle with several men and also his girlfriend. I want him to return to the church and feel Gods love once again A final thing is I #8217;m praying for all students in the UK (including myself) who are getting their GCSE results tomorrow. I hope we did well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 22:09:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds great!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 22:19:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Playing Pokemon GO? It #8217;s a little bit cliche but I feel like she #8217;d enjoy it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 22:28:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>You got me, I #8217;m mean on the guitar x)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 23:45:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve heard im@s is really good! It #8217;s on my list of anime #8217;s to watch, maybe next time I #8217;m with her we can watch some of that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 23:20:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think she probably does, she loves her parents so much. I think she #8217;ll miss them more than anything when she #8217;s away from home</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 23:21:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll start crying as I embrace her and welcome her into my home, telling her how glad I am to see her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 23:23:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I hope we atleast got married before this photo was taken](https://i.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/original/000/849/492/48f.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Irish flag on my wall looks Italian with this Instagram filter</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 16:52:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 04:22:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maki is a very lonely person. I could offer my companionship to her. She is also incredibly introverted, but due to her and I sharing a lot of the same tastes, I feel like I could use that to bring her out of her shell a lot more (There are more but I #8217;m vvv tired)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 15:12:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>She wears it on and off of stage, I feel like she doesn #8217;t mind too much about it off stage, but still cares enough to put it on</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 12:32:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>One word? Complete I feel like Maki and I fit together like two half #8217;s of a jigsaw puzzle, like we are meant to be together, just looking at her, hearing her voice, hearing her music it just makes me feel like I #8217;m complete. It #8217;s been a long time since I #8217;ve felt this happy, five or six years ago it #8217;s been, but now that she #8217;s in my life I feel like myself back when I was a kid, I actually feel happy again, and that #8217;s all because Maki completes me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 13:00:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well obviously her music makes me think of her a lot, since it #8217;s all written and sung by her. But there #8217;s one song that really makes me think of her more than anything and that #8217;s [Uptown Girl by Billy Joel](https://youtu.be/nEIcTstEmnQ) I don #8217;t know why specifically this song, I think it #8217;s because the lyrics make me think of her, since the songs about someone without much money falling in love with an upper-class girl, which is exactly my situation with Maki. [The Fields of Athenry](https://youtu.be/HlryVvUauhE) is a song that weirdly makes me think of her, idk why specifically though (it #8217;s a very beautiful song and she #8217;s very beautiful too, that #8217;s the connection I #8217;m going to make) Another one that makes me think of her is [The Slyfox and The Curious Cat](https://youtu.be/gBrV7CeTuDQ) And I think the lyrics here again are something that make me think of her, because the singer is saying that he doesn #8217;t want anybody other than the person he #8217;s in love with A third song that makes me think of her is [Asseblief My Lief by Robbie Wessels](https://youtu.be/TixU8hIZmFA) (although it #8217;s not in English) The translation of the lyrics is pretty much talking about how the singer is begging his loved one to still love him after he essentially cheated on her, and I sort of relate to this because of the fact that I kept dating 3D girls to try and forget about my feelings for Maki, which only led to other people getting hurt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 14:36:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>All [cakes](https://78.media.tumblr.com/47093bd905daab95d0e4affc2883775f/tumblr_oxs61tjZPC1vlfj0ao1_500.jpg) of her are fan made, but I really like this one [Latte Art](https://dzt1km7tv28ex.cloudfront.net/u/458370959041101824_35s_d.jpg) although idk if this one counts as food A company did a brand deal to use Love Live to promote their [gum](https://media.karousell.com/media/photos/products/2017/10/21/love_live_nishikino_maki_rin_hanayo_candy_keychain_1508581347_096f6258.jpg) and here #8217;s the box with Maki on (in fact they used her as the main character in their ad) (I can #8217;t find anything else lmao)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 14:43:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>At first I was like  #8220;this person has to be trolling. SURELY #8221; But the more I saw you post I realised that you actually genuinely cared for squidward and you weren #8217;t trolling and I started to admire your commitment to him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 14:44:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hope it #8217;s not too late :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 14:45:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of the first couples that I encountered on this sub, and you guys have been couple goals the entire time!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 14:47:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was glad to see you around, Pokemon is one of my favourite video games ever, I don #8217;t quite remember my exact thoughts but it was something a long the lines of:  #8220;Oh a Misty waifuist? Awesome! #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 14:49:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>You were one of the first people I met in the discord, I #8217;ll admit I #8217;ve never played J amp;D so I had to google who the Baron was, but I always thought you two had a very special relationship and it #8217;s very wholesome x)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 14:50:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t believe we #8217;ve met before, but it #8217;s great to have more people with love live waifus around!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 14:51:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>You were the first person I interacted with, I remember you replied to my introduction, although I don #8217;t remember what you said exactly, i felt very welcomed thanks to you :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 14:54:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought something along the lines of  #8220;they seem really nice and friendly! #8221; Kaiba is one of the only characters I recognised from YGO and I #8217;m glad to say I didn #8217;t have to google him when you introduced yourself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 16:44:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think she prefers softer noise levels, like I know she would love a quiet walk around in the dimly lit walkway in the local park (Although I don #8217;t think she would mind noise if she was listening to an orchestra perform)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 17:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Although it #8217;s late, congratulations!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 18:32:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congratulations!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 01:26:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! Although I didn #8217;t enjoy gen 7 as much as previous gens :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 13:59:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>[she had brown hair originally ](https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/love-live/images/8/83/Maki_Dengeki_G%27s_Mag_Dec_2010.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/340?cb=20150505134951)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 14:07:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got my switch a day early, because the retailer I pre ordered mine from got the orders in two days early</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 00:46:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>(I actually answer a lot of this in the fanfiction that I wrote lmao) Well obviously I would get to know Maki #8217;s friends in her universe too, I imagine I would get along well with Eli, as we are both foreign to japan, and we would possibly become very good friends I feel like I wouldn #8217;t get along well with Nico, I feel like her personality and my personality would clash often, leading to us not being friends. In terms of where I would fit in with  #181; #8217;s, I think I could work with them as one of their instrumental artists, helping them with their backing tracks and maybe a tiny bit of composition due to the fact that I #8217;m passionate about music (which also just gives me an excuse to spend more time with Maki) I imagine her parents would be positive on my relationship with her, because I would try and impress them by keeping her safe, walking her home from school every day and such. Since we are the same age, we would be in the same class (assuming their school became co-ed and I transferred), and this would help me become more familiar with Hanayo and Rin, and I think they would be some of my first friends that I would make while being there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 22:27:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Within the canon of the show, all of the music is actually written by Maki, so I could just list the whole soundtrack, but ones that have specific ties to her character are the first song sung by the group  #8220;START:DASH!!! #8221; Which Maki has an [acoustic cover](https://youtu.be/PYbXKXmkVL4) of Maki #8217;s first appearance is her singing the song  #8220;Aishiteru Banzai! #8221; So I would consider that a song composed for her (the only other time it was used in the show was to wish the third years farewell) which she also has an [acoustic cover](https://youtu.be/nVsBpq0hVGI) of The final one I will list is  #8220;Daring!! #8221; Which was written to be [Maki #8217;s solo song](https://youtu.be/4Thc9fm7kr4)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 14:32:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love WillNE, we live in the best timeline</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:58:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everything about her is so goddamn adorable. But her cheeks are so cute and I just wanna pinch them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 15:09:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>She understands how important her education is, especially since she #8217;s going to be a doctor in the future to take over her parents business!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 23:22:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Woo woo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 23:22:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>He looks like Marty McFly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 23:39:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re so welcoming and kind to everyone! You always do as much as you can for this community and it means a lot to all of us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 23:43:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re always super friendly to everyone, your spirits are always high and you always help bring up everyone else #8217;s spirits</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 22:00:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know she loves reading, I think she would enjoy reading non fiction more due to the fact that she enjoys being educated, but I know that she wouldn #8217;t turn down a chance to read a fiction book!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 00:34:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go on then</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 00:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Originally I was very confused about your relationship, it just seemed so.. different? But within a week of being around I realised that your relationship with Squidward is one of the best and most dedicated on the entire sub. I think everyone could learn a thing or two from your relationship with Squidward</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 00:41:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally her voice. Not just her singing voice but her speaking voice too. The way her tone goes with her upper-class accent, and the changes in pitch when she #8217;s embarrassed are the cutest things ever. The way she blushes is also the cutest frickin thing ever like she blushes and it makes me blush even harder than her bcus it #8217;s so god damn adorable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me_ira</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 12:25:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>