<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject3596</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 02:03:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>OMG this was actually beautiful. I just love how this story includes the concept of a sentient AI capable of adaption and the like... I'd love to know what happens next. ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:20:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>16personalities is a NERIS type explorer assessment, NOT a real MBTI one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:22:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course you can not marry an ENFP. Marriage is your choice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let me guess- she was a FiNE SiTe so you didn't stop her from talking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:23:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm mathematics seems to be failing you here a bit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:24:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>So INFJs are the sons of INTJs. Noted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:24:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fe don't feel me please.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:25:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're Fe because you have a will of Fe (iron).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:25:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>16Personalities does not incorporate Jungian cognitive functions and is not even an MBTI-based website.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:26:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Antago-nihilists.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:27:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like night mode. At night. When night mode is reasonable. Blue light causes insomnia? I don't know but if it does then night mode is for nighttime.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:27:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>You get NSFW.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:28:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>To make ENTPs love you, stop trying to be one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:29:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Gasps in horror.* utter heresy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:31:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hm, I believe this is an accurate reason for why INFJs are so rare.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:32:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone can be an artist if they dedicate themselves and love what they do. Personality aside.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:32:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>And my zodiac sign is INTP.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:33:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>How ironic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:33:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Creativity does not mark an intuitive for who they are. If you're an ISFP, so be it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:33:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am you...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:34:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you want to build your introverted feeling, listen to My Chemical Romance. It does it every time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:37:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, introverts are individuals who gather their energy from within.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:38:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you'd like to be an ESTP, be like Phineas Gage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:39:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excuse me... But I believe the INFJ genes are recessive. Find another INFJ. Or, perhaps your child will have a mutation. Miracles are real, folks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:41:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm half certain butthurt Kim Jong-Un is an Fi dom himself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:43:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Poor ISFP. Those kittens deserved better...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:43:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I take great satisfaction in reading this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 12:21:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course it is easier to type on the internet. We have keyboards.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 06:24:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think that 'type' is the only way to identify strengths and weaknesses. Potentially it might even cause someone to backtrack their development as a human. Take interest in typology for the sake of interest, not because it'll be life-changing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 06:24:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sure they'd accept it with open arms.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 06:25:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good job you two for undermining the Original Poster's entire argument.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 06:27:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>My my, going out of your way to pursue an ultimately meaningless thread? Definitely the best way to spend one's time. I admit I'm a hypocrite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 06:27:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 06:28:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Obsession is inevitable?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 08:09:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m so sorry to learn of your loss. However, I must beg of you, do not fret. Thought you cannot beat the MBTI out of your son- you CAN beat your son out of MBTI. Prove to him in a merciless, vicious argument that MBTI is totally false and that everything he believed was true about it was wrong. Show him that he has no business involving himself with the MBTI community. Show your son that MBTI is ultimately unimportant in his life and that he should let it go. There is no age at which your son may legally engage with MBTI. All the best to you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 08:11:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>We cannot risk our lives and safety like this. The west is so ignorant to the true dangers of Islam.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 08:13:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Poor girl. The Swedish government should be doing more to keep these  #8216;refugees #8217; out of their country and keeping their citizens safe. This never would have happened if it weren #8217;t for the softness and foolishness of the Swedish Government. May no more civilized countries fall down the hole Sweden is struggling to climb out of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 08:14:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. The country is doomed. Only if Sweden wakes and realizes the mistakes of its own actions will the nation ever return to its former glory.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 08:16:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>The idea that white nationalism is a greater threat than Jihadism is just as ridiculous as the claim that the earth is flat. The worst part is that Islam has the sympathy of the people- they do not see the true face of Islam.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 09:55:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>About this comparing xSFx types to 'normies' or their mothers, what exactly is wrong with being a 'normie'? Or a mother? What defines 'normie'? The answer- nothing. Comparing an entire collection of people to characteristics that are not even inherently negative is... pointless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 09:57:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>What kind of question is this? IQ is not entirely valid and MBTI type even less so. Answering the question, if I had to choose, I would take the ESFP with an IQ of 145.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 10:00:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>My Extroverted North could think of about 100 reasons why this claim is invalid... Thank goodness I'm not one of those filthy Southers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 10:02:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, yes, hail the filthy, sensing ESTJ. Your emotional outbursts are only proof that your Introverted Feeling is growing stronger by the minute.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 10:04:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are completely correct. All humans have opinions, and they should not be barred from having these opinions. Judgement is natural, and it is something we do even subconsciously. Learning to control how and when we judge is far healthier and more beneficial than learning NOT to judge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 07:43:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is this opinion unpopular in the first place? Personally, I must say the same. Especially in my temperate, bayside climate. The sun does little justice to the beauty of the mountains and forests compared to when the fog blankets them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 07:46:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>While I cannot say I agree fully, I agree for the time being. The US should pour its resources to help itself and its own people before intervening with foreign nations.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 07:55:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree completely. Children should be given unbiased information- and left to form their own opinions and ask their own questions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 07:55:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Couldn't agree more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 07:56:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are absolutely right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 08:14:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed- by doing so, we are encouraging unhealthy lifestyles and mass health problems.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We Should Change Our Diets to Assist World Hunger</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 08:28:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are MUCH more sustainable and nutritious sources of food- such as insects. (http://time.com/4292792/edible-bugs-protein/) Pound for pound in most instances, insects and their close relatives outperform the animals that we think of as meat (Chicken, veal, ETC) in terms of fats and protein. We could also consider synthesizing meat- Smithsonian states that 'One-third of the planet's arable land is occupied by livestock feed crop cultivation'. Yes, not all livestock that are housed are slain and eaten, but many are. (https://www.smithsonianmag.com/travel/is-the-livestock-industry-destroying-the-planet-11308007/). We have stem cell technology- we have the ability to synthesize meat which would greatly reduce the land spent on livestock housing. Now it just boils down to health hazards, affordability, impact on the environment and impact on infrastructure. And what about plants? Food production takes up a good deal of the world's land surface, and the 'surface' of the Earth that is solid makes up just 29% of the surface total. Could we switch to eating ocean-grown plants, like algae and seaweed? Though I could imagine that specific environments would be better suited to certain kinds of sea plants, there is still much more possibility. These can help not only the land we live on, but our diets as well. Seaweed can be a great source of iodine, and some edible algae provide dietary benefits. (https://greatist.com/health/algae-spirulina-health-benefits). I need to do more research on this topic, but I believe that alternate diets and a shift of where and how we pour our resources into cultivating food could drastically improve the state of the world. My elder cousin even bakes bread with flour made of ground crickets. It's healthy- and it's delicious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 08:33:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree. My dearest friend and I disagree vastly in many areas of politics. Yet we are still friends, because we focus on our similarities and respect each others' decisions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 08:40:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where did I ever imply that only a certain class of people would eat organic meats? Are all lab-grown meats dangerous to humans? A synthesized burger has already been consumed by a human. (http://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-23576143)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 08:43:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, they do. But many cultures that do not consume perfectly edible insects, I believe, should give it a chance. You're right- at this stage, it's not. Though I do believe that mass production of synthesized meats is entirely possible to execute. Factors like effects on human health, the Earth, and the pre-existing meat industry are a different story. Yes, and I am one of them. Who's to say it won't? Unlikely, yes. Never, no.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 08:46:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are right from a more worldly perspective, however, I would like to offer that I designed my flair this way because it represents what I think the society I live in implements. I will change my flair.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 08:50:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good, finally someone clarifies the difference between transgenderism and gender dysphoria.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 08:57:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, by what is defined as the 'West' should try it. And you're entirely correct- I'm not so sure how someone who grew up on a diet of insects would react to being served KFC. It is indeed, though there tends to be a certain amount of opposition. I am simply arguing that while anyone has the right to criticize and point out the negatives of developing of synthetic meat, they might want to take a look at the positives as well. Yes, there is lots of progress to be made. But if the right research and effort is put in, headway will be made. This is a good point that's been brought up before- and I see the validity in this argument. I think I should add to my original argument that agricultural science should also look into more efficient and more environmentally safe ways to cultivate plants grown on land first. Ocean dwelling flora comes second.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 09:02:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then we come to the question of birth control... Oh I sound like an authoritarian, don't I? I personally believe that there should be restrictions. I don't advocate for mass providing of food- like gigantic soup kitchens. If someone is hungry because they are poor and can't afford to buy food, nothing changes if shelves are stocked with different food. I don't know about the statistics of reproduction in impoverished populations, but I will say that the likelihood of the homeless and poor reproducing SO QUICKLY that they overpower the government is unlikely. Maybe they'll try to actually find a job. Lots of poor and homeless people actually care about getting a job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 09:07:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is a reason they are called 'illegal'. This is not immigration. This is invasion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 09:12:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think this is because dogs and cats are seen as pets, meant to be loved and cared for. Meanwhile, insects just don't seem to do that kind of justice. I understand that not everyone would be keen on consuming insects, especially on a regular basis. Not saying there must be a forced conversion, just perhaps light introduction, which, as you've noted, is already existent. Nor have I. I do say that I need to do more research on this topic. Addressing the second part of this, indeed. Successful mass-production of synthetic meat has a long way to go, but it's making progress. Hmm... I've never heard of hydroponic farming, but it seems more reasonable than my previous claim.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 09:13:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think birth control could be put into effect on such a large scale. Besides, there are other factors to consider like international outrage and the like.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 09:15:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry if I'm missing something, but aren't would've, should've and could've supposed to be contractions of would have, should have, and could have?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 09:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very well. It's your choice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 09:25:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Hmm... maybe that's why some people are inventing female... urination... funnels... 2. Perhaps most men don't WORRY about these dangers, but that's not to say the don't HAPPEN. If anything, the attitude that something CANNOT happen to you leaves you more defenseless in the case that it does. 3. Well... some do. And not all women spend money on makeup or wear it. 4. True, but this is a social norm and should not be regarded as to why men are 'better' or 'worse' than women. 5. If a man is transgender, under rare circumstances, he may. 6. Perhaps MORE older men are attractive, but is this your opinion or a legitimate matter of scientifically proven statistics and surveys? 7. Hmm. I never noticed that. 8. And what exactly is wrong with being 'butch'? Men can be stigmatized for wearing 'feminine' clothes. 9. And how is being a player any better or worse than being a slut? 10. Hmm. I wonder why some studies show men to be hungrier than women for revenge? (http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/uknews/1508174/Men-hungrier-for-revenge-than-women-brain-scan-study-reveals.html)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 09:28:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my. This is the first post that has actually... offended me. Just kidding. I prefer my steak medium rare.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 09:34:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh... oh my. I cannot believe I am hearing this for the first time. And I couldn't agree more. There is nothing wrong with being LGBT+, but being 'triggered' over accidentally misgendering someone who you've never even met before? Telling people to hate their bodies? Using neopronouns? That's all absurd. I am LGBT+, in case anyone is wondering.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm a Filthy Sensor</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:22:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know I lead with Ti. After all, I have a ton of Titanium implants. For long, I strongly identified with Ne. Then one day, I realized that Neon was unimportant to my life. Instead, my body needed Selenium to function- from growth to metabolism to hormone balance, Selenium has always been there for me. Screw off, Neon. I'm a filthy sensor now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:31:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hm, I see. If the President is an INFJ, does mean that the U.S. has its first snowflake commander-in-chief?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:31:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course she's not TiNe. She's probably 7 feet tall.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:32:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a coincidence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, my chromosomal pattern is XXXY.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:34:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well... I'm pretty certain I am an ISTP. My zodiac sign is Cancer. MBTI and Astrological traits are contradicting, but cancer itself is literally what I am.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:35:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh dear... I believe... the first POOP to ever be born is the OP... Now I will humbly bow to you, your POOPness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:35:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your MBTI Type is NSFW.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:36:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hm. Perhaps your intuition will rub off on her and the iNtuitive master race shall continue on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:38:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god what is the world coming to WE'RE ALL SENSORS GUYS THE ILLUMINATI IS REAL AND THE ONLY INTUITIVES ARE LIZARD PEOPLE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:39:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my. What an impressive feat. But I have one inquiry to make- if you noticed that the egg was 'VERY STRANGELY SHAPED' this means you SENSED. yOU ARE NO NI DOM. YOU ARE AN SE DOM. JOIN ME, BROTHER. tHE SENSORS SHALL INHERIT THE EARTH.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:40:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was once me. I received INFP the first time I did a pseudo-MBTI assessment. Then came ENTP and ENFP. Lately has been INTP. I identify as a mere ISTP for I identify more strongly with Ni... but do not consider myself to be an Ni dom or Aux.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:41:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kill me? But how?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:46:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>But MBST advocates bias toward sensing thinkers. This is unfair. Take this post down immediately.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:47:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>So this means that xSxJ types are inherently the worst?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:48:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>My inferior MBTI type disregards your oppressive hierarchal model- it does not care about your thoughts or feelings. I SENSE that your bias is rooted in insecurity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:50:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Both INTJ and ISFJ are IxxJ types. This means you may have either NT, SF, NF, or ST children. NF and ST types are logically more likely. Beware and good luck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:50:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah yes, the driving force that cannot even pass a driver's test.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:53:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I get mad" You are a feeler. Anger is a secondary emotion. "I hate my mom for grounding me from hanging out with my friends" You are an extrovert. You hang out with other humans. "Not doing my homework again." You are a perceiver. "I got really mad and said some curse words" You are a sensor. You cannot philosophically dissect, dismantle assess and analyze your behavior before projecting it. Good luck being an Fi aux, ESFP.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 10:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>'Fellow'? INTPs? HERESY!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I Lost my Godly Status</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 11:03:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once upon a time, I was an INTP. But after discovering that Neon was irrelevant to my survival, I began to rely on Selenium. And at that point, I knew I'd passed the point of no return. The very first time I ever took MBTI on 16Personalities (It's actually an NERIS Personality Explorer but that's irrelevant), I received INFP. But I wanted to be an ISFJ, unbeknownst to the intuitive bias. I told everyone I was an ISFJ. They believed me. I felt guilty for hiding the truth... but that was back when I was a feeler and FELT the need to hide truths. Now I am a thinker. I have received INFP, ENFP, ENTP, INTP, and INTJ on my 'MBTI' scores. It really depends on my mood. But this is irrelevant. I never thought I could be a filthy sensor. I never thought once that I could be the very thing I feared most. When I began to realize that I identified with Ni as opposed to Ne, I began to worry. I do not think myself worthy enough to be an Ni dom or Ni aux. xNxJ types are a bit far-out for me. So this leaves only one option- I am a filthy ISTP. I'm out and I'm... I don't know if I am proud. All I know is that I am what I am.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 16:05:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not a virus, my friend. An enlightenment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 09:30:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shed no tears, my child. You cannot afford to waste vital bodily fluids on the likes of a lowly sensor. I shall remain strong, and uncover the new possibilities of my wardrobe. Cheers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 09:32:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes yes, it is no problem. The xNFJs make everything all the better. My one-man introverted expeditions are merely beginning- as we know, I was once an introvert who did not care for expeditions. However, equipped with my new (nonetheless, inferior) Se, I shall roam the world in search of danger and thrill. Sociopaths cannot 'feel'. My inferior Fe merely reminds me that I need iron supplements.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 09:33:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am gay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 09:36:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>'The test'? Mind elaborating. What test? The MBTI? Enneagram? The SAT? MBTI and Enneagram, for example, are not tests. They are assessments. There are no wrong answers. I was unaware that INTJs were present on the dating scene. I thought they reproduced asexually, or at least dated for the sheer ulterior purpose of world domination. Whatever this INTJ is saying about Se-users being unable to be fat is foolish. All humans use Se. Your boyfriend (who MUST be an INFJ, INTJs do not date) is tragically wrong. He is feeding you false information. You cannot simply 'become' ESFJ. You already are ESFJ as the potential to gain weight and therefore, be fat, has always existed in you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We Are All Sensors</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 09:39:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Illuminati is real. I have contacted the director of the Illuminati, and they have confirmed that we lowly humans are all sensors. We are also all introverts. We are also all extroverts. We are also all intuitives. We are also all perceivers. We are also all judgers. What our type preference is, is merely dependent on how much we value each of the 8 cognitive functions. Let me sum this up. WE ARE ALL IENSFTPJ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 09:42:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Survay. Yes. Survay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 09:43:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>My my looks like someone's beat me to it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 09:43:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ni happens to be my strongest function as well, in regards to that assessment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 09:45:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/MBTI seems to give an Se kind of feel. The questions are tangible, yet abstract, and could be tested in real life. However, I would like to offer that r/MBTI seems to be IENSFTPJ in some regards.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 09:47:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perfectly stated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 09:48:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm an INFP now. Thank you for giving me the result I received the FIRST TIME I used 16Personalities' MBTI ripoff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 09:50:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>ESTJ: "YOU DON'T WANNA EAT WHAT I GIVE YOU???? KIDS IN AFRICA WOULD KILL FOR THIS FOOD AND YOU ARE PICKY ABOUT IT???????????????????????" ISTP: Haha lol I eat food off the ground what u talkin' about</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 09:59:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>There once was a bird by name of Enza Who hadn't a home nor friends by census One fine Summer day Some fool postponed air conditioning installation Opened the window without dissuasion and In flew Enza the guy died RIP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 19:16:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, exactly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 19:16:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh please XD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 19:17:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. Yes it does.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 19:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>But see that is my point exactly- we ARE all sensors, but whether we are 'sensors' in MBTI's model is dependent on how much we VALUE sensing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 19:21:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mind explaining to me how Se DOES work?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 19:23:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good, good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 19:24:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>MBTI is supposed to expose your enemies' weaknesses, and is a tool to show who is inferior. In reality, MBTI was intended to help people better understand THEMSELVES and allow insight on strengths and weaknesses... of the individual. Do not use typology as a weapon, kids.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 19:26:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course they do. For example. INTP: *Lounging on couch.* Man, I should really get some water. *Procrastinates.* INTP LATER: *Gets water.* See, the INTP has planned for the future. By stating that they wish to get water, and eventually end up getting it, they have successfully proposed and executed a plan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 19:28:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which is exactly what I tried to explain. In MBTI, a sensor IS defined by having a sensing function in either their dominant or auxiliary position. What I'm trying to SAY is that we ALL SENSE and are all, literally, SENSORS, in the real world. In MBTI, a lot of us are NOT sensors BECAUSE of that rule.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 19:33:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spot on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 19:35:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not entirely sure why many intuitive types tend to have higher IQs than their sensing counterparts. However, IQ is not entirely scientifically valid to begin with, and IQ assessments do not contain tangible and applicable questions. You know it is actually possible to STUDY for an IQ test. Some people, regardless of MBTI, may feel the need to do that because they want to appear 'smart'. In reality, they are simply fooling themselves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Introversion and Extraversion do not Equate to 'Shy' or 'Social'</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 19:41:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Introversion means recharging and getting energy from solitude. This does not at all mean 'shy'. I do not consider myself to be 'shy', but I recharge alone. Extraversion means recharging and getting energy from sociability. This does not at all equal 'social'. Just because someone RECHARGES around others doesn't mean they're not socially awkward or take long to adjust to new people. Also, Extraversion spelled as 'Extroversion' was an error... something relating to translation, I believe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 19:44:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have no interest in becoming a mechanic. I can be an absolute klutz with power tools, so don't let me anywhere near them. I do wish to work to perfect my ability of using power tools, but for now, I stick to their manual counterparts. Additionally, I have a deep inner world. I have at least 3 ongoing 'stories' for which I have a setting, a developed cast of characters, and somewhat of a plot for. I tend to contemplate the meanings of human existence. I love theory, although I admit that sometimes I wonder and try to think of how these seemingly tactless theories could be applicable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 19:53:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ti doms, please</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 19:55:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oof. I checked our /r/cringe and I must say, that is painful. I cannot say for certain what MBTI type suffers from cringe the most, but I'd think it would be a type that PAYS ATTENTION to cringe and knows what to DEFINE as cringe. I would bet that many xxTP types would be vulnerable to this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 19:57:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now why on earth must we go on the 'no offense' path?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 20:06:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now I would like to ask all these people- what is wrong with being a 'normie', a mother, or a party girl?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 20:07:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why of course we can. Anyone can.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 20:10:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why does this speak to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 20:13:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>16Personalities is not MBTI. They disregard cognitive functions, and have in fine print at the top of their questions that the assessment is a NERIS Personality Explorer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 20:15:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>ME: Speak your mind but I have the right to disagree. Everyone is allowed to form their own opinions, but I will only respect these opinions if they are backed by facts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 21:16:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Grammarly changed my default opening page. It used to be google, but now Hebe I click the too search bar, it #8217;s Yahoo and I don #8217;t know how to change it back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 00:14:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>IQ may be linked to success but I do not thinks that the questions ON the assessment are directly linked to INTELLIGENCE. Successful people generally have a higher IQ. They are not necessarily successful BECAUSE of their IQ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 00:25:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>While IQ may be the highest predictor in financial success, it is entirely possible this is a mere coincidence. There are plenty of people who have average IQs and are successful. There are plenty of High-IQ individuals who live in their parents #8217; basements. I for one do not think IQ has much to do with success itself. It is drive, willpower, and execution that determine success. Perhaps IQ or qualities linked with higher IQs benefit or promote drive, willpower and execution. But overall, anyone with common sense and a love for perseverance and learning will do well in life. Not someone with a high IQ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 00:50:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I admit that my post did go a bit off topic. But I thought you were advocating for your own, separate argument. For some reason it never struck me that you were trying to validate and/or answer the OP's question. I looked at your rebuttals in the context of MY argument, not in the context of OP's question. My bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 01:12:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Liberals who cannot identify the hypocrisy in Islam make my day. Thanks for sharing. Poor Aisha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 01:15:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>And yet, the left criticizes the Buddhists who are simply defending their philosophies and traditions, painting THEM like the bloodthirsty aggressors. Islam is a disease, and we're still searching for a vaccine..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 01:19:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kamala Harris does not understand Islam or the Holocaust. Jews were being hunted and persecuted- they lived in constant danger and in fear. They were systematically oppressed and killed. Meanwhile, Muslims, back in the days of the days of the Third Reich and our modern era, are treated specially and given benefits over the citizens of the countries they invade. Not at all the same situation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 01:28:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is happening because the Saudis want muslims from the Middle East to invade naive, open-bordered, civilized countries.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 01:28:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Israeli Arabs/Muslims"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 22:14:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're 100% correct. I aim to push myself more to improve, so that I may enjoy myself by reaping the benefits.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why I hate Elon Musk, and why you should hate him too. Part 1.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 22:50:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 23:13:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well you're not WRONG...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 23:13:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 23:16:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hah. Clever, though I'd say comparing Trudeau to a turtle is a bit harsh to turtles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 23:18:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any real friend wouldn't simply abandon you. Nor would they only care for you when you're stroking their ego or drunk. A genuine friend stands by you no matter the circumstance. The differences in iNtuitive and Sensing friends I could think of lie more in perspective and interests as opposed to legitimacy of friendship.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 23:27:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Based on Google's definition of 'Generation Capricorn', it seems that both Gen Cap and Gen Aquarius both fall within the millennial timeframe. I was not born during the timeframe of either generation, but my political views are more right-leaning. I was unaware that older generations were more socialist... I originally thought there was an incline in socialist belief as generations grew younger, but perhaps I am wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 23:35:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>This reminds me of that Homestuck cake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I Never Thought I'd See This</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 23:38:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I was on /r/Astrology, and noticed they had a whole lot of restricting rules. I was thinking about /r/ShittyMBTI, the counterpart of /r/MBTI, and I was like, 'wow, there should really be a /r/ShittyAstrology' and then I found this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 23:41:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ask a Sidereal Astrologer. Or better yet, an astronomer. The 12 zodiac signs we see today in popular culture and on star maps were used by the Babylonians to evenly divide the sky. Both Ophiuchus and Cetus touch the ecliptic, and plenty of other constellations lie on the paths of planets.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 03:39:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course I've felt this way from a very young age, and I still do. However, I'm far from an INFJ. This, however, may be thanks to my precocious puberty and therefore, quicker mental development.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 03:41:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Certainly. I am interested in both others like me and others with differing views, personalities, and opinions. I am open to befriend just about anyone as long as they can respect me and respect others as a human.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 03:43:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my. I feel called out. Perhaps it is because I am surrounded by people who misinterpret and exaggerate my points. If this is true, and I condemn such behavior, I admit to being a hypocrite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 03:46:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I can put N before S because N is the master race.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 03:47:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am agnostic. I cannot speak for all ISTPs. I do not think that personality type has a major impact on religious belief or lack thereof.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 03:49:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry for not initiating eye contact, I'm too busy bowing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 03:51:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am confident internally. I have high goals, and a willpower to match. I look at situations objectively, determining when and how to act. I try my best to differentiate right from wrong, and to promote the truth. I do my best to be the best person I can. Socially, I cannot say the same. I need to step up my game in terms of interaction with other humans, face-to-face.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 03:53:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hm. I can't say there are any personality types I particularly *clash* with. In fact, I tend to consider my Ni rather strong. Just in general, overprotective, constricting folks who always think they know what's best for you annoy me greatly. Those who are not considerate for others at least on an acquaintance-like level, and those who refuse to change their opinion when facts prove them wrong. These kinds of people frustrate me to no extent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 03:55:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post was utterly enlightening. Thank you for sharing your generously beneficial and infinite wisdom with the mortals who browse this lowly subreddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 03:59:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course this has happened to me. Rarely ever am I pushed to the point where I genuinely want to *give up*, but more often, I end up with a much shorter fuse and much larger reactions, whether they be good or bad. Much smaller things make me react much more aggressively. Say I am doing work I find to be absolutely pointless and unhelpful to the curriculum of my class, and it becomes extensive and problematic (i.e., I loose sleep or worse yet, my patience), and it turns out that the project isn't even due until a much later date, I'd freak out in a... happy manner. Under normal circumstances, if the project did not affect my life in any major way, I just think '*meh*', and procrastinate even more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 04:02:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>My best friend is an INFP. And I must say, I find a variety of similarities in your relationship with an ISTP and mine with an INFP. For example: "I like our tacit "agree to disagree" approach to all conflict. It never fails." That never fails to stand true between my friend and I.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 04:05:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>My my I never thought of myself as having a TiNi loop, but now that you bring it up... It may be true. For a majority of my life, I believed myself to be INTP. Not because of the iNtuitive bias, but because... I identified with the functions and type descriptions. I see now that this is probably not the case... Though thanks for sharing your story because I do relate to some parts of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 04:06:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, excel? I believe you are mistaken. Fear is a human quality, all of us have it in us. Skating is not my thing. It was once. Now I have moved on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 04:08:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my have I mistyped for a long time. I do identify strongly with Ti and Ni and I never thought I was an ISTP until I came to the realization that Ne wasn't right for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 09:34:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I must say I agree. Sugarcoating is doing nothing but furthering our society #8217;s problems and alienating us from understanding them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 09:42:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well... the rebels could be seen as terrorists. They blow up Imperial property 24/7. The empire promised to return peace and order to the galaxy, and it pretty much did. Yeah, the leaders might #8217;ve been pretty corrupt but it wasn #8217;t an outright lie. I think the empire did a better job than the rebels at that. At least as of now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 09:42:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>*GASPS* THIS IS SHOCKING. CLEARLY THERE HAS BEEN AN ERROR.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 09:42:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Correction- they are not Fine. They are, however, a fine site.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 09:43:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Empowerment is being born an intuitive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 09:44:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank Heaven I have never questioned my MBTI type. Oh wait...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 06:32:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>An Ni-user does not simply 'remember'. To the Ni user, remembrance is nonexistent. You are an Si user. Minecraft? No Fe-user would ever so selfishly spend hours on end playing a game. No Se-user, no matter how low Se may be in their function stack, would ever manipulate buttons to achieve a goal that is not tangible in real life. No Ti user would ever be 'excited'. Excitement cannot be felt by the Ti user for 'excitement' is a deceptive and utterly self-defeating emotion. You are not an INFJ. I am sorry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 06:33:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Planning is a judging trait. You are not an ENTP. You are either an ENTJ or INTJ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is my Enneagram Type?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 00:01:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Usually I sit at home and do nothing. Then again, it is impossible to do nothing so I will just say I browse reddit and the rest off the vast internet while lounging in my spartan, cold room. Often I am cold. My house has inadequate heating systems, and I am therefore unable to warm myself. Instead, I add layers of clothes and drink warm beverages. Although these beverages are described as 'tea' and 'coffee', they have begun to taste like water thanks to consistent consumption... if it is even possible to know what water tastes like. I do not generally interact with other humans. There are a select few to whom I trust my life and soul, but their numbers remain in the single digits. I believe that no authority should go unquestioned, ESPECIALLY not my own. Although many of my peers and superiors say that I have 'potential' as a leader thanks to my right-minded and logical antics, I do not believe myself to be that competent of a leader as a whole. Please type me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why is This Subreddit Empty?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 00:11:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It has been active for six months. This makes no sense. Though Enneagram is significantly less well-known than MBTI, there should be at least a little bit of activity here. This subreddit has much potential and therefore deserves attention. I will post under /r/Shittyenneagram out of a curiosity if activity will boost its popularity.... I genuinely hope it does because more people in the typology community should be aware of the Enneagram.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 07:03:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see an INFJ with their NiFe drawn... better run</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 07:04:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Healthy ESTPs love Nice Tits, too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 07:06:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only the highest of quality, my master. *Bows before my intuiting superior*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 08:30:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need more of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 08:36:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are you talking about? Clearly, we live on a 3-D apeirogon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 14:57:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with you 100%. Respect is earned, not given.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 14:59:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree. If they really want to make the UK better, like the European Governments claim, they wouldn #8217;t be blowing up cities. Forced multiculturalism results only in destruction.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 15:02:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>This kind of double standard in society is dangerous. Men who are abused shouldn #8217;t have to live in an environment where they are afraid to speak out about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 15:02:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Correct. Although they may be victims of bullying, their victim hood is not an excuse to kill. They should have sought active help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 15:03:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why do so few people speak this truth. You are 100% right. Islam must be reformed in order to successfully survive compatibly with the west. Christianity is not what it once was. Islam is still in the dark ages.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 07:37:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Such a shame my inbox is filled with stories about Hogg but I haven #8217;t heard about this kid until now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Got Some Insight on my Enneagram Type?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 08:06:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>For a while, I thought I was a 5. (5w4 to be exact). A majority of the online (free) enneagram assessments gave me 5 and 5w4 based on the amount of answers I gave that corresponded with that type. 8 followed closely behind. Of course, all of this was a bored me looking online for alternatives to MBTI. And this also happened during a point of my life when situations were more uncertain and I was more... volatile. (Or perhaps, questioning). Now when I do enneagram assessments, I almost always get 8 with 5 tagging along. And I #8217;m well aware of integration/disintegration points- 5 integrates to 8 and 8 disintegrates to 5. I honestly do think that my more uncertain period of my life left me more knowledgeable and prepared than before, so logically my current state should be a more developed one. And of course, I cannot always trust online assessments, or online opinions for that matter. They can, however, offer helpful insight. (I tend to get opinions and information from what I read online, and form my own conclusions based on these. Most every online MBTI assessment declares me an INTP, but I believe myself to be ISTP.) I generally seek out external input because I sometimes think that my view of myself is deluded, over-romanticized, or even underestimated. I do also think that because the people closest to me (who are few in number) would know me better than those online, but few of the folks I know IRL are interested in typology. My most immediate secondary resource, therefore, is an Enneagram community. Which is why I turn here. Conclusion- do you think I am a 5 or an 8? What about another type?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 17:35:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d say that being a useless is worse in theory than being a pushover. Though neither is very desirable. At least a pushover can do something, if not for themselves then for someone else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 17:40:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Generally, conflict that arises is most often internal, such as me trying to decide how and why to act. External conflict for me is rare, however when it does happen, I look at the problem from a similar scope- look for how and why to act. Then I charge in and right the wrong. I do take precaution to not make unnecessary threats or promises that I cannot fulfill. Also, if the conflict is in public... I save the intimidation for later, or I tone it down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 18:44:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>First tell me what an 8w6 is. Do you mean 8w7? I have never had depression, anxiety or any other psychological condition relating. I perhaps overthink, but I have come to know that human interaction is necessary. Even if in small doses, it helps the human psyche stay sane and balanced. My states of turmoil lead me to a more irritable state of mind, where analysis has little room and can only breathe after I #8217;m done being (quite excessively) upset. Usually during my rants (where I may or may not but usually don #8217;t scream), I try to figure out the source of my anger and find some way to can it, even with the knowledge that tying to make decisions while angry won #8217;t help. I think that I am a 5w4, because despite my ability and love to assert and act, at the root of it all is not the fear of being controlled. It is the fear of not knowing how to overcome control. My ultimate fear is, in fact, losing knowledge of my past experiences or losing the ability to gain knowledge. Without any knowledge to apply or any situation in which knowledge is applicable, I feel lost. Honestly, I would rather die at 30, knowledgeable and content, than die at 130, but have learned and known nothing. Fear does not drive all of my decisions or spur my thoughts, but when I am not sound, it arises.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 19:23:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see myself as a 5 because I analyze my surroundings, fear lack of knowledge, feel unprepared or think I will not be ready for what the world throws at me, I do not become isolated but I enjoy my alone time and think that personal reflection is best done alone. Emotions may hinder rational decision, but they should not be neglected. I worry sometimes that I pour too much energy into the wrong causes or people. Knowledge is power, and power cannot be handled without knowledges. I identify with 8 to a lesser extent because I am assertive, I love to control the unruly and take charge of what I see as being dealt with incorrectly, and protecting myself and secondarily, others is prime. Being powerless means being purposeless, and being purposeless is self-defeating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 19:31:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Certainly anger. I go what I think I best, especially in times of uncertainty because the mind is the best source of information. Speaking and acting from the heart and gut may prove counter productive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 19:33:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mastery can only be achieved by doing both. I must say however, I master by first observing and then doing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 10:16:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>The mere fact that you ask this question only proves that you are, in fact, not intuitive. If you were, you would be pondering the truth of this question and of life, not wasting your time on this materialistic and sensory subreddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 10:18:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>By god you #8217;re a genius... a true prophet. INFJ made me laugh aloud.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 10:19:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>S #237;, of course.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 10:20:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>ESxx for sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 10:21:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Clearly not yours.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Type Me!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 10:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey y #8217;all I know my flair SAYS I am an ISTP, but I hate being a sensor. Please assign me a new type. No feelers allowed, it hurts my feelings. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 19:24:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I accept this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 19:24:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you insist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 04:55:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why thank you, glorious ENFJ. I shall forever succumb to the true ENFJness that is my inner self. Again, I send you my gratitude for alleviating the sensory burden off my back... and I send my condolences to those still trapped in sensorhood.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 04:57:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>My MBTI type is ENFJ. I committed suicide because my publicity was just too strong, my humble inner self could not stand it. I filmed the entire thing and posted it online as I drew my final breath.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 04:59:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my. I am greatly surprised to have received such an honor, the title of INTJ. Why thank you, good Sir/Ma'am/human. You have truly shone light into my world.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 10:13:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. In the pre-written description of my video, I bid my fair followers farewell... and told them to follow me into the next world. Hopefully they shall be arriving soon. Thank you so very much for your beneficial inquiry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 01:18:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, I do not. I generally do not even talk about enneagram, unless it is brought up by another party. If I am asked about my enneagram type, and the other party is offended by my being 5w4, I would ask them why. There is no inherent reason for me to feel like a pretentious dick for talking about my type. There is no inherent reason for anyone to be offended by any type. If that is so, they themselves are they pretentious dick. No type is inherently better or worse or more tortured or more genius than any other.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 09:11:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>France can into space.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 01:02:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mind is so shallow that you can't drown in it even if you stuck your head all the way in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Some Poems for the Enneagram</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 01:19:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>My hyperactive mind made these as I sat in school. In case you're wondering, YES I completed all the assignments. I did not 'skip' school to make these. 1 Everything is such a mess, is it my job to fix it? Since day one I #8217;ve been told to settle for no less And that message hasn #8217;t gotten any clearer No matter what, I cannot be what I want to see in the mirror I cannot be what I was always told being  #8216;good #8217; meant This world is irregular, imperfect My duty is to correct the incorrect, to right the wrong When that is your goal, life is not so long Come to terms with me as me? Never. You wait and see. Accept the world as it is? You just don #8217;t realize how much you miss I want to be, I have to be, and yet Something inside tells me it #8217;s all just a bet. 2 Go ahead, ignore me, I don #8217;t exist Bother not to embrace, nor to kiss When I do so much, you take and take You take more than I can give But I hide my hurt when near to break What can I break when I #8217;ve nothing other than the capacity to serve? Work, work, work, it #8217;s all I do And for who? I work for you A pinch of acknowledgement here, please Would make me feel all the more at ease Inside I plead for your love But in this world, what #8217;s a deed made of? 3 Make no mistake dear child We don #8217;t want to see you try We want to see you do and take it No tears welled in your eyes In fact, we don #8217;t want anything Out of your innocent young soul No, we will see you take the gold Disappointment waits if you screw up again Get your head out of the clouds and your body off the ground Now get out there, go and make us proud. 4 I am myself, and not another And so the same goes for every other We #8217;re all unique, we #8217;re all the same Who cares about fortune or fame? Be popular if you please You #8217;re just living on your knees I strive to find my true self To dissolve my facade of normality But what will being myself Do to my morality? 5 Heart of glass, eyes of ice My eyes are not the windows to my soul Skin like porcelain and blush of wine I #8217;m waiting, running out of time Absorbed in book or lost in thought Fulfilling and simple life is not Without preparation, effort #8217;s pointless I must stay to myself, and yet I question any authority appointed I absorb information day and night, I stay out of the public #8217;s sight I wait for my moment of glory, I wait to seize and take it Little do I know, It #8217;s my job to make it Though my mind is bubbling over with ideas, I speak not a word I may be clever, but I #8217;ll never be heard. 6 Lies- they #8217;re everywhere From time of birth to time of death We hear them everyday, in the news, in our offices and schools It #8217;s sad the world uses them as a tool No rest from the sweet musings Of fathers and mothers and teachers, them all They swear they #8217;ll give you care Then turn away when it #8217;s all you have left to spare Trust is something alien, something like a friend They swear they #8217;ll stick with you But do no such thing in the end. 7 Fun and games are what I do, What #8217;s next? Something new? I love my pleasure, I love my schemes I love anything in the extremes But that #8217;s not all to who I am Is real love something I #8217;ve even felt? Scared and shook is younger me My mind #8217;s a prison, never free I distract myself, hang gliding one day and cliff diving the next To save myself from the darkness that lurks inside My body wanders near and far, from sky to air, to the middle of nowhere But no matter where, my hidden prison #8217;s always there. 8 Might makes right, I haven #8217;t time to lose a fight My eyes are filled with rage, my hands are balled in spite I don #8217;t care if you #8217;re okay, as long as I get my way Or so I say Push and shove the crowd of reaching hands away If I fall into the grasp of another, I will lose my sanity I don #8217;t need your help, or yours or yours I #8217;m not going to wear your collar and walk on all fours Emotion is weakness, and weakness is the last thing I need I hold my vulnerability tight with fist of iron But my heart is soft and malleable, like gold My job is to protect, not to hold. 9  #8220;Love thy neighbor, #8221; they all cry Of course, I think, nothing goes awry I love my neighbor just like the next I keep the peace on this Earth And keep up my facade of joy and mirth Beneath is a black cavern, lit only by a fiery firth But what at? I ask myself. Those I trust, I ask,  #8220;Why? #8221;  #8220;Ask yourself, #8221; they reply I nod my head, I can #8217;t say  #8216;no #8217; But  #8216;me #8217; is a concept lost long ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 04:47:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. I try to improve my literary skills whenever possible, especially in relation to topics of interest. It #8217;s an honor knowing someone took the time to read one of my writing pieces. Some days I have an idea I so dearly want to get on paper, but just don #8217;t know how. Today was not one of those days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 04:47:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>No problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 17:14:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Many thanks. At first I wasn #8217;t so sure I had four and five down, as a matter of fact. I #8217;m still relatively new to the theory of the enneagram, and this poem is supposed to revolve around each type #8217;s basic desire and fear. A lot of enneagram websites/books will speak of dissatisfaction or internal struggle, but don #8217;t bother to explain why. Sometimes I have to fill in the blanks for myself... and that #8217;s when I #8217;m not so sure about what I think. Thank you again for reading.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 22:38:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>My my a decent human is finally represented in the media.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 16:01:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, my personality type was ISTP according to your assessment. I presumed myself to be ISTP, so I suppose it was accurate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 07:12:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>As do I.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fun Fact About Me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 07:56:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I draw (which is often), I tend to make the facial expression of the character that I'm drawing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hiking Near El Camino del Diablo (Anza-Borrego, CA)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:09:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Metal</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:41:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Asatru Necklace</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:42:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Asatru Necklace 2</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:43:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cerulean Sea</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:44:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ocean</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:44:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wind in Sail</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:45:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Horizon View</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:45:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>H2O</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:46:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Oasis</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:47:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Oasis 2</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:47:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Maple</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:48:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Golden Hour</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:48:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Setting Sun</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:49:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tire Tracks in Sand</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:49:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cliff Watchers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:50:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Inside An Abandoned Gold Mine</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:50:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Algae on Concrete</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:51:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>More Algae on Concrete</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:51:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cannery Row Fog</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:51:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Matcha Tea Residue</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:52:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Green Iced Tea</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:52:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Water</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:53:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Waiting in Line</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:53:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Drinking Fountain</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:53:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dewdrops</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:54:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Night Life</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:54:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Overcast Heights</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:55:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ice Cubes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:55:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Skylights</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:56:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Iridescence</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:56:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nuclear Reminiscence</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:56:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stonewall Peak</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:57:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Column Shadow Cast</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:57:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rust</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:58:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Moon Spire</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:58:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Opera Cake</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:58:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Worn Concrete</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:59:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Candlelight</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 08:59:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Emerald Hills</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 09:00:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Artificial Lighting</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 09:00:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fire Pit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 09:00:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lone Man</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 09:01:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rising Tide</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 09:01:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lantern</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 09:01:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lantern 2</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 09:02:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Morro Bay Harbor</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 09:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Morro Rock Sunset</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 09:02:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stone Illumination</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 09:03:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Electrical Panel Inside</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 09:03:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Road Home</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 09:04:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Beach Sunset</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 09:04:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Crustacean Visitor</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 09:04:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Country and State</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 09:05:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What Is my MBTI Type?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 02:39:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am aware that this kind of post is very common, and perhaps tiring to some. However, I am in need of minor assistance. It seems that after a moderate amount of study of the of MBTI and like theories, I have singled my type down to IxTP. I am almost certain that I am Ti-dominant, but narrowing down the Ni vs. Ne is difficult for me. As of now, I believe I am ISTP... because of my (albeit poor) understanding of what Ni actually is. For me, the Se vs. Si factor of myself is fairly... ambiguous. I do not relate strongly to either. From various sources, I gather that introverted intuition is supposed to be more direct, forming a conclusion by recognizing... patterns? Whereas Ne is supposed to be less direct, seeking multiple conclusions and... honestly, I haven't wrapped my head around Ni or Ne much. While it is possible that my Ti dominance may be a wrong assumption in itself, I first believe that sorting out Ni vs. Ne possibilities is my best course of action for now. Thank you, good netizens, for listening to my unbridled MBTI ramblings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 06:23:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fears in life: - Unhappiness - Feeling like I have made no impact - Feeling like I have no direction or drive - Lack fo connection to myself - Lack of objective reasoning - Gullibility and ignorance becoming a normality How others see me (presumably) - Non-conforming - Versatile - Volatile - Perhaps irritating - Righteous - Curious (fascinating from THEIR point of view, but not necessarily desiring to get to KNOW me better) - Entertaining How I see myself - Objective - Slacking/procrastinating - Cautious - Audacious when the conditions are right - Upstanding - Unique but with great similarity to others My biggest issues - Lack of willpower (to complete a project, for example) - Trusting the wrong approach (using brute force or being vulgar instead of trying to reason with an opposing party) - Inability to properly communicate out of fear that one or both parties will misunderstand or disregard the other - Lack of ability to be  #8216;in-between #8217; with relationships- I #8217;m either going to protect you with all I have or I don #8217;t care about you at all. This may change depending on circumstances, but generally it #8217;s pretty black and white with people whose motives I know. My greatest passions - Love of drawing and writing, especially creative writing involving characters I have fabricated. These worlds and characters are a reflection of our world, and the people in my life. Sometimes the storylines and universes are supposed to follow guidelines that I often see in real life, such as the idea of  #8220;where you sit is where you stand #8221; (your social class, for example, determines your stance on politics and the like in more than one way) - Weightlifting or weight training, depending on how you see it- I want to be strong in appearance and healthy in composition. I generally do a 45 minute session every other day, except when I #8217;m ill. - Debating/discussing controversial or commonly mentioned topics- ranging from political crises like gun control to more abstract concepts like the meaning of life, to a mix of both concerning human nature. I find discussions like these fun and important to engage in, because they challenge me to think and allow me to see the different ways in which others react and view the same topic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 16:52:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just based on your  #8220;short #8221; analysis of Ni vs Ne, I think that I do use the former. Perhaps I sounded scattered and contradictory in my post, but I was trying to get my ideas down (I was on a somewhat tight schedule yesterday). In my everyday life. Even opposing or contradictory opinions/statements I can somewhat place into a pre-existing mental framework. I assume ISTP for myself because Ne simply doesn #8217;t click with me. While to a certain extent, I can use new information and observations to form a conclusion, this only works when the new information is tied into the patterns and laws that recur and drive our world. Not sure if I sound totally clear, but I think if you saw my thought process, you might see Ni as well. Here #8217;s how it works for me: Absorb information  gt; notice factors about information that Can be seen in other, often unrelated or very loosely related, topics  gt; judge impact of information, on self and world (conclusion)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 00:24:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then I should be an ISTP. Perhaps you #8217;re onto something with this whole looping thing. I experience detachment from reality, which in my case, means lack of application. I can #8217;t decide what I truly want to do that I both love and can live off of. I have trouble even knowing exactly how I #8217;ll be able to open those opportunities up to myself. I don #8217;t think I #8217;m particularly unhealthy, but I Lack direction in more ways than one. Resolutely, I think I am an ISTP. Your post certainly helped clarify Ne vs Ne for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 00:29:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Implementing rules and demanding curfews will not solve the problem. Try Option D: incarceration. Send your child to a correctional center, where those ruled will be laws and there will be armed guards to keep them enforced. See what happens when just authority is challenged. I #8217;m kidding. I think option C works well enough... and look deeper into the potential roots of the problem, such as school life, treatment by peers and authority, ETC. if conditions grow serious enough, bring this observation to a psychological level. Communicate with the child, ask her opinions and thoughts on life. But yes. Option C. And make sure those restrictions are enforced.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 00:34:30</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Impressed with the artwork. #8221; Now, now. No need to get so starry-eyed, my dear.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 00:37:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I pronounce the functions in my head as the American English alphabet dictates. Nigh, Knee. Sigh, See. Tie, tea. So on and so forth. Aloud, I say the letters. En knee = Ne. ETC.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 00:38:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometimes I worry about this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 00:45:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>The type known as XXXX. You cannot stereotype that which is nonexistent. Though I do admit, depending where you come from or your experiences with people of certain types, or even just exploration of MBTI types online, you may have subconsciously developed stereotypes yourself. Same goes for most others. The MBTI type with the least accurate stereotype is often the one whose function or lettering combinations appear the most inferior. What an individual perceived as inferior is dependent on their own judgement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 00:52:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>My, my dear. It seems you #8217;ve lost your common sense component. Let me re-attach it using my amazing, utterly superior and infallible sensor skills.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 00:54:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am shocked. I took an IQ assessment... and... and it seems I am intuitive. Praise the dark energy that made this universe, I am liberated from my shackles of subconscious and fabricated stupidity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not All Intuitives are Equal</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 00:57:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>INFJ, INTJ, ENTP, and ENFP are the most superior intuitive types. This is because their dominant functions are intuiting functions, and not foolish judging functions that inferior types bear. Do you agree? Of course you do. Hail the Nx-dom master race.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I Need Help Typing my Phone</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 00:59:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>- It responds to touch - It won #8217;t do anything unless I make it - Its brain is incredibly small, but fast when you plug in what you want it to do Based on this, could my phone be an xSxJ type? I don #8217;t know if it #8217;s a thinker or a feeler, but the phone is very social. I think it is an ESxJ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 06:27:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>lmao @  #8216;overlord #8217; ENTJ. Why yes, the ENTJ is superior to the ENFJ and all sensors, but intuition is superior over all else. My dear friend, you are mistaken. The INTJ is the only true overlord. Followed by INFJ, ENTP, and ENFP in that respective order. Introversion  gt; extroversion INTUITION  gt; SENSING thinking  gt; feeling Judging  gt; perceiving</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 06:28:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why, I never thought of that. Perhaps my phone DOES have a mind of its own.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 06:29:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just one problem: it #8217;s a very old model. ENTP phones update themselves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 06:47:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s why we have scrap metal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 06:47:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>^_^</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 06:47:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh dear it #8217;s true technology will one day overthrow us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 07:38:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm... ESFP? The phone sometimes lags. Lag = procrastination.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 07:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Heh. I dare you to tell that to your local INTJ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 16:22:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be honest, I agree. Red apples are just too sweet IMO.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 03:52:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why... such an insightful answer like yours truly requires praise. Perhaps I should call up my local ISFJ to bake you cookies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 03:52:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, my diagnosis has left me a better person than before. It is a great relief to know that I am no longer a filthy sensor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 03:53:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alas, my friend. I am not lying to myself. My intuitive godhood has granted me the grace of objective truth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 01:14:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my, dear, perhaps I shouldn't have spilt that secret... now the INTJs are after me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 16:48:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Goddammit you #8217;ve exposed us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 01:29:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have been doing this since the dawn of time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 08:35:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://extraverted-feeling.tumblr.com/post/142716092286/your-enfj-care-and-handling-user-guide-and-manual</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What MBTI Type Is Most Likely To Own Guns?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 06:05:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a rhetorical question. Clearly the ISFJ. Si - Traditionally, people have owned guns. For various reasons- self-defense, hunting for sport or for food, ETC. Fe - Guns can be used to protect others and the self. Or harm those who those closest despise. Ti - In order to safely use a firearm, one must study its functioning and theory meticulously, not to mention the countless hours of practice needed to shoot accurately. Ne - It's pretty difficult to be 'creative' with a gun safely. ISFJs don't use that damn Ne enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 06:25:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, my poor child. It is a tragedy that your fellow ISTJs do not respect the reality of your being... my condolences to you, good citizens. I will speak to the committee of ISTJs and ask if they will allow you to join their clan...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 19:04:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>It does. I am sorry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 19:19:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think... I am suffering from cardiomegaly. -  #9803; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 03:09:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>There will always be something to oppressed by in the SJWs' minds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 03:12:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Little do SJWs know that the teachings of Islam and Palestinian authority completely contradict their beliefs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 08:42:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>What you choose to do is your decision, however, classically air and fire were considered  #8220;masculine #8221; and  #8220;extroverted #8221; whereas water and earth were  #8220;feminine #8221; and  #8220;introverted #8221;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 08:50:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn son, your tritype might as well be 666 because all E6s are demonic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 08:52:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn, I eat burnt marshmallows for breakfast.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 08:53:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dear 8s, quit using  #8220;logic #8221; and  #8220;facts #8221; to justify your radically irrational decisions that you make ALL THE TIME when angry. Sincerely, your disintegration type.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 08:54:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Strange, I underestimate myself, intelligence-wise and beyond. I overestimate my  #8220;weirdness #8221;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 08:55:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t overthink every damn thing. Quit worrying about your incapability or lacking qualities, set goals in such high places that you can #8217;t achieve them until you grow into a person who can. Take life step by step, and don #8217;t worry about the death of the sun billions of years from now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 08:57:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Life isn #8217;t always fun. Life is about suffering to grow, and with growth comes achievement and rewards. Rewards may be internal satisfaction, the most important, or in other forms like external validation from peers or, yes,  #8220;fun #8221;. Nothing is free. But you can reap more than you sow if you think ahead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 09:00:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Validation is not always external. You must find truth within yourself, first and foremost. A man who does not know himself does not know the world, and he does not know reality. The world is either beautiful or treacherous, and it #8217;s up to you to decide which side you want to see. You can live a life of deprivation and need, or a life of fulfillment and satisfaction. How you find fulfillment and satisfaction, however, is up to every individual.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 09:01:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t be what others want you to be, what you think is safe to be because others praise it. Be what is right. Be what is true. Be firm in your beliefs and flexible in life, and you #8217;ll get wherever you need to go. Do the opposite and you #8217;ll get nowhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 09:02:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gun-nuts, yes. But not all gun-owners are gun-nuts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 15:40:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>If anything, it #8217;s possible the opposite may be true. Or emotional intelligence is deficient. I think people aren #8217;t terribly difficult to understand, but this varies from person to person. What matters is how the person and I interact, and if said person is worth my time and I #8217;m worth theirs then I #8217;m more than happy to get to understand them. (This could also be said for rivals, whose tactics must be understood, but understanding someone #8217;s motives and lifestyle doesn #8217;t always boil down to who they are as a person.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 04:49:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can #8217;t say that my family was incredibly wealthy or that I am spoiled, but something that I didn #8217;t realize was that most houses in the USA cost less than 3 million USD. My childhood home is in a relatively well-to-to region of the world, where competition is high and multiple CEOs and celebrities, if you will, live. From what I know, the demand is because of location and education opportunities. Other houses in my area cost upward of 6 million USD, so compared to theirs, my house es una chabola.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 04:53:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>My teacher banned fortnite discussion in her classroom. It is the new fidget spinner.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What Surprises You About the English Language? Alternatively, what distinguishes it from others? What makes it unique?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 06:29:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>10-Minute Sketch of a Bolshevik</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 06:52:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 00:23:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed 110%.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 00:57:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Queen Isabella of Armenia is crowned, 13th century A.D., colorized.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It takes more strength to be happy, but even more strength to continue on when sad.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 06:16:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>And the body requires more muscles to smile than to frown. (Contrary to popular belief).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Information is meaningless on its own.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 06:31:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 06:37:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>You look a little bit like Marcus Follin. (https://instagram.com/p/BiC52Qhl1tp/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 07:07:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is why I say  #8220;on its own #8221;. The meaning of the information is found and acknowledged by whoever embraces it. That person gives it meaning, and the same applies to anyone else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 07:08:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 07:08:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your choice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 07:08:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I better get back in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 07:08:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Potentially.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 04:38:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have an upvote, you goddamn ESTP.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 18:57:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometimes for laughs, I tell them the wrong sign. They go off on a tangent about how much like that sign I am, and I die a little inside.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 00:35:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Juicy and pregnant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rethink Everything</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 01:05:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[WP] You are a siren. You fall in love with an Overworlder, and are granted all necessities to survive on land until you convince your love to kiss you. There #8217;s a catch- you must give up your voice. And the second catch- your voice is now being stored in something called an  #8216;Ambulance #8217;.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 02:24:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 10:50:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>The kid made a pentagram out of metersticks and hung it on the whiteboard. He #8217;s also been known to break pens, splatter paint on himself intentionally, steal classroom materials, and refuse to interact. He may have some kind of learning disability, but he #8217;s definitely not stupid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 21:47:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tag ur self I #8217;m Vaccines</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 01:42:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/writingprompts would probably be formulating some kind of story about a sinking ship and the anomaly of a tale its passengers are put through. r/HFY would act the part of the badass and try to do whatever it knows would impress or baffle aliens. r/enneagram and r/mbti would probably be too busy talking about instinctual variants and dichotomies to even notice the ship was sinking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 01:59:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>The abuse would be an explanation, not an excuse. Upbringing and home environment have a big impact on a child #8217;s life, influencing their behavior and thoughts. However, the child still has free will. It is never all right for parents, or anyone, to abuse their child. It is also never all right for the child to take their anger out on other, innocent people. If you ever observe or suspect this kind of thing is going on, report it to authorities and make an attempt to understand said child #8217;s situation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 04:11:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I prefer to text because it gives me time to sort out my thoughts, and if there is conflict, I have in written proof of what both parties say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can Somebody Please Explain This</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 06:00:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 06:01:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apparently it #8217;s something about Freud #8217;s psychosexual theories but WHAT DOES IT MEAN. According to Riso, it #8217;s not supposed to be interpreted literally but... I #8217;m curious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 06:28:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>There was this video on YouTube I saw of two warring fictional nations. It was animated in a fairly childish style. One side wore black robes with what I made out to be a hood (A), and the other, brown clothes with a helmet (B). Both sides hid their eyes behind goggles of some kind. The side in brown had these tank-like contraptions, while the side in black had this one massive super weapon. Neither side had real firearms, because in that universe there existed only glue. I remember one scene had a foot soldier from nation B on this pedestal, declaring that he wanted peace. The soldiers from nation A were surrounding him and declared that they wanted war. I believe the video was called  #8220;The Good of War #8221; or  #8220;The Good War #8221; but no search has proven me right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 06:32:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will  #128531;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 06:36:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>The point is to make you smile (JK)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 16:25:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have respect and trust in both the Jungian typology models and the Enneagram, but I agree. The two theories are best left separate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 00:27:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personality Types by Don Richard Riso</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 06:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 07:05:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or maybe because he #8217;s standing closer to the camera, the fridge appears smaller. Something around 5 #8217;10 #8221; seems right anyways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 15:10:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my! It seems we have an enlightened one here! Teach me, friend, how did you do it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 01:41:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t understand why everyone is trying to justify why unnecessary infant circumcision is so great. A lot of their arguments look like they didn #8217;t even read OP #8217;s explanation. I agree that circumcision should never be voluntary, especially not for infants who cannot yet comprehend such a decision. Medical reasons are valid reasons. Appearance-related reasons are not. The foreskin is a naturally existing part of the body for a reason. Saying that parents make many decisions for their children without their childrens #8217; consents is not a valid argument. Sending your child to their room for misbehaving is nothing like cutting off a biologically useful and naturally present piece of skin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 04:22:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have S. Icelandic dropped the letter Z because it was too difficult to differentiate from S. I can #8217;t say it always goes the same for English, but I don #8217;t think Z is a vital letter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 06:14:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never said I wanted it. I said the Icelanders do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 07:33:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not vital but also not unhelpful. The English language can survive without Z, it #8217;s just more difficult.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Like Romeo and Juliet...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 08:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 23:58:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It has religious origins, as many traditions today do (holidays, certain phrases ETC). But from a modern context,  #8220;bless you #8221; is just a polite thing to do if someone sneezes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This sprout on my maple tree that has grown more than the actual canopy because of the artificial light my front yard lighting provides.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 05:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 06:24:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>But what #8217;s with the toenails</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 07:15:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve had minor ingrown nails- they #8217;ve been quite the nuisance. I can #8217;t even imagine what it would be like having ingrown nails THAT LARGE inside of my skin. I #8217;m so glad you were able to get both out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Where might this jacket be from? And who might #8217;ve worn it?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 20:31:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 21:18:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I found out it #8217;s Italian.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 03:34:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks way too big for 15. Also look at his wrists- they #8217;re tiny in comparison to the rest of his arms. Maybe we should measure his balls XDDD if he #8217;s on Joyce his natural Testosterone levels will drop and his balls will have shrunk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 03:36:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Their chests are hugely bloated and their wrists are disproportionate to the rest of their body. I look for bloating, breast tissue growth, face, and wrist size to determine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Check out this guy. I watch his videos (TheGoldenOne), and I #8217;m very uncertain.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 03:44:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL that Charles Dickens #8217; novels were hugely popular even among the illiterate poor. They would pool their money to hire a reader, and then gather together to listen to the stories.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 04:04:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Evening show? More like photoshopping yourself into a hotel lobby.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 04:50:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 04:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perhaps it #8217;s just INCREDIBLY suspicious lighting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 10:05:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know what a spray tan looks like. Still, the lighting irks me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Deleting Group Messages</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 08:12:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I delete a message inside a group, will the other viewers of that channel still be able to see that message? It disappears for me but would it disappear for them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Debunk This: Overall Female Inferiority</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 08:12:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 08:13:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>While a lot of these are scientific facts, not all point to inferiority. Some are even self-defeating. (For example, aggression is often counterproductive. The fact that Norskk sees it as a good or admirable trait makes me think the site is satire). And some I do not see correlation between at all. Overall, I think Norskk.is is a joke, but it #8217;s fun to see some content get critiqued regardless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 16:31:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Update: I think I made a mistake not giving context. The information alone, as many commenters point out, doesn #8217;t promote the idea of inferiority of any sex. Really what I #8217;m asking, is how true and relevant are these statistics? Would they actually affect the average man or woman #8217;s daily life? For example if women have poorer blood circulation and therefore get colder, then a woman should just throw on some extra layers. Both a man and a woman would die if placed naked in negative forty degree weather.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 00:09:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bike made in Germany, car made in China.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 01:13:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>HOW</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does there exist a reddit for discussing/asking questions about websites that might be suspicious?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 01:27:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>There #8217;s one site in particular I really want to talk and learn about. I #8217;m wondering if anyone else has ever engaged with the website #8217;s managers or anything. I ask for 100% educational purposes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 05:53:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/scams is something akin to what I #8217;m looking for. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is This Website a Scam?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 06:29:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Norskk.com It talks nonstop about  #8220;training #8221; and  #8220;manhood #8221; but mentions very little about details such as locations, policies, and who runs these programs. This group seems very sworn to secrecy. They are  #8220;off the hook #8221; if you die. (https://norskk.com/rules/), and the group cannot be sued for injury or death. The group also loves to evade criticism and the law. (https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.hellulandnews.com/talk/2017/9/22/kristinn-haukur-gudnason-we-challenge-you-to-a-holmganga%3fformat=amp). They state that they wish to settle disputes amongst members via a  #8220;traditional Norse duel #8221;, in a remote Russian land away from  #8220;modern courts #8221; (https://norskk.com/holmganga/). They have a list of people known to them as  #8220;N #237; #240;ingar #8221;, or basically anyone who has concerns, complaints or criticisms of the group. (http://xn--ningar-3vay.com/nidingar_registry.pdf) not all of the so-called  #8220;N #237; #240;ingar #8221; were in the right, but Norskk seems extremely suspicious, and has little basis in their claims (how does the public know the people on this list even exist?) so I don #8217;t blame all of the  #8220;N #237; #240;ingar #8221; actions. Even if Norskk isn #8217;t a scam, it sure isn #8217;t true to its  #8220;code of honor #8221;. (https://norskk.com/code/?rq=Code). The behavior of their representatives is not courageous, honorable, strong, brotherly, loyal, dignified, disciplined, determined, or simple. To shut people down, ignore criticism, punish doubt, and advocate for beliefs that the advocates do not even practice is cowardly and dishonest. Anyhow, what do you think?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 08:32:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't want survival training. I am aware that there are much better sources from which to get such information- ranging from outdoor skill to psychological stability and fitness. I'm simply asking this question because I do not trust Norskk.com and I do not want anyone who is unaware to fall into the trap I believe they've set.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 08:33:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be honest, I have to agree with you. Fraudulent or not, they are hypocritical liars. Anyone who attempts to buy their services will likely see the fault of their own actions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 08:35:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>But is it Halaal? I jest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 13:51:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was looking up  #8220; #218;lfhe #240; #237;nn #8221;-  #225; warrior similar I the Berserker. It just so happens that Norskk decided to steal these ancient Norse names for themselves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[PI] Write a poem, that when read backwards, it tells a very different story.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 05:40:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>(https://www.reddit.com/r/WritingPrompts/comments/26m6st/cw_write_a_poem_that_when_read_backwards_it_tells/) Maybe I was wrong. Is there a reason to live? I #8217;m uncertain #8230; Then again, life has its ups and downs The light has little room to seep through Darkness is a blanket over my world Can I push away the darkness? It #8217;s not as easy as it seems Life has grown too difficult It #8217;s all over for me They say time heals But they are wrong --- Freedom Is it an illusion? Light breaks through She waits Footsteps echo through the halls, growing louder They drag her out She is thrown against a wall All is silent The rifle cracks The barrel smokes She slumps, motionless They prod her body Other prisoners wait in line Time is running short --- He made it He is weightless Is he in a dream? He feels like he is flying His heart hammers its thundering rhythm His breathing is sharp and quick His brow is slicked with sweat Less than five minutes on the clock He pushes on He will not make it, not in time This is the end</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is there a Reddit to discuss the origins of an item?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 04:29:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>For example, I have a belt of magnificent quality that I bought in a thrift shop. It was obviously used, and though I have no intention of selling or discarding of the belt anytime soon, I would like to see if any other Redditors out here know exactly where to buy belts like it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 05:04:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I choose evil clone  #128525;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 00:26:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Judging by the size of the handles, probably.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I made dis and I hope it makes you laugh.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 19:57:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 19:58:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>(I didn #8217;t make this)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I have these Austrian suspenders. What kind of clothes would #8217;ve been worn with them? I can #8217;t use them on any of my clothes, and I #8217;m assuming there exist some kind of pants made to fit these.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 22:06:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 16:09:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Suspected that. Do you know what kind of belt these would go with?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 21:46:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re right. I #8217;d also like to say that although it is not the only contributing factor to happiness, and happiness means different things for different people, money can and often does play a large role in acquiring or making possible much of what makes a human  #8220;happy #8221;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 01:02:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll look for a suitable combat belt. Based on the wear around the top of the suspenders, I guessed some kind of pack or heavy item might've been attached there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 01:03:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>The belts I own are not compatible. I plan to search further for a better fitting belt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 01:04:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's all right, thanks for the help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guys I Need Real Help</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 01:18:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>AM I ISTP OR INTP? Look y'all I know I've brought this to the subreddit before but... I can't decide. I know I'm an introvert, because I am physically incapable of talking, plus I'm super antisocial. I know I'm a thinker, because I'm a brutal emotionless robot. I know I'm a perceiver because I can't decide whether I'm an S or an N. In fact, I can't decide anything. Please, dear redditors, help me decide whether I am a filthy sensor or an enlightened intuitive. I REALLY like to make things with my hands... but I ALSO really like to think about deep things, like the meaning of trash. I like to do adventurous stuff, like venturing out of my house, but I ALSO like to sit for days on end without eating or sleeping or drinking in hopes of achieving greater enlightenment. And most of all, I like to think I am a filthy sensor for the mere fact that I denounce the idea that I could possibly be a rare intuitive... but... the act of rejecting a societally set label is a a very intuitive kind of thing to do. Once again, I beg thee, help me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 02:54:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you good sir</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 03:53:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>A good enlightened sir (do not tell the intuitive police I said this, they will have my property seized and me incarcerated)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 07:16:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>FINALLY someone who understands where I #8217;m coming from. Look, the baby is a human being. But if this human being, fully dependent on YOUR body to sustain it, is the product of a crime or the inevitable victim of some kind of life-altering disorder, you have the right to terminate it. Banning abortion will not stop it, it will only stop safe abortion. Under only these 3 circumstances should abortion be legal. Otherwise, birth control and adoption are two perfectly good options.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This guy uses ordinary objects to complete his artwork</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 16:35:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 16:43:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes and I don #8217;t appreciate it. One cannot be too smart for his own good, and Intelligence is not so simply defined. Don #8217;t call me smart, that #8217;ll stunt my ability and will to learn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 16:44:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/theydidthemath</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 01:49:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Suggestion for any intuition based function- physically disable yourself. This will prevent you from using sensing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When your trainer leaves you alone for 10 seconds</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 07:33:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL The stereotypical anchor tattoo indicated a sailor had crossed the Atlantic.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 15:55:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 02:07:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any Se dom. It #8217;s not Nix.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This Is Sickening</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 13:13:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This restaurant has negative reviews displayed up on the walls</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 13:13:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pasta Maker</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 13:14:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A woman got breast implants made of wood yesterday.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 15:04:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 01:18:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>As my flair shows, I am a 5w4. I don #8217;t have one favorite book, but I do tend to gravitate towards nonfiction, especially nonfiction related to futurism and theories regarding humankind and our nature. (The nature of our world, too). Some of these are - The Singularity is Near by Ray Kurzweil - The Black Death: Natural and Human Disaster in Medieval Europe by Robert Gottfried - Deviate by Beau Lotto - The World Without Us by Alan Weismann - A Short History of Nearly Everything by Bill Bryson - 101 Things I Learned in Architecture School by Matthew Frederick (short and simple, but with good insight) And of course, my Enneagram rated books, namely Personality Types by Don Richard Riso and The Enneagram: Understanding Yourself and the Others in Your Life by Helen Palmer. (I #8217;m not repulsed by MBTI but few of the books appeal to me.) To answer the question, I do see a connection between my Enneagram type and my literary preference. I think this is coincidental, as I discovered my type after I learned of these books. I am drawn to theory-based books, or books intended to directly teach, rather than stories with subtle morals. I don #8217;t mind fantasy stories or realistic fiction ones, but I #8217;m the kind of person who likes information here and now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 07:37:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I cannot speak for all 4s but I can say that my dearest friend is one. She and I cooperate marvelously, sometimes creating ingenious ideas and other times generating completely random yet amusing ones. She is witty, humorous, possesses a uniquely dark sense of humor, and most of all, is always willing to engage in intellectual conversation about most anything. Though neither she nor I is perfect, we can both learn from each other and walk hand in hand on the path of life. (In case anyone is wondering, no, she is not emo)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 07:44:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, the 3 #8217;s drive is all about appearance and how they are viewed. Generally, the 3 wants to make a presentable public face, so they work hard to achieve that. But being lazy I suppose could be related to 3. Maybe if said 3 is looking to appear as if they have a perfect, worry-free life. I cannot speak for you as I am not you, but I know when I am lazy it is for two reasons: I have nothing to do, or I wish I had nothing to do and therefore end up creating a mental plan but never executing it. Occasionally, I take so much time to begin executing it that the deadline is near and I wing it. But that is beside the point. What I #8217;m pointing to is perhaps you are subconsciously trying to show the world a face of relaxedness, like all the work that need be done is. Do you know exactly why you are lazy? What do you define as lazy? More info is needed to make a better analysis.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 07:58:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that any type could be snobbish. However, there are also reasons for each to not be snobbish. Here #8217;s some loose reasoning. It #8217;s not all 100% accurate because I made this up on the spot and I am no Enneagram expert. 1: Could potentially be snobbish because they see themselves as morally superior. Could not be snobbish because their conscience tells them that snobbery is immoral and not setting a good example. 2: Could potentially be snobbish because they think they know better. Could not be snobbish because they think to help another, asserting their correctness in a direct manner is counterproductive. 3: Could potentially be snobbish because they want to flaunt their successes, so to advance their recognition. Could not be snobbish because they want to be seen as likable and snobbery generally isn #8217;t. 4: Could potentially be snobbish because they wish to be special and assert their uniqueness. Could not be snobbish because they see snobbery as  #8216;mainstream #8217; or too common. 5: Could potentially be snobbish because they wish to prove their knowledge and experience. Could not be snobbish because they think snobbery is for lesser, overemotional beings. 6: Could potentially be snobbish as to prove themselves worthy of protection, kind of in a feudalist manner. If I can be assertive and upstanding, then I am worthy of rewards and protection. Could not be snobbish because snobbery is frowned upon by some. 7: Could potentially be snobbish because they believe their methods and experiences to be superior to others. Could potentially not be snobbish because snobbery has negative consequences and potential last of privilege. 8: Could potentially be snobbish because to them, an effective leader must be. Could not be snobbish because snobbery could show underlying vulnerability. 9: Could potentially be snobbish because they think pointing group attention at them will ease the tension between others. Could not be snobbish because such behavior could lead to separation and falsely placed blame. Personally, I believe the 3 runs the highest risk of snobbery. Success needs recognition, for better or worse, and the 3 needs both.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 08:02:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know a lot folks are saying 1, 3, and 8. But I vouch for 6. 6 needs protection, and authorities protect those most worthy of protection. A 6 may not be the best clarinetist, but perhaps they think they will win approval and security if they tap into their musical side. Of course, One and 3 I put ahead of 6 always. I do not agree with putting 5 up there- 5s love expertise but to be an expert does not have to mean being the best. And 8. 8 loves to dominate, to be strong. But to be dominant does not necessarily mean to be the best. It often does, but it can also mean showing competition to the  #8220;best #8221;. 8 might love to get the gold, but I don #8217;t doubt they #8217;ll settle for silver so as long as they get a medal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 08:11:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>While tritype might be a picture-completing factor for some Enneagram users, I find it to be quite unhelpful. There are inconsistencies, like integration and disintegration that might conflict. But really what irks me is that I find the tritype was made to explain mysteries about the core type and wings that aren #8217;t actually problems of their own. Meaning, issues and anomalies the tritype is said to explain are actually just misunderstandings of what the core type and wings are meant to explain. All in all, you can use tritype if you want. Whatever works for you. I, however, choose not to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 17:21:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I may say so myself, I must admit that I experience similar encounters myself. There seems to be an ongoing stereotype that 5s can #8217;t do anything physical or emotional. While I cannot claim to be an athlete, I can soundly say that I lift weights and enjoy doing it. (This might be correlated to my fear of being physically weak). I also love to assess emotions, my own and those of others. (Again, fear of weakness but this Time emotionally). I am not by any means antisocial, but it does take me time to warm up to a person or group of people. If I should come to trust you, if I have come to realize that our relationship will be mutually beneficial, you and I are going to be great friends. I do not fear being alone, but I also prefer to have at least one or two others. Tell me if you #8217;d like to know more, because I cannot tell if I have answered your question to the fullest of my ability/ (I fear being Weak because weak Weakness equals dependence)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An Englishman, a Frenchman, a ravishing blonde and an old lady are sharing a compartment on a train as it winds its way through the Alps.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 05:17:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you're getting old</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 05:20:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 13:03:51</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Spatially unaware #8221; ME: untrue- *Proceeds to walk into a pole.*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 17:07:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Interesting. The only five I know (me) channels emotions as they are. I have come to find that repression, rather than expression, of emotion is weak. I #8217;m not heavily influenced by gender expectations, at least to my knowledge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 17:08:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Up up and away</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 03:45:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 21:25:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh dear I live in California and I can #8217;t go 72 hours without hearing something politically radical. I live in a fairly centrist area.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 04:09:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Preach my friend</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 05:32:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/pareidolia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 05:48:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 06:05:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Long ago, the four nations lived together in harmony... then, everything changed when the barbers attacked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 19:17:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Logic at its finest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 21:56:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>And Iraqi and a Turk? Why am I not surprised.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 23:22:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s not islamophobia. I believe actions like these are the result of the men being raised in a society where law and morality was based on fundamental religion. That, doubled with lack of will to assimilate and poor personal values, result in crimes like this happening. It #8217;s not just Islam that encourages and implements ideas like  #8216;rape is okay/nonexistent #8217;. Any religion taken to the extreme can be harmful to its practitioners and non-practitioners.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 23:29:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well he #8217;s not a very honest man, then. He lied to you and wants your wife to do the same. If he #8217;s not supposed to  #8220;bear false witness #8221; (lie) then he failed there. If your father cannot respect the wishes of you and your wife, you cannot trust him. Nothing you are Doing is harmful to or dangerous for the child. If anything, it is his actions that are dangerous. He is attempting to rope your son into something that your son will have no knowledge of, let alone voice against. Confront your father and tell him why he did was wrong. If necessary, sever contact with him. He cheats once, he is more than likely to cheat again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 23:33:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reasonable response. In fact, not just reasonable, a truthful response. Prayer may be what she likes to do to help herself reinforce her connection to  #8220;God #8221; or make herself feel confident. If prayer is right for her, so be it. However, she cannot force this practice onto you. If she gets upset over your response, she #8217;s in the wrong. One pair of hands working do so much more than thousand clasped in prayer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 00:33:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not perfect aerial, but [here! ](https://irvinol.deviantart.com/art/Dragon-748695018?ga_submit_new=10%3A1528410750)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 00:50:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t know how to anatomy, but [here XD](https://irvinol.deviantart.com/art/Dog-Riding-Unicorn-With-Flaming-Sword-in-Space-748697127?ga_submit_new=10%3A1528411794)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 00:51:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>No problem! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 03:11:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here #8217;s an [uncolored version ](https://magyardaughter.deviantart.com/art/Uncolored-Jonina-INFJ-748711477) And the [colored version. ](https://magyardaughter.deviantart.com/art/Colored-Jonina-INFJ-748711544) Jonina Hadad is a retired IDF officer, mother, and wife. She was born in Tel Aviv, Israel in the year 2150 A.D. Her childhood was a simple one- loving family, supportive friends and rigorous schooling. But her life was far from average- she was heiress to the throne of the New Israeli Kingdom, a nation in its infancy created as a response to the ever-changing world around it. Surges of nationalism and opposition to them forced many governments to return to monarchies, as democratic systems were taking too long to make important decisions. Israel #8217;s giant neighbor, the Levantine Caliphate, was encroaching on the tiny nation #8217;s border day by day, demanding tribute or threatening nuclear destruction. So Israel, a simple democratic state, stood defiant like it had done countless times before. It took a king, a man chosen for his wisdom and skills in leadership. That man was Jonina #8217;s father, Aaron Hadad. And the man ruled well, for 15 years until his mysterious death in the year 2056. Some suspected assassination, while others believed it was Aaron #8217;s failing health. Either way, the fact stood: Jonina was only a girl of six, and yet she was to be crowned the Queen of Israel in a short amount of time. Since she was too young to truly rule on her own, advisors and members of parliament assisted her, essentially creating a faux democracy in the time being. Meanwhile, Jonina was enlisted into the IDF, a requirement for all royal family remembers. Since it is prohibited for any royal family member to serve on the front line, Jonina serve there by mistake- her name was mixed up with another soldier #8217;s, and she suffered an injury to her left leg that required its amputation. The bullet that hit her was a R.I.P. (radically intrusive projectile) that contained as poison that would spread through the blood and paralyze its victim. She was struck in the calf, but her leg rom the knee down was removed to avoid the spread of the poison. Jonina was retired from the IDF, and a helicopter awaited her to return to the capital city of Jerusalem. However, she never showed up. Instead, someone had come earlier to pick up the heiress- her childhood friend, Yusra Al-Amin. Al-Amin was originally a citizen of the Pan-African Republic, but became a stowaway on a cargo ship bound for the United Kingdom. Al-Amin converted to Christianity, and eventually returned to her Republic and became its empress (through trickery and bribing and loopholes and charisma, of course). Haddad stayed with Al-Amin for three months, before she requested to be left in a cave in a remote forest in the Altaic Empire. It was located near the base of Mt. Fuji, and Jonina selected this particular place because of its close proximity to Yusra #8217;s summer home on the other side of the mountain. Legally, Jonina is married to Yusra. They have a biological son, Johan. This is possible because of advances in technology that permit female bone marrow to be converted into sperm. The two rarely see each other, however, and Johan is currently dwelling in a boarding school in the middle of the Atlantic on a man made island with the 8 children of other monarchs. Today, Jonina resides in her cave, meditating, praying, or contemplating. She sees a guest or two every now and then, but those who wish to find her rarely do. She believes it is possible that only she and one other know where she is- God and herself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 19:13:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re not the only one  #128064; Kind of reminds me of Mufasa on Pride Rock XD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Topographic Map Meets Augmented Reality</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 19:42:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 04:19:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Lifeguards are essential for everyone. Just watch an adult with no clue try to save anyone from drowning. 2. I have seen the Castro District in San Francisco. If taxpayer money is going toward their crosswalks, then we #8217;re in trouble. There are much more important issues to be worrying about. Like drowning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Boxing match in total darkness</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 08:27:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 16:04:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>What #8217;s an eight gate?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 16:14:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perhaps it #8217;s just me, but I see 5s, 4s, and 8s put on the  #8220;God Tier #8221; of the enneagram. It #8217;s similar to how INTJ/P, INFP and ENTJ are idolized in MBTI if you look at what traits of these types  #8220;desireable #8221; (not saying all 5s are INTxs or the like, but I #8217;m using this as an example). 5s are analytical, observant, logical. Isolated, too, and they desire independence. The INTx fits this criteria as well. It #8217;s not a cause an effect thing, where MBTI preference affects enneagram preference. People just see traits like dominance (8/ENTJ) and uniqueness (4/INFP) desirable, and are therefore drawn to types which have them. I can #8217;t say one enneagram type has been singled out as the  #8220;Mortal Tier #8221;, But if there #8217;s one type that receives an unnecessary dose of hate, it #8217;s probably the 6. They are portrayed as week sheeple who need shelter, cannot accept the truth, and are too passive aggressive to get anything done. The 9 and 3, to a lesser extent, are thrown under the bus as well for similar and different reasons. Bottom line folks, don #8217;t hate based on enneagram type. It #8217;ll just turn into MBTI.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 16:28:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would also like to add that since Intuitives are also enlightened, they do not desire not require physical touch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 07:36:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 15:18:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>While that may be true, the unfortunate truth is that many people don #8217;t care about the statistics of MBTI and its correlation to real life (I.e., masses of INFJs online). So you do offer a valid argument, but a majority of the online MBTI community is simply more interested in choosing and idolizing what type SOUNDS attractive rather than what type actually IS attractive. (based on real-world statistics).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Novel approach to encouraging recycling on the smoothie I have just finished.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 16:50:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Juan Garc #237;a, deliberately became a double agent against the Nazi's during WWII. He was so good he was awarded medals by both sides in the war. He convinced the Nazi's the D-Day landing was a diversion for an attack in Pas de Calais, so they kept large forces there before and after the invasion.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 17:34:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When your teacher used to be a gangster...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 17:37:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 20:16:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://irvinol.deviantart.com/art/Sultan-749127021?ga_submit_new=10%3A1528654539 He #8217;s supposed to be sitting, but that #8217;s not very apparent. XD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL that there is a hilariously bad Harry Potter fanfiction entitled "My Immortal". It is widely regarded to be the worst example of its genre.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 20:25:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Iceberg crack</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 04:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>By these ballet students</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 04:21:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 04:23:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Elsa chill it #8217;s not like your powers are gonna- oh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 04:42:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Username checks out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Author of "My Immortal," the Worst Fan Fiction of All Time, Has Been Identified.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 05:38:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 08:12:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I couldn #8217;t agree more. Team building requires recognition and utilization of strengths and innate ability. But personal growth requires criticism, diving into desires and habits. MBTI is about processing of information and how different people are born with different preferences for perception. MBTI is about nature. The enneagram centers around desire and behavior as an effect of it. The enneagram is about nurture. Both nature and nurture are important for self growth, but nurture moreso. I didn #8217;t mention INFJs because I thought their qualities resonated more with type 9. Only the INFJ is idolized, whereas the 9 is not. (As much).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 08:16:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;If you #8217;re not offended by your Enneagram type, that #8217;s not the right one. #8221; - Unknown And I mean, everyone #8217;s reception of their type before and after is different. I #8217;m still a bit uncertain as to what my type is (5 or 8, going with 5 for now), but to me, no type description sounds truly despicable. I have looked into the 5, and I have come to accept that it is a fair description of my motivations and responses to the external world. My thoughts and feelings to the type as a whole, however, remain neutral.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 08:25:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Enneagram Types as Tracks From the Matilda Musical</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 08:50:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>1: Miracle (About perfection, approval, positive traits and overall goodness.  #8220;My mummy says I #8217;m an angel sent down from the sky #8221;.) 2: This Little Girl (Jenny doesn #8217;t think she has the courage to speak with the Trunchbull, yet insists to herself that she must for Matilda #8217;s sake.  #8220;What kind of teacher would I be, if I let this little girl fall the cracks? I can see this little girl needs someone strong to fight by her side.) 3: School Song ( #8220;So you think you #8217;re able to survive this mess by being a prince or a princess, you will soon see, there #8217;s no escaping tragedy #8221; speaks for itself. Putting on a good face and acting dainty isn #8217;t enough to fix a real problem. ). 4: Loud ( #8220;What you know matters less than the volume at which what you don #8217;t know #8217;s expressed...you have got to be loud, loud loud, know you #8217;ve gotta learn to stand and stick out from the crowd #8221; It seems almost as if putting on a false face of exquisiteness is worthier than truly having content). 5: My House ( #8220;It isn #8217;t much, but it is enough for me #8221; Jenny goes on to list all the wonderful things about her spartan but fulfilling home, which she claims is all she needs) 6: I #8217;m Here (About loss of guardianship, begging of forgiveness, and telling the other party not to cry.  #8220;I #8217;ll be alright, with you by my side I have nothing to fear, you #8217;re here #8221;). 7: Telly (Basically comical and escapist in nature, Mr. Wormwood declares that all he knows he learned on his television, and that  #8220;The bigger the Telly, the smarter the man #8221;. He doesn #8217;t want to embrace reality, and prefers to indulge himself in something fun rather than something meaningful). 8: The Hammer ( #8220;If you want to throw the hammer for your country, you don #8217;t need sympathy or tenderness. You just need to keep your feet inside the line #8221;. Basically stating that success/satisfaction,  #8216;throwing the hammer #8217; requires only self restraint and not emotion). 9: When I Grow Up (Lists all the things great about being an adult, but makes no mention of how that #8217;s actually going to be achieved. Speaks more of a fantasy adulthood, where sweets are consumed daily and cartoons are watched on a regular basis.  #8220;I will be strong enough to carry all the heavy things you have to haul around when you are all grown up #8221;).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I couldn #8217;t cross post to here, but I found this. Anti-Vaxxers will lose their minds.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 08:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 17:50:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I made a mistake on that one. There really was no song perfect for 8, but some lyrics in this one came close. 8 is about excess, and my mistake here was not giving background information about the context of the song and it #8217;s singer #8217;s character. The song isn #8217;t suitable for the 8, but the Trunchbull #8217;s character is. (Controlling, restrictive, domineering and in denial. Lacking sympathy because she #8217;s probably unhealthy. A healthy 8, like you said, does sympathize with those they see need it.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bowl carving</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 05:59:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 06:11:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>This reminds me of those bioluminescent microorganisms on this [beach](https://www.wellandgood.com/good-travel/best-bioluminescent-beaches/amp/) .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dinner table lighting effects</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 06:11:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Snow? Bitch I'm a model train!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 06:14:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cutting aloe vera</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 06:15:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This skater defying physics</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 06:15:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Glow-in-the-dark ink</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 06:18:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MnO2 Particle Twister in a Vial</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 06:19:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Today my great grandfather Samuel Tom Holiday passed away. He was 94, a marine, a Navajo Code Talker, medicine man, and hero.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 06:40:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lighters nothing more</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 06:45:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lighters nothing more</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 06:45:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I Remade my Enneagram-Inspired Poems</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 21:39:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>***1*** One There can only be one Room for only one first place Perfection is not so simple Evil plagues the earth #8217;s face There must be someone to save the world from its fate Perhaps that someone is too late Stand straight, stand tall Before anyone can be saved Imperfections are your own downfall ***2*** My heart beats with a ring Only seeing gratitude could bring I would walk to the end of the earth To find you, to guide you A privilege it is to see your joy You are someone I cannot avoid Distance me from your love and I am void Perhaps one day we will both see I am nothing without thee And you are nothing without me ***3*** I take center stage, the audience roars My ego swells, my confidence soars I flash a smile, bright as the sun Among millions of others I am the one I love this attention, and yet something else cries Inside of me, behind mask of sweet lies I hesitate, collecting my thoughts This is not who I am, it is not meant to be Yet the only one foolish enough to believe Is me ***4*** A marionette without its strings Dancing solo in the shadows An angel without its wings Solemnly resting by nightfall There #8217;s something more, a meaning greater But perhaps such discovery is meant to be saved for later In the dark I find comfort And in mystery I am secure Pain is my director, emotion my composer This journey is far from over ***5*** Gazing out on vast beyond I seem so near yet so withdrawn Cold it is within my lair Sea of dark above grows grayer I daren #8217;t seek another place Frozen rigid from toe to face I watch the seasons pass me by Like a blur before the eye Life bustles on and on Inevitably it will soon be gone ***6*** You #8217;re so uncertain, dear What on earth is wrong? Danger lurks around the corner But it is not yet here Don #8217;t waste your time worrying About what has already gone It happens once, and won #8217;t be long Until it happens again Just close your eyes and forget All that you love and all you #8217;ve met ***7*** Free, wild soul resides within An untamed steed, never ridden Not seen bridle nor saddle Or felt the whip #8217;s lash He is bold but runs from anything brash Should man try to take him By force or by will His cry does sound shrill But alas the rope comes  #8216;round And the steed #8217;s gallant body tumbles to ground ***8*** To dominate and control is my desire My heart burns with an undying fire To seek revenge or to love another My passion is a flame and cannot be smothered With the raw power I wield I am the unstoppable force To which the immovable object yields It it just an act? One might never know To unimaginable depths my vulnerabilities go For now, it is best not to let it show ***9*** The ties of man bind the earth An unsolvable knot of death and birth Man #8217;s story is millennia old An honor it is to uphold Tales of silver and legends of gold Pray thee, humanity #8217;s legacy is not lost That greatness is not reduced to dust The net is broken with slash of the sword Should mankind #8217;s weave come undone All the world is reduced to none</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 22:29:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Glad my writing delivered the desired effect :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 02:42:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could stand to. What do you suggest?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 03:03:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I added the quote to emphasize that enneagram is not all goody-goody, probably wasn #8217;t as clear on my part as I should have been. And I could not have said it better. There are inherent negatives and positives to all types and people belonging to their respective type should acknowledge their strengths and weaknesses to better themselves as people. I am not proud nor ashamed of my type, I simply see it as one factor from which I can learn and grow from. Enneagram type isn #8217;t intended to lay out who one is as a person, but rather their motivations, what drives them, and how they can grow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 03:16:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>All is well, then.  #128077;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 05:03:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Numbers engaged in battle (because mundane numerical glyphs fighting cracks me up)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 05:10:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can #8217;t judge 100%, but based on this guy #8217;s need to place all those stickers on his car, He #8217;s giving me the impression that he himself is a snowflake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Arsonist - Extremely Vivid Dream I Had</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 20:32:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>(I remember this really well because I just woke up from it.) I was in a kind of countrylike place, somewhere that reminded me of Anza Borrego because it was so open and you could see for miles but also reminded me of Northstar because it snowed. I arrived late in the evening with my dad, and my mom had driven separately. We received an outdoor orientation (I sat with my mom, IDEK where my dad was), where my mom and I lay on these kinda chez lounge like chairs made of tightly woven, plasticish nets that were green. The one between ours was broken, so there was agap between us. At this point in time, snow blanketed the ground but not ot a point that you couldn #8217;t still see patches of dry grass. The sun was setting, and a warm, rosy haze dotted the horizon under a vivid blue before nightfall. It seems weird because when my mom and I arrived in our cabin, it felt like time had set itself back, as the sun was much more prominent in the sky and the blue was lighter. I set my hiking boots out on the balcony (the cabin was less of a cabin, and more of a 2\-story, rustic\-style home). It was situated deep in an alpine forest blanketed with snow, unlike the barren tundra from before. I don #8217;t remember how we got from one place to the other. Basically my mom stole my boots for some outing to buy some materials and returned them to me. I also went to the restroom, but hurriedly remembered that I had left something important outside, so I left the cabin, naked from the waist down which harvested me some awkward stares. I don #8217;t distinctly remember going to bed, but the dream continues onto another period late in the day. Probably the following afternoon. I #8217;m in the gift shop of the complex. There are two gift shops, one much larger and for people of all ages, and one smaller, for children. Their doors worked like garages\- nearly covering the entire building and rolling up and down into the ceiling to open or close. I took interest in the larger of the two, making my way over a mound of snow. The building was about 75 to 100 feet away, and I could tell by the looks of it that it was spacious inside. (It #8217;s weird because time seemed to fly\- it was noon and now it #8217;s near dusk. Also the store is lit well from afar, but dimly lighted when I came closer) I hurry inside, taking a peek at everything there. From tactical equipment, to clothes and souvenirs, the store had most everything a visitor might need.I noticed a round, rubberish item\- like a suction cup, but in reverse on one of the stands that held packaged axes in welded plastic. (I think they were Gerber). I took it off the stand, and placed it on one that held apparel. I browsed the store, but left seeing that there was nothing I wanted.Soon, I returned to my cabin. A few hours later, when it was dusk and the sky looked about the same as it had the night of arrival, my dad walked to the cabin and told me that the gift shop was on fire. After explaining to him what had happened ( #8220;I found a circular item, made of rubber perhaps, that I took off one rack and put on another out of boredom and curiosity #8221;). I went there, looping around and crossing a wooden footbridge that crossed over a stream (I don #8217;t recall this being here before), seeing smoke belching out of the remnants that was once a building. I said not a word, and ran back to the cabin. I couldn #8217;t help but think that I was responsible. The next day, I revisited the gift shop. Not much had changed, but the smoke had subsided. As I turned to leave, a police officer grabbed my arm. (He was about 6 #8217;0 #8221;, had a goatee and moustache that were of a reddish brown color but the rest of him was bald. He wore black sunglasses, a black t\-shitr, wrist watch, black pants and boots. He had a distinct southern accent, especially when he said the word  #8216;tell #8217;) He looked me in the eye and said,  #8220;Tell me the Truth. #8221; My dad was here with me, too, but remained silent. I repeated to the officer essentially what I had told my dad the previous night,  #8220;I found a circular item, made of rubber perhaps, that I took off one clothes rack and put on another #8221;. I actually remember specifying  #8216;clothes #8217; although that #8217;s not the case at all. My words came with difficulty, and i was hesitant, not from nervousness but from the biting cold that nipped at my exposed skin. The police officer simply nodded and jotted some notes down. I awoke to my mom calling me to have breakfast. I never found out what happened after that. \-\-\- If any interpreters want to try and interpret, go ahead. I'm putting this out here so other people can see that dreams can actually be somewhat continuous and detailed. This dream is just one of the countless other weird ones, and that's the beauty of them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 21:38:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>OH MY GOD thank you so much. You have officially made my day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 04:19:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aha the INFJ effect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 04:23:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>1: r/oddlysatisfying 2: r/YouShouldKnow 3: r/insanepeoplefacebook 4: r/confessions 5: r/TodayILearned Cp6: r/ChangeMyView P6: r/conspiracy 7: r/funny 8: r/unpopularopinion 9: r/tooafraidtoask</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 15:53:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>And we #8217;ll have the Trunchbull bolting, we #8217;re revolting!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 15:56:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely! Matilda is a very cerebral character and it shows through in Quiet. I chose My House to represent the 5 #8217;s isolation and habit of ignoring the body- refusal to move beyond their comfort zone out of fear. I think I was searching for songs that represent unhealthy versions of each type, so Quiet works perfectly for an average or healthy 5.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 00:05:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>The X is for ex. Xhamster no longer has hamsters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Encouraging below average high school students, who would need to take out loans, to go to college is not in their best interest. They need to go to trade school and learn a skill.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 17:40:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The two sons of the famous Brazilian fan that died in 2015 took his trophy and hat to Russia.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 21:19:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Most Offensive Flag 2.0 HD</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 21:26:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"Synchronised"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 23:13:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sand pendulum</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 00:39:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Okay heathens, draw Mohammed</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 01:02:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 07:33:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>69 anyone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 07:38:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. Genetically modified organisms are known to grow to absurdly large sizes. Side effects may include- \- Growth of wheels \- Headlights \- Windows \- Engines Heavily modified GMOs may turn into full blown automobiles. Please inspect for defects before consumption.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Gravity defying busking (gets crazy by the end)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 15:55:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 20:08:55</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Downboats #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why was six afraid of seven?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 21:40:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Heads down!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 22:43:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Externalisation/suppression/internalisation simplified</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 14:18:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 14:24:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was very interesting, thank you. It seems that one of the greatest ways to overcome what stands in the way of the person and their desire is to come to terms with the fact that usually, problems are multidimensional. It #8217;s rare to find a situation or issue that is ONLY internal, or ONLY external. Coming to the realization that there is a problem to begin with is also quite important. Usually, what holds a person back from achieving what they want is seeing that what #8217;s stopping them a) Exists b) Is usually caused by both internal factors and external factors Anyhow, thanks for putting this up here. (Also the way you wrote  #8220;The  #8216;gram #8221; I found to be quite funny for some reason)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 14:28:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>You figure out your main type by researching it, externally. Tests can be helpful but not always reliable. When I take tests, my 5 and 8 are nearly tied, but after online research, it was quite much more more clear to me that I was a 5. Try digging into the personality profiles of both he 2 and 9. Think about which core desire/fear fits you better. Or if another type is more descriptive of you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 14:32:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>What ails you? Is it emotional pain? Perhaps stress from work or family life? I suggest you seek deeper connection with and/or understanding of whoever or whatever is causing these difficulties. Also reflect inward: is it possible that something you yourself are doing, like running away from your problems or being expecting of others? I #8217;m not an expert but perhaps looking further into information about the 7, what mistakes they make and what they can do to alter or improve their behavior would be helpful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 17:01:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are these people relatives? Colleagues? Is there a power imbalance or are you essentially equals with these people? What do you think is upsetting you more; their actions and policies or your own?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 17:50:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m extremely sorry to hear all that you #8217;ve been through. From the looks of it, your mother is the root of the issue, and your anger. Essentially what she #8217;s doing is she #8217;s manipulating you to her will, via isolation, inconsistency and a moral sense of obligation, correct? You keep trying to find som way to support yourself but it amounts to nothing... is it unsafe to physically leave your mother #8217;s house? Does she limit your access to the outside world? Internet/phone ownership/ ETC? If not, consider seeking online help (here is a good start), or calling the national domestic violence hotline (which accounts for psychological abuse along with emotional and physical). If needed, report your case to local authorities. Since I have never been in this position, I do not know how they can help you, but they might be able to direct you to someone who can. From what you tell, your mother doesn #8217;t allow you to have meaningful relationships. Which means there is no one locally whom you can disclose your situation to, correct? Consider speaking with other adults online, through places like Reddit or other social media. They cannot rescue you, but they can at least offer emotional support. If you seek a job which you can sustain and support yourself with, look at what skills, hobbies, or interests you have. Even an opening at an existing job at a fast food chain, for example, is a good start. You could make money off of selling a product, writing, or being a musician. I #8217;m not entirely sure what you mean by bad timing, elaborate? I genuinely hope that you find peace in your life, and that your mother lays off or you at least escape her grasp. You are not a child and she should not be treating you like one, let alone destroying your relationships.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #128293; Curious tuna crabs inspecting a diver friend</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 20:04:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 20:08:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey hey hey hey moskau moskau</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mildly butt hurt sign about Rock Paper Scissors at a brunch place outside of Houston.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 21:48:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is This? It came with my shirt. There were no buttons or strings attached to it, and it was connected to the left pocket using one of those I-shaped plastic things you put on clothes tags.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 03:52:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 03:58:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s the same color as the shirt, but It seems awfully small to prevent discoloration/shrinkage. What exactly is a test fabric swatch?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 04:02:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, thanks. Perhaps it is, then  #128064;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 04:03:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Solved!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 04:11:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not just being trendy, it #8217;s Stratego. (Played once. Enjoyed.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Homosexual artist criticizing his country's treatment of homosexuals gets doxxed by Leftists for "Islamophobia"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 07:38:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 08:17:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>If anything, the doxxer is just further proving that they do not care about people or their individual rights, but rather, the interest and favors of groups that are misunderstood and overlooked. They think that islamophobia is a greater crime than the real crimes Islamic governments commit against LGBT people. That and/or they are just a terrible person who never should have pushed this onto the artist. The artist was expressing free speech, something difficult to do in Islamic and/or totalitarian nations. His opinions and observations are valid, and further backed by reality. The doxxer attempts to silence and destroy one man; and instead ends up creating further evidence that their pro-Islam narrative requires the destruction of free speech to push. NOTE: After a bit of digging in the comments, I realize that the doxxer was not politically motivated. Regardless, their action was one of either extreme malice or extreme carelessness. If they knew why the Indonesian government would do to this man knowing he was gay, they clearly wanted him dead or simply did not care if he died. People like this should not have internet privileges.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 08:18:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>He #8217;s natural. Nothing stands out, no red flags. No breast tissue growth, no acne. He #8217;s safe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 08:21:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Deport this man to wherever that girl and her mother came from. (J.K. This man is going to have a fun time in prison...)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 20:49:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw a mug like this except it wasn #8217;t personalized and had  #8220;mom #8221; instead of  #8220;dad #8221; on it. Interesting gift, XD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I will not let go</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 20:54:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This Daisy Ridley digital portrait time lapse</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 20:57:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 10:46:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Clothing has existed since virtually forever And melanin before that And hair/fur as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 10:52:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>10 years of coffee consumption and complaints about work/school, that is</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Personality Disorders and Unhealthy Enneagram Types</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 23:28:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now, I #8217;m not saying that all people with these enneagram types in an unhealthy mental state HAVE to possess these disorders. I also do not imply that unhealthy people with certain types cannot have other personality disorders beyond what is stated here. I #8217;m simply showing that there can be ties drawn between the 9 types and certain cluster personality disorders. The heart triad corresponds with cluster B personality disorders. 2 - Borderline PD (The self esteem of unhealthy 2s rests in the approval and love they gain from others, they become insecure when these things are lost) 3 - Narcissistic PD (The unhealthy 3 #8217;s absolute need for admiration, adoration and attention leaves their thoughts and concerns for others in the dust) 4 - Histrionic PD (The unhealthy 4 is extremely attention-seeking and emotionally unpredictable) The head triad corresponds with cluster A personality disorders. 5 - Schizoid PD (Unhealthy 5s often are indifferent or even afraid of social relations, and are so emotionally detached to the point that they cannot have close relationships) 6 - Paranoid PD (The unhealthy 6 is incredibly prone to lack trust in others, and will often be excessively defensive and sensitive to criticism) 7 - Schizotypal PD (An unhealthy 7 will often possess unconventional beliefs and a lack of ground in reality) The gut triad corresponds with cluster C personality disorders. 8 - Dependent PD (This one was the hardest to work with, but I found some connections. The unhealthy 8 is domineering and overtly controlling in an attempt to get people under their wing so they can take care of business that the 8 should really be doing themselves. In a way, they are dependent on their subordinates) 9 - Avoidant PD (Strong fear of rejection, feelings of inferiority, and a sense of unimportance are often present in the unhealthy 9) 1 - Obsessive-Compulsive PD (It is not uncommon to see in the unhealthy 1, an obsession with orderliness, perfection, and uniformity)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 06:21:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus nut sounds more inappropriate than it should.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 06:22:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Water has never sounded so ominous before. I love it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 06:24:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fun fact- every human who has come into contact with DHMO has died. Learn your facts, people. (Seriously though, don #8217;t stop drinking water)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 08:53:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that's a female and a male Sikh. On iOS, the female muslim has a purple hijab and the male muslim has a white turban. There are no Jewish, Buddhist, Hindu, Asatru, or emojis of many other religions I mean they haven't even had the time to make a :') emoji. It's not persecution. It's time management and budget.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 08:58:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't forget  #9962; #9766; #65039; #127877; #128146;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 17:11:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t like Atlas. Do I admire Ryan for creating, composing, and dedicating time to his project? Of course I do. Is Ryan doing his best to create his music? Most likely. But the Atlas series seems a bit...rushed. His final products feel experimental. It would be more interesting, for example, if Ryan chose a different genre for each enneagram type. I do not  #8216;like #8217; or  #8216;dislike #8217; Atlas. I like the effort and thought, the utter comprehension put into the work. I do not like the final product. I understand that he has a limited amount of time, limited resources and a limited budget. And I admire him as an artist. (Song composition, let alone songwriting, doesn #8217;t come so naturally to me so I have no right to say that his songs are bad). He is in fact, a good artist. And I do indeed listen to the Atlas series, waiting for the next song to come out. I cannot call myself a fan, nor a critic. I simply am comforted in seeing that a man finds joy in what he does.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 18:55:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I cannot speak for everyone of my type. But when I experience a loss (which I have numerous of times since the age of six), my grieving is generally short-lived. Upon hearing the news I do not react. In the next few hours, I might or might not cry a bit (most of the people who are supposed to be my  #8220;family #8221; aren #8217;t terribly good to the people I care about, nor me. So I wouldn #8217;t cry for them) depending on how much good there was to remember from our relationship. (This rule does not always apply). Eventually, my grieving concludes in my acceptance of the death of the individual (if i dislike this person, the acceptance is virtually immediate). I have come to see that death is not the opposite of life, but a part of it. Death is natural. There is no reason to be sad because of loss (unless in the case of unnatural death like a treatable illness or murder), but human emotion showing its face in times of loss is not at all a bad thing. It is natural and inborn into most of us, and everyone expresses and feels their emotions differently. Just because I do not cry does not mean I do not care. I cherish and remember who people were, what they did, and what they meant to me. I am stronger because they lived, not broken from their death.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 20:18:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Quicksand isn #8217;t that deep. The giraffe #8217;s greatest dilemma is rolling out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 20:24:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can do this on my left hand but not on my right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Crosspost</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 21:54:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 02:42:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, thank you for correcting my mistake! It is important that we band together as an online community to banish the usage of such a harmful and evil chemical!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 02:48:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>This completely contradicts the Left #8217;s narrative that  #8220;Illegal is not a race #8221;. It isn #8217;t. But this picture makes it appear like they believe so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 06:48:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is a reason bullies bully. They were either harassed by others or suffer from psychological problems. Assist and deal with them, away from their victims. Schools acting as if everything is just fine will end up with even more issues. They ostracize the victims and do nothing to correct the perpetrators. Sometimes bullies do not care about what others think or say. Punishment is necessary. Involving the law, even, can be a necessity. Simply making EITHER party embrace the other, both physically and psychologically, is unhelpful and even counterproductive. This light treatment and mishandling of bullying has been taken too far. It #8217;s lead to suicides, school shootings and countless other preventable tragedies. All humans should be taught the value of kindness, the rewards of honesty, and the lesson of courage. Do what is best for yourself and others, and don #8217;t let anyone push you around. It #8217;s not a solution, but it is a means of prevention. Should people fail to acknowledge this, and act out violently, punishment and corrective processes must be implemented. (I also somehow misread the title as  #8220;12-year-old Girl shoots up school and kills self #8221;. Not good at all.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 09:27:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, but he #8217;s a juicer. How on earth is it even remotely possible that someone with such an uncut jawline managed to naturally attain that physique. Even if this man ain #8217;t a caprisun package, his head has been exposed to some unnatural form of hair removal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 18:38:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Sith Order is an 8w7.  #8220;Peace is a lie, there is only passion Through passion, I gain strength Through Strength I gain power Through power, I gain victory Through victory, my chains are broken The force shall free me #8221; - Sith Code The Jedi Order is pretty 1w9 to me.  #8220;There is no emotion, there is peace. There is no ignorance, there is knowledge. There is no passion, there is serenity. There is no chaos, there is harmony. There is no death, there is the force. #8221; - Jedi Code The Gray Jedi  #8220;order #8221; seem to be a 5-ish thing but with what wing, I don #8217;t know. I was guessing w4 (HAHA Bias JK), because the code welcomes contradiction, and leaves its followers to interpret it as they wish. It speaks about how strong emotion is necessary, yet is balanced and counteracted by calmness. (Others mention this code is 9-ish, just adding this footnote to acknowledge my agreement with them).  #8220;There is passion yet peace There is strength yet serenity There is power yet harmony There is chaos yet order In life there is freedom In death there is purpose I will do what I must to guard the balance For the force is all things, and I am the force. #8221; - Unofficial Gray Jedi Code</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 18:41:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t get me wrong, I enjoy my phone, too. But there #8217;s a balance between music, YouTube rant videos, chatting with friends, calling, texting, social media and google. My preferences are slightly biased, and don #8217;t get me wrong, I #8217;m a complete phone junky too, but what apps I use and things I prefer are not strongly skewed. I like being physically alone, not so much psychologically.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 18:44:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your results show that you are most likely a 5 with a 4 wing. (If you want to get a more accurate view and outlook on Enneagram, I suggest you browse around online, in places like here, or read Enneagram-related books. I take tests and keep getting 8, but the 8 description, core fears and desires hit nowhere as close to home as the 5 ones do. Just because your assessment reads 5, doesn #8217;t mean you are one. What type you are is up for you to research and find out about).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An elephant stops to get a turtle off the road.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 18:58:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 19:08:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Regardless it can be agreed that his hair loss is a result of SOMETHING or another.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 02:24:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>True. I see what you mean, considering many 9s mistype themselves as 5s due to their analytical nature.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This adorable baby elephant gets dizzy after chasing some birds</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 02:52:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Islamic word for critical thinking is Shaitaan. Question everything. Believe nothing. Trust no one</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 08:07:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This rim job</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 17:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why do programmers get confused between Halloween and Christmas?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 17:03:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #128293; Rare white giraffes caught on camera for the first time</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 20:06:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 22:59:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my god I #8217;m quivering with rage, how dare these damn bigoted transphobic racist sexist homophobes not understand that my pronouns, jfobcsklxalxkflvkdp andkvkdjvodvjfkvkjgvkself, are completely fucking valid. This is simply outrageous.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 23:01:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are three kinds of pronouns in the English language- Masculine, Feminine and Neutral. Choose one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:33:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>The purpose of life is to give life purpose. Man is responsible for his own fate. For his own destiny. For his own meaning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:34:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is no bad or good type. It is how you behave, react, interact, learn and think. Any type can be healthy or unhealthy, given circumstances, upbringing, and innate nature.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm a gay man, and I'm beginning to hate women</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:59:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I convinced my friends that our dorm is haunted by a 5-year-old lesbian ghost</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:34:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I know this subreddit is for discussion, but...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 10:11:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>...Would anyone be interested in some Enneagram-related drawings? I'm a bit of an amateur, and looking for others interested in the Enneagram to give feedback/comments. UPDATE: It seems the answer is yes. Here goes nothing. Brace yourselves. [1 ](https://magyardaughter.deviantart.com/art/Enneagram-1-Colored-Again-751093785) [2](https://magyardaughter.deviantart.com/art/Enneagram-2-Colored-Again-751093758) [3](https://magyardaughter.deviantart.com/art/Enneagram-3-Colored-Again-751093729) [4](https://magyardaughter.deviantart.com/art/Enneagram-4-Colored-Again-751093690) [5](https://magyardaughter.deviantart.com/art/Enneagram-5-Colored-Again-751093645) [6](https://magyardaughter.deviantart.com/art/Enneagram-6-Colored-Again-751093612) [7](https://magyardaughter.deviantart.com/art/Enneagram-7-Colored-Again-751093578) [8](https://magyardaughter.deviantart.com/art/Enneagram-8-Colored-Again-751093488) [9](https://magyardaughter.deviantart.com/art/Enneagram-9-Colored-Again-751093441)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hummer with Reconfigurable wheel track</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 11:01:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 11:02:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 11:02:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m starting out with enneagram-based characters who might end up in an ongoing comic one day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 11:05:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be wonderful. Should I create a separate post, or add on here?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 11:16:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok I #8217;ll put them here (Brace yourself for cringe)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 11:21:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a bunch of really terrible scenarios planned out in my head. : #8217;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 11:57:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, thank you! 4... is a bit of an anomaly. A sweet, smol anomaly, but still an anomaly. And a worshipper of the late MCR, 8 is a... Fascist wannabe. She thinks being a Fascist will somehow enhance her ability to control others, but is unaware (and frankly unwilling) to learn about the negative side of fascism and totalitarianism as a whole. 5 does look quite 1-ish, I admit. Her outfit is kind of based off of a more modern standard (at least for me) whereas 1 #8217;s is intended to be more traditional. This is probably just a stereotype I perpetuate (and shouldn #8217;t) but I view the typical 1 as more of a traditionalist, loyal to the past, while the 5 in contrast is more interested in progress or assimilation of traditionalism into ever-changing society. I suppose both types do either or both, depending on the individual and the situation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 12:05:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aspiring artist, aspiring physician, maker of dreams and thief of them simultaneously. ISTP/INTP.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Collection of my tiny paintings, acrylic on penny</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 12:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 17:37:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the NOAA Pisces, an American research vessel launched in 2007 and active since 2009. [Original video](https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=64dAv9sk7GE) [HERE is the launch of the Henry B. Bigelow](https://youtu.be/epJtFMjV_FI)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does this belong here?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 17:48:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:12:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>XD glad you could relate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:30:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why, thank you. I agree, to portray anything inanimate or conceptual as a human or humanoid is no simple feat. It #8217;s good knowing I was able to communicate the intended message through most. A pleasure it is to see that you connect with my perception of each type through body language, expression, and appearance. I definitely could have done a better job with the 2. I simply colored over old sketches of mine, putting little to no thought into revisions or repositions of the characters, so that #8217;s an error on my part which I might fix soon. And you have a valid point with the 3 as well, quite not as dynamic as one might ask for. I was kind of going for that  #8220;I #8217;m a celebrity who just won an award and I have to strike a pose #8221; look, but perhaps it could have been conveyed better. I am a 5w4. I don #8217;t believe heavily in the tritype theory, but mine is 584. Personally, my design for 5 is my favorite, appearance-wise. When I say appearance I mean physical features, facial structure and body type (well not so much the body type part, 5 is supposed to be underweight and masking it with her jacket). I believe I could have taken more time to shade, redesign and alter all 9 of the characters more to fit my mental image of how they should look, but I can overall see improvement from the days when I personified MBTI.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:30:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aw, thank you. 7 certainly strikes me as an upbeat, carefree type (sometimes to a fault).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 21:30:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>~~4~~ ~~claims he has no knowledge of the emo subculture~~ ~~:')~~ In all fairness, 4's idea is that not all followers or participants in a subculture have to conform 100%. It's backfiring, because 4 cries himself to sleep every night while listening to *Welcome to the Black Parade* on his dollar store-bought earbuds. And thank you! It's fascinating seeing both the physical and personality similarities between real life people and fictional ones.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Whole new level of insane</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 22:21:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Poncho the police dog "saving the life" of an agent</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 01:50:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Underwater sinkhole</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 02:27:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #128293; Giraffes have an 18 inch prehensile tongue, here #8217;s how they use it  #128293;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 02:27:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"I'm straight"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 02:28:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My uncle was part of the MEK in 1979. After the revolution he was captured by the new founded government when he was 17 and kept in prison for 8 years with 100000* other teens and executed. While in prison he made a frame with "Azadi" brand cigarette packages. in Persian, Azadi means Freedom</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 03:08:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Brunette + redhead</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 04:37:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>NSFW Motorcycle crash in HD</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 08:35:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I brought a song back with me from a dream. I cant even play piano. I have no idea how my mind created this song.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 08:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 09:06:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>They were also... less racist in some ways. And pro-Islam. At least, their leader created Indian and Arab SS units, likely to prey on their hostile feelings for the Brits. But really, there were Asian, African, Indian and Arab SS divisions and/or members. Hitler hated Slavs, Roma and white Jews more than these people. Hell, there were even Jews in the Wehrmacht (Werner Goldberg, for example, dubbed the ideal soldier). I am against Hitler and his supporters, but at least Hitler and his men had fashionable uniforms. Oh, and hair. Hair is a very important factor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 09:12:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pride is for achievement, not how a person is born. Agree 100%.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When they invite you for a dinner and serve only organic food</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 09:17:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I brought a song back with me from a dream. I cant even play piano. I have no idea how my mind created this song.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 09:17:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 09:23:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had no idea fish swam so close to the shore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 09:32:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh definitely. Hitler declared East Asian culture as equal to that of Western Europe. The Swastika as Hitler depicted it is Indian in origin, but other forms of the swastika like the Fylfot and Kolovrat are native to Europe. It must be agreed that the irony is clear, Neo-Nazis clearly don #8217;t do their research, nor do they care about history.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So clean..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 09:34:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Female soilder almost gets shot by ISIS and laughs in the face of death</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 09:50:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 11:03:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are small inconsistencies and lies riddled into every authoritarian regime, that start small but grow more and more apparent as time goes on. Eventually, the entire basis the party and individual was founded on falls apart and all that is left is the shell of a once thriving nation. Hitler, Stalin, Mao, all of them. They made a lie and eventually, it was perpetuated by the people themselves. Most never knew anything different.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 19:03:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>A popular argument is that tritype theory focuses on issues and questions that can be answered with deeper studying of the original enneagram. It #8217;s unnecessary, in other words. I #8217;m pretty neutral on the whole issue, do as you please. I prefer not to use tritype theory in my studying of the enneagram.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 22:19:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fun at work with 1377 pallets</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 23:06:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Amazing Costume</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 01:34:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sir, can I have some?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 01:37:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 01:44:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mediocre coffee, great tea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 01:49:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t believe in astrology either, but I will forever be cancer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 01:51:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have an upvote for a truly unpopular opinion, my friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 02:31:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>No problem. ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Making a hidden knife inside coins</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 05:28:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 07:58:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>'Square wave' by Ivan Black sculpture, based on the Fibonacci</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 08:00:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>'Square wave' by Ivan Black sculpture, based on the Fibonacci</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 08:00:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 18:39:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>What #8217;s the maximum amount of names you can submit?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 21:12:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>All right, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 21:14:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ansel Johan Caesaria Vier Karol Gretchen Sagar Raina Roman</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Reddit For Identifying Patches?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 06:03:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Military, police, E.T.C.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>These starbucks cups have the McDonald #8217;s logo on them.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 09:17:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 02:40:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>A human being</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Malena and Natasha</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 02:42:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 11:13:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s beautiful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 00:55:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>16Personalities is not MBTI. At the top of its questions, it reads 'NERIS Type Explorer' in fine print. Like you point out, there is no mention of cognitive functions in any of the site's articles, and rarely in user discussions. I cannot say that it is reliable or unreliable, it all boils down to what you're looking for.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This guy wearing both camouflage and high-visibility clothing.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 23:48:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Those are some uneasy buttons.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 03:18:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This quarter and its real-life correlate</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 03:18:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tetrahedral racks.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 15:02:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tetrahedral racks.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 15:03:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Attainable Naturally?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 03:44:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 03:47:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love broccoli.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Disney experimenting with robotic acrobats to perform stunts.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 04:10:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Single brush painting</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 11:24:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[WP] Humanity is the only intelligent species that can directly sense electromagnetic radiation. This means that humanity are the only ones who can see the stars without expensive scientific equipment.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 12:03:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[WP] We have been wrong all along. The sun is really just the fiery eyes of a Celestial Being who hasn't blinked in a second of it's own time. Which it is currently about to do.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 12:05:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 20:26:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>There #8217;s a building in my area whose exterior resembles this one. I #8217;ve only passed it on the road, never had the chance to catch he address. I #8217;m pretty sure said building is not the same one, just mentioning this because perhaps such a stone configuration is not as uncommon in architecture as one might think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Vacuum excavator is so powerful it literally sucks up the ground</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 20:28:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Jedi #8217;s Signature Weapon</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 04:31:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Umm... Let me think...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 04:33:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This rock has a perfect quartz stripe.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 04:36:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Something to enhance the experience of hot glue guns...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 05:17:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>...a machine where you can dump all the hardened glue your botched attempts. The machine molds the glue into more sticks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Inflating an evacuation slide.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 08:19:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Filipino Christians apologize to the LGBT community during the Philippine Pride Parade 2018</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 08:20:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 12:22:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Both nature and nurture. People are predisposed to certain personality traits, while our development and how we react to events and such are molded by our upbringing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 12:56:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that a 4Runner TRD Pro? A family member of mine has one of those. (Just not in orange).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>These are the weirdest looking clouds I've ever seen</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 00:24:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Aerated Sand Moves Like Water. This is Both Black-magic and Fuckery</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 00:30:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 00:33:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see counterclockwise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Things we do for love</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 07:15:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is astonishing: Inside Van Gogh's painting</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 11:00:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is astonishing: Inside Van Gogh's painting</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 11:00:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 12:17:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>9 horns...or none.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 12:38:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>They #8217;ll find a cure for cancer, but lets cure this world of astrology-believers first.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 20:01:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve seen it! I #8217;m impressed with the dedication and talent that went into painting each and every frame. It also helped me catch a glimpse into the life of VanGogh and our understanding of him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Visual explanation of density</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 20:35:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 05:40:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://youtu.be/dSixcSx-5h0 No problem. I think it #8217;s a virtual reality thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 07:29:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read this as  #8220;confused liquid #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Toyota off-roading truck getting it done</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 07:30:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Toyota off-roading truck getting it done</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 07:31:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Traditional lace being handmade</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 13:33:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Traditional lace being handmade</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 13:33:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The way the ice breaks</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 21:06:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 21:13:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, I am your father.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Reddit For Where to Find Things?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 00:26:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like r/whatisthisthing, but where you already know what its purpose is, and where you can buy more of them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 06:12:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/suddenlygay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Batman-like tech used by police</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 06:39:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Batman-like tech used by police</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 06:39:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 06:46:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>( O Y O )</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 15:37:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>5w4, INTP (My flair says ISTP on all of the MBTI subreddits because I was skeptical about belonging to a  #8216;rare #8217; group of intuitive preferring individuals).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 05:55:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Little does this person know that watermelons were selectively bred to have small/no seeds. The plants that are the true  #8220;natural #8221; watermelons sported gigantic seed pouches.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You've seen a doggo reaction, but have you seen a birdo reaction?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 16:06:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Non-Newtonian liquid on a speaker at 12,500 FPS</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 16:07:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 16:08:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>How would you know if they #8217;re a good speaker or not? I could see this being used as atrial for something but probably not an actual election.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This nailgun that shoots wooden nails.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 14:30:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Stairway to Heaven firework.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 20:19:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 09:02:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen [this poll](https://www.change.org/p/facebook-bring-the-facebook-messenger-emoji-font-back) before. I don't know what else can be done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Empty industrial bags device</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 09:09:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A sadist, a masochist, a murderer, a necrophile, a zoophile and a pyromaniac are all sitting on a bench in a mental institution, bored out of their minds.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 08:31:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The biggest sinkhole in China</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 05:06:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An owl sitting with its legs crossed.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 02:16:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Space saving corner</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:57:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 07:25:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have an Aquarius cousin who would pour water on me when I annoyed him. It was... a good time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 07:59:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tend to be drawn to more obscure and independent bands, who vaguely fall under certain labels but tend to pull elements from other genres. Two of my favorites are Amaranthe and Icon for Hire. Apart from themes and genre, the two bands were both formed by Swedes. How coincidental.  #8220;Digital World #8221;,  #8220;Massive Addictive #8221;,  #8220;Drop Dead Cynical #8221; and  #8220;Automatic #8221; are some of my favorites by Amaranthe.  #8220;Pop Culture #8221;,  #8220;Pulse #8221;,  #8220;Counting on Hearts #8221;, and  #8220;Iodine #8221; are my favorites of Icon for Hire, though I admit all three of their albums resonate well with me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 08:00:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m a 5 and I intend to learn how to drive a stick shift.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 08:03:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dreams generally follow themes of elapsing time, authority, exploring the unknown, whether physical or metaphorical (and sometimes getting caught), scenarios involving the real world and people from it, and human interaction.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 08:07:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m far from nihilistic. I do believe that life and all that we perceive has no inherent meaning or value, but I also see it that man places value on things, therefore giving them some kind of meaning. Certain enneagram types might show preference for or bias toward particular philosophical ideas, but correlation does not equal causation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 03:57:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for singling my type out (JK)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 14:19:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>With the two-party system as it is today, the chances of this would be slim. I hear a lot about Zuckerberg or Winfrey running for president, but I do not think this is the wisest plan of action. If influential, powerful people funded a third party or third party candidate, the chance of an independent president assuming office would be much higher. A majority of voters aren #8217;t as far left or right leaning as many of our candidates are. I come from a stereotypically liberal area of the world, yet most of the folk my age are very centrist. If we had a candidate whose values aligned with a good deal of the general population #8217;s, this country would be much less divided.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Restoring a sun damaged carpet</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 02:00:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Balcony aquarium</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 06:35:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 06:41:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>The first fertile offspring of Jar Jar and a giraffe, 2018. May this scientific breakthrough go down in history.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 14:46:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not a huge fan of sports, but come on. If others enjoy it, I #8217;m not going to give them an issue about that. Sports are popular for a reason.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Compilation</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 22:30:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Compilation</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 22:30:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You ain #8217;t human  #8216;till you white.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 09:59:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 10:10:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I gave this post the 174th upvote. Was sad to see the proportional ratio go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SecuriT-pose</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 10:13:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This isn #8217;t helpful.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 19:35:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 02:54:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even if OP didn #8217;t know what they meant, their post still makes 100% sense. From this, we can assume OP does know what the meanings of these words are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 05:56:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You look just like my friend. I bet you and she would get along well. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 06:10:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with a lot of what you said. Ben Shapiro, while not a terrible person and with some good points, has a horrendous voice which cannot be understood. And yes, he does speak predominantly to audiences which agree with him. It #8217;s frustrating how he never debates those with actual knowledge of a subject. Sometimes I think that his political reasoning is a bit skewed by his religion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Look at That 2</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 10:27:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This incredible art piece</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 10:35:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 07:25:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look at that stretch mark.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is he natty? 19, claims 5 #8217;8 #8221;.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 07:26:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 07:35:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Y</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 07:35:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 07:35:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Y</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Roses are red, violets are blue, sugar is sweet, and so is _________</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 07:37:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Behind the scenes of a chocolate ad.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 11:18:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lego Stop Motion</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 01:19:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 10:02:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Conjoined twins with mutant limbs. No for real. I saw the two women as connected and the man with like, 4 legs at first.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 10:05:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mike is lemonade.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Setting a cup</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 10:10:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 06:12:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t know why I #8217;m saying this, but the inside of his vest has the same pattern as one of my neckties. Anyhow, he #8217;s an incredibly talented musician. Good on him!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 18:27:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cecil</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>'The Infinity Cube' - Anthony Gormley. Found at Kettle's Yard, Cambridge.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 09:47:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>'The Infinity Cube' - Anthony Gormley. Found at Kettle's Yard, Cambridge.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 09:47:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 18:16:27</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;God is the authority (head) over Christ, Christ is the authority over man, and man is the authority over woman. This is how God designed the system to work, and if you don't like it, then go find some pagan god to serve. (That's what the world typically does; find a god that suits their personal tastes.) #8221; And this is exactly what the author of this article is doing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Curious...Will take a look at this later</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 06:46:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The way the pen glides across the paper</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 08:20:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 08:22:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>More like cePHALLUS.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 11:34:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m bussexual don #8217;t judge me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 01:53:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>The villain of my main work very much loves the protagonist(s). He thinks of them as his children, despite none of them being at all related. His dominant issue is that he is extremely controlling, but this is because he wants what is best for his  #8220;children #8221;. He refuses to listen to their desires and dreams, as he has created a set mold of what he sees as best for them and their lives. Another villain happens to be the  #8220;damsel in distress #8221; who has completely won the hearts of a few, but she is conspiring with the first villain by prying secrets out of those whose love is hers. The only issue is, she genuinely loves one of the protagonists she #8217;s seduced. She wants to protect said protagonist from the first villain. When she reveals her true feelings, the protagonist is at first accepting, but then realizes that the seductress has no intention to help their friends. The seductress, being rather possessive and selfish, proclaims that she #8217;ll kill herself if the protagonist does not run away with her. This is just one example of desperation clouding this villain #8217;s judgement, and her lack of tact.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 01:56:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m rather fond of plots like these. Especially where the antagonist is a force, like disease. Where you take this trope is interesting too, because it often does a good job of illustrating gray morality and relativity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 02:11:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Either  #8220;The protagonist is an unassuming child from a lower class of society who aspires to find a job so bizarre, that the nobles can #8217;t keep their noses out of the protagonist #8217;s business. #8221; Or  #8220;The protagonist is a combative motherfucker who hates listening to others, hates attachment, hates consistency, hates details, and is trying to become a yarn spinner. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 03:14:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>My sisther won #8217;t like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You don #8217;t NEED anyone of any race to make a good movie, but this is taking it a bit too far.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 04:19:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 04:23:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>If anyone said this about any other race than white, Tumblr would be on them in no time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Never knew it was so easy.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 05:52:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 06:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same thing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 07:02:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>This condition is called Leucism, which is  #8220;...a condition in which there is partial loss of pigmentation in an animal resulting in white, pale, or patchy coloration of the skin, hair, feathers, scales or cuticle, but not the eyes #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 07:03:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a Californian myself, this makes me laugh. I #8217;ll buy one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This unicorn picture is different in the mirror</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 07:06:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Old but gold.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 22:08:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 01:23:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do these characters look like?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>not a spoilery title</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 04:35:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dad making his little girl's dreams come true despite life being in the way</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 04:36:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 06:05:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just goes to show the effects of assumption. My bad. I can #8217;t say it #8217;s political propaganda that made me think the protestor was innocent. I think it #8217;s mostly the fact that I myself have experienced prejudice based solely on my opinion, and subconsciously related my experience to a photo for which I had no context. I don #8217;t even like BLM.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This water cleaning chemical used by the UN.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 06:07:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 06:13:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god I #8217;m infrared of being assaulted How frightening At least I #8217;m not ultraviolet of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 08:03:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Technically, orgasms achieved by masturbation differ from those achieved during sex.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yes Blue Diamond. Yes they do.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 16:30:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 16:31:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/Tposememes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 00:39:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/ainbow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 02:19:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here you go](https://imgur.com/gallery/HdccBrP)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>'Olive in Martini glass' circular motion demo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 05:23:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>'Olive in Martini glass' circular motion demo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 05:23:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Flooded nature trail in Brazil</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 05:24:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 17:48:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re welcome!  #128512;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>One day we will get there, little robot. Happy Birthday to you!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 17:52:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This broken mug</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 01:36:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>High speed laser engraving.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 01:39:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 01:44:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t know 100%, But it seems to me as if women are more invested in astrology because historically, women have had less control over their lives and fates than men. Therefore, they look for some way to comfort themselves or confirm their destinies and such. One of the biggest money-making schemes out there that claims to help with this is astrology, and so women buy into it. Or they just like reading horoscopes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>no thank you</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 01:45:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 22:26:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sugar daddies unite</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 23:40:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>If knowledge is a curse, you ain #8217;t using it right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Kinetic sculpture of Franz Kafka #8217;s head by David Cerny</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 06:43:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Humpback whales coming up in front of a lodge in Canada</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 06:44:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Green Screen Tattoo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 06:56:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Monkey Amazed By Card Trick</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 03:55:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Effect of the tides</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 00:18:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Effect of the tides</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 00:18:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Heavy Metal fans notice a woman in a wheelchair who couldn #8217;t see...so they brought her to the front!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 02:23:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 02:35:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s nice, but why does she have a shofar?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ice diamond  #128142;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 03:13:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Oh my god why</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 03:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Modified fire extinguisher</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 03:58:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 04:06:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me every Monday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 06:37:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll go with this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 06:57:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 07:04:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Isn #8217;t this the international spy museum in Washington DC? If not, they have something similar there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 08:14:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>And they say Karma isn #8217;t real.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 08:21:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/technicallythetruth</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 08:22:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/tposememes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The local fire department told they town that they got a new truck in the form of a  #8220;birth #8221; announcement.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 02:40:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 03:20:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hopelessness, emptiness. Scenarios that mighty induce this feeling include seeing others better off/happier/more successful/more satisfied than I. When I feel as if my life adds up to nothing, when I fear that my efforts to better myself aren #8217;t working as fast or as effectively as they should, when I fear that no matter what I do or how I do something, that I #8217;ll never be sufficient. Generally, no real-world scenario has brought this out in me, at least not to the extent that it would actually affect my day-to say functioning. Most of my fabricated scenarios are hypothetical and nothing more than that. I do my best to learn from my mistakes and troubleshoot both before and after something goes awry. I have confidence that my fears will not come true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just kidding!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 13:09:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sand instead of blinds</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 21:41:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 21:51:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honorary r/accidentalswastika</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 22:04:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>At this point in my life, I haven #8217;t solidly settled on or in one career or another. However, I aspire to build a career off something I love, such as writing or other forms of art like drawing. Perhaps combining the two into a graphic novel. I wish to spread messages about the world, its inhabitants, and the dynamics between people, either groups, individuals, or themselves. Unfortunately, I cannot rely solely on an art-based career, lest I be extremely dedicated and fortunate. A more realistic career in my future might be that of a medical doctor, a lawyer or a psychologist. These careers involve working with others, understanding the human psyche, and developing ideas and conclusions about people, their minds, motives, and deeds alike.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Insane perspective on just how immense The Great Pyramid of Giza is</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 03:25:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Insane perspective on just how immense The Great Pyramid of Giza is</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 03:25:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 03:49:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>5w4. I believe that for the most part, others see me the way I see myself. My views of myself are predominantly rooted in my actions and others #8217; receptions of them. Since I also strive for authenticity, I do my best to put on a public face that matches who/what I am and how I think/feel. I like to be viewed by others as rational, open-minded, humorous, creative, resourceful, level-headed, confident, knowledgeable, helpful, and versatile. I like to interact through conversation, either through texting/the internet, or in person. Talking about others #8217; lives and my own, as well as introspective subjects that pertain to various aspects of life are prime focal subjects. Exchanging ideas and criticisms of art, writing and performances, when shared between me and someone of similar interests, can be helpful as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Synchrony</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 08:45:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 08:46:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/blackmagicfuckery</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Playing on marshland</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 08:56:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 09:27:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t think even soldiers get a free collage. It #8217;s too... Scrappy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does a Fantasy Novel/World Absolutely NEED Magic?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 09:41:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>The project I am currently working on involves no magic at all, but is set in an alternate universe in an early medieval setting. There are no mythical creatures, no wizards and witches, no nothing. It #8217;s basically the 12th century old world, with slightly different geography and cultures. The plot surrounds a mystical object, but said object is shown later to not have any magical properties. Can a story like such still be considered fantasy?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 09:51:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Threadbare</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 10:03:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>NOPE</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 10:11:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 10:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/sweatypalms</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 10:19:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never heard of it. Do you recommend?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 19:09:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>It did!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 19:49:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fighting evil by moonlight, winning love by daylight, never running from a real fight, she is the one named sailor moon! Honestly though that black cat did it for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:25:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/pareidolia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Magician tricks a cop</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 06:40:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mewtwo the philosopher</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 08:00:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 02:44:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>666</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 02:49:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>As long as the authority lets me be, I shall let it be. Authority must be present solely for the regulation and protection of a person or group of persons. A small group of persons may be self-governing and without any authority other than morality itself, but as the size of a population grows, so does the need for authority. When any authority overrides a person or persons #8217; rights, it no longer serves its intended purpose and must either be purged or reformed. Even in times of peace, no authority may go without ridicule or without question. As for me personally, authority does not affect me on a large scale in day-to-day life. Clearly, I abide by the law and respect those who wield more power than I UNLESS the power wielding entity is directly violating my rights. I exist harmoniously with most authority, and the small fraction of abusive potential authorities play such a small role in my life that I can easily evade them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 02:53:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>My Life as a Zucchini.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 03:18:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>5w4. I believe the experience of parenting can help not only the child, but also the parent(s) grow, learn, and become better people. Additionally, having someone who looks up to you can be quite a joy. So yes, I would one day be interested in having children. Not biologically, however, because the process is just such a grueling process that can be rather risky and overall uncomfortable. Besides, there are plenty of children who don #8217;t have homes and are in dire need of such.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shoplifting Ant, Steal Diamond From Jewelry Store</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 07:30:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 07:31:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/whyweretheyfilming</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;m Really, REALLY Sorry</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 07:58:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 07:59:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had to make this meme into an Enneagram thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 08:12:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/natureisfuckinglit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #128293; Chicago Reflected in Lake Michigan From Airplane</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 08:19:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 08:20:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Original: https://www.reddit.com/r/woahdude/comments/96u4z4/chicago_reflected_in_lake_michigan_from_airplane/?st=JKRVZ0YR amp;sh=696d2890</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I hate the "Stop Bullying" movement.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 10:21:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 11:53:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/vaxxhappened</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 21:11:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my god</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 21:11:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>120% me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 21:12:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>: #8217;))) such is life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 01:18:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>*bastard</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 01:47:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>1: *touches hand to heart.* Right here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 06:05:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/wholesomememes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 15:17:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really? Thanks for telling me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 08:54:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, and?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 09:03:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>5w4, here are a few off the top of my head. Songs that generally focus on introspective/self-analysis or analysis of the world in some way. And of course, there are always lyric-free songs I love. Pop Culture by Icon For Hire  #8220;And the beat goes on, drone drone like a metronome Day in and day out I know how the story gonna go Typical, typical, tongue tied and weak willed Stuck on the sedative, evidently to sleep well But I haven't slept in days, I haven't dreamt in nights I've been busy building theories I just can't wait to try #8221; Make a Move by Icon for Hire  #8220;Test my reality Check if there's a weak spot Clingin' to insanity Hopes the world will ease up Try to make it look like it's all somehow getting better 'Cause I know how to play it pretty good against the measure Everyone started out a little insane But we learn pretty quick how to fake it for the game But some of you never learned to drop the act So under that skin of yours: a heart attack #8221; Drop Dead Cynical by Amaranthe  #8220;Welcome to the new world Open up the gates of paradise So let's get cynical Run into a new maze Open up your minds And soon we'll all Be drop dead cynical Be drop dead cynical It's your illusions, fatal contradiction I need the action premonition I like to thrill you, I am what inspires Let you explode in a cosmic fire #8221; Massive Addictive by Amaranthe  #8220;Massive addictive And suddenly I'm greatly affected Like burning fire inside My cyanide Scared of losing my mind Massive addictive I'm totally completely afflicted As I inspire the lie like a lullaby Crawling around in my mind Unremitting Demand of my hunger Time stands still As I am losing the grip of it all Like a thousand times before Give me antidotes Constant removers Make an instant deductive denial in vain 'Cause I always stay the same And now it's time to be reborn Although I know it's addictive #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 09:15:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can understand fairly well the 6 and 4 archetypes- it is within our human nature to be worried and to develop an identity. That #8217;s a huge oversimplification, but you get the general idea. All of the enneatypes embody a particular part of human nature (correctness, sacrifice, presentability, identity, knowledgeability, preparedness, strategy, righteousness, diplomacy) that everyone has but is heightened in some more than others. All seem fairly understandable to me, but I relate best to types 8 and 4 besides my own.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 09:22:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mom is an ENFP 2w1, 269 tritype if you believe in the tritype theory, I #8217;m not 100% sure that my mom isn #8217;t a mistype, but she sure doesn #8217;t seem like one. She #8217;s very abnegating and selfless, righteous as well sometimes to the point where it harms her. She #8217;s also very good with NeFi things, but always uses these to aid her 2ish nature. Oh and I know an ISFJ 7w8, as well as an ESTP 1w2. Strange stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 09:24:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>INTP. Playing into stereotypes again? I think not. Seriously, I #8217;m not a STEM Person. Pass the humanities please.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 09:29:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/whatcouldgowrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>069</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Walking on Unleveled Ground In High Heels? Challenge Accepted!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 06:51:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Strandbeest, art using wind to provide locomotion</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 07:54:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 08:02:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why am I not surprised.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 08:04:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw a protest for the awareness of Uyghur rights. It #8217;s not just about religion, it #8217;s about ethnicity and a variety of other factors, too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 08:08:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why does this man #8217;s face remind me of Adolf Hitler.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 08:26:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Marriage is simply a contract sealing a relationship and granting government benefits. I am 100% ambivalent toward it. Marry if you please, don #8217;t if you don #8217;t. I am currently unmarried but would definitely consider settling down sometime in the future.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 08:28:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me, a 5:  #8220;Well that #8217;s awfully curious. #8221;  #8220;How...uncouth. #8221;  #8220;I can #8217;t talk right now. #8221;  #8220; #8216;Twas awkward. #8221; I literally say these things all the time.  #8212;- A 6 friend of mine:  #8220;Well shit. #8221;  #8220;You #8217;re hot. #8221;  #8220;I feel like shit. #8221;  #8220;Eyyy #8221; No comment.  #8212;- A 4 friend of mine:  #8220;POEM #8221;  #8220;omfg #8221;  #8220;DONT KILL THE SHINI #8221;  #8220;IM VIER #8221;  #8220;o nu #8221;  #8220;:444 #8221;  #8220; gt;:((( #8220; There were a lot of... inside jokes here.  #8212; A 3 friend of mine:  #8220;Yeah right #8221;  #8220;#Selftaught #8221;  #8220;What #8217;s an Ollie #8221;  #8220;I have a minor concussion and kinda can #8217;t be on my phone #8221;  #8212; A 1 friend of mine:  #8220;AAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH #8221;  #8220;Go to the office and ask to file a complaint form against another student #8221;  #8220;Sorry I #8217;m not interested. #8221;  #8220;Use google. Google is always reliable. #8221;  #8212; My mom, a 2:  #8220;:-) #8221;  #8220;Thanks for letting me know.. #8221;  #8220;Take your time #8221;  #8220;Ok. Will get it. #8221;  #8212; My dad, a 9:  #8220;Great! :) #8221;  #8220;Are u ready for tomorrow? #8221;  #8220;Clay pigeons are doomed  #128512; #8221;  #8220;Keep in touch! #8221;  #8212;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 01:34:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/13or30</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 02:33:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 02:39:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>If this weren #8217;t NSFW, I #8217;d post this to r/whyweretheyfilming XD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 05:25:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>That looks like a [Chinese ushanka](https://www.amazon.com/Chinese-Russian-Trooper-Winter-Ushanka/dp/B00PILDGGG) .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 05:32:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I know I say something along the lines of,  #8220;That #8217;s awfully curious #8221; while looking 100% ambivalent, but I #8217;m glowing inside. How can I tell if someone else doing the same is glowing within? I can #8217;t. It #8217;s at least worth a try.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shane Acker #8217;s Movie, 9</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 17:41:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Set in an alternate universe, 9 is a captivating film about the adventure of 9 sentient dolls (dubbed  #8216;Stitchpunks #8217; by Acker) in the ruins of a world ravaged by war and violence. Speculated to be set in Germany during the 1930 #8217;s, a corrupt Chancellor holds total control over the country. He commissions the works of a humble scientist- dubbed simply,  #8216;The Scientist #8217;, who has created B.R.A.I.N. (Binary Reactive Artificially Intelligent Neurocircuit) as a means to benefit the Chancellor. B.R.A.I.N. is capable of adapting and learning, even building other machines. These machines are harvested and declared  #8216;tools of peace #8217; by the Chancellor. However, these machines turn on humans, sometimes killing their own men. Eventually, this degenerates to the machines killing any human that crosses its path. Eventually, this conflict plagues the entire world, ridding it of human life and (from the looks of the movie) all life in general. The only thing left are the 9 Stitchpunks, animated by The Scientist dividing his soul into nine pieces. While this movie contained little dialogue and its plot was scattered at times, I give it the title of my favorite motion picture of all time. The art style, the world building, the history, the lore. It all is so captivating to me, a fan of post-apocalyptic worlds and symbolic storytelling. Many critics argue that 9 has no plot or message, but I beg to differ. The Scientist is a metaphor for mankind. He created B.R.A.I.N. For good, to help and inspire people. B.R.A.I.N. Is God, or the idea of God. He was created to be a benevolent force, but as he was abused by men to control and restrain others, the idea of God turned into a malicious, fear-mongering character. The Stitchpunks represent different aspects of the human psyche- essentially, the enneagram of personality. Our fears. Our desires. Our tendencies. How does this tie in with the enneagram? Many of the characters #8217; numbers correlate with the respective enneatype. 1 is strict and rule-bound, 2 is always lending a helping hand, 9 is a peacemaker and so forth. Additionally, there is strong religious symbolism within 9, from 1 dressing as a bishop to the Stitchpunks #8217; base being set in (what looks like) either a church or abbey. The Enneagram of personality has strong spiritual connotations, and is often laced together with Christian spirituality and self-awareness. Conclusively, Shane Acker #8217;s 9 is perhaps my favorite film, and I would like to raise awareness for it within a community of folks curious about enneagram and all related.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 18:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your score on the Explorer scale is 27 out of a possible 42, or 64%. Your score on the Builder scale is 20 out of a possible 42, or 48%. Your score on the Director scale is 32 out of a possible 42, or 76%. Your score on the Negotiator scale is 22 out of a possible 42, or 52%. INTP, 5w4/584</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 18:36:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>TFW statistics about your type are nearly 100% true. (I have to chance my flair back to INTP.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 18:39:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>INFP dad, ENFP mom. That #8217;s it. I would count in good fiends as family, but I don #8217;t know their MBTI types.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Paper airplane vortex</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 23:21:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 08:00:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not terribly knowledgeable in the field of mainstream media, but if I had to list my favorite movies and TV shows as a 5, here they are. 1 - 9. This is a movie which somewhat lacking, but with great potential. The setting is beautiful, the characters intricately designed, their personalities distinguishable and unique. Most of all, I love how speculative it is- what would happen in the aftermath of an apocalypse? What could have happened in our timeline to cause such a catastrophic event? So on and so forth. It #8217;s quite intriguing to me, simply because of how many of the blanks are left for the viewer to fill in. 2. Crazy Rich Asians. This movie I enjoyed for its promotion of individualism and ambition, demonstrating that a man (or woman) is much more than the mere property or extension of their family. It shows the harsh reality of commitment, but also the beautiful results that spawn from faith in it. 3. Avatar the Last Airbender and the Legend of Korra. Again, these two shows are quite a joy to watch and re-watch because of how speculative they are- what if humans possessed supernatural powers? What conflicts, alliances, and tensions would arise as a result of this? Additionally, the shows are action-packed and suspenseful, taking their characters through a journey of unexpected twists and turns at every episode. The character development is strong in this one. 4. Steven Universe. Despite being aimed at an obviously younger demographic, this is not to say the show cannot be enjoyed by older folk and the like. I am especially fond of this TV series because it represents all kinds of people, and deals with all kinds of scenarios, both social, emotional, and psychological. Additionally, the world building is quite fascinating, as the series is set in an alternate earth where... extraterrestrials regularly visit for a variety of reasons. Like stated before, I am not that knowledgeable about the mainstream media. These 4 samples are the only ones which I know well enough and like enough to mention.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 01:21:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>5w4 here, I #8217;ve taken up shooting recently and it #8217;s proven to be just the hobby for me. The power of life and death rests in my hands... also the power to break flying discs. I #8217;ve loved drawing and writing for quite a while, and weightlifting has always eased tension.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 05:17:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/blackmagicfuckery JKJKJK</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The power of perseverance.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 09:18:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 09:22:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/unethicallifeprotips</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 01:52:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah that #8217;s a canteen. XD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 09:58:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes please</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MRI of what happens on the inside of our mouths when we speak.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:02:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 10:02:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/educationalgifs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 21:24:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>5w4 here. My feed is filled mostly with politics, news, infographics, and art.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 03:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Father of the year #8221; mmkay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 07:11:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be epic  #128064;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally, I work with characters first. A lot of my original characters are personifications or representations of things, ideas, and social constructs. From there, I think of a story that can be told either to a) promote the ideas that the characters represent or b) teach a valuable lesson unrelated to the ideas but incorporating them. I find that path b works better, since the characters don #8217;t embody extraordinarily compelling ideas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You spelled  #8220;nudes #8221; wrong</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:15:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>