<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7333</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First mini in 5 years. Not perfect but I'm happy with him!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 22:08:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-16 08:51:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks mate, I wasn't too happy with seals I'll give it a go when I get round to his friends.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just got into AoS. I'd like you all to meet Draghak, Warchanter of the Bloodironz. C+C welcome.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-13 00:12:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-13 08:20:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just painted the rusted bits in a darkish red then washed and dry brushed it as if it was going to be all red. Then I used cotton wool to stipple a couple of different shades of silver. I don't know if it's a proper way of doing things I was just experimenting and got lucky I think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-13 17:16:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks mate. Thinking about dessert baces for the army but I'm still undecided.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-13 21:40:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll have to have a look at those, thanks a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 23:17:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Drink less. I'm drunk right now but it happens less often so... yay?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My first ever mini from years back and my most recent. I think I'm finally getting there with this. C+C always welcome!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 15:09:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 19:42:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not bad for 6! I think I was 12ish when I did the first one. That was many moons ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New home brew chapter for my Primaris marines. C+C always welcome.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 00:16:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 00:45:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still working on a name... sons of Mac? Mac angles? I think that could work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 08:56:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did want to have a go at the Howling Griffons but gave up halfway through. Still not unhappy with how it turned out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 22:02:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Already had an Estrella and have more in the fridge. It's going to be a long wait till 2 in the UK.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 22:58:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>In the UK it plays at the same time as in the US, that's 2am our time. Then again at 9 tomorrow. Me and the wife are staying up. It's almost 10 now and we're both getting super excited.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've got myself the Nurgle starter box. Where to go from here?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 11:06:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm look to get up to 1000 points but I'm not sure what to add to my new army (never played chaos before). Can any body point me in the right direction? I love the blightkings models but are they any good on the table?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 12:05:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks very much I'll have little look around!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 14:17:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Think I might move into rotbringers and have the daemons as some extras to summon in and the like. Thanks a lot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 15:23:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haven't look at forge world at all yet. I'll go have a gander now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 18:40:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Been having a look on the GW store today and some warscroles I think a plaugeclaw look fun and that has a -2 rend. Looks cool too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 18:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>That could be cool. The wife and I prefer more elite army's and I play her more than anyone else. Could be fun to throw a horde at her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Little kit bash I did. Still some rough edges to fix but I'm happy with my evenings work.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 21:56:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 05:15:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks mate im really happy with how he turned out. The wife plays fyerslayers, the horns are an option from the magmadroth kit that she didn't use.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 05:20:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just being very careful with the clippers then used a hobby knife to round the edges a little. Finished it with some sand paper until I was happy with it. Took a while but I'm happy with the result. I hope this helped.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I think I'm almost done. It's been a fun evening!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 21:38:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 10:34:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the one. I had just put it on when I took the photo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 20:01:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure as yet I've got a few bits and bobs from other kits and I've got some grassy tufts. Any ideas would be welcome!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 20:10:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks a lot. I think I'm going to steer clear of any vehicles so I can use him in 40k and age of sigmar. Maybe just something simple for now I've not really done anything with basing before so I'll try out some things on his boyz first.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 19:43:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Old guy in a pub in Ireland. Old guy: Are you a ghost? Me: No Old guy: Why are you English? Me: I was born there. He then necked his pint and walked out of the door. It was a good holiday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The wife said the helbrute model looked too nurglely so I did some kit bashing for her. It's been a fun afternoon! Still WIP.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 00:46:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 08:20:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the kind comments everyone. I'll post again when it finished.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 08:34:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll have a look for the old bits if I can find them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 09:58:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did yeah but I decided to move it up to cover the aquila on the chest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 00:37:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm currently painting up an AdMech army and having a blast with it. Unfortunately I haven't had a chance to play with them yet so I can't help you if you're more interested in playing than you are painting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Finished Christmas shopping early so I got myself a knight. Still WIP but I'm happy so far.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 13:29:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 23:20:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's skavenblight dinge washed with nuln oil and jacaro orange. I'm working on an admech army with this and I really like how it looks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 23:21:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah it's amazing I've been saving that one for something big.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 23:22:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>2 thin coats...well it was more like 4 very thin coats.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 23:24:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was facing away from a window to get better light. I wish it was me but it's just a lucky shot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 23:24:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks buddy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 23:25:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll give it another layer or 2 when I get too painting next. Thanks mate I hadn't noticed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 14:52:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well done young man! I wish I was half as good at twice your age.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DAKKADAKKADAKKA</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 11:51:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 10:26:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had the same issue. Gave the black areas a light coat of nurgles rot making it thinker around joints and any deep holes on the body. It gave them a nice venomous look that I really liked. Then some blood for the blood god round the mouth and claws. If you want to keep it clean then a very thin high light of fenrisian grey should look good. I hope this helped.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 16:18:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Baroness Naomi von Manchester. I named her after my wife, so it annoys her when she has to try and kill her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 17:36:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I need to mess with her as much as I can. She's a filthy heretic and must be purged.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>WIP Dreadnought. Any advice for the plasma I'm not quite happy with it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 16:32:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My knight looking even cooler than I ever thought she would.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 03:35:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 13:17:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I remember it was dream or dreams.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First finished bug. Very exited to start chomping some biomass!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 21:55:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 14:12:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gghh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Still a work in progress but I made myself a tech priest. (I'm rubbish with green stuff)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 11:35:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 12:39:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used green stuff to make the hood and cape. There also some to fill in some gaps. I've never used it before and this is my first proper kit bash.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 12:46:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks mate! I think I might have been expecting too much for a first try.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 13:10:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the advice. I've got loads left over so I'll have a play.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 14:21:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes it is I had a spare one! I also used lots of bits from destroyers box. The axe is from a fyer slayers box I had laying around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 14:21:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks a lot! Makes me feel more confident taking this my local store.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 11:56:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I worked out a way we could be married for under  #163;500. She looked at my plans said they looked great but... we now have no savings and still owe hundreds of pounds. I love that woman but our wedding is basicly a party she's throwing that I'm invited too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Running is hard without both shoes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 19:57:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Was anyone else disappointed with the Wet Nurse?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 00:42:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been loving this game since it was on PS plus but I have to say this boss left me feeling a bit let down. The run up was tough (I hate the pigs), the shadows of yharnam made a fun return, I was having a blast. Then I walked into the boss room and beat it on my first try. I'm not saying I'm amazing at the game, I'm not. PVP showed me this. Did any of you lovely people feel like this or did I just get some beginners luck?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 01:00:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok cool I was worried I hit a glitch or something. I've not tried Gherman yet but I'm looking forward to it. I've been messing around in the DLC tonight so it could be a while before I get there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 01:02:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw Vaati fighting the orphan in one of his videos. I could hardly even watch that thing. Can't wait to fight it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 01:06:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>The arms coming out of the walls panicked me loads! Wasn't ready for that. That little trick only worked once though. Cheeky little nightmare monster.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 10:28:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess that's true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thinking of starting a cult of my own.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 13:13:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been playing Tyranids for a while and am looking at adding in some genestealer cult. I have about 30 genestealers already but was wondering what I should be picking up next. Looking to build to about 1000 points. Any tips would be amazing. Thank you in advance brood brothers!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 23:26:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds nasty! I like it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to build a Baal predator?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 12:04:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've just got myself the start collecting box and was wanting to get some opinions on how to put together the Baal predator. I was thinking all flamers because that's cool to me but is that viable?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 14:05:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for you feed back guys it's much appreciated!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Looking for thoughts on a new list.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 09:25:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm Tyranid player but I've just started collecting some blood angles. How does this list look to you guys? **++ Battalion Detachment +5CP (Imperium - Blood Angels) [71 PL, 1381pts] ++** **+ HQ +** **Captain [6 PL, 129pts]:** Jump Pack, Storm shield, Thunder hammer **Librarian Dreadnought [9 PL, 172pts]:** Furioso fist, Storm bolter **+ Troops +** **Intercessor Squad [5 PL, 90pts]:** Bolt rifle, 4x Intercessor, Intercessor Sergeant **Intercessor Squad [5 PL, 90pts]:** Bolt rifle, 4x Intercessor, Intercessor Sergeant **Tactical Squad [9 PL, 171pts]** . **7x Space Marine** . **Space Marine (Heavy weapon):** Heavy flamer . **Space Marine (Special weapon):** Flamer . **Space Marine Sergeant:** Combi-flamer, Power sword **+ Fast Attack +** **Inceptor Squad [10 PL, 135pts]:** 2x Inceptor, Inceptor Sergeant **Two assault bolters:** 2x Assault bolter **+ Heavy Support +** **Baal Predator [8 PL, 164pts]:** Flamestorm cannon **Two heavy flamers:** 2x Heavy flamer **+ Flyer +** **Stormraven Gunship [15 PL, 358pts]:** 2x Stormstrike missile launcher, Twin lascannon, Twin multi-melta . **Two hurricane bolters:** 2x Hurricane bolter **+ Dedicated Transport +** **Rhino [4 PL, 72pts]:** Storm bolter **++ Vanguard Detachment +1CP (Imperium - Blood Angels) [32 PL, 615pts] ++** **+ HQ +** **Lemartes [7 PL, 129pts]** **+ Elites +** **Death Company [9 PL, 135pts]:** Jump Pack . **Death Company Marine:** Thunder hammer . **Death Company Marine:** Plasma pistol, Power fist . **Death Company Marine:** Bolt pistol and chainsword . **Death Company Marine:** Bolt pistol and chainsword . **Death Company Marine:** Bolt pistol and chainsword **Death Company Dreadnought [9 PL, 174pts]:** Furioso fist (pair), Heavy flamer, Heavy flamer, Smoke launchers **Sternguard Veteran Squad [7 PL, 177pts]** . **Space Marine Veteran:** Combi-melta . **Space Marine Veteran:** Combi-melta . **Space Marine Veteran:** Combi-melta . **Space Marine Veteran:** Combi-melta . **Veteran Sergeant:** Inferno pistol, Power fist  #160; **++ Total: [103 PL, 1996pts] ++**  #160; Created with [BattleScribe](http://www.battlescribe.net) Safeguard vets and the Dreadnought would go in the stormraven and tacticals will be in the rhino.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 11:32:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right ok i think I'll replace the dred with something else. Maybe more death company.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 15:39:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can swap it but I wanted it to be a cheaper distraction carnifex that can threaten hordes. I'll be coming up against a lot of guard and other Tyranid players.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 17:09:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't I've got the imperium half of the starter box but that's all the primaris stuff I've got at the moment. I'm guessing they work well. I've only ever played nids so it's wired to not just throw a million bugs at a problem and instead have to try and counter that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 11:07:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ui1j368u7y #249;uuuuuuuuuiol fkl #243;yu4tyuuu54y</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 21:16:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>M</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 00:25:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe move the right arm out away from the torso a little and have the left out straight a bit more. It could help it look a little more dynamic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 17:23:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can I ask how you did the bases. I've been thinking of adding some kriegers to my collection and these bases look amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 17:54:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very nice work! Are the sand bags just green stuff or have you bought those from somewhere?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 17:54:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very nice work! Are the sand bags just green stuff or have you bought those from somewhere?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 18:19:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks mate!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Made a captain for my blood angles this afternoon. Very excited to start painting him up!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 19:15:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Captain Slam almost ready for action!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 16:45:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 21:39:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah they didn't come out as I'd wanted. It's my first time trying eyes. I was thinking of going over them with some caraburg crimson so they just look blood shot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Kill team painted and ready for action. Sorry about the bad picture quality.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 16:31:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 09:57:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry for the late reply. The grey is skavenblight washed with nuln oil and the dry brushed with mecanicus standard grey. The orange is jakaro orange then a fire Dragon bright highlight. The rest is just a random mix of silver and brass with gold details here and there. To do the bases I followed the toxic swap on the citadel app. I really like it think I'll have to rebase the rest of the army now to look the same.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Test dude for my new death guard kill team!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 20:43:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 20:47:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks a bunch. If I was doing a whole army I think I'd go mad, there's just so much detail on these guys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 21:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>And so they are named. I love it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 23:18:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll put one up once there all done. I do work a little slow though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 21:22:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like to run more vanguard than rangers. Advance the vanguard up the bored as fast as possible to take objectives and run interference on the opponents army. Then a squad of rangers in the back screening for as many robots as you can fit in the list. Never run less than 2 but more is better if your playing 1500 point or up. It's the robots that will clear the bored and win you the game more often than not. Then throw in cawl (if you play mars) or a tech priest (if you don't) for reroles to hit on the robots and the rangers and you have yourself one hell of a gun line. That you opponent has to chew though 2 lines of infantry to get too. Any spare points should be put into dunecrawlers for anti tank or dragons if you feel your not mobile enough. I don't play super competitive games but this works well enough when I'm playing with my mates. I hope this helped.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 21:56:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>The vanguard can be more dangerous than people think. There weapons are assault 3 so they can fire after advancing and put out a lot of good fire especially if they have a plasma gun or 2. They give enemy's -1 toughness when they get close so people have to spend time shooting them or they have that to deal with that. Dragoons could be better in your case though. They can get up in his face real fast and hit like a bus. Give him an problem he can't ignore. Even if they wif you'll get a turn or 2 to shoot everything in the universe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 22:05:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>No problem mate. Praise the Omnissia!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>