<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7627</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shotgun bug?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 03:07:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has anyone had any problems with the shotguns lately? Example below.[Example](http://xboxdvr.com/gamer/TheSystemStatic/video/27348616/imgur)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I don't think IQ is quite used to her grenades yet.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 03:50:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mirror glitch</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-04 03:01:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is anyone having a problem with people shooting through an unbroken mirror? I was shot through my UNBROKEN mirror and my friend watched a Fuze shoot through the mirror until he hit the canister.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The new Kapkan buff</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-11 08:04:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How I got my username.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-21 19:55:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was six years old I fell into my great grandmother's pond. In that pond I drowned. I was dead for around two minutes before my father found me, dragged my from the cold water, and resuscitated me. Since then I've seen things. After reading some stories on this thread I feel like this would be a good place to tell my story. At six years old, I fell into a pond and drowned. I remember the cold waters of November as I thrashed about. I remember slipping under the surface as the world began to fade from my view. I remember the overwhelming droning of my blood rushing about in my body as the oxygen became less and less available. Then I remember the way it suddenly stopped. Then I remember the darkness. A darkness like nothing I could ever conceive. And the sheer numbness I felt. I tried to move but I could feel absolutely nothing. There was no sound, no light, just nothingness. I tried to feel my arms and legs but it's like they weren't there. I tried looking around but I had no idea if I was even moving. It felt as if I was floating, but not in water. Just floating in nothingness. Wherever I was seemed to not be affected by time. It felt like seconds but at the same time an eternity. Almost like I just couldn't comprehend what was happening. I felt so alone and so afraid. Yet I also felt so indifferent about it. I couldn't think about anything. That's when they appeared. Two eyes glowing in the darkness. As if someone simply opened them inches from me. But they weren't human. They were almost human but in a negative contrast. The whites of the eyes were black. The iris was a white ring encircling a deep, dark pupil. These eyes stared intensely at me. They bore into me. Filling me with so many intense emotions. It felt as if my body was flooded with adrenaline. They suddenly a pair of dark hands lunged from the darkness and grabbed me. The next thing I remember is the sunlight blinding me as my chest heaved and burned. I coughed hard as the water was expelled from me and was replaced with air. I could see my dad kneeling over me tears in his eyes. He then hugged me tightly for what felt like forever. Since then I've always seen things out of the corner of my eye. A dark figure always out of view. When I turn to look there's nothing there. In the dark I see a shadow only for it to disappear once I turn on the lights. I always feel it though. Watching me. Always. Then one day I turned to look and it didn't go away. For the last four years He's stopped hiding. He has revealed himself to me. A tall thin creature, seemingly made of the same darkness I seen in that abyss. He seems to give off a dark smoke-like essence. He does not scare me. He has spoken to me. Told me things. I thought I was just imagining him but he has proved to me he is real. He's told me things I shouldn't know. Things I've never learned or heard. He speaks to me in a language I can't quite comprehend but somehow I know exactly what he says. He protects me from things. Dark things that wish to harm me. Maybe he is a ghost. Maybe he is a demon. I can't tell you for certain. All I know is his name. His is.. A #874; #873; #812; #811; #815; #840; #809; #816;a #780; #878; #772; #830; #778; #831; #868; #852; #816;l #772; #789; #803; #809; #806;e #878; #818; #840; #796; #796;b #860; #853; #839; #851; #803; #803; #791;a #879; #879; #782; #859; #872; #773; #785; #862; #854; #819;s #774; #773; #826; #804;t #871; #820; #798; #811; #857;e #868; #872; #794; #773; #769; #777; #865; #839; #811; #792; #826; #811; #845;r #776; #836; #872; #788; #869; #872; #768;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When playing Secure Area on house. As a defender never reinforce the Kid's Room</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 04:43:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reasons why: 1. If any defenders decide to stay in the room then it's Fuze's wet dream. 2. If the attackers come in from the windows there is only one good route in. This creates a choke point to the attackers advantage. 3. The windows give any long range attackers a good vantage point. How me and my friends play this objective is to effectively destroy every wall in that room. We can then see every corner of the room from a distance, giving us defenders an advantage. We can then camp in the Construction Area or the Main Bedroom at farther range. You can then Mira the Construction Area wall and the Main Bedroom closet if you want to feel safer. I suggest if you reinforce the closet, only use one reinforcement so you can quickly go into the Kid's Room.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>For Shield users</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-30 04:29:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're like me and you like to play shield operators but they're all taken except Blitz then listen up. I like to play Blitz but he has so many problems you have to be either very good or very lucky to use him. I have a solution. If you're like me you know that for Blitz's flash you have to be almost right up to them or it's useless. Then they can spray after being flashed and they may hit you. So here's the fix. The FBI recruit equipped with the ballistics shield is very similar to Blitz. In fact his pistol is a little bit stronger. I use flashes to stun and smokes to help Glaz. I've been playing with this loadout for months now and it's pretty effective for shield players.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Meanwhile at Ubisoft Headquarters</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 03:31:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Meanwhile at Ubisoft Headquarters</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 23:52:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've been making these for all the operators as a way to kill time.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 01:47:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Operator backgrounds I've been making</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 02:57:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rook background I made</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 03:05:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Blackbeard background</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 03:09:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Blitz background</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 03:10:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>God?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 03:12:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A background for our Lord and Savior</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 03:13:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Capitao background</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 03:14:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rainbow Six: Siege Operators with their flags.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 15:58:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mmmmmm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 21:57:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>J #228;gered</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 21:58:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Doc</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 19:41:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Playing with a Fuze</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 06:57:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you have a competent Fuze player on you're team then don't just go around breaking barriers down. Many times when I play Fuze there is a teammate that breaks a barrier I was going to Cluster. When you play with a Fuze you need to think like a Fuze yourself as well. So you should wait to see if your Fuze will Cluster a barrier before you break it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm loving it</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 21:00:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Trap and Zap</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-06 20:04:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>A tactic me and my friends like to utilize when we know that a team is going to rush. One person goes Frost and puts traps in areas where the enemy is likely to rush into without checking. Then a Bandit puts shock wire on all the traps. This means if the enemy smokes and rushes in then they're likely to hit the traps and the shock wire kills them before they even know what happened. Note: This works best if you Know the enemy will rush. If they don't rush it is not as effective.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>VSHHHHH</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-08 05:01:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Remember when you first played Doc</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-08 06:56:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This piece of shit right here needs a roastin'</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 23:37:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The way my mom is holding my son makes it look like he has a huge leg.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-13 04:18:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I might have seen the code</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-06 03:03:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know this sounds crazy but hear me out. This is something that has happened frequently. Yet as I get older it happens less and less. What happens is I will be talking and having fun as normal. Then I'll zone out. But when it happens I freeze and I can watch the world go black. All light and sound are gone and there is only darkness. My mind goes blank. Then I just start to see strange symbols. Then usually one of my friends touch me or say my name loudly and I immediately snap out of it. And all my thoughts come back to me all at once and almost completely forget the symbols. But I know I seen symbols. I just can't remember what they looked like. Anyone else had this problem?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me and my friend were talking about being able to buy crazy outfits for Recruit and this is immediately what I thought of..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 03:58:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Made this based on a post I saw the other day</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 03:07:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Now that the new operator abilities have been leaked.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 06:05:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I dont know what all these people are complaining about. Ash's stats look right to me.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 07:05:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I think babies can see things</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-17 02:18:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen certain things growing up ever since I drowned when I was six. I was resuscitated by my father after being gone for almost three minutes. He got my heart to start again and the fluid from my lungs. But as I was saying ever since then I can remember seeing this thing. This person who seemed to be made of black smoke. I always thought I was crazy or the lack of oxygen harmed my brain. But the other day I was watching my son ( 9 months ) while his mom was running some errands when I had to go make us some food. He was in his walker watching a cartoon in the living room when I heard him start crying. I knew he probably just wanted his bottle so I started fixing one for him. But before I could finish and take it to him I heard him start laughing and moving around. I walk in to see if maybe he was at his favorite part of the movie or something but instead I almost freaked out. It was the shadow. It was kneeling down by my son. My son looked at me smiling but then he did something that made my skin crawl. He looked over to the shadow and started laughing. He saw him too. Then I became so angry I screamed at the thing, " This is my son, you do not touch my son." It stood up, turned, and vanished. I dont know what to think now. Has this happened to anyone else?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Which would be more psychologically horrifying? An Immortal killer or an invincible one?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 03:02:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>IQ is taking the controversy pretty hard.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 20:12:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you clutch a 1 vs 5 on the final round of a 4-4 match.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 01:34:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I figured since we're all playing with photoshop..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 04:46:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>They say "slow and steady wins the race" but if the hare hadn't stopped out of arrogance he would have beat the tortoise easily.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 19:45:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[WP] You are the right-hand man to the worlds most evil villain. You are the stereotypical henchman except for one thing; your ability to influence people. You've been in control the whole time.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 18:19:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>PSA: Sometimes playing the objective can get you wins.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 01:22:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I only say this because I can't help but notice how many people hate on me for playing objective. There have been many times where my teammates try to peek and rush to get all the kills they can; only for them to get easily killed by the enemy. Then I'm left alone to protect the objective. Then once I get overwhelmed in a 1 vs 4 or 5 they tell me how "trash" I am. People also seem to get angry at me for being MVP when I go 2-2-2 or something similar. They don't seem to understand how many points you can get for playing the objective. I only say this because I'll be the first to admit that gunplay isn't my strong suit. But when it comes to gathering information via cameras or other gadgets and relaying that to my team I'm great. That's why play operators like Valkyrie or Montagne. I'm a good support. My friends are awesome at gunplay so I leave them to it and I try my best to tell them what they need to know. Not everyone is suited to massacre the enemy team. It is perfectly fine to be the eyes and ears for your team. Playing the objective is helpful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anyone else feel like the game has devolved?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 04:22:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone else feel like the game is less about the operators, their abilities, and how to use them effectively? Does it not feel more like it's not about the objective but more about just team death match?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why do half reinforcements exist?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 18:35:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean I completely understand some rooms have them to help balance the game. It's just every time I put up a reinforcement on a wall and I see the reinforcement is only 2 feet wide I just give up and pick a different wall. It is so bad in library on Bartlette. And Billiard Room on House is a complete joke. Yet in Kids bedroom you can put like 5 full reinforcements( but I dont know why you would).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anyone have any interesting operator concepts they'd like to talk about? I'd love to hear what the community would like to see.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 21:30:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ying</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 01:14:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The men's bathroom where I work</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 23:10:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Aussie accents just make everything funny.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 04:19:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Those good ol' 1v5's</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 23:41:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Recruit squad, where you at?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 21:04:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[WP] You have the ability to transfer your consciousness into anyone you see, including in photos. Today you learned, while looking at a very old family photo, that time isn't an issue. But now you don't know how to get back.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 23:16:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[WP] You are possessed by a powerful demon. You fear the worst when you notice that you are still in control of your body. And he's afraid because you can control his powers.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 00:03:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Attack Healer Concept</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 23:53:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Attack Medic A 2 Speed/ 2 Armor attacking operator who is equipped with a Trauma Pack. He has the ability to heal other attacking operators through a special animation performed on the operator. This means that physical contact is necessary for the healing to occur. There are two concepts I've considered : 1. He gets a set amount of packs that heal a set amount of health. ( ex. He has 3* trauma packs that heal 30* HP each within a 3* second animation) 2. The pack has a healing durability which means he has a set amount of health he can distribute amongst himself or his allies ( ex. He has a single pack which can heal 150* HP. The longer he holds the button the more he heals. During the animation it could be something like 10* HP every second he's in the animation.) He can not over heal himself or his allies. And he can not heal himself when he is DBNO, but a team can come up to him and use one of his packs to pick him up with a slight health boost ( 75*HP instead of 50 HP) which would cause a separate animation that lasts slightly longer. Let me know what you guys think. *numbers liable to change</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Trap n' Zap</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 18:09:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know a lot of people already know this but I played recently with some people who did not. A strategy my friends and I like to use is the ol' trap n' zap. Frost puts down a trap and Bandit hides it with electrified wire. If someone rushes they'll hit the trap, get downed, and the electrified wire kills them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>He needs extra "halipinos"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 02:34:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anyone else feel like they're watching a B-Rated horror movie when the watch this?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 00:36:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I dont know if it's just me but the character s seem to make the stupidest choices along with not just solving problems when they get the chance( I guess to add drama?). It's just irritating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'll take your extra finger and raise you my buddy ClawMachine</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 03:09:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The way the "c" doesn't fit on the top of the box.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 21:25:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"Daniel", Digital, 2500x1500</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 18:38:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This guys texts my girlfriend, so she screenshot it and sent it to his girlfriend. Then he acts like he doesn't know her.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 18:17:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So is it for IPhone 7 or 8</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 23:12:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When my friend used to play Pok #233;mon Go</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 23:35:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Two guys from the 50's</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 21:46:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Two guys from the 50's were talking out front of one's house. The first neighbor says to the other, " what do you think of that new family, the Petrov's?" The second neighbor looks at him and replies, " I don't know if they're commies Teddy, but they sure do raise a lot of red flags."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Rosa Parks wasn't the first black woman to refuse to give up her seat.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 22:16:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found this in r/gaming</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 03:13:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I bought some shoes off of Craigslist.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 19:06:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know what the guy laced them with but I've been tripping all day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>People often ask what I do at the teddy bear factory.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 17:58:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;m so hung..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 16:05:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>..I could be in a Logan Paul video.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Welcome to RedditMemorials</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 04:59:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>RedditMemorials is a subreddit created to help fellow redditors grieve a loss or honor someone who was dear to them. You can do this in several ways. You can write about the feeling the loss has caused you. You can post about how this person effected your life and how much they meant to you. You can post pictures of them and tell us all about the fond memories that you have of them. You can also simply write what you wish you could say to them were they still with us. This is a place to let go of what you have inside. A place to help you come to terms with your loss. And a place to honor those of whom you thought everything of. A place where the one you lost can live on in our minds as well as yours. And in the eternity that is the internet. So please, tell us who you want us to remember.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An Easy Template to Begin</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 05:04:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. ( Photo or Photos ) 2.  #8220; Who they were to you  #8220; 3.  #8220; How they effected your life  #8220; 4.  #8220; Something you wish you could say to them  #8220; You don #8217;t have to follow this exactly. This is just a good guide to base your post off of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>r/RedditMemorials</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 05:09:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I find that one way to help me grieve the loss of my loved ones is to talk about them. To share my good memories of them. To share the things they have taught me and things that I base my life around. That #8217;s why I created a subreddit to do just that. This sub is made so that you can memorialize those lost loved one you adored so dearly. A place where you can let your feeling be let go, where you no longer have to bottle them in. This is a sub for you to tell everyone about the amazing person we all wish we could have known. If this seems like something that could help you, please give it a visit. Please, tell us who we should immortalize. r/RedditMemorials</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My friend Timmy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 18:29:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Timmy](https://imgur.com/a/e1ScR) was a friend who I grew up with about my whole life. I lost him in 2013. He was a few years older than me but I think that just made me see him as more of an older brother than a friend. He was my idol. I looked up to him. To me he was the coolest guy in the world. He was a star football player, he was popular, and he played the drums. Everyone liked him. He was always a hit with the ladies. The one thing that I always noticed though was his positive attitude. He didn #8217;t get to where he was through luck. He worked his ass off. He spent his days at school studying and taking advanced classes. Then he #8217;d work from 17:00 - 2:00 or 3:00. Then he #8217;d do it all other again. But he never complained and he never had a bad attitude. He always tried to make you smile or laugh. He always had a joke to tell. And he wasn #8217;t satisfied until you at least chuckled. A lot of how I live today is because of his impact on me. I don #8217;t let the world get me down. Instead I try my best to help others. And I always try to have a great attitude. Here #8217;s my biggest regret. The day he left for college we threw him a party. As we were leaving he was saying by to everyone and hugging them because that #8217;s what he did. He wouldn #8217;t shake your hand he wanted to hug you. But when he got to me I thought I was too cool and told joking told him to get away. That was the last I saw him alive. Two months later he went to a river with some friends to swim. He went under and never came up. They found his body at the bottom three days later a mile away. That #8217;s why to this day I never turn down a hug. I understand now it #8217;s not stupid or weak. It #8217;s a sign of love. He truly loved all of us. I miss him a lot. So please, keep the legend alive and hug someone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>r/RedditMemorials</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 18:29:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I find that one way to help me grieve the loss of my loved ones is to talk about them. To share my good memories of them. To share the things they have taught me and things that I base my life around. That #8217;s why I created a subreddit to do just that. This sub is made so that you can memorialize those lost loved one you adored so dearly. A place where you can let your feeling be let go, where you no longer have to bottle them in. This is a sub for you to tell everyone about the amazing person we all wish we could have known. If this seems like something that could help you, please give it a visit. Please, tell us who we should immortalize. r/RedditMemorials</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This game makes you think you get a free character... if you subscribe to them on Instagram and like a post.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 18:05:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This game also has a premium version for $7.99 a week. Yes, a week.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 18:12:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I made tendies all by myself. I no longer need mommy. I have ascended to a higher plane of existence. Call me god.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 03:17:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hackers?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 01:53:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is anyone else having a problem with people playing cards they shouldn #8217;t be able to play. Such as three 5 elixir cards at a time. I play with a lot of two and three elixir cards and people still somehow out spawn me. Anyone else see this happening?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The ability to make high walls.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 04:36:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We are now cracking down on spam.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 09:55:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I work at a country club. This was a bill from a member and his family. They ate a few bites off each plate and the rest was thrown away. I can barely afford McDonald #8217;s.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 02:00:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This has been reposted 5 times in the last 19 hours. If it gets reposted again you will be banned for 3 days.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 22:04:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We need some feedback from our community.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 20:40:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mobile Reddit App</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 17:55:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was wondering if there is a way to see your pending posts on the mobile app. I went to post something then I backed out. Then it said post failed and I have no way to get back to the screen other than make a new post. But then I have to wait 10 minutes to post again. Is there anyway to get there without making a post?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Apparently Jesus invented traps?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 18:34:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Being a mod of a NSFW sub gets you the best reports</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 22:32:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>r/NSFWFunny is really hard to moderate.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 02:57:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do I get to this page without having to create a new post. ( the post failed page )</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 06:37:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It #8217;s like an abstract painting</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 15:56:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I created a discord server for any of you who wish to easily contact me or send me feedback.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 19:08:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This happy lid</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 08:16:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SLAV KING - Boris  amp; DJ Blyatman [Slav Rap]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 02:20:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A guy I went to high school with kills his girlfriend #8217;s 20 month old daughter.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 05:52:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tucker and Dale vs. Evil</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 18:25:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know this has been mentioned before but I have to say this. Tucker and Dale vs. Evil has got to be one of the best horror comedy I #8217;ve ever seen. It is one of the only movies to actually use the horror movies cliches without actually making them seem stupid. It is a movie where the villains aren #8217;t the villains and the hero #8217;s make no sense. It is extremely funny and the main characters are fantastic. If you haven #8217;t seen it you should. It is available on Netflix. Edit: all these movies I forgot about made change my statement a little</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>And look who #8217;s getting downvoted</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 05:01:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Because people think I just remove things for fun.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 18:24:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Homemade] Iced Oatmeal Cookies</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 20:22:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Had a letter from a past resident of my address. I put it in the mailbox for 3 days with the flag up. Finally I wrote  #8220;No longer at this residence #8221; on it and put it back with the flag up again. Got this this morning.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 18:30:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Demon Tattoo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 19:56:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We were talking about a  #8220;rape #8221; claim.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 16:46:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Man this makes me cry every time.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 03:24:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Last night I sliced my thumb at work. (The crusty stuff is superglue)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 07:00:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I cut myself at work (crusty stuff is superglue)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 00:39:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I cut myself at work (the crusty stuff is superglue)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 16:08:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 00:39:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly the only time I even feel the need to charge is for tanks and groups. I #8217;m slightly okay with it. But I do mainly try for headshot. I practice them for hours.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 02:20:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/nsfw_wtf</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 02:21:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Post this in r/nsfw_wtf not here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 02:27:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>[How about this one?](https://www.isitdarkoutside.com)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 02:28:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Again post it on r/nsfw_wtf</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 02:54:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m a strong opposer of wearing a bra. I haven #8217;t wore a bra my whole life and I can tell you my breasts only get worse. I mean I am a man but still.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 16:38:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/nsfw_wtf</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 20:06:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I certainly did ](https://www.reddit.com/r/Jokes/comments/861ms7/to_the_man_in_the_wheelchair_who_stole_my/?st=JFBEIU60 amp;sh=4586c1f1)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 20:07:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I mean it was only a week ago](https://www.reddit.com/r/Jokes/comments/861ms7/to_the_man_in_the_wheelchair_who_stole_my/?st=JFBEIU60 amp;sh=4586c1f1)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 20:08:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Man you got screwed](https://www.reddit.com/r/Jokes/comments/87qvdr/to_the_man_in_the_wheelchair_that_stole_my/?st=JFBEL5AE amp;sh=4a6c56ed)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Narcolepes, Guardian Mage of Dreams</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 21:37:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 05:03:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which uncle touched you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 06:30:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>#FIERCE!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 06:37:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that a ^fucking ^^pun</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 06:40:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>###TURN ##IT #ON</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 16:57:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cross section of ~~an elephant #8217;s~~ **your mom #8217;s** foot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 18:09:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>As **God** intended</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 20:37:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the hell does this even mean?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 20:43:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm interesting. It looks to me like some kind of bottle or maybe a tube that might have been weathered by something. Possibly water and sand. Did you happen to find this on a beach?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 20:45:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh okay I see what you meant now. It probably is just a deformed bird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 21:20:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>For my Magnum **DONG**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 23:34:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look at all these salty people downvoting you mate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 23:37:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL I #8217;m a panda</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 23:48:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/woooosh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 23:53:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope never actually been there. Just saw someone else comment it. Could you explain?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 23:57:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>So does that mean you belong there?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 00:01:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh shit you got me mate. I guess I #8217;ll delete my Reddit now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 00:03:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you think maybe just this once I can keep it? I #8217;m really tired of making new accounts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 00:35:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 00:45:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stop posting this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 14:56:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>He looks like his next option would be to eat him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 05:31:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/nsfw_wtf?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 20:08:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was posted less than 60 days ago (35). Please do not repost until after 60 days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 00:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>You literally reposted this from the OP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 05:46:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s cool just try to refrain from doing it again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 23:51:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I too eat glue</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 23:53:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aki No Koto No Ha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Teachers need funding</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 00:07:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 15:29:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly this is clickbait!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 15:30:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/nsfw_wtf?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 18:44:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>They #8217;re turning the FRICKEN FROGS GAY!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 15:38:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but 3.7k upvotes is pretty good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 04:15:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/nsfw_wtf?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 05:51:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably because they disagree with his opinion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 05:52:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>The picture was posted but this isn #8217;t the same exact post. It has been edited to add extra comedic value. In my personal opinion I #8217;d say this is funnier than the post from earlier. And according to the upvotes many others also agree.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 17:52:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the 5th time I #8217;ve removed it in two weeks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 18:36:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>[It #8217;s been a month](https://www.reddit.com/r/Showerthoughts/comments/83nxqm/nudists_dont_have_private_parts/?st=JFTW0WM2 amp;sh=292a645d)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 18:43:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>They must have developed a form of retardation from the effects of vaccines. This is why I don #8217;t vax! /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 17:00:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is what they call in the porn industry a  #8220;squirt #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 18:36:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>It could be a momentary lapse of bladder control do to the intense stimulation cause by the gentleman removing his penis so quickly. Or maybe she peed a little because some guys think squirting is hot or some bullshit like that and she gets paid more to do so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 18:41:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rosa parks didn #8217;t even sit at the front. She was sitting in the colored section like she was told to, but when the whites only section was filled she wouldn #8217;t give up her seat to a white man. So really all she did was refuse to move.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 18:52:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand Bruce #8217;s ideology is off, but there is a significant percentage difference between male and female statistics involving things children related. Custody and child support are good examples. So what I am asking is who are you implying is more insane? Bruce or the person who still believes in a legal system of unequal payment based on gender? Edit: [A good source material.](https://www.census.gov/content/dam/Census/library/publications/2016/demo/P60-255.pdf)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 20:55:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can see enough of a correlation to address it but I will admit the way he worded it did seem off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Oops you bought peach rings</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 01:38:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 04:46:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re kind of a cunt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 04:52:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never catching cases, why they faces look so e-m-o?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 13:20:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do people just not read the rules or what? I mean it #8217;s literally the first one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 15:17:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s fine now. We #8217;ve just had a lot of problems with people posting just their nudes and asking for Snapchat and kik. It #8217;s just not what we #8217;re about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 15:21:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>That guys face looks like he can #8217;t decide if it feels good or if he #8217;s scared his dick will break off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 16:55:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can add friends on my app I just added you just fine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 16:57:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I just noticed that. I #8217;m a mod of a sub and I used it to help see how long someone waited to repost something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 01:37:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Dude are you me from middle school?](https://imgur.com/a/AOyjV)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 16:26:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but Moana would have died later in the movie if the ocean hadn #8217;t saved her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 16:44:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also in doctor strange he finds a cape that gives the wearer the ability to fly. Then later in the the movie he is wearing that cape and he has the ability to fly!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 20:28:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I literally see this fucking post on here like every week. Why won #8217;t people let it die?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 20:28:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly that #8217;s what it seems like:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 20:31:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why did they not put it out?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 16:10:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>This. This is what we #8217;re going to try to post here now? Seriously there is r/nsfw_wtf. There is r/enoughinternet. There is r/imgoingtohellforthis. Don #8217;t post this stupid shit here mate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 16:15:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was going to say it saw something really interesting over to the left.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 23:35:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn it I was just coming here to post this and it #8217;s the first post I see. Have my updoot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 12:09:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/nsfw_wtf</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Some fucked up tat</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 18:37:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 18:43:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I made my guys fight a ghost. Two guys were trying to kill it as fast as possible and the third was trying to help it cross over. The third guy was in the middle of the ghosts story about how she was raped and killed by two guys and the only way she could get put to rest was to find them and kill them when the other two rolled and killed her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 12:12:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was literally just posted less than a day ago with almost 2k upvotes. Why do you think you could just change the title and it #8217;d be okay to repost?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 22:23:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my bad sorry. But it #8217;s still been removed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 22:34:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know what Magical? Because I am a huge cunt you can post it again and I #8217;ll leave it up for a little while and see how much people like it. I do apologize for not leaving it up. And also for saying it was a repost. I could not see the link and all I could see was the thumbnail.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 22:46:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah mate I was in the wrong here. It #8217;s just every time a post gets more that 1.5k upvotes at least 6 people try to repost it like 10 hours later. So I have a bot that shows me every post that is submitted and I look at them as soon as they #8217;re posted. I had already deleted about 4 of the reposts when I got to yours. And the gif didn #8217;t work for me and all I saw was a thumbnail. So I thought it was a repost. And I was annoyed that I had already removed about 4 before I got to you post so I commented like a cunt. Like I said my apologies and please go ahead and try it again. If it gets over 300 upvotes after 24 hours it #8217;s all good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 03:34:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/confusedboners</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 03:41:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL I have a tongue condition</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A quick survey.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 18:20:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 18:21:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does any here actually read the rules?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 21:22:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know you were probably joking but that is about 80% of the people who post stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 23:42:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>This comment was a roller coaster but it is highly appreciated and rule 3c doesn #8217;t necessarily mean people can #8217;t post OC but people have been trying to post their nudes, normal porn, and their snapchats/kiks. Thats what rule 3c pertains to. Edit: for some reason the spam bot deleted this comment. Probably because I said Snapchat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 23:45:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you elaborate on that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 04:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck is this shit?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 14:08:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is exactly my thought. Humor is subjective. That is why I use the system I use. If something breaks the rules and is really not related to this sub at all it is automatically removed. But if I see a post and I just personally don #8217;t think it #8217;s funny I #8217;ll leave it. And after 24 hours I #8217;ll look again and see how many upvotes it has. There are some things I don #8217;t think are funny that get 2k upvotes. And there are some that only get 30. If I #8217;m not sure about a post I let the users decide. That #8217;s how I stop myself from being biased and over controlling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 14:15:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trust me there is plenty of stuff getting posted but most of it is bots and spam. What you see is all that is really worth it. I #8217;d love for more people to post but I want it to be good posts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 17:25:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m pretty sure this is just blatant sexual harassment/assault</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 18:34:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I dont know man, I #8217;ve seen some pretty funny porn scenes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 19:51:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly the thing I try to explain to my friends who think that guns = bad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 21:37:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s pretty close at a glance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 15:11:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>See now you seem like the type of cunt to do this type of thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 15:21:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is an analogy yes. But for the analogy to work it must make sense. See let me explain. Your analogy was this. Someone who dresses  #8220;inappropriately #8221; should not be surprised when they elicit a certain response.  gt;When someone wears shorts and a t-shirt to an interview and they #8217;re surprised they don #8217;t get the job. See in this scenario wearing shorts and a t shirt to an interview would be normally considered appropriate. But here is the problem with your analogy. This woman is wearing a bathing suit. I #8217;ll admit it is a somewhat revealing one but nonetheless it is a bathing suit. So she IS wearing the appropriate attire for her situation. So it seems here your analogy doesn #8217;t pertain to this situation at all. A better analogy might be  #8220;When a cunt comments something stupid on a post he shouldn #8217;t be surprised when people who actually use their heads completely hate him. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 15:27:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. I #8217;ve implemented new spam filters. 2. Removed YouTube links because 99% of the time they were irrelevant or removed by YouTube 3. I #8217;ve created a bot that helps combat trolls 4. We put a reddit age limit on posters to help combat reddit bots and throwaway accounts 5. We started removing post that had very low upvotes and were simply in the way. We #8217;ve tweaked a few more things but those were the main issues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 15:28:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man if only I could watch this with even more jpeg Edit: autocorrect</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 16:01:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I meant watch but it changed it to what</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 21:40:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>See here is the problem with you specific ideology. The statement:  gt; I think she is dressing appropriately, but if I were wearing such clothing it wouldn't surprise me if some horny idiot was going to feel me up You can #8217;t say a person is dressed appropriately and then follow with a statement saying something of a negative consequence. That #8217;s like saying  #8220;That suit is perfect for the wedding, but if I wore it I wouldn #8217;t be surprised when women want to grab my dick #8221;. I simply swapped the genders of your statement and it #8217;s apparent how unusual of a statement it is. Of course you #8217;re correct in saying that there are idiots who will do inappropriate things. But to a woman as attractive as that I #8217;d be surprised if it mattered if she were dressed as a nun. The fault cannot be placed on the woman for the actions of the man. By your thought process this analogy would be exactly the same as how you see the situation in the post. A man is walking down the street in a blue shirt. A man in red is driving by and sees him. The man in red says,  #8220;No fucking crips in my streets #8221;. The man in red is a blood. He then shoots the man in blue. So is it the man in blue #8217;s fault the man in red shot him. The man in blue simply decided he liked his blue shirt today. He had no gang affiliations. But according to you the man in blue should be aware that there are people out there who hate the color blue. It #8217;s his fault he wore blue. Does it make sense now why your statement is making so many people angry? It #8217;s not your idea itself. It is the way you are wording. You could have said something along the lines of  #8220; its only a matter of time an asshole would try it #8221;. But really even then people would get mad. I do understand that as a man a small part of us wants to but the difference in us and the subject in the post is our self control. Really the best tactic would have just been to not comment anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 05:08:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn #8217;t. I used super glue and it is almost completely healed. And you almost can #8217;t even tell anything was wrong with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 15:27:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>So why not say that instead of what you were saying before? What you said there was infinitely better that basically implying she was asking for it by dressing that way. All you had to say was that right there.  #8220;Dressing that way comes with risks. There are cunts in the world. #8221; That #8217;s is way better than  #8220;dressed like that she should expect it. #8221; It only took you two day to understand that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 20:11:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>[A lot of silicone](https://www.reddit.com/r/EnoughInternet/comments/8dj807/i_call_it_the_blob/?st=JGB4PDLA amp;sh=a1af75f3)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 20:15:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>[well, bad news everyone it #8217;s a dude.](https://www.heavy-r.com/video/155642/The_dildo_bike_ride/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 20:29:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>[look at what I found](https://www.heavy-r.com/video/155642/The_dildo_bike_ride/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 15:23:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/timestop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 01:22:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you elaborate?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 01:28:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>But what is considered non porn funny?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 01:30:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you want STI #8217;s? Because that #8217;s how you get STI #8217;s.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 12:13:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>[wow I #8217;ve never seen this before](https://www.reddit.com/r/NSFWFunny/comments/80rxvg/wait_for_it/?st=JGEXX7X5 amp;sh=e8bbce74)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Moderator Complaint</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 13:06:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>The options on moderating posts slightly changed. You used to be able to just scroll through and tap the shield button and it bring up the full list of moderator options. I used this to quickly remove posts as I was scrolling. Now you have to click on the post and open it if you want the full list of moderator options. Which is annoying if I #8217;m trying to quickly go through a sub. Can we change this back please?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 23:19:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hear you on that but here #8217;s the problem. We can #8217;t have a quantity of quality posts unless people post a quantity of quality posts. When I leave a bunch of mediocre posts up to give them a chance no one upvotes them. Then they get removed. It #8217;s not that we don #8217;t get a lot of submissions, it #8217;s that most submissions have no reason to be here. Most are spam, plain porn, or not related in any way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 23:33:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I should have taken that post down when I saw it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 23:35:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why do I keep seeing all these r/NSFWFunny crossposts? The mods there must be shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 12:09:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>No we dont</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 15:57:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>My luck none of the shitposters will post anything now. Then everyone will be like  #8220; see subject7627, we don #8217;t have a spam problem. Your just a stick up little bitch. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 16:39:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sure hope it will be</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 16:41:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was that last crosspost from r/funny that pushed over the edge</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 16:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or V JJ</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 17:04:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah pretty much. A lot of people have complained about there not being enough posts. So hopefully everyone can see what I see everyday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 20:40:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s really not</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 21:07:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I would never do that.](https://imgur.com/a/kKUWkij)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 21:34:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 21:40:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m 21 and out of college, but with my own money I can afford a candy bar.  #128527; hit me up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 22:25:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>What makes you say that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 22:25:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay wait a minute.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 22:35:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okie dokie then</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 22:46:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>This purge is just an experiment to show what kind of content actually gets filtered out. I see EVERY. SINGLE. POST. And I don #8217;t think people realize what actually gets posted here. So now we #8217;ll see.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 23:00:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are they still active?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 23:13:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh fuck! Dad?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 23:17:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the reason I have chronic depression</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 23:18:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just wanted to make you proud Papa..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 23:40:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty accurate actually</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 00:06:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s because we rely on our porn to cope with our own deep person vices.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 02:39:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you guys know everything I think?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 02:48:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>And you also got my username wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 12:11:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean I don #8217;t disagree. She is hilarious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 12:15:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was hope this whole purge thing could help people understand why we have so few posts. Because most are like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 12:16:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m going to give it another day or two and I #8217;m turning everything back on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 14:42:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I do this because I love you.](https://imgur.com/a/QKADZtF)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 18:35:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are we 12?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 18:56:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I first started my last job I was a dishwasher. For the longest time I was the only one doing that job. So a lady I worked with (a 57 year old Korean woman) would come over to help me when I got too busy. The problem with it was that she #8217;d complain about having to help me. And in my head I #8217;d always think * I never asked you to come over here*. Always made me mad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 19:06:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>She did a lot of things like that. I just got used to it. For me it #8217;s easier to tolerate stupid than it is to invite more in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 19:33:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would have done that but I figured she #8217;d just keel over first</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 19:33:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are definitely out of the loop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 19:37:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here you go.](https://www.reddit.com/r/NSFWFunny/comments/8f2sr3/rnsfwfunny_purge/?st=JGI8P7YX amp;sh=47442aad)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 19:57:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>[here #8217;s the explanation ](https://www.reddit.com/r/NSFWFunny/comments/8f2sr3/rnsfwfunny_purge/?st=JGI8P7YX amp;sh=47442aad)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 20:26:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re a little late</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 20:31:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>What?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 22:31:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>It still only shows the Loch Ness monster. No actual tits</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 22:32:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck did you just make me read?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 22:32:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 22:35:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Back in the year 2002</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 23:16:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be the case if it were really an experiment. It #8217;s more like I #8217;m showing you what I sift through for the sub.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 23:36:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>A blind man with no arms could wash dishes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 00:05:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>But did you at least giggle?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 02:01:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well now I #8217;m sad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Okay this fucking Purge is over you cunts.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 02:02:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 02:32:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are dead to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 02:33:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Enjoy your new flair</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 03:08:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I probably won #8217;t word this very good but just know I don #8217;t mean to sound cunty. If you have tried to tell other and they won #8217;t believe you what I would do personally is put the person in a situation they can #8217;t explain. Such as if a male were forcing me to perform oral sex on him I would bite the fuck out of him. How is he going to explain that. He can #8217;t with out admitting that he was performing vile acts. Like I said I don #8217;t mean to sound like an ass but that #8217;s the best way I could think of explaining my thoughts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 15:55:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I removed them. Because sweet Jesus they were bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 16:15:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>On attack: Blitz #8217;s shield On defense: Montagne #8217;s Shield Trust me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 16:16:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where is Idubbz when you need him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 17:01:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s over now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 18:31:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who knows?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 18:38:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was a big announcement like this one. And as long as the purge was going I didn #8217;t delete anything. Obviously now that it #8217;s over I removed all the shitposts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 18:54:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s not like anyone was getting any karma from it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 18:55:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>The purge is over</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 00:46:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not an expert but I #8217;m pretty sure a fire also destroys potential evidence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 14:47:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was literally just posted</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 14:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/NobodyAsked Edit: r/Oopsdidntmeanto</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 14:55:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay whoever reported this  #8220;the mod has a tiny dick #8221; I have one question for you. Did you have to tell everyone?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 14:59:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is straight up r/TitleGore</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 15:04:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>That rainbow symbolizes the entire world won #8217;t be flooded. They #8217;re can still be floods. Apparently people are still experiencing floods mate. Because I guess some people thing it #8217;s still going.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 15:05:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Such as?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 15:09:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>If only there was some sort of medical process that people who don #8217;t want their unborn child can go through to remove it. It #8217;s such a shame such a thing doesn #8217;t exist... But seriously why couldn #8217;t they just let her get an abortion. I mean if she wanted one, and they are legal, how can they charge her for trying to do it herself after they refused to let her see a doctor?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 15:10:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay but with my flair I dont know if you #8217;d be smart to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 15:24:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>The misery isn #8217;t yours it #8217;s your family members who have to sit there clinging onto a person who will never be able to have a true relationship and connection to them. They are simply a body and not a human. Meat with no soul.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 15:30:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you know what the medical company want you to do? They want you to hold on. Because the longer you hold on the more you pay. The doctors know there is nearly a zero percent chance and they tell you that. Most doctors don #8217;t want a family to waste away financially for an inanimate body. To keep a person alive with no brain functions is logically stupid. Without brain function it is just a husk of meat without a soul. They are already dead. What would be the point of keeping a body breathing and a heart pumping when it serves no purpose to the brain? All it does is destroy families financially and emotionally.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 15:32:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay is this title fucked up or am I having a stroke?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 15:34:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Um how about publicity? He is a criminal who committed heinous crimes and is on television. More likely than not he #8217;s a narcissist. To him the more incredible his feats the bigger of a badass he is. He wants people to fear him and he wants them to think he #8217;s evil. That #8217;s how these people think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 16:01:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ingenious!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 16:20:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is still emotional and psychological suffering. It is still a person who is not actually alive. Their body is breathing and their heart is pumping but they are in all intents and purposes dead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 20:12:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean it is nice and I can see we #8217;re it could cause an emotional reaction but it is obvious that this is a short film. But it also has 0 context. I have no idea what the hell is going on. Who are those guys? Why is he living on the street? If his family new he was there why didn #8217;t they just find him? What was the point of the TV #8217;s? Why were there actors playing homeless guys? Who #8217;s the guy in the car? I just have too many questions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 22:31:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Papa Franku?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 18:34:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>You do realize this is a sub called  #8220; 4 Panel Cringe #8221; right? Not r/Badfaketexts or r/comedycemetary</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 18:36:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would it be cheating if he wished to be the most powerful sayian?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 18:47:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Central Time zone. I #8217;m active daily in most of my free time. 2. I have been moderator of r/NSFWFunny for almost 5 months. And I have r/RedditMemorials but it isn #8217;t very active yet. 3. This is one of the first subs I added so about 1 year and 5 months. 4. I am familiar with the rules and I believe they are pretty good at the moment. Simple and straightforward. 5. I think I #8217;m the spirit of  #8220;terrible #8221; Facebook memes that there isn #8217;t really a meme that should be banned. At least not one I #8217;ve seen. 6. I think for the time being the sub is pretty balanced. It seems to flow pretty good. I may suggest lengthening the repost time limit. 7. I hope I can help you guys out. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 18:58:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would it be wrong if I #8217;d bite Will i eat my shit tonight Chances are that I might My squeaky ball is outa sight And I #8217;m contemplating where it #8217;d hide I #8217;m losing my sight I #8217;m losing my mind My master #8217;s home, and he #8217;s right outside</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 19:01:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>$5 billion and you can tell everyone they #8217;re stupid. Hell I #8217;d tell them they #8217;re stupid for free.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Reddit video player always does this to me.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 00:44:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 02:27:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see what you did there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 18:39:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least his username isn #8217;t u/PRbox</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 20:41:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>The movie theater nearby me won #8217;t let you buy more than one ticket if you #8217;re under 21</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 20:41:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You. You seem like a cunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 20:50:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>No I #8217;d say you being a cunt is what makes you a cunt. If a service is promised to me that is the service I expect. But if when I pay for that service and they change the service I was paying for to be less than what I signed up for then I #8217;m upset. Imagine if a dealership gave you a Lamborghini for $200 a month to use how ever much you want. But after you signed the contract they say  #8220;actually you can only drive it 10 miles a day. #8221; That #8217;s what this is like.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 21:40:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay how about basic mathematics? The average price for a movie ticket in the US is about $9.00. Okay so originally they promised their subscribers a deal of 1 movie ticket a day for the price of about $10.00 a month. That would mean for $10.00 you #8217;d get 30 tickets a month. That #8217;s $270.00 worth of tickets. With a net gain of $260.00 worth of merchandise. Or a 2,700% increase in gains. Now that sounds like a good deal. So you subscribe and pay $10.00 a month for 30 tickets a month. But then they change it.  gt; We learned earlier this week that for new subscribers, MoviePass is no longer allowing customers to see one movie per day. Instead, the $9.95 subscription will allow customers to purchase only four tickets per month, with MoviePass CEO Mitch Lowe admitting that he doesn #8217;t know if the  #8220;unlimited #8221; plan will ever return. Now you pay $10.00 a month and only get 4 tickets a month. Only $36.00 worth of tickets. Which is a $26.00 net gain. Or 360% increase. Okay that #8217;s 2,340% less that what you were promised. So basically you invested in something that was supposed to make you $270.00 but instead only made you $26.00. It is a gain but it is definitely not what was promised. Definitely more than a 0.001% loss you described. So yeah I #8217;d be mad too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 21:48:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>So basically never sign anything?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 23:11:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>True. It is about as bad as Verizon with its unlimited plans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 23:11:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yet how often can you go into a contact deal that #8217;s less than a year?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 23:15:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then why would you pay for a year if you don #8217;t have to?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 13:01:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/NobodyAsked</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 13:04:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Gamora is a GOTG 2. You forgot Maria Hill and Nick Fury 3. They didn #8217;t die, they ceased to exist. Gamora and Loki are the ones who actually died.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 13:10:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Loki also died separately 2. I eat ass 3. It #8217;ll be easier to bring them back this way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 13:15:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 14:28:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. I miss my dad 2. Why didn #8217;t he love me 3. It was only 2 and a half hours</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 16:49:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is already done and over</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 16:49:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah what the fuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 18:51:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Huh. I just noticed that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 15:00:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>No that would be ridiculous. He simply ceases to exist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 16:32:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why else would they make it like that if it wasn #8217;t intended to be dropped on the ground?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 16:40:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but where is the excitement in that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 16:50:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 16:52:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why do you say that? This is a good example of someone being a total piece of shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 16:53:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a sad cunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 17:02:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you think tithes are for?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 18:08:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes but the thing is that the child shouldn #8217;t have been conceived. A child should be conceived under the consent and understanding of the mother and father. It should be something agreed upon or at least something where the risk is accepted by both parties. But in a situation of rape the woman is forced to conceive that child without the consent or acceptance of the risks of conception. That is something she did not want to do. And to force her to carry into term a child she never intended to have purposely or accidentally would be wrong. A child conceived from rape is a huge burden placed on a woman who never at any point accepted the risks of such a burden. That is why it is a completely separate situation to an accidental pregnancy between two consenting individuals. They knew the risks and inadvertently accepted them when the performed sexual acts. Yet with a rape there is no choice. If she had no choice in the act then I #8217;d say it #8217;s at least fair to give them a choice in the other.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 18:21:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would normally agree with you but looking into this type of subject I now don #8217;t. With the amount of children in orphanages and foster homes. And the general overall overpopulation. For a child who would normally never had been conceived I don #8217;t think it #8217;d matter to me if she chose to terminate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 00:59:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah? Would you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 01:29:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>But I meant OP..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We have an open clan if anyone wants to join.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 01:30:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 01:59:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>How much would something like this cost me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 02:05:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well. That is interesting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 12:10:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey thats the same thing someone commented the last time this was uploaded. Almost word for word.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 13:01:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did I just have a stroke? What the fuck is going on in this comment? Edit: okay now that he wrote it in English I can read it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 16:01:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah. So you #8217;re just being a cunt then. Alright carry on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 17:00:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh I can see that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 18:20:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. I #8217;m implying that that is an interesting deal. A high quality custom digital artwork for $50. What do you want me to say?  #8220;My grandma is dying in the hospital and the doctor says he won #8217;t operate unless he gets a high quality digital drawing of a big tiddied gnome ranger covered in vanilla frosting with sprinkles. So can you do it do it for $25? #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 18:32:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was kind of a filler. A way to reply so he knows I saw his response.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 18:43:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>NUTTIN #8217; just a Purge</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 18:51:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why don #8217;t you just take you #8217;re own clean water to a priest and have him bless it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 18:52:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have no idea what this says</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 18:54:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>My thoughts would be if a human with a soul can be possessed than an animal without one can be also.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 00:15:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. I don #8217;t even know what this means. 2. This doesn #8217;t belong here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 15:08:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t want to be held responsible for giving you guys autism.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 15:21:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s herd</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 15:25:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 15:30:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why would anyone do something like this while it #8217;s moving?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 15:32:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>One *PUUUUUUUUUNNNNNNNCCCHHHHH!*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 15:37:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Qiuerro morir</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 15:42:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>No but now I have autism. Edit: Apparently my autism is something people don #8217;t agree with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 16:12:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess you took the name of the sub a little too seriously.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 16:15:59</DATE>
    <TEXT> #191;qu #233; hay de la violaci #243;n?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 17:10:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>They were cooking in a moving RV because an animal was in the road?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 21:40:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the guy in front is facing the wrong way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 21:45:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those are some broad ass shoulders</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 00:32:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is pretty related. It was a response to a comment directed to me specifically. Edit: people don #8217;t like comments directed towards me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 14:31:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck is going on here?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 14:32:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay who reported this saying  #8220;TRAPS ARE GAY #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 14:39:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m pretty sure you should have cropped out the dudes name Edit: yeah it #8217;s in the rules. #8 mate. Don #8217;t get fucking banned cunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 14:49:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm. Fat white women who are possibly racist. I feel like I #8217;ve seen a unicorn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 14:58:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>It becomes a challenge</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 15:02:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shh  #233;l es un gringo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 15:26:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe a r/scriptedasiangifs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 15:29:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was a physics lesson. Newton #8217;s first law.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 15:29:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>It would have been fine if the kid hadn #8217;t have moved</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 00:46:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re absolutely right, those haircuts are gross.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 00:47:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wouldn #8217;t this only really work if your dick was actually noticeable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 01:37:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I #8217;m just saying it seems the whole point is to show off your bulge. But wouldn #8217;t it be more effective if they **had** a bulge</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 14:23:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s a good thing those black bars are there or I might see something inappropriate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 14:26:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/nsfw_wtf?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 18:07:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>As compared to what? As far as I know that #8217;s the best sexual wtf content to find.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 18:12:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here we aren #8217;t so insensitive. Please to refer to them as  #8220;googly nips #8221;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 18:16:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay the tits are great but why does she have to make [this face?](https://imgur.com/a/Dqbew6d)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 18:40:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>ITS LITERALLY BEEN 2 FUCKING DAYS. Do this shit again and I #8217;ll ban a motherfucker for 3 days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 18:44:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some people I swear are trying to give me an aneurism.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 21:25:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay a little off topic but I love that character idea</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 21:35:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uh obviously it #8217;d be Chin-Chin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 13:03:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shit mentos here is like $2</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 15:53:03</DATE>
    <TEXT> #191;Por que no los dos?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[XB1] Just looking for some casual players.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 18:41:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>DM your gamer tag if you just want to play for fun. Obviously I play to win but I don #8217;t get too worked up about it. I just love playing the game and need some people to play with me. I #8217;m level 127 but I haven #8217;t played ranked yet because it #8217;s been a few months since I #8217;ve played. DM me if you #8217;re interested.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 04:11:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Coming from someone with the username  #8220;definitelynottwelve #8221; is a little ironic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 04:23:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>My buddy just gets nude mods.. you know... to enhance the game. And for strokes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 12:59:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>TERFs??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 13:00:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>TERFshhhmmmmm?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 13:02:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah fuck that guy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 16:06:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really? How many times are we going to repost this? It #8217;s only been 4 days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 18:35:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s not the bot that I meant to put being upvoted. It #8217;s the post that needs to be upvoted. The bot is only here to remind everyone of that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 18:43:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah pretty much. The bot was made for some people (like u/lollipopamateurs) who think every single post on here is fucking hilarious. Then they don #8217;t understand that posts that don #8217;t get upvoted get deleted. They #8217;re like,  #8220; Oh subject7627, this post is hilarious. If you don #8217;t think so then you shouldn #8217;t be a mod. #8221; And then the post gets like 30 upvotes and then I remove it. Because that #8217;s how I do this. I go by the upvotes. I #8217;m no comedy master, but I can do some simple math. If 20,000 people see it, and there are only 30 upvotes then that means people don #8217;t like it. That #8217;s it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 21:40:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s to weed out the weak. I just want to personally apologize that I made you scroll for an extra 0.26 seconds. I know that #8217;s hard for you but I #8217;m proud that you toughed it out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 21:48:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eat my ass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 21:53:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get you mate. But I #8217;ve tried it the easy way. I was going to put something like  #8220; upvote the post if it belongs here. If it doesn #8217;t have enough votes it will be removed. #8221; But you know no one will read that shit. But I bet you read every bit of that didn #8217;t you? That #8217;s the only reason it was written that way. To make people read it. That #8217;s all I want. Is for people to actually read the rules and shit. That way I don #8217;t have 20 posts a day that get removed because the spam filter or auto mod got them. Or people DMing me over and over about why their YouTube video isn #8217;t on the new feed. I #8217;m just annoyed at this point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 03:29:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow who would have guessed? 24 hours and it only has about 30 upvotes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 18:42:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck is this bullshit? A shitty meme doesn #8217;t belong here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 18:52:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>What did you saw? Wood? Maybe for a table or a nice bookshelf?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 19:01:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did I just have a stroke?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:41:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is a group of black men looking sensually at a very petite white woman. It is from a popular pornographic movie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:59:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mines 1 inch long and 10 in diameter. I #8217;m very lonely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 23:08:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>They can me the tuna can man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A dog watches me eat</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 04:47:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 18:37:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess after everyone saw her nudes she figured she might as well do it in films.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 17:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re seeing a sneak peak at some titty and this is your comment?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 17:17:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is a pretty good cookie. What did you use?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 17:31:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>See that very bottom arrow. It #8217;s pointing to where I am.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 15:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/nomorals?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 15:13:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve become a numb husk of a human being only capable of mimicking the emotions of those around me. That is how I can interact with the outside world even when my soul is gone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 15:14:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it #8217;s on YouTube, it doesn #8217;t belong here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 15:16:12</DATE>
    <TEXT> #191;donde esta la muerte?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 15:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it #8217;s on YouTube, then it #8217;s too tame for here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hello, I #8217;m a semi-new DM. I #8217;m currently in the middle of a mini adventure based on the seven deadly sins. It will consist of seven rooms that are imbued with magic traps. I was just wondering if anyone could help me with some ideas.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 15:32:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have some rooms already thought out but I need help with a few. Sloth Wrath Pride Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 16:46:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I dont know but im sad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 16:59:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah that #8217;s a lot better than my original idea. My idea was it was a long hallway. And the longer they stand still the farther the door gets. Or something like that. Edit: there obviously would be obstacles in their way as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 18:12:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>My idea was like that. But instead of damage they secretly lose armor class points.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 19:36:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know I was thinking about the same thing earlier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 19:37:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s nice too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 19:37:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought about maybe them having to dodge traps that give them fatigue effects if they fail.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 19:38:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>That could work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 19:43:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>One idea I had for Pride was they enter a room of mirrors and then they #8217;re reflections come to life and try to kill them. Their reflections strengths will be the thing they #8217;re the best in. And to defeat them they have to accept their faults and use they #8217;re weaker abilities to win. For Wrath I thought maybe the doors in the room would disappear and then it #8217;d start filling with something. And I #8217;d let them go on for a while looking for a way out until they get pissed. But when they calm down the stuff in the room vanishes and they see the door. But I wasn #8217;t sure these were that good which is why I asked for ideas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 23:09:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s not even accurate information. There are certain conditions that must be met for that to be true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 23:11:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yay now she can spend the remaining 5 years of her life with a fancy piece of paper she hadn #8217;t needed for 40+ years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 23:15:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>15x</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 23:17:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Donald Glover: let me just make a unique music video full of subtle symbolism and deep social commentary, all while being put to a unique song. Some cunt: let #8217;s put  #8220;I Just Met You #8221; over the music video. It #8217;ll be funny.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 23:23:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can even see right before she falls there #8217;s liquids coming out of her asshole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 23:23:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do too. He deletes all my posts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 23:25:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m always watching Summerie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 23:33:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/woooosh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 15:19:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>soy asiatico</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 15:32:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can tell you how I play Jackal but it definitely isn #8217;t the normal way. I mainly go with my teammates and I **always** have the visor on. Then if I see any footprints I can tell my teammates where to look out for people. I will scan if I get the chance. But really I play him as I would recruit. But I #8217;m more of a support player. I #8217;m not the best at gunplay so I use the PDW. And I mainly give info.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 21:12:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Reminds me of my post forever ago](https://www.reddit.com/r/shittyrainbow6/comments/69w3qx/remember_when_you_first_played_doc/?st=JH6MK2IH amp;sh=24ddfe2d)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 02:16:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why didn #8217;t she think she #8217;d live to see 21? I turned 21 April 20th can I have karma?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 02:21:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. But I can be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 02:22:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>But 420 though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 02:23:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>It doesn #8217;t matter because I don #8217;t give a fuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 05:07:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well. I do wanna die.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 16:36:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Edgy as fuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 16:43:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually haven #8217;t seen it for a few days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 01:45:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s Seppuku. Sudoku is a number puzzle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 01:46:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you delete your post? Edit: Pretty please. Edit 2: Wait a second! I can do that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 01:48:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this even English?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 02:13:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>This doesn #8217;t seem good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 02:14:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aw fuck not again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 02:22:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay who reported saying only  #8220;cheese #8221;?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Every time I play there is at least one match</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 02:30:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 20:41:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.grammarcheck.net/editor/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 23:08:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I honestly don #8217;t blame you at this point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 02:11:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know what Tekalmighty? You are absolutely right. It must be my incredibly small dick or the fact my parents never truly loved me. That probably why I am such a cunt. But seeing as I am a cunt I will continue to do so. Because I #8217;m not driven by how others view me. I am purely driven by the fact that I don #8217;t give a fuck Edit: what is with the comment you linked? It was obviously a joke on a r/isitbullshit post</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 02:19:14</DATE>
    <TEXT> lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 02:24:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m wrong? Can you explain?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 02:26:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh okay then. I #8217;ll let you believe that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 03:04:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 02:18:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>So again. What recipe did you use?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 03:46:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm. Is almond sugar cookies a better recipe?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 03:56:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>True. Yet could you not just skip out on the poppy seeds?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 04:08:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. Baking and cooking are really my only two hobbies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 04:29:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excellent. Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 21:24:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess the username checks out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 21:27:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean that is true but relatively speaking it won #8217;t matter due to the fact he could never know what he #8217;s missing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 21:50:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes but you #8217;ll never know. That #8217;s the thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 00:03:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every time I try to do a shaggy impression I always just end up being the surfer fish from spongebob.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 14:19:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. Say that same thing now but in English.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 15:46:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m sorry. WHAT?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 15:47:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>*sirens in the distance.* *therapy intensifies.*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 15:56:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s because Florida doesn #8217;t have a confidentiality issue on their police reports. This means that their police reports are open to the public. Which is why we always see Florida police reports.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 15:59:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was funny the first time someone posted it. Not anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 16:02:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Um I definitely would have said  #8220;rich and Jewish #8221;. If she were Jewish that is what she is. You #8217;re comment makes absolutely no sense. Stop trying to be triggered.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 16:49:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/badwomensanatomy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 19:36:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I #8217;m completely referring to the big boobs. Not the entire skeletal structure of the woman.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 20:50:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe if you have scoliosis.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 21:12:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Qierro morir</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 00:38:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>What I am say is the skeletal structure is wrong. Her skull is too small. Her spine is all fucked up. Her rib cage is way too big and it #8217;s not just because of those huge badongadongs. And her arm is fucking massive. What I #8217;m saying is that her body is not proportional to a human body. And it is all because they tried to give her huge zadoinkydougs. Yes I know scoliosis is mainly viewed from the back but you can tell when someone has a fucked up spine. So gigantic wobbleflopperdoos or not it doesn #8217;t make sense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 04:00:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>*uh hmm* Fuze?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 04:06:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s what I thought until I realized I won #8217;t get destroyed after placing a cluster charge. Now if they shoot through the surface it just bounces right off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 04:08:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>This has been happening to me as well. I thought it was just my shitty mic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 04:20:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>She #8217;d be hotter if she didn #8217;t look like Ray William Johnson.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 15:45:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>They paid to promote their dog. But you #8217;re doing it for free.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 15:46:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Post it again and I #8217;ll give you a 3 day ban.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 17:00:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every single thing I post gets taken down because of rule 10  #8220;No memes #8221;. Yet everyday I get on this sub and I see things like this getting thousands of votes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 17:03:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s not the fact the guy himself got front page. It #8217;s the shitty meme he posts getting on front page. The reason it #8217;s so bad is because the mods on this sub are biased as fuck. Rule number 10 is  #8220;No memes. #8221; Yet everyday they pick and choose what they consider a meme. This is definitely a meme but it #8217;s still here. Yet a  #8220;high quality #8221; meme gets taken down in an hour.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 17:22:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s what we #8217;re talking about. Yes it is technically artwork, but it #8217;s also technically a meme. It #8217;s is 100% a meme format with siege assets. It is hand drawn but it is still definitely a very well known meme. Edit: To me these posts are all obvious memes breaking Rule 10. But apparently I #8217;m the only one who thinks so. https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8kvmti/power_creep/?st=JHGEGJUX amp;sh=3cde1bc8 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8ktwij/r6_ubi_i_dont_feel_so_good/?st=JHGEJR41 amp;sh=20123179 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8ku4j5/when_everyone_is_selecting_their_operator/?st=JHGELS3N amp;sh=c54d7d71 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8l06kj/poor_training_dummy/?st=JHGERHC0 amp;sh=e8a7ba1f</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 19:01:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a mute main I feel very ashamed when people stop moving in the radius of my jammers. Like guys, I got this. We are covered.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 19:38:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>###MY RADIUS ENCOMPASSES ALL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 20:04:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>^my ^radius ^encompasses ^enough</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 20:23:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here is what it #8217;s based on](https://imgur.com/a/SF6OnXJ)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 02:27:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t want to say you #8217;re retarded, but you are making it really hard not to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 16:43:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay there is one too many posts over a card with a dick on it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 20:19:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Get off our sub. You got your upvote, now go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 21:17:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/scriptedasiangifs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 22:33:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whoa there buddy! That #8217;s a lot of hostility there. Do you want to talk about it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 22:34:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uh. Sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 02:06:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>So it seems you might have some pent up resentment there. Is it because of your father. I know you two didn #8217;t really get along that well but I just want you to know that that doesn #8217;t matter anymore. *YOU* are your own man now. You can be whatever *YOU* want to be. And if you choose to be a cunt, that #8217;s entirely up to you. Just keep in mind that we love you. Even if you can #8217;t take a joke. We still love you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 02:07:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shh, don #8217;t tell him. Let him figure it out on his own.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 02:08:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>He seems to be very upset about something. I #8217;m not sure what, but it #8217;s obviously something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 04:33:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 06:53:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>No</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 06:59:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>After his fight with the Juggernaut, Colossus has a dent in his forehead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 07:10:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>If Deadpool went back in time to save Vanessa, then does that mean the entire movie plot changes without Deadpool?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 07:14:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>The element of surprise can really throw a guy off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 08:00:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck? How did I not see that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 08:21:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>True</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 08:27:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that #8217;d because that Deadpool is definitely not the same Deadpool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 16:43:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m honestly surprised she could shave. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 16:52:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is definitely chocolate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 02:12:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This was literally posted a week ago.](https://www.reddit.com/r/NSFWFunny/comments/8jsj3k/the_death_roll/?st=JHJS82TM amp;sh=c1282d33)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 02:14:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really? A shitty meme. Please.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 02:18:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let #8217;s not get worked up over a post with 360 votes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 17:21:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck is this comment?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 17:23:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>[It #8217;s been fucking 8 days.](https://www.reddit.com/r/NSFWFunny/comments/8jsj3k/the_death_roll/?st=JHKOT03V amp;sh=f5ec712a)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 19:59:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was something like,  #8220; Lol. Hey. Baby. He #8217;s still got his socks on. #8221; Or some shit like that. It was from the poster.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 20:01:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I swear to god if I see this post again a mother fucker is getting banned. it literally been 8 days.](https://www.reddit.com/r/NSFWFunny/comments/8jsj3k/the_death_roll/?st=JHKUF68W amp;sh=217a6331)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 20:03:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>For like half a second I thought this was r/wheredidthesodago</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 04:44:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then you #8217;ll probably love the other posts he #8217;s posted here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 04:48:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m honestly terrified.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My girl playing with my dick</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 04:53:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 00:52:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a  #8220;prank #8221; though. Not a life hack.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 17:29:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you 12?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 18:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course not, my ideological jargon is carefully produced through an extensive knowledge of the dictionary and a total understanding of the entirety of all medical history and science. I obviously hold the knowledge that mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cellular makeup and that vaccines can cripple deoxyribonucleic acids in your body along with the complex amino acids which comprise the human infrastructure. So eat my ass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 19:26:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 20:47:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sho*I*lder *want*er S*to*uler S*die*ould</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 20:49:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck? Am I too old to understand it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 20:50:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually it #8217;s tall, not deep.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 17:06:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Water isn #8217;t a beverage. That #8217;s literally the definition of a beverage-  #8220;a drink that isn #8217;t water #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 17:14:51</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;I want to roll to invade them! #8221;  #8220;Uh, are you sure that #8217;s what you want to do? #8221;  #8220;Yes. Of course. Just let me roll. #8221;  #8220;Fine. Roll. #8221; He rolls his 20 sided die across the table. It stops directly in front of the Dungeon Master, who looks down and smirks.  #8220;Well. You go to invade Russia. You gather your troops and march right in. But you #8217;re too stupid to realize you should never invade Russia in the winter. #8221; Hitler angrily looks over to his die. He sees the clearest image of a 1.  #8220;Well hell. I #8217;ve been rolling good the beginning of this campaign. What else could go wrong? #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 17:52:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey. It #8217;s a literal  #8220;karmawhore #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 18:17:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>The show is full of rape and suicide. Both of which are pretty lengthy, graphic, and common. But, we #8217;ll draw the line at sodomy? Pussies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 18:33:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can literally hear your spine crying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 23:16:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can only blame myself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 23:17:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish I could read it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 22:45:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uh...okay?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 02:14:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like to start with baby wipes. As a kind of appetizer. Then I go in and finish with the toilet paper. So clean.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 06:49:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sit on it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 17:23:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>In The Dark Knight (2008) it is hinted that Bruce Wayne and Batman could be the same person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 17:27:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow a completely SFW meme.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 17:30:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it #8217;s from r/funny it probably doesn #8217;t belong here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 17:33:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s a street sign. Why would it fall under their porn rule?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 17:35:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was literally posted 12 hours before you posted it. Does no one notice or what?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 20:08:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can see they went all out for that helmet effect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 00:30:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don #8217;t know what cross posting is do you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 00:30:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit someone actually reads the rules.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 00:31:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s literally a link to the original post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Here #8217;s my boy, Link.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 00:33:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 01:40:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really need to make him one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 02:05:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be fair the driver might not have seen a 5 inch tall duckling directly in front of their car.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 07:06:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>You. I like your style kid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 19:45:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>She is using her vaginal muscles to squeeze the white device. The device reads this input and outputs it as a tap on the screen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 19:45:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically she plays games with her pussy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 21:10:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You really had to hit me with those feels huh?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 20:35:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>[but Turk didn #8217;t make it up](https://youtu.be/sb2np1HGqxg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 23:40:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you may be talking this sub a little too literally.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 02:01:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, but it #8217;s not his dance. You can #8217;t copyright something someone doesn #8217;t have the rights to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 17:54:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man I feel so weird seeing everyone say Monty. He #8217;s one of the first 3 OPS I unlocked and at this point I can #8217;t help but main him. As long as I have One teammate to watch my back I can work miracles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 18:07:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I couldn #8217;t figure it out either</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 18:08:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you 12? Or just mentally handicapped?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 18:10:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>If this is the post you #8217;re talking about I see why it got removed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 18:11:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s just a bottle of hot sauce. I mean it #8217;s funny if you #8217;re 13.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 18:13:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, it technically doesn #8217;t have anything NSFW. It #8217;s an udder. I mean she has comically huge bagongahoogas but other than that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 22:07:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you explain where the pun is? Because I was saying an entirely reasonable excuse for the driver to hit them. Edit: There is also no proof this account even happened. It #8217;s just a picture of a car ordering food and some ducks. There #8217;s no video or after pictures. For all we know it #8217;s a story made up just to make people mad at a guy who probably had no idea it even happened.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 22:11:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes but...why?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 02:36:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow what a cunt Edit: sorry I meant OP not Forrest Gump Jr.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 03:27:18</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; #8221;*Now spread yer cheeks laddie* #8221; FTFY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 20:17:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. It is 100% plausible that the driver just couldn #8217;t see the 5-inch y #8217;all ducklings directly in front of them. 2. There is no evidence, such as pictures or video, that this even happened. It #8217;s just a picture of a car in a drive thru and some ducks. 3. It really isn #8217;t news worthy. Either it #8217;s a story simply to make people mad a a stranger who probably didn #8217;t even know it happened, or it is a really really really slow day at the news office.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 20:20:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay here #8217;s my thing. I #8217;m not going to say what he did was right, but what #8217;s the difference between what he did and feeding rats to a snake? Like really it is just changing the animals but it #8217;s literally the same concept.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 20:21:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>True</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 20:22:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>And it was probably autocorrect</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 22:39:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can assure you that having the life slowly squeezed out of you probably isn #8217;t great either. But what I #8217;m getting out of what you said is that it #8217;s mainly psychological. As in we hold dogs above other animals for some reason. Turtles will eat anything they can get there mouths around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 02:37:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I #8217;m not saying using a puppy was okay. I #8217;m just saying if it were a rat/mouse then no one would bat an eye.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 08:13:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I #8217;m pretty sure that #8217;s what it was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 08:37:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 08:45:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to die</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 08:46:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now I really want to die</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Simple Tachanka Buff Ideas</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 18:34:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s really depressing to see an original operator being reduced to nothing more than a meme. With just a little work Tachanka could be a viable and useful operator. 1. Reduce the LMG recoil. Why is it when you fire three shots from a **MOUNTED** gun and you #8217;re staring at the ceiling. His gun should be one of the more accurate ones. 2. His shield needs a rework. More health, possibly more coverage. But it is insane to see a 1 armor operator tank a massive LMG because they peaked around a corner and took out his shield. *Me personally I think the shield should go a little below the barrel too, but that #8217;s just me* 3. The LMG needs a sight. Any sight. Even something as simple as the LMG tip on Battlefield 1. The simple metal circle with a cross inside. 4. **360 DEGREE ROTATION** I mean come on it is exactly what he #8217;s doing in his operator video. 5. His LMG should stagger shields. I #8217;m mean seriously. If a small, Brazilian lady can knock a shield out of a massive French fuckers hands I #8217;m pretty sure a big ass LMG can too. This would give Tachanka a real advantage to covering an entry point. These are literally super simple buff that could make Tachanka a decent operator instead of someone you pick when you #8217;re kicking too much ass to give a shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 20:02:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s the problem. I would honestly have some guys fixed than just add more</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 20:06:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maestro to me isn #8217;t the same as Tachanka. When I think tachanka I want to think of this big Russian beast who sits in front of an entrance and completely deter attackers from going that way. And Maestro seems to me more of a Distraction and a nuisance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 21:11:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s nice to know there are others</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 23:39:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Especially if they decide to pretend you #8217;re not even there anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 17:10:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you play on?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 22:23:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>##HILARIOUS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 22:25:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>###HILARIOUS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 22:26:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay but get this....*that #8217;s the idea*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 01:11:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay how about  #8220;*greatly reduces movement speed* #8221;?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 02:13:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are correct</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 02:19:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, my favorite scene in all of adult film history.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 04:53:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>[It *has* been about ten seconds since we looked at our lemon tree.](https://m.xhamster.com/videos/joanna-angel-lemon-stealing-whore-4304263) (NSFW) [If you were a lemon I #8217;d put you on my shelf and cherish you just like I do all our other lemons](https://youtu.be/xPW-vkohqPE) (SFWish)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 07:20:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>See this is exactly what I #8217;m talking about.  gt;They deserve to be elevated 2nd only to humans. They literally helped us evolve into the agricultural age. But here the thing. While that is true, it is also true of Cows, pigs, sheep, horses, chickens, cats, weasels,rabbits, and several other animals. Yet we can pick and choose between all of those. The consumption of dog meat has a [long history](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dog_meat) all over the world. It is currently legal in 43 states. There have been times of meat shortages in the US in which eating dog was viewed as normal for sustaining your family. And certain Native American tribes considered dog a delicacy. While others forbade it. The reason we don #8217;t commonly eat dog meat is basically because we don #8217;t have to. We live in a county and time where meat is an abundance. We have plenty of beef, pork, chicken, and mutton. We don #8217;t have to depend on dog meat for sustenance. Other countries, like in Asia or Africa, don #8217;t have the abundance in meats as we do. That is why it is more common to find there. Dogs are easy to breed and farm. I can tell by your username and history that you think very highly of dogs. And that is perfectly fine and normal. The reason we hold dogs to such high esteem is because we don #8217;t have to eat them. We get to  #8220;baby #8221; them. We get to treat them like a part of the family. We don #8217;t have to farm them. We get to simply enjoy their company. Even if we kill [2.4 million](http://m.humanesociety.org/issues/pet_overpopulation/) domesticated animals a year simply because no one wants them. But hey, it #8217;s mans best friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 17:19:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never once said that turtles eat puppies. I said they #8217;ll eat anything they can get their mouths on. Now you #8217;re just trying to put words in my mouth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 17:53:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>To your first point, a service animal is legally defined as a dog who is trained to do certain types of work. But dogs aren #8217;t the only things trained as service animals. There are cases of cats, miniature horses, small monkeys, ferrets, and even ducks which act as service animals. And do you know another animal who sniffs out bombs? [Rats.](https://www.google.com/amp/s/relay.nationalgeographic.com/proxy/distribution/public/amp/2015/10/151006-giant-rats-landmines-cambodia-science-animals) . Secondly, it is about  #8220;babying #8221; that #8217;s what humans do. Especially to animals we decide to keep. Dogs aren #8217;t designed to be subordinate because of nature. They are designed that way because WE domesticated them. We trained them that way. WE bred them that way. That #8217;s why we have dogs like pugs, English bulldogs, and Saint Bernards (just a few examples) who we fucked up and bred them until we like what they look like. Now they have so many health issues it #8217;s insane. Thirdly,I never said dog meat was a staple food. I said it was a cheap, readily available meat in poor countries. It is true it is poor quality, and not very nutritional. But when you live in a poor country you eat poor food. And I guess a history dating back as far as 500bc is a pretty  #8220;recent niche #8221; diet. People have been doing this for thousands of years mate. It #8217;s not a secret. It #8217;s recorded history. Fourthly, Pigs. They make good pets and can be trained the same way as a dog. Many people argue that they are smarter. But damn are they tasty. Lastly, hey man, that #8217;s whatever you say. That #8217;s just what the government says on their reports. But I didn #8217;t realize you were the expert. Either way simply killing a dog so you don #8217;t have to take care of it seems a lot worse than eating it. At least it wasn #8217;t in vain.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 17:57:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boy, that sure is NSFW!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 18:00:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s because it #8217;s one user posting all this shit. He #8217;s getting banned though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 21:11:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m on the Xbox</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 21:14:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can only see his goggles as a mouth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 00:36:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The turtle is dead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 00:36:36</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;TheSystemStatic #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 00:41:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty good show Is the newest season pretty good?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 02:19:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>#NATURAL SELECTION</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 02:25:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It wasn #8217;t faked, the story simply was out of context. It wasn #8217;t cancelled because of her race it was canceled because she lied about how many people were with her. But the host did use racial slurs when they argued.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;m just some random dude on reddit. AMA.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 07:37:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 07:46:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>No but I got a loan and bought a house for pretty cheap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 07:46:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty generic stuff. But I do like r/suicidegirls. No anal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 07:47:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty generic. r/suicidegirls is nice. Not really into anal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 07:48:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>You gave enough of a shit to be a cunt about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 07:59:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uh. I #8217;m not really sure. I drowned when I was like 6. My grandpa is from Manila. I was a chef for a little bit. I have a ferret. That is a really tough question honestly. What about you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 08:03:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>He #8217;s surprisingly chill. It #8217;s like having a stretched out cat with the mind of a puppy. He is obviously a little musky, but if you bathe them once or twice a month it #8217;s fine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 08:03:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Autocorrect mate. My bad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 17:50:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Colby jack?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 17:50:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not really. I #8217;m too ADHD to sit there and wait.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 17:51:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ropes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 17:51:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I danced with my ex at prom. That #8217;s pretty much the same thing I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 18:03:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>How? I 100% sure this is a joke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 19:31:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Natural selection applies to all living things. I mean if the dog wasn #8217;t stupid enough to agro the hater then it #8217;d still be here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 19:51:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean it #8217;s kind of stupid to get mad at the owner because the dog wanted to fuck with a crocodile. I mean is he supposed to give the dog a stern talking to about the dangers of scaly predators? Is he supposed to tie it up? No he can #8217;t do that or else people will get angry that his dog doesn #8217;t have freedom. Nope. The dog is just dumb.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 20:09:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s the thing. I said it as a joke. Saying the dog is stupid. Weed out the weak. Natural selection. But yeah humans fucked up dogs and now we act like they are blessed creatures who are second only to man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 20:11:07</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;~~guys~~ Pussies. FTFY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 20:12:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>To hide the pre-existing stains</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 21:17:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wash your dick every so often mate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 21:18:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whoa I didn #8217;t even know he died.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 23:15:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your daddy issues aren #8217;t humorous.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 03:52:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish my dick as that long  #128546;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 17:59:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just play MONTAGNE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 18:05:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I hope I never see you on the road.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 21:45:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey I #8217;m working on it. I #8217;m just one cunt. And I can #8217;t be here 24/7 mate. These people get banned.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 21:58:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s the only good twitch png on google. Trust me When I made some stuff for her that #8217;s all there is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 22:10:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stop posting this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 22:20:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It doesn #8217;t belong here. It #8217;s not funny at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 22:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>To each their own.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 05:04:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>The full post is somewhere on this sub</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 17:21:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You didn #8217;t see boob if you didn #8217;t see nipple.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 20:09:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s a valedictorian speech, not a protest. There was a written out speech she got approval to say. Then she decided to go on a soapbox. This isn #8217;t rage, it #8217;s common sense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 02:16:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh it #8217;s you again... You could have at least made this photo believable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 02:19:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>She #8217;s just a person who spams these shitty posts all over reddit in hopes people will upvote the shit out of them. Even though this is an obvious edit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 02:20:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can literally see where the blur tool was used, the shadows are all off, and the skin tone is all fucked. Not only that but there is 0 reaction from the other two.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 02:21:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh she *told* you huh? Well I take it back then. My bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 02:26:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never said that the other pictures are photoshop. I said this **one** in particular is. It #8217;s apparent you have big tits. But this photo is extremely obvious that it was edited. I don #8217;t *follow* you around. You post your bullshit shitposts on my sub while you #8217;re spamming your posts around reddit. That #8217;s the kind of bullshit I can #8217;t stand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 02:30:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can literally go on all of your posts and look. I #8217;ve probably commented on like 3. This is the first time I #8217;ve ever mentioned photoshop. It #8217;s not that hard to prove that. So why even bullshit it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 02:32:52</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;BLOCK ME! It #8217;s super easy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 02:35:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It took me a minute to understand what he #8217;s trying to say.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 08:34:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 08:38:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. At first I thought he meant trying to talk to him meant he #8217;ll never talk to you again or something</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 08:39:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I need to find some rope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 09:06:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>She #8217;s 3 by the way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 09:34:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess it #8217;s only because I know them personally that I know it #8217;s fake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 09:36:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I do when it gets posted all over Facebook. Her newest post says she #8217;s going to exhume his body for a DNA test to see if she #8217;s even his kid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 09:53:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well it seems some people just like ruining the fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 16:40:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically like  #8220;coming at him #8221;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 17:18:23</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;If you try to come at me I #8217;ll kill you #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 18:08:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s where he got it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 18:19:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was my major in Harvard</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 18:19:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 18:31:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but this dudes like 19 or 20</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 18:36:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I #8217;m at least 238 by now you know</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Someone posted this to Facebook and I was concerned at first.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 18:40:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 18:54:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Yeah also no Twitter](https://www.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/8qiul9/singapore_summit_memes/?st=JIBX9BNZ amp;sh=8501050f)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>He fucking showed em</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 18:57:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 19:04:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>A couple of minutes probably. I mean that #8217;s about how long it takes for the lyric to be sung in the song.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 19:05:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is obviously a text post just like that one. A lot of post on here are cropped from social media.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 19:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>That doesn #8217;t mean I care. Look this subreddit is full of shitposts. So I just decided to add one more. If they want to delete it they can. If they want to delete the Twitter one they can. If they want to ban me they can. I #8217;m not even subscribed to this sub. If you want to be the reddit police then go ahead but it #8217;s really getting you no where.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 19:13:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I was just agreeing with you. Because you #8217;re the real MVP.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 19:13:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kind of literal huh?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 19:15:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then remove it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 19:16:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then shut the fuck up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 20:20:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>True</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 20:24:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can #8217;t tell if you #8217;re serious or just plain dumb.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 20:30:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was beautiful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 20:34:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 20:47:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dudes like 20</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 22:25:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s rap lyrics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 06:40:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Delete it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 20:17:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like she posted the wrong picture on accident, but that #8217;s just what I #8217;m hoping.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 17:44:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, not only is this a repost, but you also stole word for word the 2nd top comment on the last time it was posted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 17:45:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Um guys, I think I get first dibs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 18:59:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, eat shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 22:23:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s the only thing I can do to try to intimidate such an alpha male. I can only dream that my small shriveled dick could be as large as your massive throbbing cock. I understand now that my parents loved me too much, and I can never be as bad ass as you. Please, please, please teach me your ways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 23:33:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought it was kind of funny. Do you want to suggest one?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 02:12:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is static something people can #8217;t visibly see now?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 22:44:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/ihavesex?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 22:44:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 22:49:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got TK #8217;d because I used my master key when someone decided the wanted to use their breach charge. They walked right in front of me and got blasted. Then the whole match was just each person taking turns to kill me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 23:20:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have never got to touch a girls wiener.  #128546;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 23:27:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Traps are 25% gay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An old high school friend turns out to be a Pedo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 03:01:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 21:24:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks like there #8217;s another person for the island</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 22:57:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uh, seeing as this is an actual photo and not a painting I #8217;d say it doesn #8217;t belong there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 22:58:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s already pretty deep fried.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 18:18:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please never comment on my posts ever again. I can only take so much brain damage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 00:42:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I literally saw a post that was a picture of an actual woman and a guy cross posted there. I was dude how does that make sense. This is a literal real life woman. Nothing wrong with her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 06:01:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>My ex got a 12 on her act</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 06:20:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I knew a girl with hair to her knees. It was kind of unsettling in a way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 10:26:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well he didn #8217;t touch them, he was looking at kiddie porn. So please tell me how that #8217;s the wrong term.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 17:04:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is 100% the correct term. Regardless of the state of his mental condition, addiction or not. He was attracted to children. That is a pedophile. There is a strong line between being so addicted to porn that you can only get off to midget-clown-amputee porn. And going out of your way to get over 300 GB of Child porn. That #8217;s more than an addiction. That #8217;s something very sick and specific. So you can keep trying to rationalize and normalize what he did all you want. But you are wrong. This isn #8217;t a case of porn addiction gone sour. This is 100% case of a dude who is so fucked up he jacks off to 3 year olds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 17:10:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is that retard using his thumb to check his pulse?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 17:13:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well how about you stop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 17:13:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you explain the funny part here?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 17:16:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay let #8217;s tone it down Uncle Ted, you #8217;re starting to get creepy again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 19:50:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Um yes they definitely would. If the parents actually believe that they are giving their kids a  #8220;better life #8221; then they would definitely do that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 19:51:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>The kids didn #8217;t have to do anything wrong, those are circumstances brought apron them by the parents.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 19:55:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, so what #8217;s your point? I never once called him a child molester because he never actually touched them. I called him a pedo. Because that #8217;s what he is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 19:56:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>How are you correcting my terminology when I used the correct terminology? He #8217;s sexually attracted to kids so I called him a pedophile. That #8217;s what he is, a pedophile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 21:08:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last I checked possession/distribution of child pornography was a crime. A pretty big crime. How the fuck do you even come up with the idea  #8220;Pedophiles don #8217;t commit crimes #8221;? That #8217;s fucking ridiculous.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 21:10:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>A pedophile would 100% definitely possess child porn. That #8217;s kind of their thing. And good that you read the report, I knew the guy personally and my dad is one of the officers who worked the case. So please fill me in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 21:18:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I laugh a little every time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 01:00:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m pretty sure this I a joke, not a deep philosophical thought</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 01:02:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you tried r/comedycemetery or r/4panelcringe?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 01:04:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll just leave it be</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 01:11:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah that #8217;s kind of desperate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 02:33:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 05:08:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just like my uncle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 06:02:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>PicsArt is nice but there are ads</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 06:03:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes exactly like Samson</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 06:09:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know why my grandpa left.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 06:58:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>The ring my girlfriend absolutely wants is only $68 and I honestly feel like I #8217;d cheat her out of something. But it #8217;s the one she wants so that #8217;s the one I #8217;m going to get her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 17:53:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I must be lost, this is r/enoughinternet right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 17:58:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Again, where #8217;s the joke?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 23:36:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>He started a fight, then got his ass kicked, refused medical treatment, and went home. The guy that punched him was arrested. Where #8217;s the rage?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 23:56:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favorite part is watching the people defending the negligence of the mother when they obviously didn #8217;t even read the article.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 23:58:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I literally couldn #8217;t even read the article because of all the spam.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 00:06:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>*We can post this article and give it this headline. Then people will click on it and share it on social media sites. And people won #8217;t actually read it but it will make people mad and it will make us popular.* That #8217;s probably the gist of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 00:51:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d just walk in and leave the gate open.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 02:17:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s cool mate, I worked in a kitchen for years. I know your pain.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 02:29:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then buy some fucking socks. You can #8217;t be pissed about something that #8217;s your fault.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 02:35:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>If that were me growing up, all I #8217;d be allowed to eat the rest of the day would be peas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 03:58:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The link says the same thing I did. That #8217;s what is on the police reports. His sister can say whatever she wants but there needs to be proof to back it up. I read the same article you did which says: He got into a fight, got punched, refused medical attention, and went home. The guy who punched him was arrested. Where. Is. The. Rage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 04:24:07</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Shriver, 22, of Waconia, was walking with a group of friends around 2:40 a.m. Saturday in St. Cloud when witnesses said he got into an argument with Johnson, who was walking with a separate group of people. During the argument, Johnson allegedly punched Shriver in the face. They got into an argument and fought. When two people fight it #8217;s the responsibility of both parties. And I #8217;m no expert but if a dude punched you so fucking hard that you die, I #8217;m pretty sure you got your ass kicked. And the article only says he got punched in the face. Every punch you don #8217;t see coming is a sucker punch. That #8217;s literally the definition.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 04:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. Kind of like when mothers refuse to vaccinate their kids and then the kids die. The parents aren #8217;t arrested for murder.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 05:15:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course it #8217;s you again. Saying some dumb ass shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 06:32:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>True</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 06:49:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 18:24:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>An argument is the same as a fight. It #8217;s too people who disagree trying to get their point across. And I dont know about you, but I don #8217;t punch people because they disagree on where to eat lunch. I have no doubt the kid probably said something he shouldn #8217;t have. And if you die, then you lost the fight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 18:44:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>As I said. I don #8217;t punch people in the face because they don #8217;t like the same music as me. I have no doubt the kid probably said some shit he shouldn #8217;t have. And got clocked for it. A single punch that kills you means you got your ass kicked. Now I dont know about you but if he died from a single punch that motherfucker must have hit him like a train. Then he definitely should have gotten medical attention. If not by himself then his friends should have insisted. I #8217;m not defending the dude who punched him. **You know, the one going to jail for murder.** but it #8217;s more the fault of the other kid or his friends that he didn #8217;t seek medical attention and died from something that was very easily preventable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 18:54:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I honestly don #8217;t give a fuck about the  #8220;Thin skull rule #8221; or the  #8220;Fragile skull rule #8221; or whichever one you just googled. All I #8217;m saying is the motherfucker went to jail for murder. He #8217;s being charged for the crime. So once again, where #8217;s the rage?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 19:02:45</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;He killed a guy over a verbal beef. He punched a guy one time. I highly doubt he was going for the kill shot there. A single punch isn #8217;t a sign of  #8220;*This motherfucker is dying tonight.* #8221; I don #8217;t know about you but logic is telling me that kid some something in that verbal argument that got him punched in the face. And punch He couldn #8217;t fucking take. Like my grandma always says,  #8220;Talk shit. Get hit. #8221; The guy that hit him is going to jail. *justice is served* The kid died because he refused medical attention that could have easily saved him. *Thats on him* So I #8217;ll ask you one last time. Where is the rage here?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 19:17:53</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;he needs to go to jail for 5-10 years. **HE IS GOING TO JAIL!** as I #8217;ve said 3 fucking times. He literally turned himself in. Did you not read the article *you* linked to me? My rage is from idiots like you getting angry over something where justice has been served. You are acting like this dude is in the wind. HE IS IN JAIL. And you originally posted  #8220;Fragile skull rule #8221; before you changed it. So say whatever you want about that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 19:36:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s what I #8217;ve asked myself for the last two days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 19:44:48</DATE>
    <TEXT> lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 19:48:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can only get in fight over the internet because of my insecurities and small penis. So you should be good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 20:02:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve helped my girlfriend get dressed before</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 20:46:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. That #8217;s part of the definition of fight. 2. He didn #8217;t make a comeback mate. He got punched, went home, and died. He lost the fight. If you want to get technical they both lost since one is dead and the other is in jail. But it #8217;s whatever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 23:53:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>There isn #8217;t a generalization. If you get into a fight and you die because of that fight then you lost. Whether or not you beat/killed the opponent. You still died and that doesn #8217;t seem like a winner to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 01:58:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure why not</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>That face you make when Blitz and Ying both flash you at the same time.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 02:14:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Few Points for Newbies.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 02:38:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Disclaimer: most of these are from my personal experience of playing for 2 years now.** 1. If you want Doc to heal you then stand still for five seconds. Don #8217;t move around and t-bag like your pants are on fire. He only has 3 Stims and he doesn #8217;t want to waste them. 2. If there is Rook on your team then take the plates. If you *are* Rook then put them down ASAP. 3. Your drone is your friend. When in doubt, drone out. 4. Never use a Thermite or Hibana charge on an unreinforced wall/door. 5. Don #8217;t pick an operator solely for the load out. Each operator has a specific job to do and your taking that away from them. 6. Don #8217;t waste a Nitro cell on a wall. People have impacts for a reason. Nitros are made for killing. 7. Don #8217;t waste Lion or Finkas abilities as soon as you spawn. It #8217;s pointless. 8. Don #8217;t TK over someone #8217;s operator choice. Learn to play other operators. Try to learn them all. 9. Don #8217;t put a Battery next to a Jammer. Please. Mute can cover two walls and bandit can cover singles. Plan that out. 10. Twitch drones have 10 shots. Don #8217;t waste them all on enemies. 11. Just because you *can* play an operator a different way doesn #8217;t always mean you *should*. 12. Playing the objective is actually a viable strategy. This game isn #8217;t solely a team death match. Don #8217;t get kill hungry. 13. This is only a game. Don #8217;t get too worked up about it. Just have fun. Please feel free to add more. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 02:42:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>The window leading to the ledge that meets main bedroom. You can jump out of main bedroom and got to kids bedroom through both windows.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 03:04:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lasers can also help if you #8217;re into rushes. Operators such as Ash or IQ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 03:07:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I literally played a match last night where everyone reinforced kids bedroom. I sat there as Rook and just stared at my feet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 04:34:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, but get this, there are two drones!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 04:35:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I loved that too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 04:35:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s hard, but it #8217;s definitely do-able</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 04:36:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! I can #8217;t tell you how many times I #8217;ve watched the last guy alive drone for the last 15 seconds and then try to run into OBJ with 3 seconds on the clock.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 04:37:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. Don #8217;t just spam the operator abilities just because you can. This is supposed to be a strategy game guys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 06:49:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Especially if they walk through an empty bomb room with the diffuser looking for the defender.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 06:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>4  amp; 6: if not a single person on your team has a breach charge or Ash/Buck/Sledge. Or if not a single defender has impacts then you guys are playing with the wrong load outs. 5. I #8217;m saying don #8217;t pick an operator because they have cool weapons. Pick them because they #8217;re abilities will benefit the team. 7. Lions ability only affects moving enemies. So spawn leakers probably aren #8217;t going to be effective. And you #8217;ll be too far away to do anything even if you do see someone. Your abilities are useful during combat not **as soon as you spawn**. 13. Yeah winning is pretty fun. But TK #8217;ing because you didn #8217;t get to play as Finka isn #8217;t.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 06:58:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>The most important.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 07:41:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>The whole kicking someone because they #8217;re not rushing the objective always gets me. I can never understand why people wants someone to rush into a 1 V 5 when there is still 2:00 left.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 19:09:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you think his balls ever get caught under him?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 19:25:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I probably should have added that I can see the defender on the drones. And I know they can plant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 19:30:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, people being kill hungry in this game makes me cringe. This isn #8217;t Call of Duty. This is supposed to be a ~~tactical strategy game based around planning and teamwork.~~ FREE FOR ALL.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 19:33:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where the fuck did you hear that bullshit?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 21:18:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man I wish I #8217;d finished middle school.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 21:20:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>The multiple camera angles along the with the sheer quality of the cameras themselves. It #8217;s a TV show. Edit: I can #8217;t spell worth shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 21:52:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here #8217;s what gets me. I #8217;m a Monty main (dont shit on me) and one of two things usually happen. 1. The enemy team acts like I don #8217;t even exist and I can easily kill 2 or 3 before they decide that I #8217;m worth their time. 2. The entire enemy team is trying to kill me while I #8217;m standing in a corner. Meanwhile my teammates are nowhere to be seen even though they could get all the free kills from enemies tunneling me. Like the other day I was playing in Oregon and the OBJ was in the basement. I went down the front stairs and stood in the corner. It was a 2V3. Literally all three of them where trying to kill me while I could see my teammate upstairs just looking around. If he were to just walk down the stairs he would have gotten 3 easy kills and we would have won. But instead 2 started bashing my shield while the last guy shot around it. Then they all ran upstairs and destroyed the last teammate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 05:23:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are absolutely right. I am utterly wrong. Please teach me how to have the biggest cock in the world. Please.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 05:24:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>My bad. I #8217;m on mobile and I just pressed the first option that showed up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 05:25:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>They #8217;re both scripted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>r/NSFWShitposts</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 05:34:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 05:35:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/NSFWShitposts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 23:53:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I guess I #8217;ll just be over here then. Crying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 03:15:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/nsfw_wtf?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 03:18:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/NSFWShitposts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 03:20:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well then.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 04:31:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m trying here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 04:32:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/NSFWShitposts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 07:17:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/NSFWShitposts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 07:21:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn Micheal Jackson is looking good these days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 07:30:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>My coworkers show my boss porn all the time. So I dont know if I can say anything about NSFW.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 07:44:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I honestly don #8217;t trust it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 07:52:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fucks out in the middle of an open public parking lot. Quick I #8217;ll hide my face from the camera.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 08:51:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/NSFWShitposts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 18:29:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only thing I like about this is the fact that #8217;s it #8217;s a corn dog.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 18:31:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m honestly surprised that it #8217;s not being flooded with posts. But I guess it #8217;s not popular enough yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 18:51:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>This sub gets at least 10 shitposts a day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 21:37:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reasons I unsubbed from r/rainbow6 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8tiqzi/banana_on_elas_icon/?st=JIT82FG4 amp;sh=55d3f2d3 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8tcjdt/dokkaebi_has_gone_too_far/?st=JIT84YCO amp;sh=d586167a https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8tiypj/sleepy_echo/?st=JIT85IR4 amp;sh=490d3b2c https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8thr5g/operation_para_bellum_soeeddraw/?st=JIT864MP amp;sh=31525f31 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8tcahm/after_months_of_saving_up_and_some_help_from_my/?st=JIT86IR2 amp;sh=f67f1dc6 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8tgohq/i_think_not_p/?st=JIT86TPU amp;sh=9938b469 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8sif4w/all_rainbow_six_siege_operators_together_in_one/?st=JIT8813A amp;sh=2baf948a https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8ssw1u/valk_doesnt_take_her_job_very_seriously/?st=JIT88CJE amp;sh=1df8869b https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8rugq9/praise_him_indeed/?st=JIT88O40 amp;sh=60ea9bc5 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8sbwt9/i_am_scared/?st=JIT88ZZO amp;sh=6de9429c https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8t8jio/operators_hand_signal/?st=JIT89TDG amp;sh=c4dcf10d https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8ruu52/my_friend_went_as_lord_tachanka_to_denver_comic/?st=JIT8A7D8 amp;sh=6c4c598b https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8tal6h/if_capitao_had_a_beard/?st=JIT8AX4X amp;sh=bd3f94ab https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8sd4um/when_the_thatcher_gets_spawnpeaked/?st=JIT8CERE amp;sh=39e93799 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8szjxv/happy_birthday_to_that_thatcher_57_years_old_now/?st=JIT8FO0T amp;sh=3241e770 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8t9vca/when_the_person_who_didnt_pick_up_their_armor/?st=JIT8GEWI amp;sh=61cf8fa8</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just unsubbed from r/rainbow6.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 21:45:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I originally joined because the sub was full of discussions, tips, and tactics for Siege. Now it #8217;s a shit fest where the mods are completely trash. They take down so much content that makes no sense. And all it is now is shitty comics, cosplay, and random shit that makes no sense. These are all taken from this months top posts. https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8tiqzi/banana_on_elas_icon/?st=JIT82FG4 amp;sh=55d3f2d3 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8tcjdt/dokkaebi_has_gone_too_far/?st=JIT84YCO amp;sh=d586167a https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8tiypj/sleepy_echo/?st=JIT85IR4 amp;sh=490d3b2c https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8thr5g/operation_para_bellum_soeeddraw/?st=JIT864MP amp;sh=31525f31 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8tcahm/after_months_of_saving_up_and_some_help_from_my/?st=JIT86IR2 amp;sh=f67f1dc6 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8tgohq/i_think_not_p/?st=JIT86TPU amp;sh=9938b469 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8sif4w/all_rainbow_six_siege_operators_together_in_one/?st=JIT8813A amp;sh=2baf948a https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8ssw1u/valk_doesnt_take_her_job_very_seriously/?st=JIT88CJE amp;sh=1df8869b https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8rugq9/praise_him_indeed/?st=JIT88O40 amp;sh=60ea9bc5 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8sbwt9/i_am_scared/?st=JIT88ZZO amp;sh=6de9429c https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8t8jio/operators_hand_signal/?st=JIT89TDG amp;sh=c4dcf10d https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8ruu52/my_friend_went_as_lord_tachanka_to_denver_comic/?st=JIT8A7D8 amp;sh=6c4c598b https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8tal6h/if_capitao_had_a_beard/?st=JIT8AX4X amp;sh=bd3f94ab https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8sd4um/when_the_thatcher_gets_spawnpeaked/?st=JIT8CERE amp;sh=39e93799 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8szjxv/happy_birthday_to_that_thatcher_57_years_old_now/?st=JIT8FO0T amp;sh=3241e770 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8t9vca/when_the_person_who_didnt_pick_up_their_armor/?st=JIT8GEWI amp;sh=61cf8fa8</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 22:00:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reasons I unsubbed from r/rainbow6 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8tiqzi/banana_on_elas_icon/?st=JIT82FG4 amp;sh=55d3f2d3 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8tcjdt/dokkaebi_has_gone_too_far/?st=JIT84YCO amp;sh=d586167a https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8tiypj/sleepy_echo/?st=JIT85IR4 amp;sh=490d3b2c https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8thr5g/operation_para_bellum_soeeddraw/?st=JIT864MP amp;sh=31525f31 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8tcahm/after_months_of_saving_up_and_some_help_from_my/?st=JIT86IR2 amp;sh=f67f1dc6 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8tgohq/i_think_not_p/?st=JIT86TPU amp;sh=9938b469 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8sif4w/all_rainbow_six_siege_operators_together_in_one/?st=JIT8813A amp;sh=2baf948a https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8ssw1u/valk_doesnt_take_her_job_very_seriously/?st=JIT88CJE amp;sh=1df8869b https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8rugq9/praise_him_indeed/?st=JIT88O40 amp;sh=60ea9bc5 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8sbwt9/i_am_scared/?st=JIT88ZZO amp;sh=6de9429c https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8t8jio/operators_hand_signal/?st=JIT89TDG amp;sh=c4dcf10d https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8ruu52/my_friend_went_as_lord_tachanka_to_denver_comic/?st=JIT8A7D8 amp;sh=6c4c598b https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8tal6h/if_capitao_had_a_beard/?st=JIT8AX4X amp;sh=bd3f94ab https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8sd4um/when_the_thatcher_gets_spawnpeaked/?st=JIT8CERE amp;sh=39e93799 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8szjxv/happy_birthday_to_that_thatcher_57_years_old_now/?st=JIT8FO0T amp;sh=3241e770 https://www.reddit.com/r/Rainbow6/comments/8t9vca/when_the_person_who_didnt_pick_up_their_armor/?st=JIT8GEWI amp;sh=61cf8fa8</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 03:16:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah that the one I #8217;m subbed to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 04:28:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>It says something about drinking milk. For a second I thought hot sauce. But I have no idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 08:49:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/NSFWShitposts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 08:50:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/NSFWShitposts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 08:50:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 08:51:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I #8217;m banning her this time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 23:22:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/NSFWShitposts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 00:28:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>What if you #8217;re already going 10 over but some asshole has to be somewhere 10 seconds faster.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 00:35:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m in the fast lane.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 01:08:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe, but at least I can read.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 01:12:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 02:22:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay I lied. What does it say?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 03:15:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>As someone who has depression I want to die.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 03:46:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok but no one is stealing the contents, they want the whole cooler.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 05:04:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck are you on about mate?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 05:07:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is literally one of the dumbest rage posts I #8217;ve seen on this sub. He was buying alcohol with his wife. They got ID #8217;d. That #8217;s common sense. Where in the fuck does him being black have anything to do with anything? Oh wait. He saw police while he was a black man, with tattoos, and was a rapper. He was scared. Like honestly what the hell is going on here?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 05:53:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>What if I #8217;m a cop?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 05:54:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I didn #8217;t smile at all.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 06:51:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 09:20:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>But they are. African American is a term used for[ an American of African decent.](https://www.merriam-webster.com/dictionary/African%20American) Just like European American, Asian American, or (wait for it) Native American. It is common sense. It doesn #8217;t refer to where they are from or where they were born. It refers to where their ancestors were originally from. You know, like Africa. African American.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 09:47:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>But they #8217;re white</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 10:05:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whoa that #8217;s insane</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:10:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now that #8217;s different</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:14:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/NSFWShitposts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:15:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>What?! This is fake?! No, that makes no sense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:17:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. I was hoping this could help some people get their urge to shit post on r/NSFWFunny out of their system. Apparently it #8217;s not working yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:25:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>WHAT THE FUCK DID YOU SAY ABOUT IRAN?!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:26:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Asians</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:27:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>ILL HAVE YOU KNOW THAT PERSONAL DONT KNOW SHIT ABOUT IRAN!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:28:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you sure? I could have swore you said Iran.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:33:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>This account literally spams the same two pictures all over reddit. I banned them from my sub for posting this same picture 5 times after I removed them each time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:45:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think they should get off this sub.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:51:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>[How many accounts are you going to post this with?](https://www.reddit.com/r/nsfwhardcore/comments/8u0mav/what_do_you_think_of_my_titties/?st=JIVXGKZ3 amp;sh=ca45ec58)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:52:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t think so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 19:09:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know me being a medical practitioner who specializes in vaginal stimulation, I would never lie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>He posts this stuff seriously on a regular basis</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 19:37:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 19:43:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last I checked he worked in a cooled meat department of a grocery store.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 23:17:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>You guys are really taking this comment way too seriously.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 00:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, this is definitely not safe for work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 02:10:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why the fuck can #8217;t she type  #8220;rooms #8221;?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 02:12:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I #8217;ll admit it #8217;s a little uncomfortable but it is realistic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 06:38:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe you spelled it wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 19:23:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I mean...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 20:13:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/NSFWShitposts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 20:13:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/NSFWShitposts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 20:14:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck mate?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 20:22:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a spam bot mate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When your new shipment of toothpicks came in.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 01:32:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 04:53:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s what I came here to say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 07:13:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>You guys are really starting to disappoint me here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 20:04:28</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Hmm fay da ting wid da hy #8221; Made me cry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 20:21:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah let #8217;s not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 23:12:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah it wasn #8217;t that funny</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 02:22:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are extremely biased in which posts get to stay and which don #8217;t. If someone popular posts something that obviously breaks the rules it stays. Then they #8217;ll make up any excuse to remove other posts. The rules are so vague that they can make it up on the spot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 05:24:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes but how? Edit: These comments are fucking killing me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 05:46:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>With that trajectory it #8217;s obvious it was a cannon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 07:17:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>The fact that kids masturbate. People do realize kids masturbate right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 07:26:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not saying  #8220;oh fuck yeah, let #8217;s watch kids masturbate. #8221; I #8217;m just saying this is a movie depicting a young girl #8217;s life and that is a part of a young girls life. I wouldn #8217;t personally add it into a movie myself. Seems pretty unethical but obviously the director thought it was an important plot point. Did you watch the movie? Because it never shows anything except her face. Not necessarily child porn. Close but not child *pornography*. It #8217;s like L #233;on: The Professional. It #8217;s very uncomfortable and unnerving but it #8217;s a key part of the plot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 07:54:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>My point is it #8217;s a movie. Shits fake. All that is shown is a kids face. What #8217;s the big deal?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 08:20:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>God, I forgot to carry the 2. That #8217;s why my math was off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 13:51:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did that because I find the comments funny. I #8217;m sorry if I offended you by sharing that tidbit of information.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 13:55:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shit mate. Who the fuck touched you as a kid? My god that is a lot of pent up aggression.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 14:08:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok judging by your comment history I can only assume either 1. This is you alternate account for you to troll with. 2. This is you alternate account you use when you just want to be a cunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 14:12:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>What #8217;s wrong with this guy wanting to make rope swings for journalists. Sounds like a fun time. I used to have one as a kid and I swung on it all the time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 19:58:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh wow you googled the definition. I #8217;m going to say this again. It is a movie. It is fake. All that is shown is a face. The movie is under investigation. If they determine that it is illegal then that #8217;s them. It #8217;s whatever, I don #8217;t care. To me it #8217;s just a really uncomfortable scene.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 20:02:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>*too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 20:14:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean... You #8217;re not wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 22:07:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like I said. It whatever the courts decide. I really don #8217;t care.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 19:22:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>This makes me so uncomfortable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 19:31:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>If this doesn #8217;t get removed I will be thoroughly pissed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 00:28:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>You tried and that #8217;s all that matters</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 00:34:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>The spoiler isn #8217;t set up correctly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 00:36:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s what I said</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:06:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:14:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This account is someone who is photoshopping pictures and pretending to be someone else. They need to be banned.](https://www.instagram.com/angelikittyy/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:15:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This account is someone who is photoshopping pictures and pretending to be someone else. They need to be banned.](https://www.instagram.com/angelikittyy/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:15:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This account is someone who is photoshopping pictures and pretending to be someone else. They need to be banned.](https://www.instagram.com/angelikittyy/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:15:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This account is someone who is photoshopping pictures and pretending to be someone else. They need to be banned.](https://www.instagram.com/angelikittyy/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:16:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This account is someone who is photoshopping pictures and pretending to be someone else. They need to be banned.](https://www.instagram.com/angelikittyy/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:16:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This account is someone who is photoshopping pictures and pretending to be someone else. They need to be banned.](https://www.instagram.com/angelikittyy/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:16:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This account is someone who is photoshopping pictures and pretending to be someone else. They need to be banned.](https://www.instagram.com/angelikittyy/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:16:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This account is someone who is photoshopping pictures and pretending to be someone else. They need to be banned.](https://www.instagram.com/angelikittyy/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:16:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This account is someone who is photoshopping pictures and pretending to be someone else. They need to be banned.](https://www.instagram.com/angelikittyy/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:17:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This account is someone who is photoshopping pictures and pretending to be someone else. They need to be banned.](https://www.instagram.com/angelikittyy/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:17:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This account is someone who is photoshopping pictures and pretending to be someone else. They need to be banned.](https://www.instagram.com/angelikittyy/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:17:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This account is someone who is photoshopping pictures and pretending to be someone else. They need to be banned.](https://www.instagram.com/angelikittyy/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:17:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This account is someone who is photoshopping pictures and pretending to be someone else. They need to be banned.](https://www.instagram.com/angelikittyy/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:17:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This account is someone who is photoshopping pictures and pretending to be someone else. They need to be banned.](https://www.instagram.com/angelikittyy/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:17:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This account is someone who is photoshopping pictures and pretending to be someone else. They need to be banned.](https://www.instagram.com/angelikittyy/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:19:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This account is someone who is photoshopping pictures and pretending to be someone else. They need to be banned.](https://www.instagram.com/angelikittyy/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:19:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This account is someone who is photoshopping pictures and pretending to be someone else. They need to be banned.](https://www.instagram.com/angelikittyy/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:20:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This account is someone who is photoshopping pictures and pretending to be someone else. They need to be banned.](https://www.instagram.com/angelikittyy/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 23:42:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is not her. These are images stolen from u/KittanLuvr and they are photoshopped. Report this poster to the admins.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 23:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for your assistance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 23:48:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>These pictures are stolen from u/KittanLuvr and are photoshopped. Please report this poster to the admins.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 08:08:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s just my go-to font. I like the old typewriter feel of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 06:37:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I watched that episode just the other day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 22:28:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m sorry u/ThisIs_MyName but I have to disagree here. You #8217;re math is all wrong. Based on a recent study in trapology we have concluded that traps are approximately 12.5% - 25% gay. While it is closer to 24.7% we round it up for mathematics sake. Here is a quote from the head researcher in charge of the study:  #8220;Fapping to trap porn is the least gay thing there is. If you fap to gay porn, that's 2 guys, and that's 100% gay. If you fap to 'straight' porn, then that has a woman, sure, but you're also fapping to a guy, which makes it 50% gay. But a trap is like half male, half female, and thus a trap with a girl would add up to 75% girl, and thus only 25% gay. 2 women would be ideal, but that would be a lesbian relationship, which brings it around to gay again. If you fap to furry porn, then it's in a weird gray area, where if it's people in fursuits, the same rules apply, but if it's with animals, I would think it depends on said animal's sexuality. Then there's consent. If a person doesn't consent to something, but the other person does it anyway, that makes the other person stronger, and thus less gay. Let's say that means they're about 50% less gay. If it was gay -blam!-, that means that it's now 75% gay. If it's straight -blam!- by a man, then it's 25% gay. And, if it's trap gay porn, than that's 12.5% gay. So technically, yes, -blam!- trap porn is the least gay porn there is, but that's still looped in with trap porn, hence why fapping to trap porn is the least gay thing there is. #8221; [Source.](https://www.bungie.net/en/Forums/Post/233537348?sort=0 amp;page=0)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 01:42:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are we seriously going to start this up again?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 04:03:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get charged $3 a month for my account. Well due to some mishaps with the computer work I got charged 3 times for the same thing and it left me with like $2.37. The bank then decided to take my $3 out that very night. I then got charged $30 for the overdraft fee. I was a little upset. I did get my $300 back but I still had to pay the fee.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 04:28:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>What? Did someone say something?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 04:52:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. They #8217;re not that bright where I live.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 04:58:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gross COD.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 05:01:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 05:02:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>F</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 05:14:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>You obviously didn #8217;t carry the 2.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 05:46:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m honestly way more curious than I am disturbed. I really just want to know what the hell that is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 05:46:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>God it needs more JPEG</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 05:52:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m like 98% sure this is CGI. The lighting and stuff is way out of wack.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 06:05:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is pretty interesting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 11:02:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you were a lemon I #8217;d put you on my shelf and cherish you like I do all our lemons.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 20:04:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>You repost this after 1 day?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 20:05:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>And repost it twice?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 22:25:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>This makes this sub kind of boring if you only allow the same 5 generic posts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 22:26:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does this post break the rules?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 22:27:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess this breaks the rules too then huh? Why is this the rule here?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 22:29:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Gwen Stacy comment is what got me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 02:42:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just have been going the easy route and equipping the laser.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 02:43:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Obviously he #8217;s mentally handicapped</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 03:48:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>This rule is shit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 08:15:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let #8217;s calm down there bucko</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 19:48:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>It wasn #8217;t her entire body. It was her tits. The things she was showing off anyway. So yeah. I #8217;m fine with that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 19:54:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe you should change the rules so that you actually allow good posts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Please don #8217;t be a repost.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 20:10:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 20:11:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Speak of the devil.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 20:15:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>If they are acting like a cunt then that #8217;s their fault. I don #8217;t have to like it but it #8217;s not jail worthy. You #8217;re acting like the guy fucking ran down there and ripped her clothes off. He hit her with an air cannon. She made the mistake of not wearing a bra.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 01:19:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks I was just about to do that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 04:13:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey this post contains CGI!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 04:19:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s my boy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 04:29:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is why I sometimes think of quitting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 06:10:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s why we always make a big cake and a tiny cake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 06:27:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>My ferret likes to pull my leg hair.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 06:52:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 07:31:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you that insecure about someone else #8217;s beliefs that you can #8217;t respect the great lesson this man is teaching?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 19:01:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. You see this post? This post right here. If I see this post one more fucking time, a motherfucker is getting banned. That #8217;s it. I #8217;ve deleted it 6 fucking times already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 01:54:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>So basically she just hates men?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 03:51:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>What platform are you on? I #8217;m a Monty main. Maybe we can practice in a custom game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 03:57:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sweet, so am I.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 04:36:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>All in all it really depends on your play style. Whether you are aggressive or support. I am a support player. I don #8217;t always have to be MVP and I don #8217;t have to get 12 kills each match. As long as I can successfully assist my teammates in a victory I #8217;m satisfied. I used to main Valk because her cameras allowed me to give my team more information about the enemy. I could also help hold off enemy advances by placing myself around them and being able to pop shots off at them. So if you are more of an aggressive player I #8217;d say Valk. Maestro is my new favorite defender. He allows me to gather info while also messing with the enemies. I can destroy breach charges, clusters, and drones. I can also distract enemies by zapping them while my team moves closer for the kill. And if an enemy gets too close I can pop up from behind my shield and unload 31 shot gun rounds into anyone and anything in my area. Not only that but it #8217;s fun to zap people when they #8217;re not looking. So if you are more support I #8217;d pick Maestro.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 05:22:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>u/ThisIs_MyName I don #8217;t want to be a downer here but this isn #8217;t really getting too many upvotes after 4K views and there are a few good reports.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 06:47:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>To each their own</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 06:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t post this again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 07:05:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Especially if they have been watching the evil eye for a minute straight waiting for it to open. Then as soon as they turn around they get zapped.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 21:23:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shittiest of bots</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 21:28:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depending on the intelligence of the enemy team. I #8217;ve had my fair share of 1v5 #8217;s as a Monty main where the enemy seems dumber than a sack of potatoes and I just run the clock out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 22:25:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. That helps too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 22:10:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are downvoting because the mods have a shitty rule for a sub that is 80% content that is breaking the rule.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 19:48:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s because the mods are shit here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 20:38:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>If that #8217;s what you #8217;re into</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 06:54:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was community service</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 07:00:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don #8217;t know what hospice care is do you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 07:53:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>How the tables have turned</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 08:03:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay this whole thread is a train wreck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 06:56:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d do it just for the fun of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 20:01:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>What pun?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 20:02:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 20:03:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I watched the video</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 20:04:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 20:23:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>She doesn #8217;t look like she #8217;s having much fun</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 20:25:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another spammer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 22:46:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because they are dying out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 09:18:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>The worst is when you are clearly shooting at an enemy but all your teammates decide it #8217;s time to rush said enemy. So then you end up suspended for TKing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 20:07:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>The airlines dont control the weather conditions. So how is it their fault they had to stay grounded?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 20:14:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is one of the dumbest rage posts I #8217;ve ever seen on this sub.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 20:20:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Be careful who you elect?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 20:46:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who was physically stopping them from getting up and getting off? We #8217;re there 30 guys with guns keeping them there?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 21:20:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay I #8217;m that case. Are they supposed to evacuate the whole plane? Then when they get the go ahead do they have to wait to fill it back up again? This to me seems like standard procedure. The idea is to wait until it #8217;s safe to go that way you don #8217;t waste time getting everyone in and out. Because by that time it might not even be okay to leave anymore. This seems more like a case of impatience and people with certain medical conditions being in the wrong place at the wrong time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 21:23:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read the link you posted and it literally says they don #8217;t have to do anything until after 3-4 hours.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 21:24:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there any other source besides this video? Because I find people whining on the internet are usually hyperbolic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Xbox] Any new players in need of practice?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 22:35:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a lot of experience in siege. I have been playing since February 2016. I love playing the game and I know how fun it can be. But I also know how hard it can be to learn when you first start playing. I am a casual type player so I love to play for fun. I try not to be too sweaty or try hard while playing. That being said I #8217;d be happy to help lower level players level up and learn some of the basics and tips of the game. My schedule is normally: Mon-Fri 10:00-1:00 Central And usually Free Saturdays and Sunday most of the day. I #8217;m night shift so I #8217;m prone to being up late. Feel free to add me: TheSystemStatic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 02:27:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can #8217;t treat this game as if you #8217;re auditioning for the next Esports tournament. You have to remember the main purpose of any game is entertainment. If you #8217;re not having fun then why play? There is absolutely nothing wrong with playing to win. There #8217;s nothing wrong with trying to get MVP or get the most kills. I mean who doesn #8217;t try to do their best? But you can #8217;t treat it like you can put it on your resume. The easiest thing is to remember there are people who get sweaty and salty. They treat this game like a religion. That is just them though. If they want to message you or yell at you. The best thing to do is to just mute them and play on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 02:31:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only reason I have my mains is because I pretty much only play the objective. I #8217;m mainly an anchor(Maestro) and  #8220;support(Monty) #8221;. I get her info and I take care of contesters. I know that I #8217;m not that great when it comes to straight up gun play but my friends are great at it. I #8217;m perfectly fine with a few kills and a ton of assists as long as we win.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 02:52:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like I said I #8217;m not a hardcore player. I play for fun. So I have no problem playing with newbies if it can help them improve. I just hate seeing people get this game, they play a little, think it #8217;s too hard to understand, and then quit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 06:10:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will you be on in a few hours?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 01:06:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I play mainly objective. I #8217;m not top notch when it comes to gun play so I play anchor. To me personally I like using the cameras to be able to see enemies outside the objective. Or in high tragic areas. This gives me the ability to make an effective strategy to counter, or at least give a viable callout. Now if you were a more aggressive player and you plan on roaming or going mainly for kills I #8217;d choose the other gadget.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 01:07:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s pretty much the same concept of the last post. So I #8217;m considering it as a repost.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 02:31:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>No they are going to be treated as reposts. I #8217;d rather not have the sub filled with women pretending to have sex with fans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 02:33:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh shut the fuck up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 02:36:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess you still don #8217;t understand the concept of what a moderator does. The reason you can #8217;t find the recent posts is because, like yours right here, they have been removed. Mate I #8217;ve worked with you. I let you have the Codi Vore post back and I let you post the porn logic post that has appeared on this sub for the dawn of time. So please give me a little leeway here. And don #8217;t be a cunt about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 02:41:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s a different person doing the same exact bit. It #8217;s not that it #8217;s not new content. It #8217;s just not *original* content. I like your posts, and you seem to get a lot of votes for them, but just make it a little more reasonable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 02:55:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 03:47:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Isn #8217;t that the porn star?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 03:50:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kovu?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 09:51:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I only say that because that #8217;s what she said</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 21:08:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably a scam</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 21:08:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is this a gif?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 21:10:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>100%</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 21:12:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>He #8217;s literally just asking for a favor. Then he #8217;s making sure people know he #8217;s dirty before they come get him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 22:19:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you married to it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 22:19:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/woooosh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 22:23:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>#lik</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 22:32:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>What if you #8217;re a fate-ist?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 22:34:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 22:39:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you are an active part of your child #8217;s life I #8217;d agree. But more often then not if you pay child support then you probably skipped out on something very important. My son #8217;s biological father pays child support. Do you know why? Because it took him over a year to even claim he was his. Instead he wanted to refute it and call my girlfriend a whore all because she left his abusive relationship. It took him showing up to the dna test a 14 months later for him to ever even see him for the first time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 22:45:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn it I came here to say that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 22:56:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate when people say  #8220;the n-word. #8221; Man up and take responsibility. Just say it contextually. I mean if you #8217;re quoting someone and they say  #8220;nigger #8221; will you not say the quote word for word? Do we really need to censor it if it #8217;s within the context of someone saying it? Is that wrong?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:06:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey that #8217;s Tim Cruise</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:30:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>At the risk of sounding racist; just white people look alike?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:39:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also you have to account for the slight refraction, especially over water.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:41:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idiots tend to converge in on each other.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:49:57</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;  #8220;I put his name on the ticket for good luck because he #8217;s like a son to me  #8211; he was, #8221; Reddick said *Immediately threatens to take his winnings*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:51:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>#STOP FEEDING HIM</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:53:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s all the prof I need that I want to not be alive anymore</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:55:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can #8217;t see it, is there a mirror link?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:56:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck is going on in this thread?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:57:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair enough. I #8217;ll find a womb</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:58:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Quick batdick me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 00:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 00:40:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow would you look at that photoshop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 04:55:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The big giveaway is his legs. Their position makes no sense. The other giveaway is that the man and and body have slightly different photo quality. Then if you look at the head of the penis the outline is dark like they didn #8217;t cut it out close enough to his skin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 04:59:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are a ton of people who do. I just have automoderator remove comment from people with negative karma.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 05:11:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well my pants just got a little tighter</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Choppy Video?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 05:44:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>It seems that all last week and currently I #8217;ve had weird issues with choppy video. Everyone #8217;s ping will be between 30-80 but it seems to lag still. My ping will be 30-40 and my FPS *says* 60 but it #8217;s acting like it #8217;s 20FPS. Is anyone else having this problem?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 02:17:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s what I thought. I sound like a chainsaw when I sleep. I #8217;d definitely get found out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 02:28:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope to god you aren #8217;t really this dense</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 02:33:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck are you on about mate?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 19:05:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Obviously you do not</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 23:30:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>You do realize  #8220;canon #8221; means it #8217;s directly in the work? Like it #8217;s not a fan fiction. This is something that #8217;s part of the movie written by the directors.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 02:21:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s not a pun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 18:41:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that supposed to say something in Spanish?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 18:59:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>What am I, a fucking cat?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 21:42:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>S #237;, pero  #191;c #243;mo se supone que debes obtener "qiuero" de keto?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 23:20:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>s #237;, pero eso es algo est #250;pido</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 05:53:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck are you on about mate?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 05:56:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay? His career and organization are faith based. What does this have to do with anything? He still teaches a great message to a child who needed to learn from him. Editorializing a message? What the fuck are you even trying to say here?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 05:57:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 08:57:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>True</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 20:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh yes, this man is definitely a close friend of mine and I watch his shit all the time. I know each one by heart because I watch them daily. Are you fucking stupid? I watched the same fucking video you just did. All I know about this motherfucker is what I just watched. And what #8217;s the difference between leaving it in and leaving it out? It #8217;s the same message either way. So really you #8217;re just bitching on the internet like a teenage girl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 23:29:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow you want to know what I just realized? It turns out we are on the same fucking side. You just don #8217;t know how to fucking talk. This whole time everyone thought you wanted the part cut out, but actually you are complaining that it got cut out. Wow, I #8217;d apologize but honestly all this is because you #8217;re stupid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 20:03:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:46:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course I make a sub specifically for these types of posts, but here they are in the main sub with over 1,000 upvotes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 21:49:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, honestly that #8217;s really impressive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 23:41:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t believe that man is her father.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 17:13:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, leave Sylvester Stallone alone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 19:04:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this all 86 genders?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 20:35:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish the mods on this sub weren #8217;t such fags.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 21:35:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes but how do I do the thing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 00:51:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god it didn #8217;t work</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 02:03:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/NSFWFunny</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 22:10:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It the sub default dumbass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 22:11:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god this better not be the new  #8220;DJ Air Cannon #8221; post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 22:49:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s literally copy and pasted from the original post numbnuts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 04:19:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. This is the 7th time I #8217;ve removed this in 4 days</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 04:20:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Post something like this again and you will be banned.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 03:26:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d say the fact she can look both left and right at the same time makes her great and find problem areas. The filth can #8217;t hide from her!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 05:37:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey I #8217;m not asking about the logistics here. I #8217;m just saying she looks like Sid from ice age.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 06:15:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>And damn you got lucky because I was going to remove it as a shitpost.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 23:33:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>So what the fuck are you supposed to do with $40 for college? You can barely afford a fucking disposable, one-time use, paper booklet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 18:32:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shut up and take someone else #8217;s money because I don #8217;t have any.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 18:34:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t have the beard to be smoking out of a pipe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 18:37:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>But he did have that dope ass stache and he developed the theory of relativity so I #8217;ll give him a pass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 18:44:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>God I laughed my ass off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 18:47:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s some next level shit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 19:12:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I #8217;d love free college</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 19:14:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah that #8217;s free college right? Paying $0 for college.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 00:52:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>That means you #8217;re doing it wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 20:01:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awfully big ego there to think that anyone gives a shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 20:19:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 20:42:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ironic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 23:35:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 06:46:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually this is the 8th time it's been posted</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 06:50:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Photoshop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 19:29:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can I get some context here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 22:11:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m pretty sure you read that wrong. Because it #8217;s just saying that the cauldron is a symbol of a legend. Not that it is a MacGuffin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 22:21:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Being a cunt won #8217;t get you very far mate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 03:41:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, that #8217;s makes it pretty sad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 20:03:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>She did, it has been removed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 20:24:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or, stay with me here, sell them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 20:38:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I only say sell because this is the government we #8217;re talking about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 21:18:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d have to say no there Carl.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 05:27:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I pulled it back when I first cut it so I could clean it and it sprayed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 20:01:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 20:05:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would you like to be banned for promotions?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 23:45:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I dont know if you are aware how hospitals work but they do not *own* you once admitted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:00:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please don #8217;t post that there...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:05:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did it to just play matches for the blunt fun of it. Without worrying about run outs, spawn peaks, or just plain tryhards. When I #8217;m stressed after a toxic match I like to go to my alternate account and just act like I #8217;m brand new to the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 02:40:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>How is this rage when the mother is in a horrible situation? If the police are involved it is obviously this is something sanctioned and is probably best for the child in the long run.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 04:46:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is a polo ball mate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 15:10:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Normally when you play on your normal account you are worried about getting kills, leveling up, and getting higher ranks. You have to play more carefully and you tend to get invested in being better and better. With an alternate account I can destroy all the walls of the objective and try playing knives only.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 15:13:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes but my alternate account is more for doing shit I would normally never do. Like stupid strats. Like playing pistol only, knife only, or trying to only kill people with my gadget. I can open all the walls around the objective and try to win without stepping foot in the objective or try to win without setting foot on the same floor. Just stupid stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 16:52:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hardly play solo so my teammates are usually in on it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 20:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>God you #8217;re a moron</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How adaptable is DnD?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 20:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>How hard would it be to adapt DnD to a different setting? Is it possible to do a fallout style apocalyptic world? Or what about some form of superhero world where instead of magic there are super powers. Could we do space? Pirates? Modern day? I #8217;m just afraid that my friends are starting to get bored of fantasy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 20:26:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sweet thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 20:27:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>You mean how I #8217;ve always DM #8217;d?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 20:38:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only reason I #8217;d like to stay with DnD is because I #8217;ve put so much time and effort into learning it. I #8217;d rather not have to learn (and teach) another game. But I may have to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 20:43:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is a convincing argument there mate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 05:28:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>ELI5 please because I do not want to google it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 20:05:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m pretty sure school bus drivers can #8217;t do that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 20:09:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m sure if that were to happen today there would probably be an angry mob of slightly overweight moms marching the school.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 00:16:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spitting at people and leaving a kid on the side of the road somewhere are two very different things.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So satisfied</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 20:26:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 20:28:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s something I live by</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 23:47:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hop on it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 00:15:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You lost mate?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 02:11:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I yeet. You yeet. He, she, we yeet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 04:11:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Present tense - yeet Past tense - yeeten</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 20:06:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was just thinking the same thing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 20:11:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay can someone take this guys soapbox before he hurts himself?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 20:17:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I need context. The way each person was acting seemed off for the situation. Anyone have the audio?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 02:40:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck you are one retarded cunt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 02:41:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>OP did you have a fucking stroke?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 10:54:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please don #8217;t post this there. It has been reposted into oblivion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 00:44:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>No it is supposed to be Pok #233;mon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 00:46:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>He is, I went through his post history</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 00:51:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, I remember this post fondly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My girlfriend keeps wearing my underwear as shorts around the house so now I have no clean underwear.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 02:39:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 02:46:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well what do you think I wore to work?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 02:47:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay that seems plausible but is there a source?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 02:47:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are you on about mate?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 02:48:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to think thongs were sexy but now I know they #8217;re uncomfortable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 02:50:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>See that seems to be more in line with everyone #8217;s reactions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 02:54:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I work 3-12 and I #8217;ll tell you what! It #8217;s just fine for me thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 04:34:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are playing with fire mate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 04:56:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whoa mate, don #8217;t bring logic into my post. You #8217;ll ruin it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yokai asf</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 05:24:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 05:33:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>But I #8217;m already a 5 #8217;6 #8221; 200lb manlet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 06:24:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good idea. I usually just turn the ones I #8217;m wear inside out. Then backwards. Then inside out and backwards. That way I get 4 uses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 06:30:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was a little bored.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 06:40:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>me llaman papi gordo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 09:22:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can have my axe anytime</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 17:03:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mate are you okay? Literally all I did was ask for a source. And here you are acting like a cunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 17:04:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. Let #8217;s take a step back mate. Take a long look at this comment and take that moment to realize you are stupid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 17:05:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>And go commando! Fantastic!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 17:07:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay...but what did it do? It looks like it effects like two frames.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 19:34:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone calls you stupid, so you double down it it. Excellent strategy. 10/10</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 19:36:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>No I #8217;m pretty sure you literally just called me complete scum. Otherwise I wouldn #8217;t get a notification saying you just called me complete scum. So get the fuck off you soapbox and take a moment to realize you fucked up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 19:36:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s almost as if you didn #8217;t read the huge thread about me saying I was wearing her underwear and people asking for pictures.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 19:38:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, my whole life I wondered why I didn #8217;t think of that and now I know why. A 50 year old going commando is a horrible thing to think about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 19:48:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just need to know. Which pants leg do you keep you balls in? And does it not hurt when they run against your knee?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 17:28:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I found the vegan. They are ants guys. What do you guys do if they get in your house? Let those guys chill? Make them a snack? What if they cover your yard? Just never go on  #8220;their #8221; territory?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 19:33:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t be a cunt. The only time suicide is an option is when it #8217;s preferable to communism</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 20:16:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where did you come up with the pedo part?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 21:21:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah! No questions around here!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 21:51:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. And yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 21:56:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m 80% sure that he had a water bottle. I #8217;m pretty sure you can here the slight crinkle and it sloshing when he pans around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 01:49:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It would mainly be the more *conservative* Christians.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 02:28:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah not only that but he does a specific amount at a time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 06:22:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stop spamming subs for karma cunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 19:55:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s what I was going to say. For months out of a year all my music was that size. I just ended up memorizing most of it so I didn #8217;t have to carry it around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:40:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are not wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 06:47:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like someone is a little upset that they got turned on by a dude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 08:17:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>He has Xbox too. We used to play daily</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 00:33:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>u/cedehh u/Numberonenutthing is right. You can not just [shorten a gif from 3 months ago](https://www.reddit.com/r/NSFWFunny/comments/8n247c/conan_obrien_having_the_time_of_his_life/?st=JLH58XM0 amp;sh=a05b93a1) and call it a  #8220;new gif #8221;. It #8217;s the exact same content but 10 seconds shorter. Please stop doing this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 01:40:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not saying that you posted it too soon. My problem is that you posted it at all. Think of it like this. If I took the new avengers movie and I cut out a clip of them fighting each other and then I said  #8220; hey look at my brand new movie! #8221; That #8217;s not new content it the same exact thing but a shorter clip. This is not new content. It is the same gif but trimmed to be shorter. So basically you #8217;re milking a 6k upvoted post by acting like you made it again. When it #8217;s literally the same post. Don #8217;t be a karma whore mate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 02:15:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t trust Adam anymore. The show took a stupid turn once he started getting biased. I stopped watching after the wall episode.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 02:20:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, now I want to die.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 02:21:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are making it worse!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 02:25:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit this was in Stillwater? How is this the first I have heard of it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 02:32:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>He #8217;s trying to say the mother MURDERED someone and she didn #8217;t take any responsibility for it. She lied about what happened. And used her connections to get away with it. That #8217;s is not a good example. Unless it #8217;s an example on how to be a cunt of a parent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 03:27:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t encourage him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 04:59:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m only being  #8220;rude #8221; because I #8217;m constantly having issues with you u/cedehh. And every time I explain the problem you say,  #8220; Oh yeah. I understand. Each sub is different you know. Lol. It #8217;s all good. #8221; But then something exactly like it happens a couple days later. And then when I remove it, or call you out on it you act like it #8217;s all news to you. It #8217;s really kind of tiring. So either stop doing the stupid shit I #8217;ve told you not to do over and over again every time you mod mail me or I will put a temp ban on you. Maybe then you #8217;ll stop playing dumb and get with the fucking program.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 07:05:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>You got any juice? Alcohol just makes me beat my wife.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 08:58:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are one dense motherfucker</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 09:23:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>The problem is you aren #8217;t listening to a fucking thing I #8217;m saying mate. I have said several times already that just because you trim a few seconds off a gif you made before doesn #8217;t not mean it #8217;s a completely new gif. You have done the same thing several times where you post a  #8220;different #8221; gif of content that was posted before. Such as a  #8220;different #8221; scene, length, or extremely similar content (Ex. The fan fucking gif) your content continues to copy itself and other high karma gifs. And then you act like you don #8217;t understand why people give you shit or remove your posts. Then you act like a dumb cunt and you play the victim. That #8217;s the last I #8217;ll say. If you still want to act like you don #8217;t understand what the fuck I #8217;m saying then I give the fuck up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 22:35:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. You guys are really trying to get to the bottom of the barrel here. Can someone please explain the funny part. I mean obviously there is a ladder but that #8217;s just stupid, not exactly funny.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 01:14:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh yeah I did. Lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 01:26:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a former manager of a local grocery store I #8217;ll say this. I once caught a girl shoplifting and I followed her while calling the police. But I wasn #8217;t going to follow her all the way home. So I let her just go. While talking to the police and giving her description. I got wrote up for letting her go. Another instance I caught this guy shoplifting and he started to run. So I chased him and grabbed him before he could get out. I held onto him while a coworker called the police. I got wrote up for holding the guy against his will. Obviously I quit working at the shittiest place in the world. Sometimes you don #8217;t know what to do to save your job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 04:23:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least he #8217;s not standing on the very top of it. That #8217;s dangerous</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 18:38:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Technically if you are enough chocolate it #8217;s toxic to humans too. But it #8217;d have to be like 40 kg It #8217;s all about the type and the quantity compared to the size of the dog. The part that makes it bad is the theobromine. When it is metabolized it widens you blood vessels and stimulates the heart. Which is why too much is a bad thing. The reason it #8217;s worse for dogs is because they can #8217;t digest it as quickly as humans. They only need about 300mg per kg of body weight. ( sonic the dog weights 1kg then 300mg could cause problems) It begins with various digestive issues. Nausea, vomiting, and diarrhea But if they #8217;ve eaten enough then the symptoms are worse. Cardiac arrhythmia, seizures, internal bleeding, heart attacks, and possibly death. A 20kg dog usually starts showing digestion issues after about 240g of dark chocolate. Here #8217;s a neat [calculator ](http://www.askavetquestion.com/chocolate_toxicity.php) if you want to know how much theobromine is in something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 22:38:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I left my Fitbit on the charger for the last year and a half.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 22:43:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dad is a devout Christian man. He obviously believes in prayer. But he #8217;s the kind of guy that will do everything in his power to help first. He doesn #8217;t pray God will send someone, because he believes that he is that someone. Then after he does all he can hell pray *with* them. Not for them. He #8217;s the kind of guy I strive to be. James 2:14-26</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 01:47:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah it #8217;s easy to talk but it #8217;s difficult to act.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 04:22:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you explain how you came to that conclusion? Because going up to my original comment, I #8217;m pretty sure I said to do both.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 19:47:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last night Monty killed me with his shield up, sooo...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>