<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject3667</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-28 12:57:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of Gods and Generals. 4 hours of what felt like my anal cavity was being searched with a rusty anvil.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-31 15:52:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have promise me this isn't photoshopped, holy crap!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 12:44:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do a very transparent audit of the city's finances.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-06 13:55:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You live up to your username. It matters if anyone is murdered by anyone. But your reaction and sarcasm is to be expected. Throughout history, whenever minorities take issue with systemic racial issues, people like yourself attempt to redirect. It's either the media that's to blame, we're told it isn't the right time, we're race baiting or we need to worry about our internal racial issues. Don't worry, we'll press on regardless of your attempt to reduce the issue. In reality, police overreach affects us all. #blacklivesmatter</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-07 17:43:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>There were reports of the Apple Watch selling for less than $200 yesterday. Hope that helps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-24 13:49:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Believe me it's gonna be great! Some of the smartest people in the world have endorsed this idea. It's probably the greatest idea ever! It's gonna be HUGE, believe me folks. (Sorry, I went away and I came back. I couldn't resist! Let the downvotes begin.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-28 03:35:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe through the net?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-30 11:32:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Superman Returns. No one wanted that movie to written the way it was. There was hardly any action, Superman had about 12 lines and the plot was just non sense. But dammit if I haven't watched it about 15 times!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-10 11:09:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Much of people's support for Trump isn't logical. I don't mean that to insult, he's the ultimate protest vote.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-12 14:16:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm assuming he meant Ecuador...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-13 02:59:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry dude, I'm laughing...that's some sad but funny shit bro!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-15 01:35:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-15 01:37:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trump's face is a meme my friend. It is the meta of the meme world. (Fuck, did I actually use "meta"?!)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-15 04:43:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish the dash was a little more in focus but that's still a really cool shot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-15 04:47:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nikon D7100, 100 ISO, 1.8f</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-01 19:29:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome shot!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 11:31:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, what he said!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 20:14:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You make an excellent point. The only problem being if they use it to steal your identity or your intellectual property you also have limited recourse. And considering how China doesn't follow the same ethics as America the information could be sold on the Black Market and used to blackmail you if you talk about unethical things in it's presence. I don't know, it's a crazy world of possibilities now. Either live scared or don't live, there's really no in between.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 12:29:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>With that he's still talking about the state investing millions to make that cap of 2% possible. The plan doesn't truly do anything curb cost, it just shifts who's paying for it. This is similar to the debate over healthcare. Every is talking about the rising cost of insurance but now how to keep healthcare costs down. (There aspects of ACA that attempt to address some of it, but it's largely an insurance reform bill.) the same with college tuition, there are tons of proposals to help students pay for tuition but nothing is being done to keep the cost of tuition from rising.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 19:31:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great point but the administrative portion of school budgets as gone up significantly in the last decade. Some is to keep up with technology some is keeping up with Jones's like fancier dorms and increased marketing.  #175;\_( #12484;)_/ #175;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 14:11:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like this. I wish the leaves covered a little more on the bottom, but very nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 14:14:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really love the vibe. Like the others have said the cone is distracting but maybe you can desaturate a little in post process to help with this photo?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 14:16:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be honest, the cat makes the shot. The cat adds feeling and I don't even like cats. Good work!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 20:16:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's slick! Never thought to do a long exposure on an escalator</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ITAP of a musician</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-24 12:07:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-17 11:17:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah man, after you leave the Rock Roll Hall of Fame the rest of the town is lame.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-17 11:31:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree, just one point he missed. Improving the defense at least takes pressure off Flacco to perform and provides us space to get the ground game going. I say draft should focus on WR, OL, LB or whatever Ozzie's two SB rings say we should do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In the park today, snapped this.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-19 21:56:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 12:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! Took me forever to getting around to shooting it, glad I finally did.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 06:08:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's been there for as long as I can remember if you're referring to the 40mph sign heading south past Cold Spring. I've here pretty much my whole life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 13:00:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, sadly you don't have enough hands to pick up my typos at work. I don't know how I stay employed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 18:36:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not exactly what you asked for but, I'm hoping it's helpful. Avoid the Rokinon 10mm 2.8. It's good in a pinch but the images are super soft. I admit it's gotten me a few shots I wouldn't have otherwise been able to, but I rarely use it because I know I'll be disappointed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 18:29:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not gonna be as deep as the previous comment (well said btw). It's a great shot and I'll leave it there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why doesn't anyone go to Iggie's anymore?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 05:26:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know ownership has changed but the food and atmosphere are still same...imo. Yet, Iggie's used to be a place where you couldn't get a seat on Friday night, now you just walk right it. Anyone have thoughts on what's changed?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 05:39:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep, I drive by almost everyday. Maybe the construction next door is having a bigger impact than I thought?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 15:17:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. I haven't heard of some of those places, I'll definitely give some of them a try. Birroteca is AMAZING! Love the beer selection there too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 15:20:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've only been there once, ordered a sandwich with some friends. Can't believe I haven't been back because it was one of the best sandwiches I've ever had. Thanks for reminding about that place.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 15:27:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hope you get well soon!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 03:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just went to their website, I'll be picking up a pie on my way sometime this week.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 23:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well said!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 17:27:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use to work for a state senator that worked closely with this guy. He was shady as hell back then, I'm totally not surprised. I think as the previous commenter said, it's more of surprise they went after him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-06 03:35:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Beautiful! You've inspired me to step up my portrait game!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 18:01:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm kinda mad the site didn't work. I would've bought a candle or two on GP. Now I'll just sit here in bitterness and farts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 01:25:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like to focus is a little off, am I right? Or is her skin that smooth?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-15 20:39:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>It actually wouldn't be that hard to explain if one wanted to inaccurately paint a whole group of people with a single color. Try this, some liberals are gun owners, but all gun owners are perpetrators of mass shooting homicides. The second portion of that statement being totally false...sort of like your meme.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 21:19:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you need clinical trials on that "vitamin's" performance, I volunteer to test it. I'm dedicated to science.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-25 13:27:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a GREAT deal, just sold my D7100, body only for $515, sold the 18-140 lens for $225.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-30 01:45:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's also fake</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 15:19:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Promise that you're both virgins. He's a devout Christian, he'd eat that stuff up! Your fallback would be Tim Tebow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 13:37:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did no one notice he 'trademarked' "niggas"? He fittin to be rich!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 18:27:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had Sigma 17-50mm. It was a very useful walk around lens and did admirably with portraits. Initially I thought my 35mm 1.8 was dramatically sharper then I learned to turn off the Optical Stabilization when using a tripod or if the situation doesn't demand it. My images came out a lot sharper. The bokeh on either lens isn't very impressive when compared to the nifty 50 if that's what you're looking for:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 12:55:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Correct. So it can work as an effective portrait lens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 18:09:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Considering the costs vs speed, what's the benefit of having Port Networks? Is the customer service just better or is a F*** Comcast thing (which I totally understand and might actually be worth it)?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 17:56:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's software that can be used to upsize digital photos without major degradation. That said, where did find the image? Maybe you can track down the Artist? Edit: Just realized I didn't comment back to OP.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 17:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where did you find the image? You could start there to track down the Artist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 04:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your focus could use some work. The sunglasses was a nice shot, but the lack of focus killed it. Be patient with yourself, it takes a lot of time. Also, become technically proficient with your camera. Have you picked up any books?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 10:49:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the online tips are helpful once you've got the basics down. For me, having a book for casual reading really helped on learning composition, ISO, Shutterspeed, and Aperture then on to a lot of experimenting...a lot...A LOT! I still have a crap ton to learn and keep learning something almost every time I shoot. But it was sitting down with a thorough, professionally written and easy to understand book that really helped get me started. Since then it's been using Instagram to meet up with local photographers. My local photographers are super helpful and encouraging. I hope you find the same. Good Luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 20:56:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Truth Bomb!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 23:08:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like the "filler" episodes. I like knowing the characters in depth. For me, none of it's filler. The small conversations or incidents make the final episode that much better. I hated shows that every week something big needs to happen. I've quit several shows because the story was replaced with poorly done shock and awe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lack of protest over RGIII Potential signing shows bias against Kap</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-02 01:14:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>The fact that no one is complaining about the Ravens potentially signing the poorer performing, fragile RGIII proves that those folks who said it was because Kap sucked are biased.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-02 19:58:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The very reason the potential signing of CK is in the news is because of visceral reactions like the ones you all have had. Ravens fans have been loud in either their disdain for CK as a person or a player. Though none of that went to RGIII who has shown to be a lesser QB and more flawed as a human e.g. throwing teammates under the bus, demanding who coach's him, lack of accountability, possible cheating on his spouse). Where's the outrage?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dr. Huxtable was a GYN examining patients in his basement, why didn't we see Bill Cosby coming?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 12:37:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 12:48:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>ZING!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 17:13:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>On the reason for going select "peer to peer education exchange". To go as a journalist you'll potentially need proof of employment later. With the peer to peer you just need to keep a journal of Cubans you've talked to everyday and what you talked to them about and be able to reproduce it for up to five years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 17:17:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also, I just left. Be mindful of paying in Pesos vs CUC. At mom and pop shops the price is in Peso which are worth 1/24 of a CUC. No one will give you that exchange rate. So when if possible, get your hands on about $50 pesos and your trip will be super cheap. Oh and like most 3rd world countries, you're safe except no one does anything for you there without expecting a tip. Most prices are very negotiable. Never settle for the first price they give you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 17:18:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>La Mankina was some of the best food I ever had! And Zengua was good and the lady bartender is super fun!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 05:33:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's even worse than over throwing Crowder, he was forcing it to the double covered receiver.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Let's congratulate Andy Dalton!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 13:17:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 02:04:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>NFL Memes my friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 22:37:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was really hoping he had a great week to confirm the awesomeness of the Raven's D.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 13:43:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think he started rough last season, then picked up the pace after game 4 or so. Here's to hoping.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 21:43:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like that idea, sounds like a comedy science fiction movie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 18:54:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>For me it's that every song sounds the same</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 05:04:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hopefully I didn't ruin it for you. I took a listen to their latest efforts and it sounded exactly like I remembered them from about 16 or so years ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 05:10:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.bbc.co.uk/newsbeat/article/36022068/theres-a-study-on-why-people-really-hate-nickelback That might help</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 01:11:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was already gonna be a tough game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Too old to care now</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 18:32:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 18:36:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>In 40 weeks we'll find out if they both lost.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 18:45:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>The meme is incorrect. The CDC reported 624k abortions in 2013. The number goes down every year. That same year, there were 73k handgun related deaths. Also, if you're against murder, you'd want to stop all murder anyway you can. So the handgun deaths should prompt you to support gun law reforms. Pro-Life shouldn't just be pro-birth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 00:27:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Netflix  amp; Marriage #reallife</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 05:39:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>And that fertilized egg is worthless without a womb. We all make choices.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 20:23:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Always. But according to you it's not murder to abort a child. If killing off sperm isn't murder because it's dependent on an egg, than neither is abandoning a fertilized egg because it's dependent on a womb. Per your definition life would start once it can self sustain.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 20:29:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Always. But according to you it's not murder to abort a child. If killing off sperm isn't murder because it's dependent on an egg, than neither is abandoning a fertilized egg because it's dependent on a womb. Per your definition life would start once it can self sustain.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 12:29:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s not anti trump, it #8217;s pro easy material. Trump is a meme goldmine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 13:21:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish we could have signed Kap in the offseason, but st this point there #8217;s no QB that could come off the streets and be productive mid season.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 10:42:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chiparellis in Little Italy might be able to sell you a whole one, they make it onsite. That said, don #8217;t let the delicious tiramisu fool you into ordering anything else there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 13:41:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>So dangerous he came back out within a minute.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Was this year #8217;s draft class a fluke or has Ozzie lost his fastball?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 16:01:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mama  #8216;bout to drop a 5 back hand classic</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 19:42:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New Wireless Broadband Provider Hammer Fiber No timetable though they announced in October.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 19:51:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 19:53:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>The pricing structure looks awesome! But the Facebook reviews are mixed.  #175;\_( #12484;)_/ #175; Fixed wired seems like the only real solution that could disrupt Comcast #8217;s monopoly but I remain hopeful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 05:51:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah, imma pass. Why not Drew Brees if we #8217;re talking older QBs, at least he #8217;s still winning and could work in Jay #8217;s offense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 17:06:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>With each warming/cooling event there still existed a scientific explanation. For instance, the earth warmed in previously due to green house gases as well. The difference being that the five degree temperature increase took about 5000 years. The earth has cooled due to volcanic ash in the sky as well. If the current warming is not due to excessive carbon dioxide from humans, than what is it? We #8217;re on pace for a 6 degree temperature increase over 100 years. That #8217;s a really rapid increase that breaks strongly from 4.5 billion years of history. If it #8217;s not humans, where are the green house gases coming from?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 16:48:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hilarious!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 16:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Came to say the same!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 21:15:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty sure that #8217;s not even a picture of a mask. Hopefully I #8217;m not being captain obvious but that looks like MS Paint over so poor dude #8217;s eyes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>He #8217;s a parody of himself.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 21:32:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 20:19:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly, small businesses become BIG business. Moreover, an investment in infrastructure (fiber, public transportation, etc.) makes your city more attractive to companies without having to race to the bottom in a competition with other states.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 16:53:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>At the risk of being called stupid, where are Cap and Hulk?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 04:47:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Moreover, the rating aren #8217;t actually down all that much in terms of viewership. More folks are streaming the games and Nielsen doesn #8217;t capture that. That said, I defined watched less football this year but that had nothing to do with a protest, my life has just gotten busier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 15:21:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>*you #8217;re Also, It #8217;s impossible to discern someone #8217;s race by their opinion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 05:05:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dayyyuummm, is that an original beat?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 22:04:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>My interest had waned at the start of this season, but by the mid season finale I was back to being hooked. It #8217;s one of the few shows I #8217;m caught up on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 03:23:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dammit! I swear I scanned for like 20 minutes to see this wasn #8217;t posted. Oh well, I #8217;ll take it down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 16:26:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. Someone else commented that it would encourage studios to produce shit movies since they have a guaranteed revenue stream. Instead I #8217;d be willing to pay $25 per film to watch it from home. Still cheaper than the theater, way more expensive than pay per view and maintains the profit motive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 15:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Football players have a relatively short period of time to make more money then an entire family 5 lifetimes. That said, I don #8217;t blame him for trying to maximize is income. However, he #8217;s not the guy I #8217;d want to build my team around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 23:10:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good thing Obamacare covers alcoholism.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 16:53:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was a committee hearing yesterday, it still has a long way to get voted on by both chambers to make it on the ballot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 16:55:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t forget private prisons opposition. I #8217;m in general horrified that there #8217;s an industry that profits off the creation of criminals.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 17:01:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Legislative leadership has said they see passage as a long shot this year. But honestly I don #8217;t like this bill. 1 oz is a relatively small amount when you consider how much 2-4oz one plant can grow. And if it #8217;s a ballot measure to change it we need to go to the polls again. It would be better is the amendment merely secured the right to purchase and grow marijuana but left the specifics up the executive branch and legislators.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 17:56:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think breaking with the rules of composition here might help. I think there #8217;s too much sky. Comparing it to the original you #8217;ve done a good job of bringing life to the sky, but there might just be too much of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 00:44:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>That does look better, glad I could help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 12:03:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 19:24:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>[City Broadband Strategy](http://www.magellan-advisors.com/success-stories/business-planning/204-city-of-baltimore-public-broadband-strategy-development.stml) Anyone knows what happened to this report and strategy? Wasn #8217;t this supposed to help decide if we should build our own network?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 16:30:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Today your name is  #8220;Money #8221;! Thank you. Where did you find the actual report? Tell me is wasn #8217;t on the website I posted!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Remember, marriage is a sacred union...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 11:27:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 19:20:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 19:21:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s Ms. Caitlyn Jenner and they #8217;re fabulous.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 13:36:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>The cue ball hurt coming out so now the monkey makes sure things aren #8217;t too big before eating them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Seeking A Model</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 16:03:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m looking to hone my portrait skills. Looking someone interested in getting some free outdoor shots, male or female. I #8217;m free Friday during the day. I have no money to offer. You can see some samples of my work below. [Pagoda ](https://instagram.com/p/BfYXLDOnSm1/) [Artscape](https://instagram.com/p/BW3B2gGBvwH/) [Shamirre ](https://instagram.com/p/Bgv8LkfHi_3/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 16:35:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll PM you but maybe we can schedule something for a different day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 18:34:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sweet! I #8217;ll PM you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 19:37:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome sauce!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Anchor Formerly Known as Sean Hannity</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 15:36:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 01:16:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>The public comment period is apart of the rule making portion for any law. Before the executive branch can move forward with enforcing the laws, the rules for how the law will be enforced must be established and the public gets to comment on it. Totally normal process.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 15:33:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nicely done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 21:59:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>No one should ever rob you. The police wouldn #8217;t even need a picture to catch the perpetrator. Just words.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 17:59:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>That worries me too. This combined with vertical integration doesn #8217;t leave much space for competition.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If Solar Panels ever became 100% efficient at capturing all the light and energy that the sun shines on it, they #8217;d be just dark spots on roofs. They #8217;d look like tiny black holes from space.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 05:38:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 12:02:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not surprised this guy is a Trump supporter</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When it comes to facial hair, the only thing worst than shaving your neck beard is having a one.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 12:42:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 17:33:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not at all!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 22:50:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you. I thought I was missing something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 11:25:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was literally just thinking that!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 18:11:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Legit question. They not gonna miss we Eatin #8217; a bag of fries but the snitch my think they will. Not encouraging stealing, but they don #8217;t pay fast workers enough to be on their feet for 8 hour shifts getting yelled at by Karenn for putting three pickles on her burger when she clearly only wanted two. That free bag of fries was enough to keep me from screaming on a customer and ruining the business.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 09:56:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m fine now, but thanks for asking. I was just reliving memories of a long time ago. Now I sit on my butt in a cube farm forcing myself to go for walks in the building to keep my watch happy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 19:44:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just for the sake of comparison, how many balls have the other receivers dropped in practice and how many did he catch?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fired Longtime Eagles Employee Gets Super Bowl Ring and Credit for a TD</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 12:05:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lamar Jackson fastest QB in Madden.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 20:08:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 00:27:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! I learned the game from playing video games</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 13:09:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Frosted Flakes with marshmallows will get you higher than you #8217;ve ever been, but the crash is hard.,</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The fact that comic book fans can get violently angry when a superhero gets married or has children tells us a lot more about the readers envy than they #8217;d care to admit.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 23:53:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 21:52:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude! Who you tellin #8217;. I #8217;m like touched they send that, then kinda jealous that they out there living their best lives and I #8217;m grinding away. I mean it #8217;s what I do it for, but still, I #8217;d much rather be with them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 21:56:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s kind of the point of telling a story right! But to be fair, I think the point is that the story is being picked to support a predetermined narrative.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 11:33:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m so ashamed of myself. There was a period in my life when I didn #8217;t think Bill O was a bigot. What the hell was wrong with me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 12:45:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>For me, I #8217;m jamming to a song then find out it #8217;s by her. Her the song again, get excited and totally forgot it was her again. I think it #8217;s because she #8217;s fairly formulaic as a singer and I don #8217;t sleep enough to remember things.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 12:52:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>A chocolate man #8217;s chocolate milk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 01:42:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s just a weird fetish that I don #8217;t understand. To each their own I suppose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 01:44:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it gay to suck your own? I mean, it #8217;s not gay to touch your own...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 01:46:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess dude has never eaten a sausage</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 01:50:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oil My Wife 2 Feel Your Best? That #8217;s definitely it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 17:16:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Always struck me as odd that black people are so committed to Christianity and the black church is so powerful but Christianity wasn #8217;t our choice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 21:40:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excellent point! Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 02:03:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha! I remember two of my gay friends being pissed about marriage equality becoming a reality. They really felt like they lost one of the big benefits of being gay. I say this to say, don #8217;t worry, life will find a way!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 17:52:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your child brain was awesome!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 17:54:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>And my wife accidentally stopped taking BC for six months...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 12:12:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. As if to say being called gay is an insult. We have a long way to go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 20:22:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unreal! Great job on the composition and finding a unique spot to get the skyline! Love it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 20:28:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Plot twist, that cheetah is paid better than Chester.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The first guy to give a woman an orgasm probably thought he did something wrong.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 12:05:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 22:02:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>This exchange made my day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 22:15:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks def fade. I #8217;ve been married for a lot of years and I see the amazing woman that #8217;s birthed my children, cared for me when I was sick, got me through college and laughs at my jokes no matter how we #8217;ve aged. I wouldn #8217;t risk or trade that kind of woman for a prettier face ever. She might annoy me at times, but she carries me too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 14:42:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can #8217;t imagine being so humble that I #8217;d see an attractive woman wearing a shirt with my face on it that I wouldn #8217;t do some lewd shit. There #8217;s a reason I have a dad bod and work in a cubical, this is all the sexiness I can handle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I wanted someone different...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:24:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>