<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject3605</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tracked my net worth during college (05/2015-12/2017) [OC]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 02:35:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 02:41:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>grinding through part-time jobs, summer internships, investing in stocks, cryptocurrency. I was also extremely luck to get a scholarship which helped with no debt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 02:43:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did try startups but they were extremely difficult to manage during college and did not go anywhere apart from a little bit of money from freelance work/internships I got as a result</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 02:45:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was extremely lucky to receive a scholarship for college. I saved every cent and still do, worked during every summer break/also part-time, made sure to save and invest a good part of the money I was able to earn (stocks and crypto).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 02:54:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha I'm pretty sure that sharp peak in June/July 2017 would correlated pretty well with an ether graph. thanks! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 03:21:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>* Data source: self sourced * Data visualization tool: Excel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 03:21:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>done!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 21:50:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got into crypto in 3/2017 and have always kept it no more than 10%-20% of my net worth</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 21:51:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I have been tracking my net worth for more than 2.5 years during college [OC]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 18:46:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 18:50:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here is a line chart version with the different segments: https://imgur.com/a/Zbd5F Recently I've been tracking it almost daily. I was extremely lucky to receive a scholarship for college. I saved every cent and still do, worked during every summer break/also part-time, did a bunch of side projects, made sure to save and invest a good part of the money I was able to earn (stocks and crypto). I posted a different visualization of this data previously but many people were asking about allocation/source of earning, so I took some time to create more detailed visualizations. * Source: self-sourced * Tool: Excel and Sketch App</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 20:05:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can get there! Work hard, keep your burn rate low, save a ton, invest/compound. For a number of reasons, * I always try to keep enough for 6 months of living in case there is any unpredicted situation. * when I started buying stocks (in 2015), I wasn't very confident about my skills to choose stocks or very confident about stocks. I also grew up in a very risk-averse family where they always told me to be careful about stocks because you can lose all your money. Throughout 2016, I became much more informed and started being more confident about choosing my portfolio. * part of it is debt, money that other people owe me. Won't go into much detail but now the debt part is down to $5K. I am not a fan of having much in cash (apart from the emergency cash), especially after I saw a compound calculator in late 2015. So that number is on its way to $15-16K now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 22:05:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes, it's net worth. I didn't have college tuition debt because I received a scholarship. I got a little bit of debt here and there along the way but it was discounted from the chart amounts, and I made sure to pay them off quickly as soon as I earned/saved enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 04:21:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>what is your major? doing my side projects helped me a lot. the one I sold was a transportation software.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 04:23:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you referring to 11/2/2017? If so, what happened is that I sold a project (so I received money for IP) and then gradually moved money into stocks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 22:31:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>a transportation software</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 22:32:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>yup! picking up side projects in the area you want to work in will help you for sure! helps build a portfolio + you might get an offer from a company in the space or freelance/consulting work. best of luck!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 22:34:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>definitely! still saving a lot and trying to earn money through freelance work/my current work. yes, both my stocks and crypto were falling during that time, but crypto fell much more. i agree and that's why i made a line chart too with the different segments: https://imgur.com/a/Zbd5F</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 08:32:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Robinhood has been great! They don't charge any commission fees so it's great if you're just getting started</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;ve been tracking my net worth for the past 2.5 years during college</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 20:19:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>During college, I started paying more attention to my finances so I started tracing my net worth and my spending. Recently I've been tracking my net worth almost daily. On my spreadsheet, I break down my net worth into different categories so I keep my allocation in mind (the big categories shown on the graph are cash, stocks, cryptocurrencies). It's been very helpful for planning, saving and budgeting and I'd definitely recommend doing something like that. Maybe not daily but at least monthly. I started off with little debt because I was extremely lucky to receive a college scholarship. I got debt here and there but I made sure to pay it off very quickly as soon as I earned enough. During college, I worked summer internships during all breaks, worked part-time during school, worked on a few side projects and freelance projects, saved a ton and learned about stocks/crypto. I'd appreciate any feedback on how I can improve my finances moving forward now that I am done with college. Enjoy! Here are the charts I made using that info: https://imgur.com/a/Zbd5F</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 07:41:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks! i know zero about roth IRA and 401K, and also zero about credit so i guess they are two things i will need to learn about now that i'm gonna start adulting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 09:48:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks for the advice! i feel you. the biggest issue for me is that i get too caught up on the daily changes and that sets the mood of the day in a way that it shouldn't. as of now, i am self-employed. can i still contribute to IRA? do you have any recommendations for an IRA to pick (Vanguard?)? should I choose Roth or traditional IRAs?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 22:34:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks a ton. seems like roth is the right choice then!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Recent college grad: which credit card to choose for building credit score and cash back?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 23:36:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am a self-employed recent college graduate with no debt. My biggest priorities are building my credit score (I don #8217;t have one yet because I #8217;ve never owned a credit card) and cash back. I never spend more than I can afford.  #160; **SPENDING INFO** Here is the rough breakdown of my spending: https://imgur.com/a/6x9DP The 3 top categories are: *TRAVEL: 39%* * RIDE-SHARING: 24.2% of total spending * HOTELS (mostly Airbnb): 17.4% of total spending *FOOD  amp; DINING: 21%* * RESTAURANTS: 14.1% of total spending * FAST-FOOD: 4% of total spending *SHOPPING: 15%* * SHOPPING (mostly online): 9.5% of total spending * CLOTHING: 4% of total spending  #160; **CREDIT CARDS I'M CURRENTLY COMPARING** Here are 2 cards I #8217;ve been looking into. Let me know if there is any other card I should consider: *Uber Credit Card* * No annual fee * 4% on dining * 3% on hotel and airfare * 2% on online shopping * 1% on everything else * $100 subscription bonus * $50 for online subscriptions (I pay over $50/year for music) * $600 mobile phone insurance * $0 annual fee *Citi Double Cash* * 2% on everything assuming I will pay it off * $0 annual fee  #160; **THOUGHTS SO FAR** For now, assuming my spending habits will continue similar and only looking at cash back, Uber seems like the best deal (about $4 or 10% more cash back per month than Citi Double Cash) without including the $100 bonus. I don #8217;t know how they compare with regards to building credit and I am making a few assumptions, such as spending habit continuing the same, which will likely be true for at least the next year  #8212; I don #8217;t believe it will change dramatically in the next 3 years, and based on my own (and Mint #8217;s) rough trend estimates.  #160; **Which credit card would you recommend? Is there any other credit card that might be better than those two?**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 23:57:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Travel flights is only a small part. About 60% of the travel costs are uber/lyft and 20% are Airbnb</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Recent college grad: which credit card to choose for building credit score and cash back?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 00:40:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found a website that shows recent crime rates in SF. My friends and I have been using it to avoid crime and street harrassment</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 23:31:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 23:35:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>why?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 23:35:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>yup, i try to avoid spots with high crime rate EDIT: I can't move because I work in the city. I actually just got robbed earlier this week. I don't think avoiding robbery/violence/street harrassment is a spineless thing to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found a website that shows recent crime rates in SF. My friends and I have been using it to avoid crime and street harrassment</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 23:41:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 00:13:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am really surprised by the comments here saying that I should move just because I try to stay safe. I have many other female friends who have had issues with street harrassment or robbery in SF so the solution is apparently to move to Lafayette and not step foot in SF if we can't "grow a spine" and get robbed/harrassed? I just wanted to share something I found useful but now I am just surprised with the response and don't know what to say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is it worth to start a 401K or IRA if there is a 50% chance I will not retire in the US?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 20:06:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I plan to stay in the US in the short-term (next 7-10 years) but there is a 50% chance I will want to leave the US after that. I am 23 and my first job (a paid internship with a W2) was at 19. Given that uncertainty, is it still worth to start a 401K or IRA now? EDIT: I am self employed EDIT 2: I am not a US citizen. If I did end up not retiring in the US, I'd be retiring in Brazil.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 20:42:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. I am self employed so that #8217;s not an option</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 20:42:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. I am self employed so matching is not an option</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is it worth to start a 401K or IRA if there is a 50% chance I will not retire in the US?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 21:23:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 21:24:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>but what happens if i remove the money before retirement? i thought both 401K and roth IRA had penalty for early withdrawal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 07:38:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd be moving to Brazil if I did. also I am not a US citizen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 07:42:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>A - If I did move, I'd move to Brazil (my citizenship country). B - Yes, I am considering both but not sure which to choose yet. C - I am not a US citizen. D - I am at the beginning of my career, so I am assuming taxes will be higher when I retire (if I do it in the US). I think taxes would be around the same as they are now if I retire in Brazil but I am not sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My doctor said I might have hypertension so I tracked my blood pressure in the past 10+ days [OC]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 18:53:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 18:57:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I went to the doctor on 1/26, my blood pressure was very high so I've been tracking my blood pressure since then and I am meeting her again today and showing her this graph. Here are some events throughout the 10+ days: * 1/25 night: preparing for stressful meeting 1/26 morning and argument with SO that evening * 2/5: started watching my sodium intake and doing cardio daily. My average blood pressure has reduced after 2/5 Info: * Source: self-sourced * Tool: Excel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 21:05:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The average is my average. I chose to compare with the average because the ideal (below 120/80) is very easy to see, so I don't need a line for that when showing it to the doctor. However, my average is important because that's what my doctor cares about -- as long as the average is not too much above the ideal, having a few peaks (like the two 140+ for systolic) is fine according to her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 08:00:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thoughts on CRSP?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 08:07:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>My portfolio: * 18.98% AMZN * 16.28% GOOGL * 15.53% FB * 14.38% VOO * 13.76% NVDA * 7.87% TSLA * 7.24% V * 5.96% BRK.B</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 20:45:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why do you consider it defensive? Based on large-cap concentration I guess? I am actually trying to increase non-tech positions to decrease risk/dependence on tech. I am planning to increase my BRK.B and V positions to be slightly higher than my TSLA position. I start off with smaller investments (like my V, BRK.B, TSLA) and then increase progressively as I am more and more convinced about how solid the company is. For TSLA, I have a lot of belief in the long-term potential (I'm in the auto space and, in terms of product, they seem to be the ones leading in all the areas that will be important in the future of auto, such as autonomy, software integration, sustainability), but I am not fully convinced of how solid the company is given financials/failure to meet targets.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 07:51:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>My portfolio: * AMZN: 13.33% * GOOGL: 12.21% * VOO: 11.37% * V: 11.29% * BRK.B: 10.71% * FB: 10.43% * NVDA: 9.55% * VIOO: 8.97% * WM: 8.73% * TSLA: 3.33% * CRSP: 0.07%</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 07:56:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm trying to diversify by adding a non-US stock (maybe like India or China for example. being non-tech would be a plus, but doesn't have to be non-tech). Any suggestions of non-US stocks?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I have been tracking my net worth for more than 3 years during college and after [OC]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 08:23:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>