<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject5000</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-05 06:15:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Forza has made a simulation game yes, but its a simulation game that I feel like still has fun too it. Idk about the rest of you but when i used to play the Gran turismo series I got bored with them quickly. I think the developers of Forza(don't remember who and to lazy to check the box) could make a great game regardless of not having real world data for acceleration, handling, etc. the developers of burnout could make a fun game too. though it'd be much faster paced and thered be alot more of the crashing emphasis. might not be a bad idea. lol. burnout game play with forzas graphics. that would own</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-05 18:13:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>get a program called Maya. its by a company called auto desk. you can get a student edition for free from their website.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Set list for the tour</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-30 06:27:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Time Consumer no world for tomorrow cuts marked in the march of men 3 evils deranged feathers the crowing ten speed here we are juggernaut devil in jersey city faint of hearts mother superior a gotye cover in keeping secrets sentry the defiant full band a favor house atlantic welcome home It's alot of IKS, im assuming bc of the 10 years of it so they wont have to do another neverender tour. Was wishing there'd be more good apollo 1. also no everything evil surprised me, since its josh's favorite song. thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Set List For The Tour</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-30 06:50:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Time Consumer no world for tomorrow cuts marked in the march of men 3 evils deranged feathers the crowing ten speed here we are juggernaut devil in jersey city faint of hearts mother superior a gotye cover in keeping secrets sentry the defiant full band a favor house atlantic welcome home **EDIT** My friend who was at the show got claudios set list, several of these songs will change throughout the touring, the crowing will be swapped for apollo 1, mother superior with pearl of the stars, and the cover just says COVER and he heard that they have several prepared and will just decide which to play. He also said there was a song that was sharpied out on the setlist **EDIT** It's alot of IKS, im assuming bc of the 10 years of it so they wont have to do another neverender tour. Was wishing there'd be more good apollo 1. also no everything evil surprised me, since its josh's favorite song. thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-30 07:07:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah this shattered symphony is epic. I was really hoping for more GA1 stuff but i wont complain. I'll be filming either the chattanooga or lexington show. and it'll be on youtube. Usually in the past im in the front row when i film, but idk if i'll make it to the venues early enough to get front row. but i actually get good audio from the front. check out my channel. youtube.com/cocafan33</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-30 07:36:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha badass dude, the louisville show was actually the first one i started filming from that close, had no clue my camera would hold up that well in the front row. glad you enjoy them man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-30 07:37:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>ill try to get as much of the set as i can. these will be my 9th and 10th shows</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-30 17:55:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>tickets are only like $30 including ticket charges</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-30 21:51:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I almost bought a ticket for bloomington. that would make 3 shows in 4 days for me. but i didn't want to go to bloomington bc i didn't know anyone going. Also funny fact claudio stated last night that faint of hearts is about phone sex. lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-30 21:52:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://coheedandcambria.cinderblock.com/tickets.html states ticket prices fees included ranges from $24.25-$30.17.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-02 00:16:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I worked fast food for a while, you'd be surprised how many people that come in the drive thru and tell you that its to go, or that theyre gonna come inside to pick it up lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-08 09:33:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>its an inward scream, its not hard to do. and i believe mic did do all the inward screams</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-08 09:35:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>got the cover filmed. i'll check the video quality tomorrow, i know audios fine but i had to sneak film, asshole security yelled at me after time consumer(first song)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-08 17:57:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>My videos from Chattanooga are up on youtube.com/cocafan33 . right before time consumer claudio almost got hit by this giant fluorescent light that fell from the ceiling, its in the time consumer video.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-19 01:05:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love wild blue! can't get it in tn where i go to college though :[</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-20 05:35:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>They were selling it on this past tour.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-20 06:13:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've heard of sea dog, and they sell it down the street, might go try some. Haven't heard of the other. I've had Sweetwater's blueberry beer(don't remember the name) tasted more like a blue berry muffin, but it still wasn't that good IMO. of course i haven't found a Sweetwater beer that didn't taste like dirty dish water to me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-26 22:58:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>ah, the ravitch proceedure? im a fellow former pectus excavatum haver i guess. lol. except i had the nuss proceedure done. had it three times unfortunately bc my first surgeon didn't keep up with the proceedure so it failed twice, then he wanted to do the ravitch(massive scar and removing the sternum) but we ended up getting doctor nuss to do my nuss proceedure and it finally worked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-26 23:38:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah maybe thats what it was, i think like they saw through it then break it and put a bar in it? something like that? its been like 6 years since my final nuss proceedure. i got my bar out like 3 years ago now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-26 23:40:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>so many people with pectus on reddit. but your surgery sounds way more intense than mine was, i had the nuss.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-26 23:41:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>this wouldn't happen to be clarksville tn would it? random guess?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-26 23:46:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah sounds about right, I was 15 when i had all my nuss procedures done, they said its usually best to have around puberty but after that the ravitch is usually more successful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-26 23:47:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah, sounds pretty damn painful. how long was the hospital? stay just curious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-26 23:54:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>jeeze now we're coming out of the wood works. but welcome. its funny i never met anyone else who had the condition until i got mine fixed. then i started noticing it everywhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-27 00:11:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>smosh is not funny at all. he's really annoying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-27 00:40:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>best of luck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-27 00:57:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>run</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-27 00:59:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>thought the kool-aid man said "oh yeah"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-27 01:03:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>me three.. lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-27 05:01:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>ah ok, one of my roommates is from clarksville. but we both go to mtsu.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-27 05:03:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha yeah, when i saw people talking about pectus i felt like the forever alone guy when he's screaming "friends" lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-27 17:41:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>ah, thats smart signing up for dissability. when i was told about the ravitch procedure I want to say they said the hospital was either 2 weeks or a month, I don't remember. But I know it would have kept me out of high school for a long time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-27 18:09:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its never to early for chinese leftovers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-27 19:38:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol my bad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-17 05:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>heard about this today while at work, I'm prepping the orion Festival in nashville. Sad to hear it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-20 19:44:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>dude i just checked out your youtube channel...you sing really well man, go for it. If you enjoy music and playing it then go for it man, do what makes you happy, if you get success from it then badass, but if not worst comes to worst you had some fun and maybe made a little of money. Even If you don't make it you never know if your music will impact someones life or at least make their day better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-21 17:16:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>god $50 for pinball.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-08-01 08:26:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>up voted for pei wei! love that place lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-08-03 06:54:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I went to middle school with her lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-08-03 07:11:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>so i opened this because i was at this concert, then heard me yell, then saw who uploaded. evan is this your account? its andrew lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-08-27 17:55:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>when you preorder it pays for both albums i thought? so its clearly not a money grabbing scheme. Claudio did an interview and he said he wanted people to focus more on the content because peoples attention span is so small now that if you give them everything at once they wont pay as much attention to it as a whole. so he broke it up into smaller chunks so you'd pay more attention to it. its a way to keep us excited more. because we get new music two times in a year. its a great idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-08-28 04:13:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>hm good points, i think he's trying to appeal to both. which is a good decision especially since they have dropped their label and are running as a do it yourself band now. But i think he's just giving us time to let the album sink in and us to pick the story appart before giving us another chunk. and personally id rather getting shorter albums more often than an album with 3 more songs but have to wait another 6-8 months longer or something to get.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-08-28 04:38:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah its something that the industry is switching towards. alot of bands are starting to focus more on EP's and put music out more often for their fans. I go to mtsu as a recording industry major, and we talk about this kinda stuff often. But seeing as coheeds history i don't see them just release an EP there wouldn't be enough content to tell the story i don't think. But it'll be interesting to see where it goes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-08-28 18:04:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>obviously didn't increase intelligence points</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-08-29 17:17:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>you sir, have saved me time of doing it myself. Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>who said college kids can't eat well for cheap?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-13 02:46:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-13 02:51:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, I forgot to post. Homemade Beer battered cajun shrimp poboy and homemade onion rings, with a cheap beer. lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-14 21:16:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>where do you live? pabst is one of the cheapest beers everywhere I go, its cheaper than natural light.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-15 05:12:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hm I don't know why it would cost anymore there...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-15 18:46:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh god, I wish I could upvote more than once.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-24 22:31:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>man, this is one of the best interviews, they actually ask him shit that doesn't get covered in every damn interview. thanks for posting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-25 00:14:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>i still thought he was dead?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-30 00:46:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>thought this ended already? i know they gave mic the money.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-14 02:28:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>so happy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-14 02:32:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>looks delicious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My mom likes to hide baked goods in random places</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-14 05:48:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-14 06:04:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>note as a college student on fall break, coming home to find random cakes hidden in the cabinets is awesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-14 15:30:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>nope, no cat. that would make too much sense if she did lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First attempt at Deep Fried Pickles</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-16 04:59:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-17 17:12:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>deep fried pickles are amazing, turned out pretty well, had to fry them longer than I originally expected to get them to come out crispy like they should be though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-18 17:29:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>its clearly Optimus Prime...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-20 08:05:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>correct, was about to add that myself lol. though he calls her barbs alot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-28 21:50:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>it says "GoodsEx" making fun of fed Ex but obviously saying "Good Sex"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-30 16:20:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>guinness beef stew, bangers and mash, Shepherds pie, salmon au gratin. just to name a few</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-04 23:53:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>everyone has different levels of pain tolerance and not every break is the same, a hairline fracture and a compound fracture are both "breaks" but I would imagine feel completely different in terms of amount of pain(never had either personally)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-05 05:52:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>was part of my thinking when i first saw it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-05 21:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>i didn't think we got +1 with this early entry?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-05 22:53:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>i had a girl tell me that i was the kinda guy she wants to marry not date. i was like wtf? makes no sense</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-05 22:55:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>so you have to pay $15 to get someone else in early with you? that sucks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-06 03:46:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>more balls than me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-10 17:57:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still has headset on. friends can't understand a word he's saying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-12 23:02:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>i was about to say more weight and more time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-14 15:27:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't even get my friends to gift me games during the steam sale lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-14 15:36:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>where's the bottom bun? lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-14 16:12:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>all i want is CS source and garry's mod lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-15 02:03:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>wow i didn't realize i got downvoted so bad for that. not expecting anyone to get it for me, its just the game i want at the moment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-15 23:12:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol seananners videos on youtube of garry's mod makes me want it so bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-16 08:01:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>first picture is photoshoped, you can see the lines...was proven a long time ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-18 07:31:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>the inner child in me is extremely jealous</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-19 04:35:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>i would hate trying to use that...im sure im not alone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>any love for pomegranates?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-19 23:40:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-19 23:51:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>the veto system was in place on the earlier halo games, it had random map rotations and would present a map and if the majority voted to veto it would skip that map and you were required to play the next map that follows. now you get three maps to choose from and the highest voted map is the one thats played</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-20 05:47:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>how else do you eat them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-20 06:00:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>sounds like a great way to stain your clothes lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-22 16:22:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually have a professor this semester that lets us use our calculators on our phones lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-23 03:21:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was able to buy Counterstrike today...small win for not having bootcamp</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-25 07:03:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>hate to be that guy, but its mothers OF men</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-25 16:44:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>you have</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-25 17:30:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>just a weave, cut into strips, and then alternate going over and under pieces</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Recorded some of tonights(Dec. 4th) show at marathon music works</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-05 10:33:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here is a link to my youtube account. http://www.youtube.com/cocafan33 some of them are up, the others are uploading now. may take a little(coheed videos are in 720p) the coheed songs i got tonight are: Gravemakers, Everything evil, Afterman, Goodnight Fairlady, Domino</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-05 10:38:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was at this show, i filmed from the front row, videos are uploading to youtube now. http://www.youtube.com/cocafan33 but to answer your question, they are generally good about it for a little. some nights are better than others. you do much better showing up very early for the show, they are more willing to talk to you before the show rather than after especially for more than 5 seconds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-06 05:21:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>youre welcome, i filmed from my iphone for the first time it took really good audio, but the LED par lights really messed with the video quality in my opinion, particularly when the lights were red. so sorry for the video quality not being the best</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-06 22:14:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>wasn't this posted like 2 days ago?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-09 04:06:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>can you talk to my neighbors in my apartment complex? lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-09 22:02:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>trying to make detroit and chicago. not sure yet, 8.5 hours for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-10 01:25:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha thank you, never seen coheed north of indianapolis, so it'd be different at least in that aspect. it would be shows 13 and 14 for me if i come</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-10 02:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha i've seen them 4 times this year alone. but i know people in their 30-40s show range. so i've got nothing on them. if i wasn't in college and paying my own way trust me i'd have been to more myself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-10 05:03:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>guess you didn't notice the MTV 3 plates, lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-10 05:10:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha all good. but yeah....money...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-10 05:22:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>who said there wasn't?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-11 04:47:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>two things I noticed. I'm confused why you're using a capo? the songs in standard tuning, unless you're in a drop tuning and doing this to avoid tuning up. second the second video reminds me of blood red summer, you should learn to play the slow jazz style of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-11 05:59:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TxXitD4NvG0 this version, im not expecting you to sing that high though lol. just the chords and strum pattern fit alot better for an acoustic translation</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-11 21:33:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>upvoted for coheed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-11 21:51:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>always</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-15 05:34:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like those pants were invented so you could shit yourself and no one would know...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-21 07:06:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>its not exact, but its close enough that it made me laugh and want to share with you all</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-23 18:10:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Garry's mod is alot of fun, im still knew to it as well and exploring all the different game mods and figuring shit out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-28 06:50:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>im from louisville and never been there, fuck that place</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-29 07:32:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>you did an awesome job, looks great, glad you got your DSM back on the road!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-12-31 17:50:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>dat smell...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-01-25 20:37:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Doesn't matter who uses it, you can borrow it to get someone else in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-01-26 06:13:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Avoid full sail. I go to mtsu and am a senior in recording, great program. if you know how to record and are proficient at it than getting a degree in it wont help. the industry is about making a name for yourself and who you know. the paper doesn't do anything for you in this field</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-01-27 00:44:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>this is very true, alot of engineers only think that they can get a job in a studio but if you're willing to expand your horizons there is a very vast field of work opportunities</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-01 06:19:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>i'm confused why louisville doesn't connect to nashville and then to birmingham</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-01 06:40:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>reminds me of starfox...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-11 01:01:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>hope you know, most lighting stuff for concerts is programed. coming from an audio engineer that also does lighting work as well. but I'm also glad to see you throwing props out to a guy that most people will never know what he does for a concert or who he is</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-25 21:36:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>i just bought the s2000 yesterday myself, can't wait to take it out. is there really any big difference between the 2k and 3k? not trying to sound ignorant, just my first shotgun i've owned.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-26 06:08:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gotcha, thank you for the info. I'm still excited to take my 2000 out for my first turkey season this year</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-25 14:21:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tn turkey season starts this saturday, can't wait! seen a few toms strutting around in the woods on my friends farm. It'll be my first turkey season though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-25 14:28:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I spent many a restless night watching this infomercial...made me so damn hungry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-25 20:30:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, really my first time hunting ever so i'm pumped about it. can't come soon enough</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-05 01:49:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>go hunting, silence your phone, or if you have a Iphone, set it to do not disturbed, set an exception to your wifes phone, if she calls stop hunting, if not best of luck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Created A Natural Turkey Ground Blind</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-08 18:55:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-08 21:21:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>alright thanks, theres leaves all over the ground near it so it shouldn't be hard to blend it at all. its big enough for me and my roommate to sit in. its dug down about 3 feet probably. so he can do his calls and you can't see his hand movements at all. Also its good because you can move and stretch your legs without making noise or being seen. and having the comfortable back rest helps too! trying it out on saturday for the first time! will let you all know the results.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-10 16:50:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ill just say walmart actually has some good deals on turkey camo shirts, long sleeve shirt was only $8. and its a good camo shirt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-10 18:16:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>"would you kindly"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-16 01:16:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Being a Tn resident, our seasons being going since march 30th, been several times. Got their habits down, getting very close to getting one. It's killing me seeing them, but being slightly out of range. Also hunting on a bluff makes it hard to sneak up on them at times when theyre out of range.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-16 01:22:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm from Louisville actually, but live in Tn for college. You'll need to get a hunting license, and possibly have to take a hunters education class, the best option for a gun that allows you to hunt multiple things would be a shotgun. I'd recommend a 12 gauge, a lot of people will suggest a remmington 870 great guns and reasonably priced. This would equip you to hunt: turkeys, squirrels, rabbits, etc. keep in mind that it would be a good idea to invest in camo/decoys/calls. also look up hunting seasons and what not. http://fw.ky.gov/20132014proposedseasondates.asp</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-16 01:34:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know its illegal to shoot or have an albino deer in your possession in Tennessee(where I live/hunt)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-23 02:22:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alot of people complain that the scope isn't dialed in straight out of the box, and that the bolt is very sticky(but they also say that after you oil it, its fine), and the forestock sling clip breaks off. nothing that would deter me from a cheap gun, i've seen it as low as $350 new.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-23 15:19:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Current MTSU student in the Recording Program, Graduating in May. Glad to see others(and alumni) mentioning it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-23 15:21:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>nice turkey, where was it taken at?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-23 15:28:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>really hard to do with a record label, label usually has the most say in the video</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-23 15:42:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>you do? lol how so?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-25 14:30:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I followed the same path. I'm waiting to decide if I go to the steam box next.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-26 18:57:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>where about in tn are you hunting? i live in murfreesboro, but hunt with my roommate up in Springfield</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-28 01:43:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>sounds like a coyote to me, get a rabbit distress decoy, set it, move away and shoot it when it comes in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-05 04:56:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>MTSU has one of these, just spent my last semester in college in the studio class with this console. love the thing, sounds great and very versatile, and like several people said the bus compressor is pretty awesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Graduated college yesterday, went hunting before hand and got my first ever bird on the next to last day of the season!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-12 21:56:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-13 03:06:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>no haha, I had a 2pm ceremony. had perfect timing to hunt, check it in, drive home, clean it, shower, dress up and got their right on time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-13 03:20:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Story: Went hunting in Robertson county, TN on my roommates families property, usually he goes with me but he was out of town on family vacation. I got into the woods around 430, set up and after about 15 mins I heard some gobbles off to my left at the base of the bluff, decided that they were too far to probably call in. After a few more minutes I heard one on the other side of the gully that I was facing, so I decided to try to work this bird in. After a while with very light calling, the bird had wondered off else where. Around 6:20am, I noticed that it had been very quiet for a while and knew I needed to try something different. There had been some very light rain, and I'd always heard that rain pushes turkeys to the field earlier. So I snuck back up through the woods/hill. As soon as I looked out I saw a Flock(I'm guessing thats what you call a group of turkeys? Please correct me if I'm wrong) about 200-250yards away, so I decided to sneak through the woods to the corner closest that I could that we've seen them enter and exit from. After walking that way some I heard a gobble off in the distance, I had to choose whether or not to try to work that bird in or keep going to the ones I'd seen. I choose to move towards the birds I'd seen. When I finally got to the corner, I glanced out carefully and saw a Jake about 45 yards away, It was walking towards me on its own. The jake was clucking and purring alot too, I heard a gobble off to the left in response to it, so I wanted to wait to see if a bigger bird would come in. After a while and no other bird showing up, the Jake turned around and started walking off. Right before it was out of range I pulled out the box call and clucked twice at him, he turned around and walked right back to me. I took the shot at around 20-25 yards. Had it not been the next to last day of the season, my last chance to hunt, and the first time we had a bird in range, I would have let him go. But it did add to an already memorable day. Bird was taken with a Stoeger STF2000 12 gauge. TL;DR went hunting graduation morning, after a while of no luck, spotted turkeys in the field, moved through woods, got in range of a Jake, took the shot at around 20-25yards. Taken on Stoeger STF2000 12 gauge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-13 05:25:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>my brand!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-14 01:24:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like I've seen this comic at least five times</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-14 18:30:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha gotcha, I must have missed it a few times</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-15 22:27:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>what part of Ky? I'm from Louisville originally, just graduate college in TN and hunt in northern TN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-15 22:28:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe you're still correct on this, or at least as of like December you were when I was with my friend when he bought a new .22 rifle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-18 03:07:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>just curious, whered you find the coheed iphone case? i've tried looking on amazing and ebay but i can't find them anywhere</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-18 03:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>www.ultimate-guitar.com search coheed and cambria. they have great tabs, and chord listings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My Girlfriend even wrote herself a warning note(which she chose to ignore)...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-18 23:03:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-20 15:10:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really hope you're walking out there with more than a bow...especially with cougars. anyways still awesome you got all those on cam</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-20 15:57:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>aren't those poisonous?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-20 16:19:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Glad to hear it, best of luck on your hunts, please update if you do indeed get something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-20 19:21:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>scumbag op</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-25 06:13:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>recipe?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-01 03:18:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>idk if i'd exactly call claudio tall, and last I saw him, he had slimmed down alot. but yeah he's a badass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-05 14:48:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got some video from front row, YouTube.com/cocafan33 . As far as I know the early entrance VIP passes are still good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-06 14:51:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I second these, good earplugs and only like $7 on amazon I think</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-06 16:05:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not all states only allow one bird per season, Tn allows you to take 4 per season</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-12 14:39:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>wouldn't everyone just add their friends to their family list then?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-12 14:57:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha its all good, I wasn't hating on youre response. I just know if it were true and if I got one(which I'm not) I'd be adding all my friends so I could have access to their games.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-12 15:04:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>ten family members added or access to ten games?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-24 16:07:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>very nice bird, have a fall turkey season where you are by chance?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-24 16:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>goodluck, update if you get him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-12 16:36:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>its illegal where I am(TN) but if its not where you are then by all means take the deer when your season rolls around</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-19 03:46:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>James!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-21 18:33:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>came in expecting a compilation of different epic coheed riffs...recieved 2113...did not dissapoint</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-03 01:33:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>MTSU has an SSL Duality and an API vision. but then again we aren't a community college... both were great consoles that I loved getting to use while in school.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-03 01:46:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah, middle tennessee state.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-03 05:24:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>congrats its alot of fun, some long hours but its worth it. oh and RTFM!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-03 05:24:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>always awesome to find more blue raiders on here!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-03 05:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah, i was gonna say that moonshiners is a good show. yeah some of them are very "hilbilly" but moonshining is a huge part of the mountain/southern culture thats been around since prohibition and still exists today.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fall Turkey Season Question(need advice)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-03 20:22:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I'm fairly new to hunting. This being my first full year hunting I was able to get a Jake on the next to last day of spring season (http://i.imgur.com/umPvFOK.jpg) . I just found out yesterday that Tennessee has a fall turkey season(Mid Oct.) and I can take upto 6 birds of either sex. My questions is do turkeys behave differently in the fall than spring? do i need to set up differently, call differently, etc? I will be hunting on my roommates farm, that has both fields and woods. The jake I got was shot in the corner of the field near the woods. Thanks for any helpful advice you all can provide</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-07 05:53:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>you're now obligated to set your text/ring tone to this http://youtu.be/eR-FMK0HuXE?t=1m2s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-08 05:06:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>does anyone else think it looks more cartoonish without the filter? The colors look great and vibrate but they don't look natural to me. Either way I thought the game looked great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-24 17:30:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm in murfreesboro, but hunt my roommates farm up in springfield, i haven't seen boars anywhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not necessarily hunting, but related.Is this a legit document? Have you all heard of this?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-25 02:14:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-02 03:17:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>congrats, today was opening day in Tn as well. but my roommates farm the corn hasnt been cut so it'd be a nightmare to find the doves. hope it gets cut soon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-09 04:27:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>i only live like 30 mins from there, sorry it happened. some people are real asshats :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-26 05:43:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>quit bragging Brian lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-01 05:48:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>the mattskins guy has been trolling r/hunting the last few days. just ignore him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-02 00:57:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>this was awful for me during spring turkey. glasses would fog something awful in the morning. had to force myself to breathe through my nose the whole time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-08 17:32:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>from the thumbnail I thought you turned a refrigerator into a console storage</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-09 06:27:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>was waiting for this post to show up. lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-14 01:13:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>i don't</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-16 20:47:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>it told me 5.7GB lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-16 21:33:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>goodluck, im just excited to play good custom games again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-22 04:51:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>sorry just found your comment, yup 90 gsx.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-24 03:35:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>hope you dont get hurt and need it, i wouldn't ban them. just put them in your pack or something at least.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-24 04:06:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>always good to have some sort of communication.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-24 17:14:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>just curious what phone/app are you using to log gps locations?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-25 08:08:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>let it walk to get bigger, shoot a doe if you're hurting/wanting for meat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-25 21:23:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>:( poor Sam...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-26 16:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man i'm jealous our rifle season doesn't start until Nov. 23rd...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-28 03:48:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>correct</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-29 15:45:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>reporter: are you sorry? guy: yes reporter: why? guy: because I went to jail. what...? he's only sorry because he barely got in trouble, and not because he actually shot at another human, but he talks about if you want to shoot at something go to afghanistan. the guy is crazy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-29 16:32:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>there is... http://i.imgur.com/qsbzQ.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-29 18:04:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>wish i had a bow to be able to hunt with until then :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-30 06:22:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>was my thought exactly, reminded me of the comment you're referring to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-30 06:29:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>your beer looks delicious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-01 20:37:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I grew up watching this in Ky on saturday nights with my dad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-02 05:14:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>congrats! story?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-04 06:59:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've got an 2000 as well. my first year having it, but so far i love the gun. Great budget shotgun in my opinion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-05 07:35:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>how is the hunting in percy priest wma? im in murfreesboro and haven't ever hunted WMA before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-18 05:38:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>ruger american is a good cheap reliable gun, i have one in 30-06 and love it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-20 14:43:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>looks like guy tracked his deer immediately following his shot, found the deer on the ground walked up, kicked at it, it opened its eyes hopped up and tried to gore him before running off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-21 04:30:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>im 30k in the hole and now work at a car dealership lol. trying to get my foot in the door touring though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-21 04:31:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>i graduated from MTSU back in may from the recording program. if you have questions feel free to message and ask</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-21 15:36:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-22 14:52:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha whoops... it happens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-02 01:29:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>i shot a jake(young male) back in the spring, and got decent meat from it, it definitely has a game flavor to it. But I thought it tasted good, and I liked knowing that it wasn't pumped full of steroids and other things to grow bigger.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-02 04:17:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>its a fun game, just needs more players</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-20 02:35:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>"The Tennessee Wildlife Resources Agency (TWRA) decided to reintroduce elk to the state in the late 1990 #8217;s. Part of the agency #8217;s mission is to restore extirpated wildlife when and where it is biologically and sociologically feasible. Beginning in December 2000, the agency began conducting small releases of elk from Elk Island National Park (AL, Canada) into the North Cumberland Wildlife Management Area. There were 201 elk in total that were released over a period of eight years. It is currently estimated that the Tennessee elk herd numbers a little over 300 head strong. With this estimate, in 2009, Tennessee announced their first ever elk hunt in almost 150 years. For more information on Tennessee #8217;s elk hunts visit www.tnelkhunt.org" thats from the TWRA. So they're being stocked. I hunt around middle tn and haven't seen one, but would love to one day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-20 02:42:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>care to share the info to a first year deer hunter that has never shot a deer?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-20 05:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>-_- thats it? I figured there was something more complicated than that...I kinda thought that was a given</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-31 06:12:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Louisville?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-23 04:59:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>came here to say that. haven't had one in forever...it may be time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-24 15:34:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>nice looking deer, what part of tn are you hunting?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-25 06:31:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>gotcha, im in murfreesboro, but hunt up in robertson county. didn't have any luck deer season, saw some doe's but were too far for me to feel comfortable shooting at</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-09 01:33:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're wanting to start on deer, then you're going to have to wait about the rest of the year since deer just ended not long ago. maybe look into turkey hunting in the spring if you have them in your area. outside of that you could move into bird or squirrel when their seasons arrive. just a little food for thought to calm the hunting itch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-13 01:36:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>probably instagram, more than likely used the focus filter that blurs the top third and bottom third</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-13 02:40:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>not sure if the stores right outside the right side of the frame....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-16 05:37:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://brightback.files.wordpress.com/2010/12/380spaceballs.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-16 06:33:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>funnier*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-19 02:54:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work at a honda dealership and we got a 90's model civic that comes in for routine maintenance and has 606,000 miles on the original motor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-19 17:53:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>just do your routine maintenance and oil changes, try to use oem parts as much as possible and you should be good. we see this car at the dealership probably two times a month.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-19 23:45:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>sounds like you all got your moneys worth for sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-28 06:08:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>that 2g</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-28 13:39:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>i've had one 2g, and 2 1g's. love em.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-08 04:23:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>where'd you get the bird at? another fellow middle Tennessean</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-21 05:18:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>too bad its turkey hunting season now...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-26 01:56:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>this pictures been on the internet for years...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Recording electric guitar in an apartment</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-16 23:55:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>So do any of you have experience tracking electric guita in apartment settings where you can't really be loud? Whether it's using an ISO cab or amp modeling software. If you use an isolation can and you built it, can you post any tips for building one or a link to instructions you followed. Or anyone using software which software have you used and thoughts on it? The only amp modeling software I've used was the line 6 pod farm free version and it was terrible in my opinion. Very muddy and had no definition. But I've heard the platinum was much better. I'm not trying to limit to line 6. Just trying to explore options and see what's most feasible and cost effective. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>wma bow hunters</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-03 01:05:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>question for you seasoned guys, this is my first season bow hunting, and first year hunting wma. our season starts mid/late september and just started scouting today, my question is do you guys hunt from the ground or use climbing stands? wanting to hear from people with experience because I don't want to carry in any gear I don't have to. Also any other WMA strategies tips are appreciated. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-05 02:52:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks for the advice, yes it will be whitetail. I went scouting this weekend, and found a good spot, the problem is, is its within a mile from the parking area and im afraid its not far enough in, but its pretty thick woods to get there. i'd actually be worried about how to get it out if i do shoot one. but i found prints from where theyve been walking and its a small clearing with two shooting lanes, and the clearing leads to a field. there is also a river within half a mile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-24 03:15:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a Stoeger 2000 and absolutely love it, gun hasn't had any issues. just oil your gun properly and it should be fine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-15 04:06:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>titans dont have much of a chance after watching them play today anyways...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-16 03:28:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha sorry, i'm a colts fan but i live in tn now, and i'll be at the titans bengals game in cinci next week. I'm hoping you all get better again, i miss the division being competitive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-16 04:12:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>you can buy tickets from people reselling them on stubhub for like $75 -_- assholes...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-05 17:42:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>generally they'll have you fill out an application, and then they run a background check on you, goes much faster if you have a concealed carry license, but plan on waiting upto 30 mins if theyre not busy. generally theres an age limit on buying firearms, i believe rifles and shotguns is 18(at least in the states) and i believe pistols are 21? not sure how much different canada does things from us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-07 09:35:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>nothing some corrective lens can't fix! http://img.gawkerassets.com/img/17ps964hk7brbjpg/original.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-20 20:27:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>PC game, starts out free but is limited, you can buy different licenses and guns to further expand the game. https://www.thehunter.com/landing?src=</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-20 20:44:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>quick to the internet!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-20 20:46:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>hello fellow Middle Tennessean! WMA?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-21 17:39:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>any luck? good to see more fellow Mid Tn out there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-21 18:11:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>My last trip to the percy WMA i didn't see a thing, got in my car to leave drove 20 seconds and saw a buck and a big doe. Sums up my season :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-22 07:11:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>never been out there but goodluck with the rest of the season and stay safe!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-29 02:55:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>its still rifle season in Tn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-29 07:29:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>our rifle runs to january 4th</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-27 13:23:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>12 gauge is the best in terms of being able to hunt multiple animals, based on what choke and shells you use. shoot anything from squirrels, to birds, to deer. There are many great reliable cheap shotguns out there, remington 870 express is pretty popular on here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-13 05:44:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>just curious how do you know theyre recording in nashville, and do you know what studio?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-13 06:03:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>well shit...i live 25 mins from nashville...howd i miss this? lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-13 06:09:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah, i've been slacking on that stuff. still a shame i didn't know about this since i work in the music industry. that seems very opposite of coheed to do, though i think fans would freak and love it at same time. just dont see how that method could be good for sales...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-13 06:23:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>true, i guess when you have artists of that scale word spreads pretty damn quick. the albums have leaked since nwft as far as i know, and probably before that, that was just the first one i saw leaked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-18 16:27:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>graduated in spring '13, loved the program, bust your ass, get involved with production programs such as the tv truck and production services(both will pay you to work for them and you'll learn more real life experience doing so). Network your ass off as well, I know it gets beat to death but this industry is all about who you know and the reputation behind your name. Alot of people that don't make it in the industry either didn't pursue the field enough or didn't have proper contacts from networking. Just remember there are more jobs with audio than sitting in a studio, explore the options, some pretty awesome jobs out there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-03 05:43:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>probably didn't dry the potatoes before frying if they're home made.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-23 22:16:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>this is all I heard in my head watching this, https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4KmKkV3ddAo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-23 22:29:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>looks like they're in Cozumel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-23 03:35:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>good to see other people from murfreesboro. I have to deer hunt out at percy priest wma due to no land myself. no luck yet. good luck this year guys</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-16 01:54:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>that can lead to pushing the deer to a farther distance, or coming across a deer that isn't dead which can end up being dangerous for you. always smart to wait some time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Might have taken the best/luckiest picture on my cell phone I'll ever take last night.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 14:21:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 14:49:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>iPhone SE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 18:37:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's actually not. Complete freak accident that I captured lightning. It hadn't lightninged all night, and this was the first one, was honestly just trying to grab a picture of the cloud</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 18:46:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Correct</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 18:56:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Riding on a bus, probably side of the window</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 19:21:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Taking a picture of the cloud because the lower left side looked like it was glowing blue. Complete freakish luck to catch the first strike of lightning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 22:15:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can confirm, bullshit luck on automatic settings</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 22:23:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Heading there now, train to Hell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 22:26:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone's already posted it there, try at least have me credit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-12 22:30:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Correct. Right outside of Knoxville</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 23:59:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just curious, what's wrong with your American? Me and my buddy both have one and absolutely love them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 20:26:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry to hear that. I've never had any of those issues. Absolutely love mine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-14 07:11:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nailed it. Thanks  #128077; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 18:59:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can of wet food got opened</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 09:22:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve got the Ruger American in 30-06 and love it. My roommate has the same gun chambered in the .273 and loves it as well. Great gun for a budget rifle. I believe they have it in 308 and 270 as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 21:59:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry .243.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 17:35:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you like dim sum(Chinese street food like dumplings and noodle bowls) go to Zoe ma ma. It #8217;s insanely good. I go every time I #8217;m in Denver.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 05:03:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah he did it in Nashville as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>