<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject4719</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-31 14:45:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have no idea how they are still in business. The place smells disgusting, the oil they use tastes disgusting, and their fries taste like fish, probably because they are trying them with the fish. I'm getting sick just thinking about it. Fucking disgusting establishment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-31 14:57:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to have to disagree with you. Quality has gone up lately, their breakfast items are pretty good, chicken doubledilla (with extra chicken omfg, so fucking good), steak cantina, shredded chicken burrito etc. all good stuff. And for very little money. I spend half the money I normally would going to Taco Bell, and I get more food. That's why I keep going back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-07 19:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I forgot to mention I told my parents. I didn't tell them we broke up or anything. I just told them I might be seeing someone, and asked them to not be weird if I bring her over one day. They said "we will talk about it". I told them there is nothing to talk about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-07 20:10:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Except I didn't choose work over her. I was in a tight position. I had no choice. But even then I tried super hard to come over even for just a half hour or 45min</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-07 20:18:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea. I was just blind sighted because she promised me 6 months. Earlier that week I was trying my hardest to tell them. But trying isn't succeeding...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-07 21:37:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>The problem wasn't the fact that she went out with friends. I had no problem with that. The problem was that night we had pre made plans to see each other. She rejected my phone calls. She couldn't answer the phone for 5 minutes to talk to me and tell me what's going on? I don't feel like that's asking much. I always call her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-07 22:04:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>US</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-07 22:05:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some pretty solid advice in there. I'll keep all of that in mind tonight. Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-08 00:42:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't mean it like that... I meant it like I had my arm around her, I moved my arm to let her up. The wording was just weird. I don't view women like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-25 14:16:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Leave. Call your dad and tell him you can't do this anymore. Tell him you want to be transferred to another high school local to him. Tell him you're at the end of your rope living with her. And ask him if it's possible to see a therapist if it isn't too much of a financial burden to him. Tell him you've been holding on to these feelings since you were a child and you feel like suicidal thoughts have entered your head. Be honest with him. As far as college, you can get fasfa, they will give you a long term loan for the whole thing. Go to college, get on with your life. You'll love college. A whole new outlook.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-28 09:57:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Get the windows tinted to the legal limit, and get a sun deflector for the windshield. No one can see in, and you'll be able to see out. Should help keep the sunlight out too. Keep things a little cooler inside</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-04 00:27:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>A disk best best served via a CD/DVD Rom</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-07 16:39:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work at a small car dealership. I get asked very very stupid questions all of the time. Example: I'll list up a car online for $200 with a bad engine. I'll put "BAD ENGINE" all over the ad and title. Got at least 6-8 phone calls going something like this "Hey do you still have the Acura?" Yes I do. "Good, how's it run?" .... Or I'll get asked "Price looks fair, any issues with the car?" Oh yea, it drives great. Minus the fact that the engine shot a rod out of the side of the block. Every damn time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-08 20:26:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hope you are having a fantastic day today!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-16 05:21:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are over thinking this. He gave you a verbal warning to slow down. You won't get a ticket</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-18 01:02:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was recently cheated on myself. Worst feeling in the world. You were already pretty before, but just gorgeous now! Your ex definitely made a mistake. I'd date you so hard haha. Hope you find someone who treats you right!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Man gets ticket for broken windshield.. in parking lot of windshield shop</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-19 22:23:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Man gets pulled over and ticketed for broken windshield... in the parking lot of Auto Glass repair shop</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-19 23:09:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-24 18:16:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very simple. Create a new phone number, but leave your old line open. Put the SIM card in your closet. Then when she keeps on faking messages, document everything. Go to the police and tell them you would like to press charges. You now have proof that she tried to fake messages that aren't real. Because you got a new number and didn't tell her. Call your cell phone provider and get documented records for proof as well that you stopped using the other line. Make sure you also file for a restraining order.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-27 12:20:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hear cooking meth is all the rage now with the youngins!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-01 00:40:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate it say it man. Something's up. Could be anything. Did you do anything to make her mad? How long have you guys been dating?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-01 13:28:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yuuuup.. time to move on. She's wasting your time. Sorry man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 14:11:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fast and Furious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 14:18:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would quietly get a DNA test done. Don't do anything crazy until you have the facts. Keep us posted. Hope you get some answers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 15:01:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have the technology</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-15 18:44:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just curious, why did you still make him wear a condom even though you had your tubes tied? I was under the impression that it's no longer possible to get pregnant with the operation finished</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-24 07:38:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now I'm l no expert, but why don't YOU try to run the idea by the lady mentioned and see how she reacts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 21:56:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fantastic. Now they need to come up with a drug to stop and possibly reverse hair loss and we would be golden!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 14:58:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lawyer up. Them searching the car illegally is one thing, them damaging your property adds fuel to a fat payday fire.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 16:11:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>More than likely what they did is tear your car apart looking for drugs and whatnot. That includes opening your hood and gas tank. I'm no lawyer, but if you didn't consent and they had no warrant it seems pretty cut and dry to me. I'd talk to a real lawyer though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>EPA: Fiat Chrysler software enabled emissions cheating</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 06:09:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 05:48:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually for best results I've found over the counter rubbing alcohol to be the most effective. I have these little bastards show up and make nests all summer on my lot. I fill up a squirt bottle of alcohol and go ham. They die in about 2-5 seconds upon spray</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-21 15:23:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>K</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-22 15:53:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Run. Run as fast as you can away from this guy. I can smell the bullshit all the way from here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 07:26:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry you've gone through so much. But you have Stockholm syndrome. Do you really want to marry this person and spend the rest of your life feeling like this? I think you need to find someone who really appreciates what you have to offer. This relationship is toxic. Get out while you still can. Move back home. Start over.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 16:24:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need to get out now. Tell her you're going to visit your parents. If you need to ask them to help you financially. Once you put some distance between the two of you, you'll be able to recharge. Make that final phone call telling her you've had enough. Once you rip off this bandaid you'll feel... free.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 16:36:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Car dealer here, when we submit a deal to the bank, the bank will automatically put the person with strong credit as the main buyer. That's just how they do it. Here's the good news though. Since it's been 4 years since the car has been purchased, and she hasn't missed any payments, you can have the car refinanced to have your wife removed from the loan! Chances are the interest rate might go down too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 17:06:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Car dealer here, don't buy a Dart. Absolute trash of a car. Same goes for the Chevy Cruze, and Ford Focus. Reliability/fuel economy wise, I recommend the Honda Fit/Civic, Toyota Corolla, Hyundai Elantra (no don't even think about a Hyundai Accent), Kia Forte, Nissan Sentra, Mazda 3 etc. You're better off buying one of those (even if it's older than a 2014) than buying a Dart. They do not last. They fall apart</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 14:55:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I'm so sorry, I got drunk with a few friends at a party, and they thought it would be really funny to send these inappropriate images to several of my contacts to get a reaction while I wasn't looking"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Iraqi parents were so happy for their son to get American medical care that they named their son Trump. Then Trump revoked their visas.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-04 22:24:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-04 22:37:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll take "Alt-Right" for $500, Alex.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-04 22:58:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm honestly kind of impressed. Criminal of the year?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-05 08:34:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what a pawn shop does... they pay the bare minimum. If you had something valuable you should've sold it on eBay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-11 01:38:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>First of all, I don't think that's legal. Second of all, distance yourself? Wtf? She's your girlfriend dude. You're supposed to look out for her best interests. Talk her out of it, this is smelling like bullshit all the way from here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 06:09:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is toxic man. I think you need to sit down and have a conversation with her. I understand jealously but this is overboard. You need to tell her that she needs to trust you. If there is no trust this relationship will go nowhere and you'll both be miserable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 23:46:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>It means your dumbass should've held on tight to that ring lmfao. Chill man. You love each other, get another ring.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 20:49:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You'll have to rent a car. You'll spend roughly $1500 for the month to rent a car, but hopefully by the end of the month you can purchase something, or put a down payment on something and finance. Considering you've had no income for 5 months you'll have a hard time getting a loan right now. That or look for a buy here pay here and get the cheapest vehicle they offer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>CNN banned from White House press briefing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-24 20:51:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-24 22:24:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>My first gold! Thanks stranger!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 00:01:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm having the same issue! The system I have here is a Ryzen 1700 with MSI B350 Tomahawk motherboard, 16gb of Gskill 3000mhz ram running at default 2133mhz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 20:50:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>This website really hurt my eyes trying to read. But good info, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 16:19:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>What card do you have? I didn't OC my RX 480 up until a few days ago, but I'm stable at 1405mhz core and 2215mhz memory clocks. Doesn't go above 68c, air cooled</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Israelis hold teen over US Jewish Community bomb threats</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 14:47:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 17:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The 290x is basically on par with the RX 480 in performance anyway, just the RX 480 uses less power/runs cooler. I wouldn't upgrade either lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 05:26:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's fucked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 14:49:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's cool n all, but AMD already announced their 32 core chip. Bit late to the party Intel, should've dropped this a while ago</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 15:03:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't say that, AMD has Demo'd the chip by simulating some server workloads, and even turned off 10 cores to match Intel's current top of the line 22 core chip. Results were very good. https://youtu.be/ZtYTPcshyA0</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 21:47:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely unneeded. I'd be fucking livid of that was my child.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 21:17:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://i.imgur.com/Pv48jrg.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 21:41:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why only 1350 though? Crack that bad boy up!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 22:56:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is due to SMT, the usage isn't accurate. But with further optimization it would perform better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 22:57:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems to be performing between the i3/Pentium and the i5 from these tests. But this is also the 1400, which has half the cache of the 1500x Quad Core. Would be interesting to see that unit paired with good ram. I was hoping it would perform a little better than this though given the price</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 23:18:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I took mine up to 1400 core and 2200 on the memory off the bat, instantly stable without further tweaking or voltage</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-04 04:36:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll agree with that, but most of the testing it looks like it's sitting between the dual and quad core Intel chips in gaming performance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 07:59:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Might be a dead CPU or Ram. No post on 2 motherboards? Yea it's going to be one of those two</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 16:27:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>2500k reporting in. 4.5ghz on air stable as a rock. So far gaming wise I'm getting similar fps in games to my friends stock clock 1700. It still holds up honestly. Both of us have an RX480. But it seems like the RX480 is the limit for this CPU. At stock clock speeds the 480 wasn't even close to 100% utilization in most of my games. With the overclock it is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 23:39:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it would be a perfect match. My 2500k at stock speeds with my RX480 was a bit of a bottleneck, but not over the top. 470 would probably be perfect. I'd hop on it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 16:24:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd probably recommend the 1600, then use the extra money on a better GPU.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 16:24:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, I'd hold out another year for next gen Ryzen. The CPU is good enough for gaming. Hell I'm still teething away at my 2500k @4.5ghz lol. Works well enough for now. I'm going to wait for next year's Ryzen before upgrading. Giving time for the platform to mature. Get some of those higher clocked</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 19:36:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I disagree. I'd rather have the 4GB RX480. I have yet to run into a game that uses more than 3gbish at max settings @1080p. It's way better to have the stronger GPU than the weaker one with lower frames, there's no point to that video memory on such a weak card imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 15:31:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's an issue with the Nvidia driver. As far as a fix, I don't have much advice unfortunately</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 02:59:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're probably the only person on the planet to ever say that. I've never had a single issue with Newegg.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 03:02:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you able to overclock your Xeon? I personally think you'd be better off with a video card upgrade, I'm not sure you'd gain much. Or at least wait till next year for next gen Ryzen/new video cards to arrive and just upgrade the whole system. Your current setup really isn't that bad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 03:04:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>In for info</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 13:58:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like a motherboard fault, consider warranting it out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 14:02:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>In your situation, I would go used. You can find an older 7970 for roughly the price of a 460, and it will perform very very well. Trades blows with the much more powerful RX 470 in terms of performance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 06:54:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pm'd</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 00:32:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>pm'd</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 00:47:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>PM'd</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[USA-MI] [H] Paypal [W] Looking for an Intel i7 2600k</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 04:08:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looking for a 2600k to upgrade my 2500k, pm me if you have one! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 04:45:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea I messaged him but he hasn't gotten back with me yet lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 05:37:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 05:40:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>How much?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 15:25:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Doesn't seem to be worth the money, they run hotter, don't OC as high, and the performance difference is like 5ish% for the price of a brand new AMD Ryzen 6 core. I'm not sure why people are selling them for so much money :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 15:30:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate the offer, but it's a bit rich for me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[USA-IN][H] XFX 290X/Intel 2500k CPU [W] PayPal</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 04:41:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Selling an AMD 290X, unfortunately the card does not work, the fans spin up, but just has a black screen. $85 shipped, or $70 local pickup Also have a 2500k that I've had since late 2011, works perfect! Ran at stock speeds all of it's life until about 3 months ago, when I got a nice air cooler and bumped it up to 4.5ghz with only +.1 voltage. Runs around 65c under load with this setup, never had a problem! - $80 shipped! Also the 2500k will stay in my system until it's sold! https://imgur.com/gallery/SBKSO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 05:01:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last time I tested it, just got no output whatsoever. Seems like it spins the fans and everything just fine though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 06:00:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait, 2nd gen Ryzen already? I thought this was going to be based off of the current ryzen, I didn't know they were already gearing up for the 2nd gen!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 14:45:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfortunately these are 1155 chips, Intel doesn't support backwards compatibility on anything haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-13 05:18:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>8gb. /Thread</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-13 22:40:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've already purchased a CPU, thanks though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 20:53:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, an RX 580 really isn't enough for 144hz at 1440p. A 1070 might do it in certain games, but really even a 1080Ti would struggle to do 144hz at 1440p depending on the game. Most games it could do it, I guess what I'm saying is, don't expect any sort of budget graphics card to be able to handle that sort of workload.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 21:25:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea exactly. 144hz is extremely difficult with even top of the line hardware like that. An RX 580 won't cut it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[USA-MI] [H] Paypal [W] Looking for an Intel i7 2600k</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 01:51:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looking for a 2600k to purchase! Message me if you have one! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 16:50:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>eBay is overpriced due to eBay fees.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-19 05:47:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where were you like 4 hours ago when I was buying one lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 05:29:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you should wait another year for Zen 2, the 6950x is a pretty great chip already! Wanna trade my 2500k for it? ;) haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 05:38:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why not just under clock/undervolt your current chip? Maybe even disable cores?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-21 07:16:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Might as well buy a Pentium g4560/Core i3 and overclock the ever living piss out of it honestly. High clocked dual core Intel chip will serve you better, I've seen those i3's get 5.0ghz+, that's where they will shine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-21 16:10:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea the overclock was meant more for the i3 chip. lol I feel like I have solid advice and yet I got downvoted to hell. Overclocked i3 will break 200 single core cinebench score, it will perform extremely well on unoptimized games</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-21 16:33:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not for the games OP plans on playing, for example: World of Warcraft. That game hardly uses 1-2 threads. Thanks to the engine those types of unoptimized games use, they would highly benefit frames wise from a highly clocked i3 vs locked i5. Could be as much as 20+fps difference. Focusing strictly on the games OP plays I can't recommend the i5 not Ryzen unfortunately</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-21 18:10:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's right around 1500-1550</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 16:36:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a used car salesmen, I take offense to that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 22:48:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really really hope this isn't the new iPhone design. It looks so bad. I might actually skip this one if this is the case. I feel like the peak of Apple's design was the iPhone 4/4S. I wish they would bring that design language back. But for the love of god do not put the home button/fingerprint scanner on the back. Steve Jobs is rolling in his grave</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 22:52:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>How is it not a good idea? Ryzen offers amazing performance per watt. at 2.5ghz a Ryzen 8 core CPU uses as much power as a 7th gen i7 for laptops. With 8 cores/16 threads vs 4 cores. Imagine the possibilities for a 4/6 core APU powerhouse with amazing battery life. Or a Mac pro/iMac with the upcoming Threadripper 16 core/32 thread CPU. The performance would be outstanding on a Mac, and with low heat/powerdraw</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 22:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would take it apart, order some very good thermal paste, clean the CPU/GPU with alcohol and apply a generous amount. Clean the fans with some air, and reinstall. Download an application called SMCfancontrol, and you can manually adjust the fan using this application. You should see several degrees get shaved off doing all of this, bringing new life into your old air!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 23:59:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>1100rpm is very low, it won't be audible. Nothing to be concerned about</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 15:59:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>My 7 Plus used to work well when it was new, now it takes several attempts, 50/50 shot on whether it reads or I have to type in my password. Kind of annoying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 20:40:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just to rule out an overclock issue, have you tried saving your profile and then reverting back to stock clocks?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 20:53:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the best all around chip would be the Ryzen 1700, it games well, and it is a hell of a multi tasker. If you plan on doing STRICTLY gaming, and nothing else, the 7700k would a good choice. Some people are going to tell you to wait, I think that's just a waste of time. There will always be better hardware that's going to come in the future, there's no way to stop that. If you want to play it safe, the Ryzen would be the way to go because it's a brand new platform. The AM4 will continue to get new CPU's over the coming years, where as the 7700k is the last chip in that platform. There is no upgrading from a 7700k in the future after purchasing it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 16:20:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you'd be better off waiting for zen 2 honestly. Would you gain some multitasking performance? Absolutely. But is it worth the money to jump ship right this second? Nope. Wait for the next gen!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 16:35:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Consider just buying one from /r/hardwareswap Honestly it's hard to find a reasonable price at a retailer, but you can still get a good deal from that aubreddit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 04:50:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea, you'll see a huge boost in performance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 15:38:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>It won't be though unfortunately</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 15:39:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>More than likely it will be $3500-$4000 price tag</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 16:06:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>In real world testing it's roughly on par with a 5960x, last gen's 8 core chip. But really the 5960x can overclock like hell, it pulls into the lead. Not trying to knock down on the Ryzen, it's performing very well especially for the money, can't complain!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 02:32:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.ibuypower.com/Site/LandingPage/AMD-Ryzen Also http://www.geforce.com/whats-new/articles/nvidia-geforce-gtx-battlebox-ultimate-essential-pcs?ref=indiekings.com</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 13:27:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>That will be stable, I think it's wreckless to hammer it overnight. You did a near half hour test, you're good to go</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 06:16:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since they obviously can't focus on making a single powerful GPU, they need to quickly figure out how to use infinity fabric with 2 GPU dies coupled with HBM.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 06:20:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>It sounds like a potential ram issue, I had a similar problem with my Intel system a few years back, and it ended up being the ram. Got a different brand, and everything worked perfect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 06:27:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, the best bargain right now is to buy a used 480. The performance difference is minimal between the 580 and 480, and you can pickup a used 480 around 175 in /r/hardwareswap</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 06:44:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>They won't, want to know why? They don't want that CPU to last forever. They are putting an artificial death sentence on these chips so that you go buy the latest and greatest. They are not about quality, they are about quantity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Have an older i7 and thinking about upgrading in the near future to another Intel quad core? Don't.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 07:07:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is just a bit of a rambling post, but I have a 2600k i7 system. I thought at first maybe I was missing out on newer 6700k/7700k gaming and multithreading performance. Turns out, I wasn't missing on much at all. Using a $20 newegg cooler, and hopping into bios, I was able to easily overclock the CPU to 4.9ghz... on air. I dropped it to 4.8ghz for temps and long term usage stability. Max temp on 4.8ghz is 76c(average across all 4 core). Cinebench score: 870 Multithreaded, 170 Single thread (For Comparison, google search reveals a 6700k gets around 185 Single core, and 890 multithreaded at stock speeds). Gaming performance is perfect. I'm not sure if this is a testament to how good Sandy Bridge is, or just how many years Intel has been yanking our chain and slowing to a crawl on CPU development. But either way, if you're thinking about upgrading, you might want to just do what I did. Breath a bit of new life in your old system. If you have an 1155 board but don't have a 2600k, you can easily pickup a 2600k for 100 bucks used and you're good to go. So much cheaper than buying a new board/CPU! That way we can see what Coffee Lake/Zen 2 have in store for us next year without throwing money away! Those are the real upgrade honestly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 08:04:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly the Ryzen 1600 is the better buy vs an i5. Gaming performance is near identical, and multitasking is miles ahead of the i5, with less power consumption. It's the king of price/performance right now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 08:10:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depends on your needs of course, but there are Ryzen 8 core laptops in the pipeline getting dropped soon, I'm sure the 6 and 4 core will follow shortly thereafter</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 14:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not without its kinks. It's being held back when it comes to he the memory department, which Ryzen really relies on due to infinity fabric. This upcoming AGESA update seems to really fix a lot of stuff though, a few people snagged the beta bios and are running 3600mhz clocks with tight timings, and they claim up to 4000mhz will start working. At 3600 it Puts it in the running with skylake/many lake i7 level gaming performance. It's getting there! I think they just releasesed it a bit early before they ironed out these bioses honestly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 15:49:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I remember correctly my dynamic Vcore is set to .250+. Unfortunately I have one of those motherboards that uses dynamic Vcore instead of just showing me the voltage lol. I'll check later in CPUID what the voltage is when I get home for you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 16:55:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had a 2500k, went to a 2600k. The difference was pretty drastic, I was able to clock higher and the hyperthreading/extra cache really helped. But even with that 2500k at 4.5ghz, none of those benchmarks showed unplayable performance. If you turned off that frame counter you probably wouldn't even notice (unless you had a 144hz display of course. It's worth waiting for the next gen!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 16:59:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It reads 1.39 volts using Core Temp in Windows under 100% load</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 17:50:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's exactly the point I was trying to make. And you can do what I did, crank the clocks the hell up to hold you over until the good stuff comes. AMD and Intel are really going to give us some excellent products in the near future!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 22:27:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's safe to assume that was a typo, but anything is possible. Doesn't discount the claim of ANY single GPU, so about doesn't make sense</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 22:54:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes and Yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-01 22:17:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly yes. Just keep using it, the 3930k is still a good chip, wait for next generation AMD/Intel. Or jump ship to the upcoming threadripper CPU if you do intensive tasks, it looks like a real beast from what I've seen so far!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-01 22:18:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those 920's are beasts! I'd just slap a new cooler on it and bump it up to 4-4.2ghz, you have a lot of room there on that chip!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-01 22:24:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>The title seems a little overexcited lol. Intel's brand new 10 core CPU barely beat AMD's 8 core CPU in cinebench with roughly the same clocks. Am I the only one that expected more from Intel's new lineup in terms of performance?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 14:10:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've gotten my friend's tomahawk to OC the 1700 to 3.9ghs on air stable no issues</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 14:20:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The vrms are designed to handle it, it will do 5 years just fine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 19:29:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's Intel. They will kill 1151, they will have a new socket for coffee lake, I guarantee it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[USA-IN][H] PayPal [W] Wanting to buy GTX 1080!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 23:53:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looking for a 1080! (Just standard non-Ti model) Please message me if you have one! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 23:55:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will pm you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 02:30:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea if you like the 1070, a 980ti will get you 98% of the performance for a hair less money. It's not a bad option for you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 14:27:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am PayPal ready with $400 shipped! I live in Indiana!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 16:17:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>They sped up Coffee Lake due to ryzen being so competitive, it wasn't supposed to come out so early. 6 months doesn't mean anything to Intel. They will more than likely have a new chipset/socket</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 21:26:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm PayPal ready, I want that 1080. Message me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 01:43:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll take the Premium Pack version, I'm Paypal ready! Message me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-05 18:28:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>It more than likely won't. Coffee Lake is rumored to get delayed into 2018 as well, and the only CHANCE of getting 40 PCI lanes is maybe the next enthusiast platform. Which won't be until later 2018. If you need more PCI lanes just get Threadripper</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 02:33:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm trying to get a deal, I'm not paying $370 for a 1070</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do we know if the new Forza 7 will be cross platform compatible on multiplayer?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 18:30:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't seem to find an answer on google, I am a PC gamer and a majority of my friends have Xbox. I know Horizon 3 was cross platform which is awesome, but will Forza 7 have the same treatment?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 21:09:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's fantastic! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 22:51:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was in a similar boat recently, I was tempted by the 3770k. I had a 2500k before. Instead I bought a 2600k and overclocked the everliving piss out of it lol. 4.9ghz on air. 3770k's run too hot and will tap out at 4.4ghz after a ton of research. Cinebench results were on par with stock clocked skylake chips. Pretty happy with the results. I'm doing this to hold myself over for Ryzen 2 next year</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-13 00:11:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's no difference between the two besides stock clocks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-13 03:14:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Should be alright honestly, I'm using a $20 Newegg deepcool cooler. Nothing fancy, I just set the fan to 100% all the time. Doesn't go much over 75c on load</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-20 12:57:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're thinking about this too much. No one is going to care about the name of whether it's "Unprofessional". They care about performance. They care about power consumption. And the Opteron name carries a certain weight with it, it's a good thing they moved away from it. They want to differentiate the old from the new much much improved product line.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-29 15:09:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's crazy is how well the 7970 aged. It smokes the 680 in almost any game now a days thanks to finewine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 01:38:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read somewhere the theoretical Infinity fabric "1:1" so to speak is around 4200mhz. Meaning that's the wall where performance gains stop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 06:39:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol you don't think so? Then explain the panic announcement of the 18 core Skylake X chip after they were only planning on releasing a 12 core chip. Explain to me how competition from AMD didn't cause that either. If it were up to Intel, they would continue selling "high end" quad core chips at insane prices because the profit margins are so high</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 06:43:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly the gains from that CPU to a newer 7th gen aren't THAT huge. If you want to squeeze a bit more performance out of it, delid it, and overclock it to 5ghz. Your temps will be much lower and you'll get a nice boost in speed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 06:45:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually am going to recommend the opposite of this. The 6950x is a proven platform. It's matured, all of the bugs and kinks have already been worked out over the years it's been on the market. Stick with that for a rock solid performer with no issues. The new x299 platform will have bugs and kinks that need ironed out, some reviewers on YouTube have already found a couple in their short time of testing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 06:26:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will never understand this fanboy mentality. Why would you hope AMD sinks to bankruptcy? So you can keep buying a GTX 10XX card for the next 20 years? Without AMD, you don't get new substantially better Nvidia products. Period. AMD might not have a multi billion dollar budget Nvidia has, but they are doing a damn good job at trying to stay competitive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 06:31:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>980Ti is a hair slower than the 1070, sooo yeaaaa. Stick with the 1080. I did the same thing, I sold my RX480 and upgraded to a 1080. Big jump in performance for sure. Only thing I miss is AMD's software. Honestly it was better than Nvidias. But hey, double the horsepower, can't complain!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 14:40:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a 2600k @ 4.9ghz on air. Your locked 3770 is going to bottleneck the card, you need a CPU upgrade to fully take advantage of the card. My recommendation would be to sell the 3770 and buy a 2600k and overclock the heck out of it like I did</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 14:48:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>At this point it's all been worked out, x99 is now "Bulletproof". Unfortunately the same can't be said about x299 just yet. Intel seems to have rushed board makers into a half baked product, these boards have flaws that a software update can't fix. Overheating VRMs for example. It might be another year or so before we have a solid problem free board to choose from for x299. It happens sometimes with launches, Ryzen had some hiccups as well, but luckily it was fixed with some bios updates shortly thereafter</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 14:50:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely. To maximize performance try to get 3600mhz Samsung B-die ram and do a little overclocking. It will breeze through games no issue</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 14:54:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some people reported switching between high performance and balanced power plans yielded extreme results. You can give it a shot and see if it helps any</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 15:02:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea honestly the RX 480 was being bottlenecked believe it or not. (2600k and 3770 had virtually no difference in performance at stock clocks). When I OC'd my CPU with my RX480 I had quite a jump in performance. If you can swing it try to get 3200mhz, ram helps gaming in Ryzen. If not 3000mhz will still perform well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 15:29:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I usually play Rainbow Six Siege, I went from 80-90 fps to 110-160fps(averaged around 130) after the overclock. It was a pretty substantial jump for me at least in that game from base CPU clocks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 15:49:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I play using everything maxed lol. With temporal filtering. Which might explain my hovering around Gold 3-4/Silver 1 rank</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 15:50:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>With the 1080 I'm getting anywhere from 160-260fps, depending which map/area I'm in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 16:14:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, if you want to save a little money and hold out for next revision Ryzen like I'm doing, upgrading to a 2600k is not a bad option, they are going for around $100 on eBay/Hardwareswap subreddit. I got a cheap $20 Deepcool cooler from Newegg and bam. There ya go. 3770k's are too expensive and don't overclock as high due to heat. Sandy Bridge is a hell of an architecture haha. This is what I did to hold me over until next year once Zen+ hits the market</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 03:19:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Considering a 3.6ghz Ryzen 8 core chip is about 28,000 this makes no sense</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-09 07:20:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, I have a 2600k and a GTX 1080 Seahawk lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-09 07:24:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>1607! If I win I would love to put this in a guest gaming machine!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 13:24:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just curious, where are people buying G4560s for $66? Newegg it's still over $100</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 13:41:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would guesstimate and say maybe 2 more weeks before preorders are up. So not too much longer!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 13:43:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>While I'm hopeful that Zen2 will clock higher, it more than likely won't hit 5ghz. Mid 4ghz could be possible though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 03:04:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would overclock that puppy. I have a 2600k @4.9ghz on air. It is enough to power my GTX 1080 without many issues. I used to have a 2500k and I considered a 3770k, until I found out they have thermal issues. They use Intel's favorite toothpaste under the heat-spreader, so I purchased a 2600k for $100 and sold my 2500k for $70. The 2600k's are better overclockers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 03:08:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's been reviewers that overclocked the 7900x to high clocks as you mentioned, but it only lasts for a single bench run. Any steady usage shows thermal throttling kicking in and holding the chip back to a weak 3.8ghz. It just runs too damn hot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 14:44:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure I'll do it when I get home. I did run cinebench before, I was almost 800multithread score if I remember correctly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 14:47:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're honestly better off with a Ryzen setup. Money and cost wise. Ryzen 7, or wait 2 more weeks for the Threadripper launch to have the highest end chips at your disposal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 14:55:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. The real excuse is cost. Intel wants more margins, and it simply costs a lot more to solder a CPU than to smear the cheapest chinapaste they can get their hands on under the heatspreader. Oh, and also planned obsolescence. If the chip runs hotter, it is more likely to fail over the coming years, so you eventually buy a brand new one. I've seen more chips fail in the 3000+ series chips than I have Sandy Bridge and older. Which were soldered. My old 2600k is still kickin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 15:01:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>If your board can overclock, I'd actually recommend the 2600k. Cheaper, IPC is almost the same, but it overclocks sooooo much higher. I'm on 4.9ghz on air</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 15:12:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand what you mean, but if what you're saying is true you won't like Skylake X. While you CAN overclock to 4.5ghz, it doesn't stick. This new platform runs so hot, even with excellent water cooling the clock drops down to 3.8ghz due to thermal throttling on the chip. And it doesn't help that the VRM's on the motherboard get really hot. And since you do heavy workloads, short several second bursts of 4.5ghz isn't helping you in the long run unfortunately, I imagine whatever workload you are doing will be 30min+. In this case Threadripper will actually have better single core performance at a smooth stable 4ghz. So you really have 2 options here. A. Go back to a broadwell E system, or B. 16 core 4ghz Threadripper. The new TR4 platform is a better option because it will keep getting new CPUs for the next 4 years, so you can always upgrade whenever you want more</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 17:25:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure. But consider this. A used 3770k sells for $175 on average, maybe a couple extra with shipping. Then a $30 delid fix. It won't be much faster than an overclocked 2600k, if any. Biggest difference is power draw, 2600k is a little more power hungry due to being 32nm. Used 2600k? $100 bill. Lookup benchmarks between the two. If clocked the same, the 3770k doesn't pull ahead anywhere. MAYBE a couple %, nothing significant</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 23:54:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh wow, that's crazy. You're right. Even the 3770k went up too, over $200 now on eBay. Even then though you're saving $50 on the CPU + $30 delid. You could put that extra $30 towards a water cooling setup and push out 5.2ghz+ and still have low temps</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 00:11:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's only a matter of weeks in my opinion before A. Reasonably priced new RX 580's hit the shelves, and/or B. Used market floods with used 480's/580's. Which would be a decent little upgrade compared to what you have now. I'd sit tight and watch the market burn lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 00:14:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why not? Memory is really the biggest hinderance to Ryzen, shouldn't be too much of a surprise honestly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 00:20:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe the lowest end will be 12 cores. It will be $799</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 03:05:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I ran it. I apologize my clock is actually 4.8ghz, not 4.9 as I previously said. But I got a 645 Multi Core score, 425 Quad Core, and 127 Single Core score. I'm not sure how good these are compared to other CPU's haha Edit: I'm going to bump it up temporarily to 5ghz to see what happens. I don't have a water cooler so I can't do this for long periods of time, but I'm hopeful that I can sneak in a quick bench before it melts hahahaha Results @ 5ghz: 670 Multi, 453 Quad, 133 Single! This is pretty much stock clock 7700k territory isn't it? I'm really impressed with this old thing. At 5ghz on my cheap $20 cooler it hit 89c, soooo it got pretty warm. If I had a good watercooling setup I could probably squeeze a few hundred more MHz out of this thing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 15:58:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know what's funny? Xbox One is running Windows 10 under the hood. A modified/skinned Windows 10, but Windows 10 nonetheless</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 16:02:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Threaten Newegg with social media. Reddit, YouTube, Facebook, google reviews, yelp. Tell them you will effectively go after their reputation for this $300.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 19:45:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Turbo was disabled, just stuck it at 5ghz and cranked the CPU fan to 100% and hoped for the best haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 18:36:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Clock for clock, Ryzen is basically the same as any Intel chip. The part where Intel pulls ahead is overclocking. Hence why 7700k's @5ghz are getting better frame rates in gaming vs 4ghz Ryzen chips. But if you clicked both at 4ghz, they are identical for the most part. But I am suspecting anything over the 10 core Skylake chips are going to struggle to overclock. Hence the lower baseclocks. Ryzen is pretty linear, we know it will get to 4.0-4.1ghz and stop. Regardless of core count, but we can't say the same for sure about Skylake X. At least higher core count models.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 15:18:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/ayymd is that way ----- gt;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 19:34:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Calling fake on this one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 19:35:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol what?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 21:37:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup. Nothing adds up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 06:53:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think in theory infinity fabric reaches 1:1 around 4200mhz, so probably not. We should still keep getting gains the higher we are able to go. Granted there's a limitation to the memory controller, it can only be pushed so far</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 07:15:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Steve from Hardware Unboxed is NOT bias. He's probably the most thorough tech tuber out there. It's likely he could've received bad or faulty hardware.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 15:18:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a few places that don't let you pump your own gas funny enough</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 18:38:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who says their service doesn't meet Intel's? I've had a friend RMA a CPU in the past with AMD, he had a replacement within days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 18:40:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Coffee lake won't be using the same motherboard anyway. Regardless you'd be buying a new board. At least we know for a fact AMD's AM4 boards will keep supporting new CPUs for at least 4+ years</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 18:44:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Simple answer? No.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 05:16:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not according to last week's leaked info saying otherwise</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 05:19:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's kind of to be expected though, any CPU release is limited in terms of supplies. Including consumer chips. Look at the new Skylake X chips, sold out everywhere due to short supplies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 16:50:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>He absolutely did not have any bent pins. Don't be a sheep. http://i.imgur.com/O7pWj8g.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 18:46:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are keeping AM4 for 4 years, so yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 13:30:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's pretty cool, but how's the thermal throttling? When I used to have my 480 Red Devil, even at 100% fam speeds, my OC was 2300mhz on the memory which was stable, but core speed didn't matter where I set it. I left it at 1390, but honestly it would thermal throttle to 1290-1330ish the entire time. It would never run over that in any game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 13:46:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did undervolt it to achieve a constant 1290mhz as well. Overvolt just made thermal throttling worse and would sit at like 1190 lol. This card likes less voltage for more clock it seems. Oh well, I sold it during the mining craze and bought a water cooled 1080. I don't even remember what thermal throttling is even like anymore hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 16:01:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do appreciate the info! But I've since departed with the card, I sold it on eBay and purchased a watercooled 1080</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 15:43:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think this IF idea will be the trump card for Navi, but not Vega. Vega is looking to be DOA sadly. I think they are betting on Navi with massive power consumption cuts and performance increases from starting fresh with a new architecture. GCN will be most likely wrapped up with Vega. I would be shocked to not see Navi have a dual GPU or multiple smaller GPU dies setup to create a card for any level of consumer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 15:46:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea. They need a massive wall in Alaska, you know. To keep out all of the Snow Mexicans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 15:28:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eehhhhhh not quite, most benchmarks are now just single digits behind a 7700k. They've made massive improvements in the past few months</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 16:02:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should probably just buy a 1080Ti, but hey! You do you boo boo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 18:06:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wasn't talking about the 1400. Why would I compare such a cheap CPU to the 7700k lol. And yes that ram optimization and compatibility has translated to massive performance gains across the board.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 19:18:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why would I compare a $300 product to a $150 product. Who cares about core count. For the same money I can buy an R7 1700, which will outperform the 7700k in everything but games (If you don't count streaming). My wallet sees no bias nor core count lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 22:58:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>They give him free hardware, he doesn't pay for anything Intel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 00:28:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think people realize how small of an upgrade Intel has given us over the years. My overclocked on air sandy bridge scores around stock 6700k territory in benchmarks. Soooo that isn't saying a whole lot lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 14:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>In this situation I'd actually go with a Ryzen R3 1200. Higher core count would do better with large amounts of tabs open/photoshop compared to the dual core i3. 8GB of ram is a must these days, 4gb is not enough. The higher clocked dual cores would be a bit better for stuff like gaming, but since you're not planning on doing any of that this is the better option IMO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 15:04:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude I'm still on a 2600k and it's fine. You don't NEED to upgrade. It's all in your head. There will always be something better/faster. There's no point in constantly throwing away money just to have the best. The day your games aren't performing well enough/you have a system bottleneck or system failure should be the day you upgrade. If it ain't broke don't fix it. I've always been tempted to throw it all away and build a new system. But then I look at the numbers. Why should I spend $1000 on a brand new setup to gain what... 10% in fps? Not worth it. Even today with my 2600k I'm getting similar enough performance to newer 6700k/7700k systems. And my system is 5+ years old</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 18:57:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, he mentioned the i3, which is priced similar. But I did not take into account the GPU. So that is a fair point</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 23:24:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>5 monitors isn't a problem with much lesser cards, your 1080Ti's won't have an issue with normal usage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 04:30:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea, we've established that earlier in the comments if you bothered to scroll up half an inch on your screen lmao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 15:26:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Daily*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 06:16:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Skylake X doesn't sound like what you really need. I mean, you can spend a few thousand more dollars on more Xeons, but in terms of raw power it sounds like you need an Epyc setup. Each die can have up to 32 cores/64 threads, up to 64/128 with 2 chips installed. You'd never have a bottleneck even if you wanted to upgrade later on. And they cost less than the Intel Xeon counter parts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 20:41:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty sure 16 core Skylake X chips are 2.6ghz aren't they?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-02 15:19:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't hold my breath on that one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 22:29:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Plot twist: AMD just "leaked" this rumor so that everyone starts snatching Vega cards "before the miners get them all". Or: Plot twist 2.0: The hash rates are real, and it will be months before normal consumers can get their hands on Vega. Which by then AMD is hoping FineWine will kick in and start stretching towards 1080Ti level performance in games Plot Twist C: I'm drinking too much of that koolaid and I'm insane. Brilliant marketing AMD!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 16:02:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think we will see a decent amount of performance difference between these and the X versions. The X's are all basically guaranteed to hit 4ghz or higher. Extra 200-300mhz over 16 cores is quite a bit of performance. If you're already spending this much money on a platform might as well go big! Unless power consumption/heat are a concern for you, then the non X is more appealing of course</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-05 06:11:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes the 7700k is the better flat out gaming CPU. But to respond to the "smoothness" comment, frame rates do not equal frame times. I've experienced this personally first hand. Ryzen systems for some reason have very smooth gameplay, and I just don't know why. Regardless, both excellent products in both of their respective categories</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-05 06:20:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's the thing people fail to realize. In terms of raw power, Ryzen is up there around (being rough here) Broadwell E level performance clock for clock. But, for years Intel was the king. 99% of software is optimized for Intel chips and the way they work/ execute tasks. Nothing is optimized for Ryzen... yet. The games that are optimized for Ryzen are performing incredibly well. On par with the Intel counter parts. It's just going to take time before the software catches up. With AMD and Intel punching out crazy core count chips like 16 core thread ripper and 18 core i9 chips, 8ish+ core utilization will start to become more normal quickly. And then we will all reap the benefits of optimization</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 01:54:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah my mistake. I thought I read at launch that it did have ECC memory</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 22:02:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeaaaa you need a couple of things. A new Hard Drive (SSD is preferable), and you need more ram. Minimum of 8GB, if you can swing more I would. Then you should be smooth sailing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-08 06:57:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't wait to see this in action compared to Threadripper. 200 more points compared to Threadripper in the Alienware. Very interesting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-08 06:59:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>So it's better to have less PCI E lanes! Can't have latency in them if they don't exist in the first place! Lol....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 06:53:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same here. 2600k @4.8ghz stable on air. Works like a charm. Going to wait for Zen 2 honestly. Going to eyeball Intel's 9000 series too, but if AMD makes a 12ish core high clocking chip for i7 money, I wouldn't complain lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ryzen Threadripper 1950x, 1920x Review: Core i9 killer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 15:22:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ryzen Threadripper 1950x, 1920x Review: Core i9 killer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 15:24:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 15:33:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>For future reference, buy a can of electronic parts cleaner from your local auto parts store. It's pressurized in a can, it will remove anything and everything without physically touching it. Spray, let it dry for 2 min, good to go</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 15:38:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>TLDW Version: Single threaded performance is slightly behind Skylake X, Multithreaded does extremely well. 6 more cores for the same money really helps. And in other news, the sky is blue and water is wet lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 17:44:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure looks like it, only thing it fell behind in was 1080p gaming. Which honestly, I feel like whoever is spending $1000 on a CPU isn't going to have a 1080p monitor lol. But nonetheless, still excellent information. Productivity wise it smashed everything</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 18:10:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the hell kind of graphing is that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 19:48:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's probably a way to dial it in, and get it just right according to hardware unboxed, willing to bet most reviewers just didn't have the time to sit there and figure it out. I'm sure overclocking videos will start to pop up over the next week with people figuring out how to squeeze every drop of performance out of these chips</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 19:52:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>1080p on high settings (not ultra) Performance is decent. Intel pulls ahead in those tests. Anything higher than 1080p on max settings in most games (1440p-4k) the gap is going to be nonexistent compared to Intel chips. If you're buying this CPU and intending to do strictly gaming I'd look elsewhere. If you want to do real work and game, absolutely get Threadripper.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 19:58:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>A. You're comparing a server chip to a prosumer chip. Xeon needs to be compared with EPYC B. Xeons don't overclock C. Here's a 20 core Xeon basically on par with the 16 core Threadripper in Cinebench, just for giggles. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3U9Gj8Vklgg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 21:47:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Judging from every other review on YouTube, this looks to be false.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 23:52:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm really not, I'm just saying there is a way to dial in a stable 4.0ghz 16 core overclock with XFR set to 4.2 so that you gain extra single core performance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-11 14:13:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>There might be a way with tweaking around in the Threadripper software utility</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 02:17:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, 3 radiators custom looped together? I mean, if it works it works lol. That's a lot of money in cooling but it seems to have paid off for you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 20:17:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait for proper benchmarks and reviews boys. All of this means absolutely nothing as it stands right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 20:26:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Download core temp and check your temperatures. It will also show your clock speeds, run a few benchmarks. If temps are high, that's the issue. If everything looks good, and clocks are hitting where they are supposed to be, then I'd warranty out that chip</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 20:29:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can actually overclock your CPU without getting a new motherboard if you are trying to get some more life out of it. Using electrical tape, you can cover up 2 pins on the CPU, and it will overclock to 3ghz off the bat. Google the "BSEL Mod" for more info. Super easy to do, and costs you nothing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 20:35:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll be honest with you, I just helped a friend upgrade from a Q9650 to a Ryzen system. The difference was night and day. His RX480 gained over 60-100fps in some games. I'd save up your pennies and buy into a new platform. Core 2 Quads are dead these days, even if you bought a new board and overclocked it, the performance just isn't there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 14:00:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're well within the period of time to return it, yea. Most 1700's hit 3.9 no problem. Don't listen to these other idiots.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 14:20:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>This game is badly optimized, your 390 is a good card, but it still isn't powerful enough to push the game at maximum settings. It's less a CPU issue and more GPU at the same time. The game is poorly optimized</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 17:31:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're kind of SOL on this one. Only thing you can do at this point is buy a decent all in one liquid cooler. $78 for a refurbished Corsair H100 v2 from Fry's.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 17:53:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfortunately this is a big issue with these i7's. Maybe it's time to order a delid tool instead :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 18:25:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, they don't want to warranty it out anyway from the sound of things</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 19:45:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or call them and tell them the chip stopped wording, see if they will send you a new one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 02:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I notice a difference in performance if I have things open like multiple browser tabs, or other background programs. 2600k @4.8ghz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 05:33:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's really not. The difference between Sandy Bridge and Kaby Lake is not substantial. The recipe is about the same, but restructured a bit, moved a few things around to become more efficient. As well as shrunk down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 22:48:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>People are blowing this power consumption thing out of proportion. Vega 56 for example consumes less power than an RX580, and performs much better. And with further undervolting (we all know AMD loves to overvolt the crap out of their cards) you can get it even lower.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 08:09:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now keep in mind, I am comparing a completely different architecture when saying this, but the results are quite interesting. A Ryzen 1600 with SMT turned off (so it's running only 6 cores/threads) scores 788 on cinebench. A Ryzen 1500x scores exactly 788 on cinebench as well funny enough. At least from the YouTube videos I found. Food for thought haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 23:31:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bought GTX 1070 from /u/kristoferen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 14:48:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>2600k @4.8ghz user here, a decent amount of games my 1080 is sitting around 85% utilization, and some peg the 1080 at 100%. But for the most part I still have a bottleneck. Not that it matters much when I'm already getting over 100fps in just about everything I throw at it lol. Hence why I'm waiting for 7nm zen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 16:38:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea I am stuck at 1600, my Ram doesn't want to OC higher. I've tried :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 20:13:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>While this is true I don't want to spend $800 on a G-Sync monitor</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 05:17:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>At stock settings a 16 core thread ripper hits mid 60's on an air cooler, there's no issues with heat at all that would warrant trying to mess with it. Don't try to fix something that isn't broken.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 14:22:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>This applies more to AMD GPUs not really CPUs. On Ryzen they OC better with more voltage. Ryzen doesn't have a heat problem</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 15:10:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ryzen and Kaby are clock for clock about the same. Want to see the difference in Single threaded performance? Underclock your 7700k to 4.2ghz. And run your script. It will be roughly the same experience. Personally I think it's worth the jump for the multithreaded performance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 15:21:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think so. EPYC has more memory channels and some other small differences. I don't think the Threadripper socket could handle 32 cores</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 15:24:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're going to want to OC the shit out of that 2500k. Mine was bottlenecking an RX480 pretty good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 21:38:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there any alternative salt branded that I can purchase that would be free of plastics?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 01:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea you're pretty close with a 1060. I upgraded to a 2600k and overclocked it to 4.9ghz to try and keep up with my 1080 lol. For the most part it's working</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 14:47:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pharah has super thick armor... 200hp -.-</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 22:36:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>980ti is basically a 1070 in terms of performance. Honestly your i5 wouldn't make full use of a 1080 anyway. I doubt you'll see much better frames rates than you did with your RX480 honestly. But go for the 980ti. It's the better value</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 23:53:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a heavy user, my battery life is good. You might have something wrong with your device</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 05:49:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's all purely speculation at this point, but I can pretty much bet anything it will improve. The question is, by how much. If I had to take a wild guess, it might slot itself somewhere in between the 1080 and 1080ti. I don't feel like it will quite reach the Ti in all scenarios, but I think it might inch closer in certain titles. I do think it will beat out the standard 1080 with time by a decent amount though. At least in my opinion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 22:05:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Coffee lake is Kaby Lake but able to handle extra cores. It #8217;s not something revolutionary. Don #8217;t think AMD has anything to worry about</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 21:07:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s quite simple. Businesses and other parties will actually purchase the 6950x over current hardware because the 6950x is now proven. It #8217;s had all of its kinks worked out. It will be 100% stable. People who need work done Pick the proven hardware over the bleeding edge. And they will pay a premium for it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 08:25:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>There #8217;s a difference between faulty hardware and stability. Typically once things are up and running there #8217;s little issue</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 08:33:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you just do gaming I wouldn #8217;t bother with a CPU upgrade. I have a 2600k and GTX 1080, work perfect. You should upgrade your video card if anything. And OC the CPU a bit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 14:17:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why are you concerned with power consumption? It would literally cost you single digits in terms of electricity cost to bump that up to 4.5ghz and Run it vs spending several hundreds of dollars to jump platforms for minimal gains. I don #8217;t understand your logic whatsoever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 14:21:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uhh from several sources they are pushing 750-850w of total system power draw during a CPU only workload. It #8217;s way more than 550</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 15:59:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>8350k is literally a rebadged 7600k, why would that bother you. Anyway, you #8217;re only upgrade path is 7700k, which you should #8217;ve considered in the first place. Ryzen 1600 would #8217;ve also been ideal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 06:19:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try it again with SMT off, report back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 06:20:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try it again with SMT off, and report back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 06:21:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn #8217;t, you will degrade your chip very quickly with that voltage. If it were be I #8217;d run it at 4ghz, with lower voltage</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 05:47:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. You #8217;d get the same frames as someone with a Sandy bridge CPU. If you want better 4k performance stick to whatever CPU you have and get 1080Ti #8217;s in SLI</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-02 05:20:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just return it and get a different one, honestly majority of 1700 #8217;s can do 3.9 at the very least. I #8217;d be unhappy with that result</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-02 14:54:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not with that attitude you can #8217;t</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-02 15:05:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why would you pay a restocking fee for an exchange? That makes no sense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 00:38:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is your 2700k holding anything back? I #8217;m a 2600k owner with a water cooled GTX 1080 Seahawk. While the upgrade is tempting, my CPU isn #8217;t really struggling with today #8217;s games. Unless you are doing some crazy editing or something else besides gaming that more cores would be beneficial, I wouldn #8217;t even bother upgrading this gen. Wait for cannon lake or Zen 2. That #8217;s what I #8217;m doing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 21:31:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depends. If you're using your computer for mainly internet/gaming, honestly no. The gains aren't really worth it. If you do other things such as video editing, or maybe workstation type things like CAD it would be worth looking at an upgrade to save some time. But gaming and other basic things I'd hold off another year</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 15:05:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Purely speculation on my part, but as far as I know the Pro shares the same silicon with the standard Ryzen. So the ECC might be a 50/50 not on it working or not. I #8217;d play it safe and grab a 1900x Threadripper system</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 15:12:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly you should consider a Phenom X6 or FX6300. And overclock the heck out of one of them. Preferably the FX6300, it will overclock much higher</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 00:24:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d just hold out one more generation if I were you. Cannon Lake/Zen 2 is where the real gains are to be had</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 16:17:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>My now ex girlfriend whom I blindingly trusted was texting other dudes. Then a few weeks later left me for someone else. Didn #8217;t find out until a month later from her best friend. Probably damaged me forever when I found out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 18:33:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea you got a baaaaaad chip. I got my buddy #8217;s normal 1700 to 3.9 on the same voltage</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 02:23:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's never correct it seems like. My friend's Ryzen system reports like 7ghz, my i7 reports 6.2ghz, it's all messed up. Also please for the love of GOD overclock that 2600k.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 06:06:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fun fact: a lot of Lamborghinis have a button in the car that raises the front for large speed bumps! So this isn #8217;t much of an issue</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New Intel Core Processor Combines High-Performance CPU with Custom Discrete Graphics from AMD to Enable Sleeker, Thinner Devices</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 15:23:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 15:32:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s happpeeennniiiinnnnnggggggggggg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 14:44:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>How is this possible. The EPA #8217;s job is to literally protect the environment. And here we are about to destroy half of the entire world #8217;s supply of Salmon. Over what? Some metals? Unacceptable. We must do something. This has to stop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 13:50:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uhm, I was running 8gb of ram just fine, not understanding your point</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Trump administration to end immigration protections for Haitians, giving them 18 months to leave</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 01:36:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 06:56:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. Every little bit of extra ram Speed helps in gaming and tasks. I #8217;d say maybe 2933mhz would be  #8220;enough #8221;. There would still be gains going from 2933mhz to 3200+MHz but not as noticeable as 2133mhz to 2933mhz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 20:41:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mainly tested Rainbow Six Siege with an RX 480 8gb Care. I saw plenty of gains playing with the ram. Granted that game runs above 100+FPS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 22:21:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why do you assume being locked to a 60hz monitor means that getting over 60fps doesn #8217;t make the experience more pleasant?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 05:15:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mueller and his team aren't stupid. They know exactly what they are doing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 14:46:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>It just does. The input lag/smoothness of the game is massively different between 60fps and 90fps+. I played Rainbow Six Siege at 60fps with my old video card. It was acceptable. But when I upgraded to my 1080, even though I was still using a 60hz monitor, it felt sooo much smoother. I was getting 110ish FPS. Then I overclocked my CPU. Gained another 60fps. It felt miles better at this point. The response time was immediate. If you still don #8217;t understand go watch some YouTube videos of others explaining it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 14:48:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have to also keep in mind not all games use that full 8 threads the CPU has to offer, so it might not show he #8217;s using 100%. But I can promise that the CPU is bottlenecking that card, 3.7ghz isn #8217;t enough @1080p for a GTX 1080</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 14:50:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have to manually overclock the CPU. There is no button that #8217;s going to easily squeeze the most performance out of your chip. Look up some YouTube tutorials. Download prime95 to check stability. Coretemp to monitor temperatures. Set the multiplier to 4.5ghz and slowly raise the voltage on the core until it stops crashing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 07:02:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>While yes this is great and all, I #8217;m still deeply disturbed that Jones took the race by such a slim margin. Over 600,000 people felt Moore was better than a democrat. Someone who #8217;s been accused of sexually assaulting multiple women, someone who wanted to repeal constitutional amendments put in place to protect the people, someone who outright spoke fluent Russian in an interview when asked what he would say to Putin. They #8217;d rather have him run the show than a democrat. We have serious problems in this country. This is truly terrifying and eye opening.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 13:59:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I exaggerated that part, it still made my eyes pop out of their sockets when I watched it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can't access BTC on Bittrex? Anyone else have this issue?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 17:38:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just noticed this morning that I can't click on BTC in my wallet. Also using the search bar, bitcoin disappeared from Bittrex. Is it just on my end? Can someone confirm? Did something happen?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 01:41:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Usually takes me 30 min or so, depends how slammed the servers are</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 23:00:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>The YouTube comments are horrible. What is wrong with people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 14:16:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everyone doubted bitcoin too. Now look at it. Some imaginary coin has flirted with 20k in value. There #8217;s always a chance something huge happens, no matter how unlikely it seems</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-26 22:33:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since you like battery life as well, consider buying a cheap chrome oil of sorts along side your new beefy laptop. Hours of battery, around $200 price range</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 00:14:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chromebook* damn iPhone spellcheck hahahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 17:54:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>It could be even more extreme than that. Ripple has grown 5000% this year. If it kept growing at that rate, it would be $93 by the end of next year. Now I know that #8217;s a bit unlikely to hit that mark, but anything is possible. It could potentially go past $10</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 21:06:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>We #8217;re missing out on not millions or hundreds of millions. We #8217;re missing out on BILLIONS.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 02:29:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait, April? I thought it was coming out in Feb?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 02:53:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re also forgetting about the part that it might be seen as Pumping And Dumping in the eyes of the law. Which is illegal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 16:23:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use Bittrex, works well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 16:41:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably like.. an hour?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 15:20:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://mobile.twitter.com/KatyTurNBC/status/948703754743885825</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 16:49:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s also because ETH servers were overloaded and they can only process so fast. Litecoin is much faster and has less fees if you #8217;re moving coin to an exchange.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 16:55:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Considering LTC recently had a massive sell, it #8217;s been stable retaining its value after the dip. I expect by Feb or March it will surge and grow once again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 17:08:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Considering LTC recently had a massive sell, it #8217;s been stable retaining its value after the dip. I expect by Feb or March it will surge and grow once again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 14:40:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>The trickledown whataboutism on the Red team seems to be working very well. Bravo  #128079;. Because comparing a fiction novel to someone who wrote a novel on what happened in the 1 year he spent inside the White House is exactly the same thing. 100% the same. Fiction. You should just cut your losses and admit you voted for the wrong person instead of choking on the sand because your head is so far down into the ground</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 16:33:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Listen up and listen closely. You were scammed. The ledger doesn #8217;t have preconfigured words. You need to track down the seller via paypal, and eBay. Notify your local authorities. You need to act fast. Somewhere along the road they have to have left a trail. Find the packaging they sent you the ledger in, look for the return address. Keep us posted. I wish you the best</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 19:41:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t worry you two. I #8217;ve been watching Ripple for months. What it #8217;s doing is normal. It fluctuate a few cents here and there, up and down for a couple week or so, then grow a MASSIVE amount, then correct. But the correction is always higher than the old price pre-spike. Then rinse and repeat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 07:37:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>It probably won't stay there long, Ripple will overtake it again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 15:03:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wow I give my opinion and get downvoted into oblivion lol. I #8217;m not bashing Ethereum. I have a bit of skin in the game with the coin myself. Both offer a laundry list of benefits, but the single easiest key point for me is, Ethereum has a pretty level global penetration (compared to XRP), while Ripple has minimal west coast penetration, for now. 80% of its value is with the Koreans because they see the value in it. Once more people in the US start to see it (which it appears to be gaining traction) it will surpass Ethereum IMO. Maybe not by much, but it will get there and probably go back and forth between those two for the #2 spot for quite a while</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 16:07:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bios updates haven #8217;t rolled out yet, the Windows update doesn #8217;t seem to damage performance too much, low single digit percentages. But the bios will paint the clearest picture. That #8217;s why you aren #8217;t really seeing performance figures yet. Servers though got hit the hardest, 30-50% performance drops. If you haven #8217;t used the chip or anything yet, just wait and see what AMD #8217;s new Zen+ has to offer, we should get a picture in the next few days</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 16:10:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>He has every right to be worried. Especially someone with sensitive financial data on their computer etc etc. I #8217;m personally jumping ship to Ryzen 2 when it drops in a few weeks over this. I #8217;m taking 0 chances</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 20:18:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your best bet is a 980ti, around $300 used, similar performance to a 1070</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 04:42:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>About $450</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 04:49:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, 980ti #8217;s are going above $320 all the way to $450 depending on where you look. You #8217;ll need more then $260 to get one unfortunately</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 14:39:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea, because foreign policy and relationships with other countries is exactly the same as the president getting freaky cunnilingus on the side. This is more comparable to Trumps recent news of having sexual relations with a porn star while he was married, and while his wife was pregnant with his son. I hate this whataboutism that #8217;s been a trend lately.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 14:57:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually recommend the 2600k, it will overclock better than the 3770k, and it #8217;s soldered, doesn #8217;t use Intel branded toothpaste lol. Meaning it runs cooler. And it #8217;s cheaper!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 14:59:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s normal, this happens every year https://i.imgur.com/Ss6b4bW.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 15:06:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;d get the same performance if you bought a 6700k and overclocked it. No point in spending all of that extra money on an 8700k</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 21:17:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn #8217;t bet on it coming down anytime soon, this dip is temporary. By March we will see record highs again. Unfortunately you #8217;ll just have to wait for the right moment to snipe a deal when they become available</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 00:43:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>He #8217;s streaming 720p lol, it won #8217;t make a difference</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 10:05:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, personally I don #8217;t think that #8217;s super weird, it #8217;s his daughter. She will always be his baby girl regardless of age. Meanwhile Pence calls his wife  #8220;mother #8221;. Now that #8217;s weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 21:37:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do we know if they will change this policy eventually? I wasn #8217;t planning on selling my Raiblocks anytime soon but I #8217;m not happy knowing they are now stuck on the exchange.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Trump Ordered Mueller Fired, but Backed Off When White House Counsel Threatened to Quit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 05:55:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 02:33:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why wouldn't you buy Altcoins?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 20:34:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>The 560 is pretty decent honestly. I installed one in a PC for my friend's little brother (Actually it was a 460, but same thing pretty much). The 2GB model I was super surprised at how capable it was. Runs a lot of games fairly well at 1080p. With 4gb I felt it would have been quite the little card!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 06:18:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t want to burst your bubble but Crypto is going to keep the prices of these cards high. Come March I have a good feeling profits are going to soar again. The best thing to do is keep looking for GPUs. They do pop up for sale on Newegg and other tech outlets, but you need to keep refreshing all day and they last only a few minutes. You can also try craigslist, or Reddit #8217;s own /r/hardwareswap for a deal. I was lucky and snagged a 1080 locally on Craigslist. Just keep looking! Vega 56/64s have also occasionally popped up very close to msrp. If you find one just snag it, even a little above msrp is worth it these days</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 00:41:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got extremely lucky and found a 1080 for 450 used. But again, I got lucky lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 00:51:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Offer him $550 lol. He will counter at $600, and bam. You got a decent deal on your hands</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 15:55:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>There #8217;s nothing on amazon I haven #8217;t been able to find on eBay. Sometimes I can actually thing things on eBay even cheaper</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thoughts on the new operators?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 18:35:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not normally one of these guys that complains every season about how the new operators are "OP AF", but I did play the TTS and I have some thoughts. I think Lion is ok, I don't exactly like his ability, but it is what it is. You can easily counter it by just standing still. However, I do think Finka is overpowered. The no recoil thing is just too extreme, and the defenders don't really have a way to counter it. I feel like it takes away from the game. I think she should buff the reload speed instead of recoil. That would make it more fair and balanced. What are your guy's thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 06:53:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just think the recoil is super OP. She can be countered but her recoil can #8217;t. Smoke can get killed by the time he tosses a poison gas grenade</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can we get this thread stickied? YES your B350/x370 Motherboard WILL support the next generation Ryzen chips shipping soon</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 16:07:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's multiple threads every day about this, figured it might be time to just consolidate it into one single thread. Yes your current board will support the upcoming chips. AMD said they would support the current socket until 2020, and given their history and track record, I'm confident in saying they will keep their word. They did the same thing with the AM2/AM2+/AM3 sockets in the past, I see no reason for them to change now! Feel free to comment questions, and hopefully one of us here can answer it for you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 16:15:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just because it  #8220;supports #8221; 4000mhz ram doesn #8217;t mean it will work. Hell even Intel systems have a hard time jumping over 3200-3600mhz. Also, the memory controller on the CPU also plays a large role in memory speeds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 00:34:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is called Microstutter. This is the big downside of multiGPU setups, and this is why AMD/Nvidia aren't really promoting/supporting it much anymore</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 14:38:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a low gold, I take offense to that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Server side delay</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 14:51:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>First off I want to say, I love Siege. It #8217;s definitely my current favorite game. But I feel like this is long overdue. The delay between client and server is just massive. If I have a 30-40 ping, why are there missed shots at point blank range, or sometimes I #8217;ll shoot 3-4 rounds, and in the killcam I #8217;ll have shot only once. Sometimes I won #8217;t have shot at all. There #8217;s always been a little delay, but I feel like after Chimera it #8217;s gotten worse and worse. Servers really need a higher tick rate, or something. Anyone else have a similar experience?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>RUMOR: Apple is leaving Intel to partner up with AMD to create "Custom Apple CPUs"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 17:07:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was reading some articles today, and watching a video from "Everythingapplepro" on youtube, and the idea was brought up. The idea that Apple might parter up with AMD and together work on some custom chips for their computers. Thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 18:02:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>The other thing I was think about also was the fact that ARM Chips aren #8217;t good at heavy workloads like x86 chips are. Couple this fact with your suggestion and it sort of makes sense</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 05:23:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why? What is the motive for this anger?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 06:04:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not 100% sure on this, but wouldn #8217;t AMD lose its x86 license if they get bought out?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 06:09:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m personally someone who uses everything, regardless of whether it #8217;s Apple, Samsung, Microsoft, etc. I think you #8217;re just plain wrong. It #8217;s because of Apple that we are here today. They lead the industry and forced everyone to be competitive. The reason we have so many wonderful products today due to Apple. They make a solid product. Are their computers a bit more on the expensive side? Yes. But guess what? It #8217;s built to a really high standard, and people take notice and appreciate that. And that #8217;s another reason why residual value is so high. You #8217;d lose less money buying a Mac, then selling it a couple years later to upgrade, then to buy a prebuilt PC, and sell it a couple years later. I used to be like you, until I realized that I had 0 reason to hate on Apple. They are just doing things their way, and it works. It works extremely well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 16:31:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does the title not say  #8220;RUMOR #8221; in massive bold capital letters? Also ARM is good at power consumption, but not at being a power house.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 20:00:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boom goes the dynamite</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 16:33:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually from what I understand, a 980Ti edges out a 1070 when both are overclocked, but the 1070 uses less power. 900 series cards were excellent overclockers compared to the current gen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Russia prepares for nuclear war with US</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 17:35:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 19:48:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>At this point they need to put it on a few space ships and send it to Jupiter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 00:05:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>How would you feel if I said to you I hope your stock portfolio goes to 0?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 02:29:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the accuracy is there, great job on that part! But to me it just feels like all weapons are using Finka's ability now. It's just... too easy. Feels almost Call of Dutyish. There needs to be a lot more recoil added to basically every single gun in my opinion. I feel like I'm just shooting people with laser pointers, spawn peaking has never been easier, shooting someone across the map is cake now regardless if I am attacking or defending. I think there needs to be more side to side bounce on most guns, and more vertical recoil in general. Keep it up guys! It's getting there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 20:40:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd rather that didn't happen. Most people in the market for a 6 or 8 core CPU have dedicated graphics. Why should the rest of us have to pay more money for a chip we won't need or use ever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 16:29:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>TL;dr if you #8217;re a streamer you want the 2700x. Frames don #8217;t drop on the viewer side like the 8700k.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 20:54:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Frames per second isn't the only measurement of a game's performance. There's also frame time. My friend's AMD Ryzen system with 8 cores actually gets maybe 15ish fps less than I do on my Core i7 system. But I can tell you with certainty his system feels smoother. And it comes down to frame times. Siege's engine is quite good in using system resources to the fullest. There's not a single dip, jitter, or anything in the way the game plays on higher core count CPUs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 07:55:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>While the hardware is similar, software isn #8217;t. Xbox runs on a modified version of Windows 10. Song uses their own OS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Netflix doesn't work</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 23:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there a trick to getting netflix to work? If not, Is there anyway you guys could keep changing your ip addresses every once in a while so that netflix keeps working? I bought a subscription basically for this reason, but I'm thinking about canceling because I'm still within my 7 days. Any help? Thanks in advanced!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 16:28:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Expert mode: Explain Lion and Jackal  #128293;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 16:38:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Her DMR is good. It #8217;s accurate and powerful. She #8217;s basically a better glaz. I racked up 5 or so kills with it last night in ranked with no real issues. Just like all single fire weapons, it requires practice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 16:42:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope this is false. I was a high gold before and played with Copper 4 #8217;s in the past. We even had a plat on our team</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 16:44:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m just stuck in silver now I feel like, I #8217;m constantly getting 20ish points per game, sometimes low 30 #8217;s. But then if I get unlucky and play with a bad team, knocks me down 60-70 points. It #8217;s so frustrating</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 23:52:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally don #8217;t think the new recoil system they made was a suitable replacement for the current one. I #8217;d rather they took their time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 00:23:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>No need, I #8217;ll just do it for you right now! Crazy British man has massive hammer and swings it at walls! /Thread</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 16:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fun fact: PUBG at 60hz still has twice the latency that Fortnite does at 30hz. And PUBG only runs at 60 when there are less than 40 players alive. It dips as low as 22hz.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 17:06:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d shoot for a 2600x, or 2700x. The 2600x has a nice bang for the buck though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 17:09:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the extra 80ish bucks, is return the 1070ti and snag a Vega 64. Performance is in the GTX 1080 ballpark, and no screen tearing while maintaining high FPS in gaming. Plus you won #8217;t have that awful input lag that comes with Vsync</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 21:25:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t bet on it, even debaur said it #8217;s basically just a mild bin 8700k. It #8217;s not an extreme bin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 02:17:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mid range would be closer to 1080/1170 performance, not 1080ti/1180 performance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 02:23:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not this next generation. They are making the 1180 the new 1080ti. Look at the specs sheet that leaked</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 03:25:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you take a look at computing performance on the leaked 1180 specs, it is almost as powerful as the 1080ti.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 03:35:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I must #8217;ve looked at an old leak then, my mistake</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 16:24:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>The RX560 does have 4K support, so it should work. What cable are you using to connect it to your monitor? This could be the limiting factor</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 16:34:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some games gain performance with SMT off, and some lose performance. Same goes with Intel #8217;s hyperthreading. It #8217;s pretty much down to each game #8217;s optimization</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 17:05:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>What #8217;s the max resolution it will let you display?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 17:09:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically it should display 4k@30hz if you have a HDMI 1.4 cable. If you have a new enough TV it might support 60hz. Makes me think you might have an older cable than that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 17:19:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like an old cable, try another one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 17:29:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm. It could be seated weird. Try swapping both ends. And throw a driver update to see if it changes anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 14:01:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go to your local auto parts store and buy a can of electrical Parts cleaner. Give the keyboard a good soaking. See if it helps</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do you feel about all of the new changes?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 08:06:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just curious to see how everyone feels about the new changes to the game? I personally don #8217;t know how I feel about it. I miss the speed of 3 speeds. I #8217;m a little overwhelmed with the amount of cameras a defending team can have now from all of these changes. So many traps and cams everywhere. Especially with Maestro in the mix</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 15:45:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly about 1in3 enemy engagements with glaz look like this for me. I #8217;m CLEARLY hitting him, but it doesn #8217;t register</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Easiest solution for teamkillers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 16:08:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>A lot of trolls these days will just one or two tap a team mate and run away to avoid getting banned. Very annoying. Especially in ranked. It #8217;s really a fairly simple idea, why not have a punish or forgive system? If someone does over 50 damage to you, a prompt comes up saying if you want to forgive or punish this person. If they try to shoot you or another teammate again, you take no damage and it autokicks them. That way the team doesn #8217;t stuffer from one person #8217;s toxicity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 17:52:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friends had to rebuy the standard edition too. Luckily, they bought it during the recent Ubisoft store sale, so it was much cheaper. But yea it sucks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 18:00:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Close to 1100 hours here, you #8217;re going to die a LOT the first 100ish hours in the casual game mode. Watch the killcams, and learn from them. After a few killcams you #8217;ll learn what not to do, and eventually start to get into the groove of the game. Terrorist hunt is a great way to improve your aim. I find using a 3 speed operator and sprinting through a terrorist hunt classic game mode is a great way to learn how to quick peak corners and learn how to get some snap kills. Make sure you setup your graphics settings properly for your hardware. Higher frame rates really help in this game. 100+FPS is the sweet spot. And most importantly, even if you #8217;re dead, use those cameras and give your team callouts! Doing this, you #8217;ll eventually figure out what the rooms in each map are called. Use that compass too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 18:16:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I came from CSGO, so I can relate haha. The operators are what makes the game interesting. As far as frame rates, what sort of hardware are you currently working with?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 19:05:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s a solid system, set textures to very high, you can turn everything up pretty high actually. Set render scale to 50, and use T-AA for AA. Assuming you have a 1080P monitor of course. V-Sync off. Should get you into the 120fps realm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 20:20:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, does anyone really need more than 8gb for an ultraportable laptop? I still have 8gb if ram in my gaming desktop and it #8217;s fine. What could anyone possibly do to require over 8gb? 300 Chrome tabs? Maybe Spotify running in the background?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 15:04:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>And that kind of person isn #8217;t buying a budget $600 ultraportable. They are spending more money for that extra horsepower. 98% of consumers aren #8217;t doing that stuff on a low dollar laptop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 17:51:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 09:32:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>You might not have a CPU problem, but rather a hard drive problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 16:49:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not to get anyone #8217;s hopes up, but this could be a sneak peak into the future for Vega owners. Possible Finewine at work. Developers actually optimizing and utilizing all that the Vega cards have to offer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 02:08:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I couldn #8217;t be wrong, but don #8217;t normal Ryzen chips support ECC, unofficially?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 02:12:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s the OS. It #8217;s extremely well optimized. There was a video I watched a while back comparing the weaker GPU used in Apple #8217;s computer to a higher end GPU in a custom built system. Then they exported a high res video, and the Apple system edged it out even with weaker specs. Hence why Apple can get away with selling lower end systems</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 16:28:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>She has a high skill curve. She #8217;s not an easy operator to master.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 06:19:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally on a daily basis I get the server lag icon, at LEAST once or twice a game. If not many more. I think it started happening when the whole thing with Intel #8217;s CPUs being effected by meltdown and Spectre. I #8217;m suspecting Ubisoft is running Intel chips. Because before that lag was really a non issue for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Twitch wasn #8217;t ready for Bolivia</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 19:23:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 20:04:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is original content, my friend took this screenshot! Edit: I was wrong, he did not take this screenshot. My apologies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:29:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>If the rumor is true that the new AMD chips will have high clocks and a 10% IPC gain and 12 cores, I #8217;m all in on the Ryzen 3700x.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 17:37:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>If that #8217;s true, this would be the first time since the early 2000 #8217;s where they would beat Intel by a massive amount in basically all tasks, benchmarks, and gaming. Even at 10% gains it would put AMD in the lead. Either way I #8217;m very excited.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 00:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>7nm is IBM #8217;s design, and IBM has always had the best results over the years. I think we will see far beyond 4.5ghz, especially since the current generation is already pretty close to that mark</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My friend possibly got the world's first ace, and possibly the world's first Pre-Fire, in Rainbow Six Siege in a pre-beta build of the game</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 02:05:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 02:52:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also he recorded this waaay before he uploaded it. Back then Ubisoft had people sign an NDA to not upload or show anything about the game until certain dates. So he sat on this footage for a good long while before uploading it September of 2015 to Youtube</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 15:39:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea hahaha. When I asked him about that, he said he had 0 idea he was there, pure luck on his part. Just goes to show how much of a noob everyone was in those days. The game is played much much differently now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 20:59:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was a little worried about this, the 1950x might actually be a better CPU than it #8217;s successor because of the way they have the memory layout setup. But I #8217;ll wait till the full reviews come out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 15:20:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, I thought the 1950x had separate channels for each CCX</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 15:38:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right, but from what I #8217;m seeing Threadripper 2 has to share a channel with another die. Which would create more memory bottleneck compared to the 1950x</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 18:27:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahhhh, thank you for the clarification</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 23:00:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a solid chip, most of the chips I've played with needed closer to 1.385v to hit 3.8-3.9ghz stable. As far as lifespan, that voltage isn't anywhere near high enough to cause degradation. So you're good. Above 1.45 is when things are iffy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[USA-IN][H] Intel Core i7 2600k + Motherboard + G Skill Ripjaws X 8gb 2133mhz DDR3 Memory [W] PayPal</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 04:27:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Selling my CPU/Motherboard/Memory combo! Everything works perfect, mildly overclocked to 4.6ghz, stays very cool with my AIO water cooler. Can clock higher (I #8217;ve gotten it to boot at 5ghz, but I ran It for maybe 30 seconds, then downclocked it back to 4.6 for daily use and system stability.) I can reset the clocks back to stock if the purchaser requests. The system will ship without a cooler. Just CPU, Memory, and Motherboard. It #8217;s a gigabyte Motherboard, used it for years with 0 issues. Has a GSkill Ripjaws X 2133mhz set of memory with it. One of the higher performing Memory sets out there for this platform for sure. Only reason I #8217;m selling is because I #8217;m gearing up to buy a new setup. I will continue to use this system until it #8217;s sold! I can send more pictures or videos if requested of the system working! Asking $195 for the whole lot. I might entertain parting the system out though, feel free to make offers on certain parts. https://imgur.com/a/ZMR3X6D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 04:32:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Replied</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 06:27:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fantastic chip honestly. Holds up really well, even today</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 14:30:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 14:44:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought I had an i3 6100, but it turns out it #8217;s a i3 4170 lol. Wouldn #8217;t happen to need one of those would you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Putting together a budget system to finally replace my aging 2600k, wanting to use it for streaming. Need advice</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 23:02:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey guys, need your help! I have decided to purchase potentially a used Ryzen 1700, seeing as more cores would be helpful for streaming. But I need help picking out a motherboard! I was thinking maybe an x370 chipset, I will be overclocking the chip about as far as I can push it to try and maximize frames. What motherboard do you guys think I should get, maybe around low $100? Which boards have better VRMs/Phases etc. Same goes for memory, what are some recommendations for a 16gb set? Thinking around $160ish</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 23:16:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw those, but neither one seemed to have good reviews. Makes me a little scared to purchase</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 23:37:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>3770k wouldn't really be any faster than my 2600k lol. I don't really care to wait to possibly save $20, so it's not that big of a deal to me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 00:38:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>You probably overpaid, There's several sets in the lower to mid 300's right now.. Unless you got a super fancy cl14 high clock speed set with RGB, that's a whole other story lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 01:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 14:51:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you live in the US, you might want to just buy now. Trump tariffs are kicking in around the 20th. All PC parts will skyrocket in price, including ram, CPUs and motherboards, and that won #8217;t change for a long time. So don #8217;t even bother waiting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 14:56:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s odd, might have a bad board, or it #8217;s not getting enough power from PSU</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 15:55:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you feel about the Asrock X470 Master SLI/AC?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 19:39:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, I get it #8217;s a little pricy lol. I meant like build wise. Vrms/phases ok? I got mine on sale so I didn #8217;t have to pay that steep Msrp</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 21:48:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>RIP me. That #8217;s what I get for buying by just reading reviews. What do worse FETs translate to? Reliability issues? Or potentially worse performance overclocking?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 22:31:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right on, I will look around for a small fan. Have no idea how I #8217;m going to mount it though lol. I appreciate it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 08:41:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate the advice! Although I think I figured out something. I swapped the sticks to the other slots, and now I have them overclocked all the way to 3466! On CL14! Pretty excited about that. I guess it didn #8217;t like the other slots haha. You must have a golden 1st gen chip! That #8217;s really low voltage for your clocks! I don #8217;t think my 1800x is as good as yours</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 07:17:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Siege uses up to 16 threads, so that #8217;s to be expected on an FX CPU. It even puts my Ryzen 1800x through the ringer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:35:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uhhh, homeboy Que #8217;s with high plats and diamonds. Do you even watch his videos?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 04:23:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>The rumor is mainstream 3700x will be a 12 core unit. This time with higher clocks and 10-15% better IPC</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 19:58:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can do it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 19:43:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let me rephrase your title for you.  #8220;Favela is not competitive yet #8221;. As a casual map, it #8217;s a blast. It #8217;s so much fun and so frustrating at the same time. You have to keep in mind, this is a game after all. The whole point is to have fun. It #8217;s not going to be in ranked, so just forget about it and enjoy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 19:45:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>My frames are pretty much consistent with other maps too. What cpu/video card do you have?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 19:30:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s not hard to get 25k renown. Especially if you do your challenges and play regularly. Took me a couple of months to save up 120,000 renown</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>