<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7377</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-02 14:30:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>For me, I would say Isco, he has grown more and more into his role, more than i've seen from Bale. Isco is like the spider in the middle of the net, building up everything into a tidy show. The same as Casemiro. Bale is replacable if you ask me, right now Isco is not. Also Isco is not a man made of glass like Bale. And sometimes it just feels like he's given up in the middle of a match where as Isco always fight on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-02 14:40:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also I would like to add that the real problem in the BBC is not Bale, it's the oaf Benzema...god damn I wish we got rid of him this transfer window, but seems like he is too close to Zizou and Perez.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-02 14:51:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amazing is not the word, shit is the right one I think, but that's just my opinion, in every position that is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me [24 M] with my GF [24 F] 2 year relationship, need advice on argument.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 11:29:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know where to start exactly, but I love my girlfriend very much, although we are very different we complement each other sometimes good, sometimes not. And it is the "not" thing that bothers me sometimes. We hade this argument tonight, she has been testriding a horse she wanted to buy from a friend, the same friend said that the horse was for sale. She has become close to the horse already and last night her friend said that she had changed her mind about it and wanted to keep the horse. Naturally my GF burst out in tears. I tried to comfort her and tried telling her things to improve her mood. This is when she snapped at me, with an awful attitude, and told me to lay off and only comfort her without trying to improve her mood, and she started to change all the direction of her negativity towards me. This is when i snapped and said that i would not accept that sort of behaviour, it's not my fault what happened with the horse, i'm laying here trying to comfort you in the best of ways and you attack me. I said that im tired of her behaviour when negative things happen to her and that she always put it all on me and snaps at me. She started crying more and wanted to apologise but I said that apologising doesn't change the fact that she always do this (we have discussed this before), she has to show me instead that she has changed in her approach to these kinds of situations. I wasn't having it so I said that I didn't want to talk more tonight or try to solve it, i just wanted to go to sleep (was really tired and i have work to go up to early in the morning). There was nothing to solve this night, she always puts all the anger towards me when someone else hurts her feelings and i'm kinda tired of it. Adults shouldn't behave this way. It all ended with her going to the livingroom and sleeping on the couch and crying. And I didn't want to comfort her anymore because I was also hurt and angry and wanted to sleep. My questions is, am I wrong to react this way during a sensitive situation? Am I wrong to be angry about it when she was this sad? And is it wrong to think that a person can change their ways when it comes to handling their emotions? Appreciate you all for reading this wall of text, really need some advice. *TL;DR; : My girlfriend often snaps out at me when she is sad or hurt by something or someone else than me. And this is a recent example. *.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 15:40:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for your answer. It makes me understand it a little bit more, i don't really know if she has some sort of anxiety about it, but I know that she has a lot of other anxietys and problems socially. The thing is, i'm just tired of her apologising, I don't want her to apologise, I want her to show me that she has actually thought about what i have said about the problem. Words are one thing but action is the way you show that you have taken in what the other person have told you. But I have one question for you, am I a coldhearted bastard for not comforting her when she moved to the other room and laid on the couch crying? I feel guilty but I dont want to give in to the crying when I was hurt and angry myself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 09:27:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get that i'm not without wrongdoing here, I know that I also could have reacted less. But I won't sugarcoat my words, "always" is the true word here, always she finds a way to snap at me when she is mad at something or someone else. And this is really the only problem we have in our relationship. I just scares me somehow when she does it, that she can cry and be teary eyed one minute and then suddently she's got this cocky aggressive attitude. I don't like it, she feels like another person. And thanks for your response, I was also looking for constructive criticism against me so I appreciate that as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 09:41:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; ke her feel bad The thing is, I would love for a solution like this, but it is almost impossible. Because when we fight, and it's not often, but when we do she always wants to solve it directly, she always wants to discuss it right away. I have tried leaving the room to avoid it but it just makes her follow me with tears in her eyes pleading for us to solve it and talk, and she begs for forgiveness. But we talked it over last night and we came to the conclusion that she will try harder not to direct her anger towards me and I will not leave the discussion, we will always try to solve it directly afterwards. And i appreciate the feedback!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 10:27:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>A sad day, and I'm a Real Madrid fan, but a good player leaves La liga and football became more about the money then about the game and the glory. Ironically I never liked neymar very much but I love the sport.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 22:03:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Asensios goal was beautiful! Magic! Made me smile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Vintage Nike Air jacket, know which model it is?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 18:43:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 19:40:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trying to find out from which year and which model.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 22:24:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>It makes me a bit mad actually every time Vazquez fucks something up as usual and he has this stupid grin on his face like he knows that he was trash.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>To remember who Bale is and what he's done for us until he gets back!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 18:54:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Small thing but I need advice.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 18:59:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>So me and the girlfriend has an awesome night at a hotel. And I took a lovely picture of her in a red dress. She said that she didn't like the photo and that she thought she was ugly in it...as usual. But I still wanted to put it up on social media and write how much I love her. Instead of getting happy she got really mad at me for putting up the picture she said that she didn't want me to put up. She told me to change the picture but instead I deleted the whole post because it's either the picture I pick or nothing at all. I won't alter something I uploaded out of love because she doesn't like how she looks in a picture. And for your information the picture was identical too all the others I took. And when I came home from work today she was still pissed off about it and was drinking a lot of soda and eating a whole bag of cheese doodles for comfort and was all cold on me after she had spammed me all day to remove the picture. So my question is if this is normal? We are both 24 years old, been together for two years. And I just feel like this is a very immature behavior . It's not like it's the first time but it's certainly the biggest reaction this far. I mean am I right for being mad at her right now for how immature she is? Or am I in the wrong? I wanna tell her how immature I think she is for our age but I don't know if that's a good idea. P.S. I've been with sensitive girls before but that was in my teens. Is this normal for adult women to be this sensitive? For such a small thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 19:06:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for replying, and yeah I know that she is insecure but I think that even if she is insecure the way she reacts over it is a lack of maturity when it comes to expressing herself. Or am I wrong?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 19:10:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>But she says that every single picture I take is ugly? If I always did as she said I would never be able to put up a picture of her. And I never do stuff to show off to people, how dare you? I did it to express my love openly and because I wanted to put up a picture on my birthday, since that was what we were celebrating and I wanted to thank her for the whole day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 19:18:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>She never thinks she looks good in any pics? If I followed that all the time then I would never be able to put up any picture of her. And since she payed for a hotel and a restaurant and gave me a nice present I saw it fitting to post a beautiful picture of my girlfriend and tell her how thankful I am for having such a woman in my life. And then all I get is piss all over me? How am I rude? Please explain.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 19:26:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I should put up a picture of a black box and thank my girlfriend instead or never put up something that has to do with her? Or maybe she could just have appreciated my gesture instead? No I think that in a normal adult relationship one should be able to take pictures of each other some times and also express your adoration towards each other and show what a beautiful and kind hearted partner you have to others, to raise her and not to show off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 06:20:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You really don't understand huh? So if let's say you did something wonderful for your parents. The next day when you wake up, you see that they posted a picture of you on let's say Facebook and thanked you and told all of your friends and family how much they appreciate and love you. You think the right response to that is to write to them and tell them how immature they are and how they need to grow up and how stupid it is to care how you appear on social media? No sir, you are the immature one, and the one who needs to grow up. And I don't understand all this focus on me uploading a picture on social media and why I want to do that. My question was about the resulting behavior around the situation, not the social media thing itself. God damn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 18:42:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn you are a damn lunatic, and a fucking jerk, keep calm. She loves when I do it, this time she didn't, what do you know? Nothing. So don't even reply anymore. For your information she has done the same to me without me even reacting. So don't try and make me sound like a thick headed idiot with you trying to be clear with me what she likes and don't like.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 19:09:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn, if he really said this, I'm a bit salty as well. A real king shouldn't have to declare himself as a king. This is disappointing...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 23:51:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why all these Barca fans in our sub? You jealous of our sub now? You don't have your own?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 17:45:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nooo Isco is warming up...prepare for the game to die</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 17:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>One bicycle kick = 2 months injury</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 15:40:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imagine the faces of everyone in the world if we get a third consecutive UCL trophy! Bliss! Especially the Barca fans!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 22:30:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dont you dare criticize a player who has piss poor form, misses shots 2 meters in front of goal, treats his fellow national team players like trash. A player who is not a striker but a straight passer to cr7 in a nr9 shirt. Who has cost us a lot of important matches with his inability to score and who sometimes seem to disappear when he should be fighting for his career. How dare you!! We shall all downvote you! (I'm talking like this to be able to criticize without getting shot down by all the fanboys)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 23:04:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd take cavani over benzema anyday I'll say (let the downvotes begin!).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Our chances in el clasico?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 23:19:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Guys let me hear what you all think, what are our chances to win this one for real? I believe in Real Madrid always but I am so nervous, I can't even sleep right now and it is Wednesday!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 16:36:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Plus this match is a lot more important for us it seems. Since this is really decisive in the league. And it seems that the players won't come into this without full concentration and ambition. They know the importance of this game. But one of my best friends is a Barcelona supporter so I am fearing the awful banter that will follow a loss haha. And I'm not really one to brag if we win.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 16:41:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could you make one with Ramos pretty please?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 21:22:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks like everyone has been forced to play together in our team, I see no chemistry, no will and no happiness whatsoever :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 21:23:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Back to shitty crosses again lol, fuck me for thinking new year, new tactics .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 22:11:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Carvajal put his foot in front and pushed the ball so Lucas shot got skewed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 21:38:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is not the first he saves our asses since he came back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 21:42:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>When he came on in CWC as a sub and scored a winner</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Could there be a shock transfer like this you think? And how much credibility does the express have? Maybe the statements about transfers in January from zidane has all been charades to keep everyone in the dark? ;)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 18:11:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 22:53:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like how kovacic literally had to wave both arms to get a pass when we were attacking and he still got a late pass and because of that nothing came of it....sigh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 23:03:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't yet seen in any match what makes Ceballos so talked about? Can somebody please explain? And I am serious. I haven't seen anything special from him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 23:11:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the first match ever that I have stopped watching before it is done...this just makes me feel bad to watch. And I feel disappointed...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 23:16:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you come to Real, all of your past glories are gone. As Morientes said, at the bernabeu you have to prove yourself again. Seems like that vision has died in the young today seeing as ceballos is yapping about more playing time when he doesn't prove himself when he gets to play... :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 23:17:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>"The kids" didn't win at home versus a lower division team...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 23:19:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are we playing lacrosse or football?  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 23:32:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also because I am way past my bedtime haha,.. I have work tomorrow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 16:54:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are playing good today! Nice to see! But can Kroos please stop with his shots aimed at the moon? How many of those has really hit the net over the last seasons...?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 17:03:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fucking referees!!! About time video refereeing made its way to La Liga, these decisions are appalling!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 18:11:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>My reactions is not even to be mad anymore...I'm just expressionless... this is just so disappointing...and I feel bad for our players that is playing good. And I feel bad for our youngsters not getting any game time, they can atleast win matches...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 22:16:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Leganes is just chilling with the ball, it's like they have no worries. They should be terrified to face Real Madrid and they should be all pressured by us in the attacking half but no...they chill like we are a segunda b team. It's embarrassing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 22:52:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm tearing my chest hair out, it looks like we are doing the same "attack" over and over again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 23:22:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it normal to be mad every time you see Vazquez smug face?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 23:27:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm done with this shit, downvote me all you want but #zidaneout</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 00:38:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks brilliant but can you make one without a green background? Makes it hard to see icons. Black or white is awesome  #128076; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 21:08:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well he got the other players fingers in the face so maybe that made him unfocused for a sec and his elbow went up. Not a yellow in my book.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 21:27:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The look on Ronaldo's face when he is offside or fouls someone makes me a bit angry this season. It's like he thinks he is above the rules and believe everyone else's is wrong on all occasions. Come on man. Man up and accept that everyone makes mistakes sometimes. And maybe if he actually accepts that he is doing stuff wrong he can improve again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 21:30:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know that he is like that overall but I accept it on seasons when he plays like a god and makes up for that slight dip in attitude. But not right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 21:53:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>But he will come back  #128076; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 21:54:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I now finally understand and relate to Kroos pace rating in FIFA  #128514; haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 21:58:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>All my love to Navas</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 22:17:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for everything Luka Modric</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 22:24:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>The upvotes I'm gonna give the person who posts that pic of nacho and Isco!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 22:24:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahahah Ronaldo to the cameraman lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 22:31:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even the Swedish commentator is speechless...he's baffled by real madrids defense</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Something to shed some hope!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 23:31:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 16:54:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nathaniel Clyne?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 17:03:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>"All luck" according to ESPN podcast...by Steve Nicholl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 17:34:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol that was not what they said in their podcast, said it was mostly luck and a low quality of play overall. Very low, an unorganized chaos they said. Damn turncoats.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 21:21:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not even disappointed, was expecting that for like 15 mins.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 22:38:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nacho in pain after final signal :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 22:41:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cant believe no one talks about that rat Suarez diving like a professional scuba diver.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 23:02:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Except the whole game well the one where he got his yellow card.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 19:57:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Leganes is playing 11 men, we are playing 10 + 1 (Isco) it's so obvious damn. Maybe Zidane is introducing a new type of football.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 19:59:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is la Liga mate :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 20:04:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whenever I see Isco ball hogging (every time he touches a ball) I think of that scene in the movie GOAL! Where the Newcastle coach shoots the ball a long way and asks Mu #241;ez to run and get it. He fails every time so the coach says "do you know why you can't catch the ball?" Where Mu #241;ez says "I need to run faster?". The coach says "no, the ball can travel faster than you! In this team we pass the ball! So pass!". I don't think Isco has seen that movie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 20:06:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe zidane needs to bring the popcorn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 20:09:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your comment isn't appreciated enough</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 20:14:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Article about Isco "And when he did finally get on in the 73rd minute, he decided to hog the ball and show off his skills, rather than play for the team. An attitude that didn #8217;t please Luka Modric, who snapped at him and told him to  #8216;pass the ball a bit. #8217; Isco then shushed him, but little Modric wasn #8217;t having his insolence, and told him  #8216;don #8217;t do that. #8217; Don't mess with modric" - article from May 2, 2016. He's been at it a long time apparently lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 20:20:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Isco in his younger years!! :'D](https://i2-prod.mirror.co.uk/incoming/article4436256.ece/ALTERNATES/s1227b/Animal-pictures-of-the-week.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 20:22:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol swedish commentator called Bale "a wild beautiful stallion"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 20:29:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who's this Ceballos you speak of?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 20:31:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>El capitano!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 20:32:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I loled</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 20:34:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was just sad to see...Ceballos, don't leave us :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 22:00:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope This is gonna turn into a meme</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 22:21:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ronaldo should have had 50 hattricks now!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 22:31:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's wrong with bale? :( didn't even smile a lot after his goal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 18:47:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it only me or does Bale look angry and fed up every time they do a closeup of him?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 18:53:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Theo Bieber</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 18:58:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't fathom how we can drop him... if we do it's really stupid, that's what I think atleast, will miss him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:00:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>True that...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:03:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thinks it's alright with nacho, looks like he just injured his ankle when he stepped wrong. I don't think that takes too long to heal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:04:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you think Theos hair is so white that it will pick up grass stains?  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:05:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't see any crying though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:09:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>It could have been something else that was triggered than the ankle when he stepped wrong yes :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:10:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only secure enough to finish when no one else is moving on the pitch  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:13:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>By the way lads, it feels like we get a lot of penalties, does anyone know which team has gotten the most penalties so far in La Liga? Any stats?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:14:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the peroxide is stinging his eyes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:16:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok! Thanks for the info</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:18:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I give 10 points for that barrel roll</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:23:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know that formations get to much of a blame when things go wrong. Everyone who has played football knows that it looks good on paper when you have a certain formation but when the game starts, people run all over the place to perform the idea that the manager has planned. A formation is a good backbone but it's not that important in the end.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:28:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't say that it doesn't matter? Tell me where I wrote this? I said that it gets too much of the blame if someone loses. Especially us this season. And I have actually seen a clip of Johan Cruyf saying that a formation is just a backbone and when the game starts we play a bit differently. So if you think my views are on an amateur level then so are cruyfs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:39:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>As far as I've heard and read cruyf is seen as a tactical genius and his best asset was his understanding of the game? I think I will rather take the words of an actual player of the game at the highest level than from you. He said in the clip that all looks well and good on paper but when the match starts there is a lot of fluidity through the formation, players flow between each others positions to and from. Formations he said is also a simplified version of explaining the tactics for people who doesn't know football at an advanced level, and in reality there is a lot more behind it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:46:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bale has attitude problems right? I mean I love the guy to death but still  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:54:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is what makes you confident? Being able to not care about what people think? It comes from the inside and from how people treat you on the outside.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 20:05:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly! So how Real Madrid perform this season can't be blamed so much on the actually formation but more of the tactics from zidane and the players performances themselves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 22:10:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>That made My day, I'm so pleased with life atm, because I witnessed that golazo!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 22:13:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is it so quiet in here? :o</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 22:31:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to wreck Barcelona in the champions league, would be sweet!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is it just me or does Bale look out of place in this shot and also quite sad? :( he looks like a kid who just wants to be in the photo to look like he's one of the cool guys but nobody cares about him. Sad shit, or maybe I'm overreacting</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 11:06:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 23:13:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jag brukar l #228;gga v #228;skan d #228;r s #229; att folk inte ska s #228;tta sig bredvid mig n #228;r jag v #228;l sitter d #229;. Brukar st #229;. Men jag  #228;r 192cm och ganska bred d #229; jag tr #228;nar och v #228;ger ca 98kg. P #229; grund av detta s #229; kan jag helt seri #246;st oftast inte sitta med benen rakt fram utan jag beh #246;ver vinkla dem. Detta fattar inte folk och ska tr #228;nga sig in  #228;nd #229;, d #229; f #229;r man sitta med kn #228;na intryckta i s #228;tet framf #246;r och d #229; jag har ett d #229;ligt kn #228; s #229;  #228;r det sm #228;rtsamt. Dock h #228;nder detta inte ofta d #229; jag kanske inte ser s #229; trevlig ut att sitta bredvid o f #246;rdomarnas land med snaggad skalle och n #228;svingepiercing. :'D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 07:57:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are an idiot. He's the best capitan ever. And cares so much he left his company and went down to cheer on his lads.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 22:20:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I the only who thinks that we are not playing good at all? Our players are looking like they don't care enough. No creativity, no flair, just cross cross cross like early in the season...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 22:28:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks guys! Just giving my two cents! Feeling the love</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 22:44:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I must agree now, playing so good, I like all the attacks from Bilbao. And the nervousness in the defense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 23:21:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>No we were the best, don't you see? That's why it was a draw</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 23:23:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I said that we didn't play good in half time and you all downvoted me to hell. Do you still think so huh? A draw against Bilbao on home turf with a shitty display? Fuck you all who downvoted me and shame on you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 23:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah keep on downvoting me!  #128076; #127995; #128076; #127995; let's set a record</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 23:26:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh I'm the douche? I told the truth</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 10:30:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is -20 all you've got?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 21:32:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't wanna face salah in a final :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 21:38:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I beg you papa Perez! Splash some cash and steal the mofo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 21:53:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have actually never heard someone being afraid of him. And all my friends watch football. People mostly say shit like "only way he is gonna score is with a penalty" or "afraid of a diving peynaldo? Nah" so mostly negative comments about him. Never heard someone being afraid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 21:58:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not saying that I wouldn't fear him, I would fear him the most. I love our cristi  #128076; #127995;I just said I always se slander. But I should check r/bayern</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 22:05:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally read their whole pre-match thread and didn't see a single comment about fearing Ronaldo. Saw one about Salah though haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 22:08:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm actually 25 and so are they. And it's just banter. And I never said they did. I just said that I have never heard or read anyone fearing him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 22:10:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It says stop Ronaldo? Not I'm afraid he's gonna score, or anything like that. Stopping or trying to stop a main goal scorer is pretty standard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 22:12:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>You really got pissed? I was just being factual about my statement. I'm sry if I came of as stubborn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 22:13:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never asked anyone to discuss it though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 07:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, I didn't take it like that. How you read into it is not my fault. I meant that I have never heard it from my friends OR read it anywhere else. But everyone chose to focus about trying to make me look naive. And thanks for the downrates btw.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 22:04:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Navaz Looks like a formidable aztec warrior!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 23:00:21</DATE>
    <TEXT> #161;Hala Madrid!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 07:57:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can buy it from you but I won't be able to until payday which is the 25th. So I'll see if his thread is still alive by then.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 08:04:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which player on the back?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 08:09:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely, gonna buy a new kit on 25th anyway as well with Ramos haha. My girlfriend washed my 2016/2017 kit so the logo fell off...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 22:09:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for all the tips guys! Sure will heed them in the future.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 00:23:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>They have it in Sweden and you can use it tomorrow but you gotta have the swedish football streaming service :/ I'm swedish but I'm gonna watch it at a friends house.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 13:52:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sent a request to you, name is beastonehunned</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Calmate Los Blancos Por Favor...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 08:58:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, I have been reading a lot of depressing stuff on this forum lately, though it seems reoccurring every season no matter what happens. So for one, yes we have had a beautiful streak of winning three champions league titles in a row, and yes we have only won one la liga title during this time. You see you can pick holes through everything, and when you get something you have striven for you just want more. This is important but it is just as important to not forget and writhe in agony and pity. All these threads complaining about our situation doesn't help anyone, it makes the threadstarters anxious and the readers anxious. So come one, the season hasn't started yet, but the complaints have. I don't know what careers any of you have, but I think that it's most likely not a position of power in the club or a position at all. The people at Real Madrid are no morons or imbeciles, they know what they are doing, they have had the exact conversations we have had in this forum, albeit with more confidence i guess. So believe me or believe in the club, they are working on it. This is their job, and they have done it well and the evidence is in the clubs history. Believing in the club is one of the most important aspects of being a supporter and the belief lately has been weak. Please don't be weak, be strong, together we are Real Madrid! P.S. I hope the players of the club never sees what has been written here lately, it would make them disappointed I believe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 09:12:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>More posts like this please. It boosts morale for everybody. It is not like this is their first season in charge, if it was the accusations would have had some grain of truth in them. But these are seasoned tacticians and businessmen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 09:29:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>The thing is, you have a right to post critique and we should never bury our heads in the sand. But the general posts I have seen have been complaining, not giving critique, there is a difference. And for one, complaining never helps anyone, and strong people don't complain. The club is positive I think, and so is the management, they reflect it anyhow, and so should we as supporters. Because it has been toxic to read this forum lately.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 09:42:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tried at least haha. My Spanish is not very good. If you could reply with the correct term, it would help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 10:13:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate the lecture, I really do, this is good criticism, not complaining like in most threads. I always like to learn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 10:35:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think they have earned the right of us having faith in them, how much or how little is really up to yourself. And when it comes to questionable decisions I understand, for the uninvited a lot of decision can seem questionable. The thing is, everything is not about what we want as a club and about the economical aspect, neither you or I have a definitive answer of what was fully behind Ronaldos transfer. One aspect for the club was the money of course, but if Ronaldo wanted to leave don't you think he has earned the right to make that decision? I personally think it was a mixture of a lot of different aspects, it is rarely as simple as a one answer question. It was the right time, the right price and the right emotional drive. And I think it is a different subject when it comes to the Man Utd situation, it is harder to compare to now. And when it comes to Modric, of course I want him to stay, but not at the cost of what may punish us down the road, we don't know what will have the most positive outcome, forcing modric to stay two seasons more with kovacic on the bench and ceballos with no playing time. Or letting kovacic shouldering the responsibility and see where it leads while we cash out on the best possible deal we will ever get for Modric. Time will tell, it is a risky game, but risky games give the greatest rewards. I have faith until proven otherwise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 11:55:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even when you assemble your house accordingly and as good as possible certain events may still blow all that away. You can be as good as tiger woods in PGA and still lose. You can be be the best motogp racer in the world and still crash. Just because we had one season in recent history where we didn't do as good as planned it doesn't mean that they don't know what they are doing, losing is learning. And using the experience from our failed la Liga season is exactly what I think they are doing. And calling my opinion a load of shit won't get you anywhere else than reproach from people and bad karma for you. And I don't really mind so you don't need to tell me your sorry, it's ok, I understand your anxiousness. Nobody is excused from criticism, which I didn't say, but I feel that most of the "criticism" has been more of a complaining than true criticism. Just my five cents.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 12:48:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't even know what to answer here. You are projecting stuff now out of the blue. The season hasn't even begun, calm down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 13:21:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course there is a lot of work to be done, i don't think no one has denied that fact. But from my viewpoint that is exactly what has been done so far, a new manager with new tactics and some small transfers is moving in the right direction. We don't know the outcome of these changes until the season has begun. For me that means it is to early to start calling things a load of bullshit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 13:43:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look, I'm with you, I never said that we shouldn't be skeptic, or that we should kid ourselves about the nature of the situation. I was just posting this to try and stop all the complaining, and stop all the shit throwing. I't reeks of toxicity in this forum lately. But what I am saying also is that I myself will at least give them until the beginning of the season until i start trying to predict our whole season. So to underline, everything is not well, everything is not a 100% and sad things has happened lately but that doesn't mean we should throw a shitfest at our club before they have even started playing the season.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 13:46:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>My name doesn't imply 24/7 skepticism, it is put where I feel it is needed. And I haven't said that I am not skeptic to it all right now, but I'm not gonna start complaining about every little thing because of that. I am skeptic, but I am holding off my judgement of it all until the season is in full swing and there actually is more content to critique.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 00:40:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pass pass pass throw a shady ass long ball aimed at the moon pass pass pass through ball which lands on juventus feet pass pass pass long ball aimed at the stands haha lol, liking this new style so far</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 00:42:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 00:45:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>We still have the fire breathing welsh dragon!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 01:22:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>The smiles they already put on my face gotta love our boys!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 01:25:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>In this match we have seen a Vinsensio! Is this a term?! Is it?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 01:27:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still a kid. Nerves. Love him this far though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 01:33:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so happy with what I'm seeing atm from our youth, but I know, and so do you, that we are surely gonna be frustrated with them a lot during this season as is normal. Ups and downs. But yeah, I'm loving it and can't wait.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 01:37:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Took the words from my mind man! True shit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 01:47:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a save from Lunin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Sky Italy] Kovacic loan will have an option to buy for Chelsea  #8226; r/soccer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 15:40:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 11:01:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Gal #225;cticos (Spanish for galactics, referring to superstars) are expensive, world-famous Real Madrid football players" Actually I can't find any definition that says that a galactico is only someone who has won a Ballon D'or. It is generally considered to be a superstar signing. James is considered and was considered a galactico at the time, so was Beckham etc. Beckham is even referred to as a galactico in a Real Madrids own documentary on youtube.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 17:27:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would love for that to be true</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 21:12:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>So you want to lower yourself to his level? Great...this sort of shit shouldn't be promoted or endorsed in any way...shameful. I hope you realize this as you get older and more keen on seeing things from different viewpoints and not just this simple minded tunnel vision.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can these damn rumors stop already!! I can't take it :( even if it is lies!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 21:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 21:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nobody was thinking of doing this to hurt someone with rats physically ofc, it's the psychological shit throwing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 21:33:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>So you are validating his claims of wanting to be with his children and then you are still agreeing to publicly shame him for abiding by that same reason? Ofc his behavior was bad?! But he's a human ffs and a person. This is silly behavior from football fans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 21:34:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>So do you have evidence of me booing a Real Madrid player?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 21:38:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ofc not, but is him being unprofessional a strong enough reason for thousands of people to publicly shame him at his workplace?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 21:40:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>With that same logic I'm a racist because I'm a swede and some swedes are racist and some are not. But because I am part of the group known as swedes I am not allowed to have an opinion or talk about racism without any evidence of me being a racist? I just see salt talking and no logic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 21:55:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not being so defensive. I'm simply pointing out how stupid your comment was. So that maybe in the future you don't sound like a moron to someone else and make a fool of yourself. 1. I posted here because I saw this post here? Not at the r/atm ? 2. You made it your concern in your comment and now you are contradicting yourself? How surprising. 3. Did I say it was?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 22:07:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sigh...you know what? If you can't see your errors in this conversation then I don't really care to enlighten you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 22:51:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>And just because other people shame it is ok to do it? And it makes the people exaggerating all in the rights huh? I'm not being a wimp or a snowflake, he deserves criticism, but the level it has reached is silly and disgusting. I don't care about courtois, not a bit, but it's sad seeing people behave like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bayern's Thiago has 'agreed' terms with Real Madrid</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 17:42:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 17:49:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Thiago agrees terms](https://en.as.com/en/2018/08/10/football/1533895344_937188.html)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 21:37:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice pass from benz to bale!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Real Madrid preparing 200+ mil bid for Eden Hazard. What do you guys think? A grain of truth in it this time?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 09:56:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 21:08:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chill the fuck down people. We have the whole game in front of us. People are doing whole season reviews on a fly here ffs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 22:24:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please modric! Sign that fucking contract! And I will donate a kidney!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 22:29:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone! Anyone! I don't care! Modric is god</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 23:26:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Isco keeps losing the ball...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 23:34:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha English commentator saying casemiro uses dark arts to protect Real Madrid</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Could this be true whatsoever or is this pure bullcrap? What do you think?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 11:51:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 13:02:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't know if this is something that he has power or influence over. So I wouldn't say that it would be cred to him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 13:03:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>But if they will be forced to sell a high value player then they would have to accept some bids at least right? Because they would be forced to do so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 13:03:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>But aren't they already under FFP scrutiny? With the current squad?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 15:12:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sry mate but I don't think they will part with anyone. It's psg, the richest club in the world, they will find a way I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 15:57:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I said If</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 16:13:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not specific players, but a sum so high that they would be required to sell a more expensive player. It comes from the accusations that when they bought Neymar they broke the FFP with the transfer sum. And therefore they would have to sell players for the same value. Therefore if there is any truth to this, the logic thing would be to sell Neymar or mbappe and not 4-5 other players.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 22:58:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg we need competition for our players...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 23:01:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha yeah, but I'm thinking mostly about Marcelo, kroos and a lot of others. Benzema is looking energetic though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Up vote party for Big Benz! He made me smile today! We want our master poacher back!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 00:28:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 00:30:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Benzenaldo!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 00:31:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Le K (king) Benzema!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 00:42:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Benz is like the one who didn't want to end the relationship but ends up being more successful after a a couple of weeks out of the breakup.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 21:49:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>In my eyes a definite upgrade over Borja Mayoral!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dybala to Real Madrid, can anyone give me a reality check on this, is this a crap source or is there some small chance that it is true?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 23:11:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 23:24:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m really bad informed when it comes to what is tier 1 and tier 2 etc. is there any site or guide or any information of what is the most reliable newspapers out there? Or is it just that everybody has learned through experience?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>