<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject522</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ISIS admitted defeat after checking snapchat today</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 19:12:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Need some advice: how do you deal with getting into a fist fight as soon as you awaken also who was in the wrong...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 02:13:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Essentially I've been asking my roomate to recycle since we moved in 2 weeks ago for college and I came home drunk last night and said fuck it and threw all of his dishes away to retaliate for not recycling (BUT I WAS DRUNK) and I woke up to him punching me in the face while I was still in bed, HUNGOVER</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 05:32:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>"no papa"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 01:19:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I told my gf about my rival highschool while we were visiting my hometown from college and later we were at the movies and I was buying a ticket. Then she ran up and was like "we gotta go." Turns out she saw a girl wearing my rival highschools sweatshirt and she sucker punched her! So I could say school spirit manifests itself in weird ways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 02:45:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have passed like 20 calculated deadlines and we are still here. Who cares at this point</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 05:18:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd have to agree. In college I was able to bag about 6-7 on a slow week and my grades were all A's. My friends always figured I was able to pull so many girls because I was super smart and quick witted. I had already come to the conclusion that getting laid often makes you smarter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 05:20:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Us gamers have been oppressed for 2 long yet nobody cares about us</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 05:30:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>And you can tell. I drove through lousina recently and their roads SUCK!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 05:31:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those will get so gross that I'll no longer have to look at the inside.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 05:37:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I envy the man that you allow to mate with you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 05:45:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stuff like this is why I am always so annoyed when people only focus on little things. Like chill out, trumps your president. In 1000 years nobody will give a shit because they'll be too busy doing something we can't even comprehend so stfu.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 05:50:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>So many leaks about Russia coming out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 05:53:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or they just murdered a bunch of fish bc they can't survive the fall. Um gonna post this on /r/vegetarian and /r/vegan to see if they agree</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 15:04:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the problem with society. They are YOUR kids. You should be able to give them cyanide if you want. They aren't the states kids why do they care what happens to what's yours? Too much government oversight into things that don't concern them if you ask me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 15:09:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>If they suck too much CO2 out of the air won't all plants on earth die?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 15:10:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>OP you may not be aware but this gif is in reverse lmao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 15:13:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really because I thought the Sex Junk song was inspirational. It litterally turned me and my friends gay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 15:28:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>What if he had wheels instead of paws?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 15:31:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought this was /r/circlejerk at first</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 15:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be fair the Trump supporter was likely getting harassed. Atleast from my observations. But I'm a European so idk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 15:38:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Than why isn't the earth 100% smooth?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 15:39:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought race was a social construct and had nothing to do with ACTUAL differences?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 17:48:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>This name quote will be said by many in like 20 years when some new guy is president and they'll be like "this is different than Trump and *whoever is next* because of *reasons. * People always think this same thing because they don't like who's in power. It'll be fine like it always is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 17:50:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not an expert but I'm pretty sure the Samoan PM isn't a world leader in the slightest sense. What does Samoa do for world leading?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 19:53:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but who actually cares about the UN besides countries that don't matter?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 05:50:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I envy the male you allow to mate with you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 06:13:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idk about on the blackhawk but settling with power can happen if you have a low forward airspeed and a sink rate of atleast 600fpm in the helicopter I flew. You get out of it by moving the cyclic in any direction. Or there is a maneuver where you do full right cyclic and left pedal that'll push you out of it quicker than the first method. I've never settled with power so I cannot vouch for the effectiveness of either maneuver but I hear the ladder will get you out quicker.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 15:21:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I forgot the name awhile ago and it's been bugging me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 17:47:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've never seen a person in the kkk in my life but I sure see a lot of racist black people and this subreddit promotes them. Facts are facts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 23:44:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another childish display by the left that is sure to end le drumpf!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 23:45:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's the reason he won anyways</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 00:00:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Buzz aldrin is full of himself... Have you seen his Twitter? Calm down fella</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 00:07:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go to bed earlier idiots. 830 is for unproductive members of society</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 00:08:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I forgive him. Mistakes happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 00:10:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not like that's his own doing! He was SELECTED. It could've been practically anyone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 00:12:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this /r/furries?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 01:03:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you a doctor?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 01:05:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you hitting on his wife through him?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 02:42:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I was interviewing for a job at this office and pulled up into that parking lot I'd just leave</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 05:01:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow just called em and I just got a degree</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 05:35:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why tf isn't there a subreddit for this?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 14:39:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why would you unsub? That sub is fucking hilarious  #128514;  #128514;  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 14:59:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been lurking since 2005</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 16:14:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reported</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 17:33:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>James Cameron has been outdone at his own movie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 18:34:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's like 5 episodes where they go to the moon and the moon but with volcanoes. Also Greece and Mongolia. A lot of Egypt too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 18:38:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>How did your dad know if your mum was attractive or not? Also how can a blind dude bang girls but not me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 21:26:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe for you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:21:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be fair, I have eaten vegetarian foods and enjoyed them but I think it's unfair to insinuate that omni foods taste bad. There is just as much potential for flavor. You could litterally put salt on a brick of coal and it'd probably be palatable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:22:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Upvote if you give a shit about Samoa  #127484; #127480;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:26:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>My life is dedicated to making the most flavorful batch of fries ever made. I am bankrupt atm because I spent it all on potatoes. But one day I will do it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:26:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who Tha fuck is ruchard hamman</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:33:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did not realize this about pawn shop. Thank you for you're service</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:45:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright well I believe you bet try posting this to /r/foodporn. I think it's good enough to get upvotes there dude!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:50:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I essentially only drink soda. Water is too boring and I don't deserve to drink poor people liquid. Haven't drank an actual glass of water since like 2016 I believe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My girlfriend is napping but I know she is on her period. Do I need to wake her up at all so that she can change it at the right time?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:06:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never had much interaction with a female before this...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:17:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I just don't want her angry if I didn't wake her up because idk how it works</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:39:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man now the illegals are vandalizing it too?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:09:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I showed her the post and she said it should be on /r/wholesomecringe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:14:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>She said I can't be concerned about what is going on down there till marriage if it happens</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>