<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject4785</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How important is breakfast?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-12 06:25:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>How important is it to eat a good breakfast if you want to lose weight? I am very bad at eating breakfast. I have seven breakfasts outlined on my weekly menu, and I'm supposed to eat them every day, but I don't always follow them. (it's the one part of my menu that i fail most). I do have to eat something in the morning, because I take a med that requires me to take it with food, but hopefully that won't be a forever med, and often, I wind up just eating a quick granola bar or something so that the med is taken with food. I've seen studies that have shown that eating breakfast helps with weight loss. I.e. two groups, both consumed the same number of calories in a day, but one ate breakfast and one skipped it. The breakfast eaters lost more weight than the non breakfast eaters, and sometimes the non breakfast eaters gained weight. But then, I read about a fasting type diet, which to me basically looks like skipping breakfast. If it works, then one might conclude eating breakfast isn't so necessary. So, what's the real scoop on breakfast?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Trouble with calorie counting/not always cooking for myself</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-17 03:10:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>O.k. I have a kind of tricky situation here. I am required to make a weekly menu and grocery list before I go shopping. So is my roommate. I usually make my menu when the ads come out so I can stretch my money the farthest by planning foods that are on sale. I always include a fresh fruit with each lunch and supper, and I eat some sort of veggie with lunch (usually carrots or sugar snap peas--raw), and I serve a fresh or frozen veggie with dinner. Well, today I made my menu with an eye to calorie counting. Breakfast and Lunch were fairly easy. Dinner, not so much as I tend to cook from scratch, and am not exactly sure how to add up the calories. But in the future, I can use recipes with nutritional information. This week I am trying to empty my freezer, so in the future I will know my calories. (I cook two days when I work and on those days I don't get home until about supper time, so I usually pull left overs out of the freezer or cook in the crock pot). So, I can get a decent calorie count for the days I cook. But, my roommate cooks three suppers a week. I don't really know how to count calories for her suppers. Also, her meals aren't as healthy as mine. She counts french fries as a vegetable. She serves chips a lot (I don't eat them otherwise, my vice is sweets), and she often makes a dessert as well. I get around the dessert by eating it as my bedtime snack with meds (because I have to eat with meds). She doesn't always have a fruit--usually it's either a vegetable or a fruit, not both. She has a lower food budget than I do, but not much, and she cooks one less night a week. I know staff works with her to make healthy menus. In the beginning, she had almost no fruits and veggies, and was counting Kool-aid as a juice (and therefore a fruit!). She was resistant to changing her menus, but when staff explained she didn't have to change anything, just add fruits and veggies, she was less resistant. So, the fact that she has any fruits and veggies on her menu is progress. But, I still don't know how to put her meals into MFP. Or mine that I've already prepared. And I know that unless I reduce calories, as well as start exercising, I'm not going to shed the weight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How accurate is MFP on calorie intake?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-20 05:35:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>O.k., so I haven't been at this very long. Just a few days over a week, according to my wii fit. But, I'm a little concerned by how many calories MFP is suggesting I eat in a day. (1510) When I lived at the RCF (residential care facility) I started on their basic eating plan, and I *thought* it was around 1800-2000 calories. I gained all my weight on that plan. I was eventually switched to the diet plan (1500 cal). I lost a little weight, but really mostly stopped gaining. So, I'm kinda wondering if I should be eating less than 1510 calories to lose weight. But, from counting calories, I think it would be very hard for me to eat less. I'm usually right at or a little over for the day. My only scale is my wii fit (but I think I may start weighing myself on the scale at the YMCA). I have been doing the wii everynight since I started (except the last two, but did it again tonight). I know it's not the best, but it's what I have. I set a goal of 2lbs in 2weeks. at the end of last week, I was down a pound with one pound and one week to go. Tonight, my weight was up, and now I have 3.5 lbs to lose in a little less than a week!! HELP! I dont' eat back what I exercise and other calculators are giving me similar daily calories.... TL DR Been using MFP, think it's telling me to eat too much, gained 1.5lbs in my 1st week...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Would this work for a salad dressing?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-25 05:52:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>O.k., I like ranch dressing. But, it's not exactly healthy. I can make a decent ranch dip by mixing ranch dressing mix with plain greek yogurt. What if I thinned that mixture with some sort of vinegar? Would that make a ranch dressing, or would the greek yogurt not work right with vinegar? Normally I think I would mix ranch mix with mayo and vinegar for a dressing, so the yogurt would take the place of the mayo. I know in the dip it's replacing sour cream, so not quite the same as mayo? Is it worth experimenting with, or should I not bother?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can one bad day derail your whole week?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-26 04:37:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I eat poorly enough on one day, can it negate all the good eating I've done for the week? I know enough that if I have a bad day, I won't try and make up for it the next day by starving myself. But, if I ate too many calories, could it cancel out a weeks worth of calorie deficit? Currently I have MFP set to a 1260 calorie diet. Supposedly that should mean a 1.5lbs a week loss. 1510 calories is a 1lb a week loss. I'm not too worried if I go over my 1260 by a little (less than 100 cal), but I try to stay close. Yesterday was bad. I skipped breakfast, but wound up eating burger king for lunch. Then, my roommate decided she didn't want to cook, so we went to Pizza Ranch for supper. (an all you can eat Pizza buffet). So, when I totaled my calories for the day, I was over the 1260 by a little over 600 calories!!! (I was semi-good at the pizza place, only one plate, 2 slices pizza, 2 cheese sticks and some dipping sauce). I had planned for today to be my bad day, since I had a pizza party tonight. I ate sparingly earlier to help, and only went over by about 150cal, so that wasn't too bad. If I hadn't caved and had a third slice of pizza, I may have been under! Tomorrow might not be good either--it's a friends birthday, and we're having her over for lunch. I can eat mostly well, but the birthday cake will get me. One tiny piece can't hurt too much though. So, yeah, I know several bad days could def. derail my diet, but will yesterday negate my whole week because I was over by so many calories? Or could I still manage a loss if I'm careful from here on out?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Strange question, but do meds have calories?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-04 19:33:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>The title pretty much says it all. I don't log them as having calories, but maybe they do have some? I'm on rather a lot, so could they affect my daily goal?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shocked by my homemade soup calories</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-05 18:49:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, I just put a homemade soup of mine into Lose It recipe, to find out the number of calories. For the most part, it is a really low-cal soup--UNTIL you add the rice!!! I had no idea that rice had so many calories. So, next time I make it, I will put in half the rice, or maybe none--I think it would be good w/out any rice. (the rice in the soup was about 1400 cal, the only thing that came even close was the chicken at 440 cal!)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What should I eat for lunch?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-07 03:24:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been mostly eating canned soup with crackers and a fruit for lunch. It has served me well. But, I'm getting a little bored of it. Even with all the different flavors of soup. It's still very cold here, and the hot soup does feel good, but I'm in the mood to change things up a bit. I'm aiming for around 300cal at lunch. So, my new idea is to have a greek yogurt (plain) with ranch mixed in (the only way I like it), and eat some veggies (bell peppers and carrots or celery) with it. I usually have a fruit too. My calculations have that at around 200cal, so I've got another 100 cal to go. I plan to consume the whole yogurt--but it's got protein, and dairy. What should I eat for the last 100cal? Some sort of carb? (maybe a 100cal pack of crackers or something?). Or eat more protein? Or, leave my lunch as it is and have a 100cal snack in the afternoon? Or leave my lunch the way it is and have it on the days my roommate cooks and dinner is out of my control? Any suggestions would be helpful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Made a yummy low-cal dinner that my roommate approved of!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-09 18:35:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>The title says most of it. My dinner was around 300cal (this is something I'm going to put into my lunch rotations), but very filling and my roommate liked it and got full!! (usually when she cooks, she makes something that has four servings, and feeds me plus her and leftovers for her lunch the next day. I probably eat 3/4 of a serving so she eats a little over 1.5 servings at each meal!) Here's what I did: I took a pita pocket (1/2 of one, 100cal) and put two tablespoons of cream cheese (measured mine, just spread some on for my roomie), put one piece of deli turkey (mesquite smoked), and filled it with tons of veggies (lettuce, cucumber, bell pepper, tomato). It was yummy, and both of us were stuffed! We also had a fruit. A clementine for 35cal. So, not bad all together. And I weighed myself on my Wii last night--I hadn't been on for a week, I was down 3.5 lbs!!c</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Good Food Scale</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-10 19:56:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>O.k. I don't currently have a food scale. I am measuring with measuring cups and spoons, and relying on the wieght the meat counter slapped on my package of chicken, beef whatever. For various reasons, I cannot just order one online. But, I will be going to the 'big city' in the near future, and a trip to Bed Bath and Beyond is definitely in the cards. I'm guessing I could find a food scale there, right? If so, what is a good brand that they would carry? About how much would it cost? What about Williams Sonoma, would they have a good one? And would it be reasonable to buy on there, or would it be mondo expensive at a place like Williams Sonoma, but the same scale could be found at BB amp;B for cheaper?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I HATE shopping for pants (Rant)!!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-13 03:03:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sigh. So, I went clothes shopping today, to spend my Christmas gift certificates. I would have liked to have saved them for when I lost weight and got skinnier, but I needed new clothes now, so, I had to buy some. Tops are easy. I can often fit into a regular size XL, and in plus sizes I'm either an X or a 1X. The hardest thing about tops is when a store is out of a style/color in my size. But, finding pants is HORRIBLE! I used to fit just fine in an 18 regular, I even got as low as a 16 regular once upon a time. (well, once upon a time I was a 6/8, but that was before the evil psych meds.... which aren't so evil because I am at least mentally stable). But, now, a regular 18, sometimes fits, and is sometimes too tight. But, buying W pants doesn't really work either. 16W is sometimes a bit small, or if not small just well, WRONG. 18W is too big. (why plus sized clothes are sized differently from normal clothes I will never know). But, most of the plus sized pants expect me to have more fat in places that I don't. But, they fit around the waist and behind without being too tight, but look like clown pants elsewhere. I guess Ideally I would need a regular pant in a size 20, but many of them don't go past 14. Occasionally I get lucky and find some that go to 16 and even 18. But, higher than that and you have to go to the plus sizes. And they just don't really work. But, I've been counting my calories, and I am working my way back into exercise, so HOPEFULLY the next time I go shopping, I can actually buy smaller pants.... They had really cute dress pants (for work) in the regular section that didn't go above 14. They had nothing that looked even similar in the plus sized section. Don't us bigger girls get to wear cute clothes too?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anyone here tried TOPS-Taking Off Pounds Sensibly?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-20 21:45:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>The title pretty much says it all. I'm thinking of joining, but wanted to know if anyone could share their personal experiences. My Oma (grandmother) was in TOPS pretty much my whole life, but I think it became more social for her, because I don't remember her losing much weight. After you hit your goal, you can keep going as KOPS (Keep Off Pounds Sensibly).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fell Off the Wagon</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-09 18:54:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, my. Last week was not good. I was sick for much of the week, so I didn't make it to water aerobics. That wasn't so good. When I was sick, I ate very few calories, and most of them came from the Ginger Ale I was drinking. (The only time I drink pop is when I'm sick. I already didn't drink pop when I started my healthy lifestyle, so I couldn't just cut out pop and watch some pounds melt away :( ). But, after I felt better I was HUNGRY so, I way over ate. Friday, I ate out for lunch because I worked all day, and I had fast food. Not so good. Saturday, I had planned that I would be eating out for lunch because I was going to the big city. It was going to be a semi-cheat day. We ate at Hu Hot mongolian grill. I made mostly healhty choices there. A little chicken, lots of veggies, lemon juice, ginger, once scoop of a sauce that was only 20cal/scoop. But I wanted garlic. So, I took a scoop. tried to get mostly garlic and little liquid, because the liquid it was in was oil!! Lunch wasn't too bad. But before we came home, we had ice cream, and I ordered two scoops. I told myself, it's better than the three scoops my roommate ordered. But, still not good. Supper was healthy and around 300cal. So not bad there. But, then I had a late night snack.... I'm getting back on the wagon today. But, any 'extra' progress I made by being sick and not eating was totally cancelled out by my eating habits Friday and Saturday!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Am I Doing Something Wrong?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 02:08:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>O.k. I bought a food scale in mid February. It didn't work. (I pulled out the little tab to protect the battery, and pressed the on button, and NOTHING). So, I figured it was a dud. I went back to the store where I got it, and was going to exchange it, but they were all out, so I had to get store credit. I went to a different store, and bought another food scale. I brought it home, pulled out the tab, turned it on and NOTHING! Is it something I'm doing, or did I buy two broken scales? My mom told me last night that I needed to put something on the scale to weight it before it would show me anything. I tried to explain that no, it should say something before I put anything on the scale, because I have to know if it says zero before weighing anything to make sure it is weighing the item accurately. She understood what I was saying, but still thinks for the first time, I need something on the scale before it will turn on. I don't think that sounds right at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Marinades and Calorie Counting</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-23 22:27:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>O.k., how do I do count calories in a marinade? I entered it as a recipe in MFP, and since I am marinating two little eye of round steaks (one for me, one for my roomie), I said it served two. But, most of the marinade is left behind when cooking the steak, instead of being consumed by me. So, do I count it as if I ate half the marinade, or what? I think I will, just so I will err on the high side of calories. (I'd rahter log too many than too few). Nothing in the marinade is particulary high in calories except for two TBS of canola oil. But, I'm not sure that is really a necessary ingredient. I think I may omit the oil when I make this recipe in the future.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>GA Jade Mystery Snails near Des Moines, IA</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-29 01:10:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a BUNCH of Mystery snails/apple snails (P. Diffusa) that are jade in color (gold shell, dark body). I preferr to deal locally, but MAY consider shipping if someone pays the shipping costs. It's been a VERY long time since I've shipped snails, so I would need a "how to" guide, and I would prefer to wait until the weather here is less flaky.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Trouble with MFP?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-11 03:40:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is anyone else having problems with MFP? I'm trying to log in tonight, and it won't let me. It just keeps going back to the start page where I can choose to login or register, but it gives me no error message about an incorrect password or anything...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MFP Problems</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-12 03:09:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am having issues with MFP on my home computer. It used to work just fine. Now it isn't. It works fine on my phone and it worked today from the work computer just fine. So, the issue is somehow with my home computer. I'm not sure if there is tech support, or if I can even reach tech support from my home computer. But, basically, when I try to log in, it just takes me right back to the front screen where I have the choice of creating a new account or logging in. All the links on the front page take me to the front page except for the blog link. Any ideas why MFP isn't working for me? Any ideas how to fix it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's Your Dream Tank?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-27 20:19:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just as the title says, what is your dream tank? My realistic dream tank is a 125gal planted tank. I have an empty one in my parent's basement, and when I eventually buy my own house, I will set it up. I plan to house dennison's barbs (roseline sharks)--a good healthy sized school, maybe 12. Also, six clown loaches, six pictus cats, and I'm not sure what else. Maybe some angels, maybe some GBRs, I dunno. Something for a focal piece. But, this is a realistic dream Now, for a totally off the wall dream. I would love to have a tank made by the folks on Tanked. Not sure what shape/size. I think it would be it's own room in my house and two-three rooms would have walls that opened up to the tank, so you could just watch it from any of those rooms. It would be a large tank--several hundred gallons at least. As for what would go in it, I'm not sure. Fish that get big--but not too big. I don't really want monster fish. I think I might make it a cichlid tank. Hap/peacock, maybe mbuna. Get the color in it. (one more realistic tank I want is a 65g (I have the empty tank already) hap/peacock male only tank, but I can't have too many tanks). Right now, I only have one tank (all my apartment allows, or I'd have small hosptial/QT tank as well as my main tank). It is a 37gal tank. I have a school of cherry barbs, one angel fish, a school of cory cats (juleii), a BN pleco, and a bunch of p. diffusa, (because I missed an egg clutch and it partially hatched before I found it).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Calorie Question</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-08 05:45:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have two questions about calories. The first is about no stick cooking spray. I use store brand pure canola oil. Now, I know canola oil is not calorie free. But, I understand that the cooking spray can claim to be calorie free, because such a small amount of oil is sprayed in the pan to prevent sticking that it really has almost no calories. So, at what point do you have to consider calories? My roommate goes crazy with the no stick spray, and leaves a large puddle of oil in the pan. She is afraid of sticking. So, is she spraying enough to leave calories? Second question--raw fruit and calories. Riper fruit tastes sweeter. Does it contain more calories, because it has more natural sugar than less ripe fruit? Is there enough of a difference to matter?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Chicken and Rice Question</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-03 00:38:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>O.k., I would like to make chicken and rice in the slow cooker. I work all day, and don't have time to put it in the oven when I get home. I have tried several recipes in the past, but find that even though there is plenty of liquid, my rice doesn't seem to absorb it and is still kinda crunchy. I often have this problem when I bake it in the oven as well, so I don't know what I'm doing wrong. I have boneless skinless chicken breast (about two pounds). I plan to cut it into cubes and sear them before adding them to the pot. I have a can of cream of chicken soup and a can of cream of celery soup. I plan to add those along with some water and rice. (the rice and soup/water on the bottom, the chicken on the top). How much water should I use? How much rice? Any other ingredients? I have to serve two people, but would like to get 4-6 servings. (leftovers). Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fell Off the Wagon--Big Time!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-27 01:32:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I started off doing really well. I was tracking all my calories, I was slowly getting back to my regular exercise plan (it got messed up because of some surgery), and I was all excited for my weight loss journey. Then, my mood took a nose dive (and my anxiety did the opposite), and well, I stopped doing everything. At first, I stopped tracking calories, but still ate decently. I was exercising, but I had to stop again for another surgery. (But that *SHOULD* be it for, well hopefully forever...). I then started eating not so well. At the beginning, I didn't lose more weight, but I didn't gain back what I'd lost. Now, I'm afraid to step on a scale.... On the plus side, the pants I wore last summer require a belt or they will fall off, so that is good. And, my 2x belt is almost too big (on the last holes, it barely works). But, my 1X belt isn't quite big enough (it barely makes it to the first hole). Well, I know I need to get back on the wagon and start doing this right again. But, I'm concerned that my calorie counting/restriction is what caused my mood slip in the first place. I hope not. It's also possible that I was a bit hypomanic when I first started out (which is why I was so excited), and I just experienced the inevitable crash that comes with mania. (but neither the high nor the low were so bad I had major consequences, I just went all out and then didn't on my eating). This weekend, I am visiting family for my Niece's birthday. I've decided to re-start my weight loss journey when I get back. I will track my calories again, I will not binge on cookies and ice cream, but I won't go so overboard that I can't have a treat now and again. That plan seemed to work well for me at the beginning, so I'll stick to it again. If I notice that my mood seems to take a nose dive when I start focussing on my diet, then I'll reevaluate, but I think I can handle it. I am back at water aerobics, but I leave class early because I can't do the part of class where we use the styrofoam weights (under water, they create resistance and act like actual weights). I can't lift heavy weights or do stuff like that until mid/late July when my hand will be fully healed. But, I will go to water class regularly, and once I am able I will stay the whole time. (It's a 45 minute class, sometimes I get to stay for 30min, sometimes for 40min.. it all depends on how much time the instructor leaves for the weights). TLDR Fell off the wagon when my mood took a nose dive. Trying to get back on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Improper use of feeder fish (RANT)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-05 01:01:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>O.k., I get that most feeder fish are bought for the purpose of feeding other critters--mostly big fish or reptiles. Hence the name feeder fish. Although the merits of whether these should be fed to the critters concerned could be debated, I generally have no issues with them being food. Sure, they don't have the same chance of escape as in the wild, but their death is quick and I'm guessing relatively painless. I do not like them being used as centerpieces in weddings--what happens after the wedding? Who will care for the fish? Will they all go home to tiny bowls and live a miserable life? I also do not like them as carnival prizes, for much the same reason as why they make bad wedding centerpieces. I hate that fish bowls and small tanks come with pictures of goldfish on them, since they are too small and/or inappropriate for the fish or both. But, none of that compares to what I saw today. My roommate and I were at our local pool for some 4th of July fun and games. One game involved releasing LIVE FEEDER FISH into the SWIMMING POOL!!! Then, the kids went into the water and tried to catch the fish. When they caught a fish (using their hands) they went to the pool office and got a soda cup (with water) and a lid to put their fish in. They got to take the fish home to keep as a pet. I think they also got a baloon as a prize for catching a fish. I'm sure these fish will all die soon, since the pool is a chlorinated pool. Plus, a healthy fish in a huge pool would not easily be caught by hand! Most parents were shocked as well. I guess in years past, they floated the fish in bags in the water, so they wouldn't be exposed to the chlorine. But, I guess they decided that catching fish in bags was too easy, so in the pool water they all went. My roommate was outraged as well, but mostly because she was then afraid to go in the water because she thought the fish might bite her, LOL. TLDR: they put live fish in our public (chlorinated) pool, and had the kids catch them in their hands for a 4th of July game!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does this happen to anyone else?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-11 18:43:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>O.k., I weigh myself once a week. If/when I weighed more often, the daily fluctuations made me crazy. So, I weigh once a week with similar circumstances (time of day, clothing etc.) I am aiming for a 1-1.5lb a week loss, so when the scale shows I have lost about a pound, I am satisfied. But, I am also worried. I mean, what if the weight it is showing I lost is just because I was a bit dehydrated or something? What if the next week, I'm the same or higher? I always wonder about that, and wonder if I'm really seeing meaningful weight loss or just seeing the everyday fluctuation of weight. I am always happy/relieved when the next week I have lost another about a pound. Then I figure at least my weight from the week before was probably right. And, over time those pounds have added up. (I was very excited to change my flair to 15, and quite relieved that when I back-slid, I only gained 2lbs, so I didn't need to change my flair). TLDR for those losing a small (1-1.5lb a week) amount of weight at a time, do you ever wonder if the loss on the scale is real loss, or just fluctuation?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Where I live we aren't allowed to have Q-tips because we might clean our ears with them. I always tell my friends how dangerous it is to clean your ears with a q-tip.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-24 18:00:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is my tank still water-tight?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-14 00:02:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a 65g fish tank that has been in a storage unit for a LONG time (like maybe eight years or so?). This storage unit is more like a garage than a nice climate controlled unit. It has no insulation or anything, so it gets hot an cold. Also, it isn't weather tight, so if it snows a bunch, there might be snow on the floor of the unit. (yeah, not a great storage unit, but my parents pay the rent on it, so it's cheap, LOL). Anyway, is this tank still going to be water tight when I want to set it up in a few years, or has it already been ruined for that? I've no idea what the changing temps do to the sillicone. Oh, and I'm in Iowa, so we get REALLY hot in the summer and REALLY cold in the winter--it's seen temps over 100 and temps well below freezing, if that matters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Struggling</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 04:48:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>A bit about myself. I used to be a serious self harmer. Not just your traditional self harm either. I did all sorts of things to make myself very physically sick so I would require hospital care. Nearly died a few times. I also engaged in some typical cutting and a smidge of burning. (but the cutting didn't hurt, so I did a lot of it. the burning hurt a LOT so I didn't do much of it). Things spiraled out of control eventually and I wound up in a residential care facility for the mentally ill. I was there for three years, and then moved with a friend of mine into an apartment. At first I had staff every day to check up on me. Now, they come twice a week for about an hour each time. I've been in my own apartment for two and a half years now. I haven't hurt myself since going to the RCF. So, that's over five years clean. Lately I've been having TONS of anxiety (and my PRN won't touch it). I've also had lots more thoughts/more intense thoughts of self harm. I keep telling my staff I'm fine and I have no symptoms, because I feel like I'm not allowed to have symptoms. I am afraid of going back to the RCF, but I know that won't happen right now. I'm not that bad off. I could probalby even hurt myself some and not go back. I'm also afraid to hurt myself because I would be letting my roommate down. I know she would be pissed if I hurt myself. So, I'm hanging in there barely, really wanting to be in the hospital for any reason, but knowing that can't happen. Thanks for reading if anyone did. TLDR I've been injury free for over five years. I am now full of anxiety and thoughts of self harm. I have people who check up on me and I'm telling them I'm fine when I'm not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>