<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject8081</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm "helping" in Texas.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-03 08:22:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My favorite burrito place has a unique way of labeling the ice dispenser.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 22:58:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 23:06:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, this was at a Freebirds in Wichita, KS. Surely this isn't company-wide policy, right? You'd think there'd be some royalty dollars owed to a certain Mr. Cube.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My 81-year-old grandma (and lifelong Ohio resident) has some thoughts about Lebron James coming back to Cleveland.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-14 20:41:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-22 01:16:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, sir, we at AOL are offering you 20 free hours of Internet this month!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why did I give her the Pitch Perfect soundtrack for our road trip???</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-10 02:11:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-10 02:55:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>She was singing "Hit me with your best shot" so that's when I chose to make my move (I didn't actually hit her).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We spoofed the Direct TV "When you have cable" ads for my church's "join the choir" campaign. Here's our first idea. We need more. Any suggestions?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-15 19:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pumpkin spice chunkiness: my 6-month old nephew</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-20 01:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When mom says, "That's enough candy for tonight."</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-01 06:07:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My nephew not amused as a lion</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-01 17:57:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Copy the Reindeer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-12 06:21:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This guy's mopping method at Chicago-Midway.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-23 17:05:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm 32. So is this stupid Christmas tradition. Thanks, mom.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-25 06:14:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found this in an alley in Savannah. Don't know who wrote it or whom it's to.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-28 23:33:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found this in an alley in Savannah, GA. Don't know who wrote it or whom it's to. [image]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-28 23:54:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ELI5: Why do cable TV companies still assign numbers to channels? Wouldn't they be easier to find if they were alphabetized or groups by category (sports, news, etc.) then alphabetized?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-20 18:21:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know channel numbers were useful back before program guides, but I don't see the point anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How much weight could the average American adult male lose if, on the same day, he got a haircut, took a leak, donated blood, clipped his fingernails and toenails, took a dump and shaved?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-08 07:45:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just trying to be as lazy as possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-18 05:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was playing Trivia Crack this week when I thought, out of the corner of my eye, that I answered a question submitted by Justin Yu. I hit "continue" before fully realizing what I thought I saw, so no screen shot. Can you guys confirm that Justin actually submits questions to Trivia Crack? Impressive achievement. Getting a question approved is actually pretty difficult.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-25 00:09:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>New Pebble watch. I love the one I have (the original, not the Steel). Jeff and Iyaz, what's better for a smart phone: as many bells and whistles as possible (Apple Watch) or simpler pieces that can't do as much but compliment a smart phone (Pebble)? https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/597507018/pebble-time-awesome-smartwatch-no-compromises</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My father-in-law showing off his earnings as a fish grader in Alaska. Summer, 1975.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 15:53:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 20:03:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hard to tell, but those are Benjamins. Work in Alaska can be quite lucrative, I've been told.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-31 22:21:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably Venus? It's closer than earth and Mars, right? Source: Aced second grade science. But things could have changed. I'm old. #ripPluto</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I don't have a fenced-in yard, but my dog likes to sit in the sun.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-10 18:40:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-27 20:21:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>An ad large enough to show a readable map in a newspaper large enough that people actually read it will cost you more than $1,000.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My 1-year-old nephew thinks he can read.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-29 06:03:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If aliens came to earth, what language would/should they speak to ensure their message is delivered as effectively as possible?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-31 15:45:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just plain curiosity here. But this is more than just a "Which language is spoken by the most people?" question. It's a matter of communicating effectively to the right people, world leaders, etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My wife visited her mom for a weekend and brought back "a box of old junk."</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 17:08:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 18:37:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I LOVED the Power Pad as a kid. Will my 5-year-old nephew think the same thing or recognize how dated it is?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 21:19:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember that game. Noah had to go find and pick up all the animals. The snake was the hardest to catch. Kinda wish he'd just given up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 22:52:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seriously? I didn't know that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 23:56:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>"and this is our Duck Hunt TV." Well done, sir.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-01 23:59:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is complete. Even has the official Bible Buffet Quiz Book. Example question from page 24 "Sarah was to bear Abraham's seed and his name would be ___________. A. Jacob B. Ishmael C. Isaac</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-07 03:15:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Minions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 19:51:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>How long of a wait from the time a photo is taken and sent to earth 'til we are able to view it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bike ride! Let's take a selfi-ahhhhh!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-17 06:48:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is nothing sacred??? Back off, supermarket tabloid.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-22 21:17:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This truck delivering a base to a windmill farm in Limon, Colorado.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-24 03:47:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just pulled into a casino town in the Rockies. What do I need to know before I start gambling?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-31 00:45:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically, trying not to get swindled.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-13 08:37:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sphere, how often do you poop on weekends?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My 2-year-old nephew is overwhelmed by Rainforest Cafe.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-21 04:08:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-31 06:12:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone else having a hard time understanding what this is all about? The professor says there's some type of shady pattern that indicates fraud but the reporter only talks about a lack of tape. What's the pattern? What does the professor see that would indicate actual fraud has taken place? Seems like those are kind of important questions that this report doesn't bother addressing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Soon-to-be first-time Akita owner here. Need some advice.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-31 06:36:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>My wife and I live in a suburb in Kansas with a 6-year-old, well-behaved male Westie, who lives inside but enjoys our fenced-in backyard. We're getting an akita puppy next month. What's your advice, pro tip or word of warning for us? Thanks for any input you could give.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-31 07:52:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>What anomalies??? The story doesn't go into enough detail and the prof's web site is pretty vague, too. Not saying she's wrong, but I need more than "I should get to look at voting machine tapes because I don't trust voting machines." What are these anomalies?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-01 07:56:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>We found a breeder one state over - in Mansfield, Mo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>At what point should I switch my Westie over to "senior" dog food?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-09 06:39:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>He just turned 6-years-old, and we give him Blue Buffalo chicken and rice adult food. Blue Buffalo has the same thing but for "senior" dogs. So just trying to figure out when my Westie is a "senior."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>No way this is to scale, Time Magazine</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-24 21:07:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-24 23:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow. Time wasn't even close. Did they think it was billion instead of million, maybe? Trying to come up with a reasonable explanation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Only at a Walmart Subway</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-26 02:53:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The first car ride is always the scariest.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-28 00:11:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This guy's "occupation" in this infomercial.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-10 19:56:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Jeff, do you know anything about the Jersey Devil? This looks crazy!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-14 05:03:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why???</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-18 04:00:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why???</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-20 08:39:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Airport responsibility?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-31 04:28:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>My group of 10 and I were returning to the U.S. from Honduras today after a week-long work-and-witness trip to build a church. Our flight landed in Houston 30 minutes EARLY and we had no trouble having our passports checked and turning in the form that lists the souvenirs we brought back. Even our baggage claim experience was quick and painless. But then we entered a line that literally snaked around the entire baggage claim area. We had an hour and a half layover before catching our flight to Wichita, but standing in that line took all 90 minutes and we hadn't yet gone through security. The long line was for one of two border security agents to look at the traveler, look at their passport, then wave them through. Didn't check carry-on or checked bags, didn't ask us to declare anything, didn't even speak to us. Just a seemingly mindless exercise that made us (and thousands others, it was obvious) miss our flight. It was just one big bottleneck where a few thousand people spent 30 seconds each, and it delayed everyone. Other airport staff actually climbed onto one of the baggage carousels to take photos of the long lines. It was ridiculous. Of course, this was the last flight to Wichita, so we missed the flight and now our group had to spend hundreds of dollars on hotel rooms and dinner in Houston. United Airlines wouldn't help us because it's not their fault the lines at the airport were wrong. Can the airport or TSA or border security be held responsible for making us miss our connecting flight even though we arrived 30 minutes ahead of airline schedule?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-31 13:52:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fake? Come on. Why would I take the time to make this up? Yes, we used the kiosks, which was a smooth process. That's where you electronically claim anything aside from luggage that you're bringing into the U.S. That process scanned my passport and took a photo of me and also required an agent to manually check my passport. We thought we were in the clear after moving swiftly through that area. But then after we got our luggage we ran into the long line that bottlenecked everyone into two agents redundantly checking passports. Made no sense. Update: Red Roof Inn was HOPPING last night with people who missed their flights because of the delays. Overnight we got what I think are the remnants of Hurricane Patricia here in Houston so there are more delays this morning. We'll get home eventually; it's just frustrating because it seems a more common sense, efficient system would have allowed us to avoid all this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The third-most plentiful ingredient in Mountain Dew is orange juice.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-31 20:26:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My neighbor just won Christmas</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-04 21:36:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-04 23:48:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe Justin called it DontWorryAboutit.com</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's bedtime already???</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-11 06:51:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I guess we're selling the poor guy by the gallon now.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-17 20:07:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bigfoot sighting near arcade in Ohio</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 04:02:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ELI5:Why does washing my hands (with water!!!) result in dry hands?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-30 22:54:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems like the water should, you know, keep them from drying out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Running my first half marathon this spring, and I'm looking for a GPS watch.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-03 03:26:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is the Garmin Forerunner 235 really worth the money or should I save $120 and go with the Vivoactive?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-03 03:39:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. The Forerunner and Vivoactive are both Garmin watches.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-03 05:40:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mainly training for my half marathon, but I also really like the smart watch notification features that both are supposed to have. The only other smart watch I've owned is the original Pebble, which was great, but I really want to be able to leave my phone at home when I run.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I get the feeling my akita is not applying herself at puppy obedience school.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 05:38:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Common to who???</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-07 00:02:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dan is the worst!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-11 06:44:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-17 06:48:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>When sending a letter, write your address in the middle of the envelope and your intended recipient's address in the top left corner. Don't bother with the stamp. When the mailman sees there's no stamp, he'll put "insufficient postage" on the envelope and deliver it to the "return address" written in the top left corner. Free mail delivery! Also, mail fraud!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-17 09:39:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>When sending a letter, write your address in the middle of the envelope and your intended recipient's address in the top left corner. Don't bother with the stamp. When the mailman sees there's no stamp, he'll put "insufficient postage" on the envelope and deliver it to the "return address" written in the top left corner. Free mail delivery!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-17 09:41:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>A fart in a car. Seriously, there's just no resisting it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Runner looking for podcast suggestions.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 08:21:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Training for a half marathon and as my miles increase, so has my time listening to podcasts while I run (I know, I'm weird. I prefer podcasts over music). So the podcasts I normally listen to are great, but I need a few more suggestions. The ones I already subscribe to are the TED Radio Hour, Fresh Air, Wait Wait Don't Tell Me, the404, The HERD with Colin Cowherd and RadioLab. Any other good podcasts you'd recommend?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 08:29:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't. -I started out by strapping it to my arm. Hated it. Couldn't even see the screen to adjust music, see my time, pace, distance, etc. -So then I just held it in my hand. Hated it. Nearly dropped it a few times, couldn't deal with a water bottle or gel packs, hand started hurting from holding it that long. -So I just broke down and bought a second generation iPod shuffle for cheap online that is small and clips to my pocket to I can listen to music/podcasts and got a Garmin Vivoactive watch (with GPS!) to track my distance and pace. Because of those two things I can leave my phone at home! Highly recommend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 08:31:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>This. Couldn't agree more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 08:39:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't imagine a single scenario that explains what the white car was trying to do. He wasn't changing lanes and had the truck not been there it looks like the car would have just gone off the road and under the bridge. Weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Weather Channel, reporting live from Reddit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-21 00:35:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-21 04:22:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure if you're a religious person, but www.thrivewichita.org is a pretty cool place to meet 20-somethings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-21 07:21:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I'm 33, and I'm not the oldest in the thrive group. Let's be honest, it's a church so they're not exactly checking ID at the door.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Warning: Warming up your car could cost you $125 in Kansas. Not sure I've seen a more ridiculous law.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-21 20:34:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-21 20:54:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're willing to take the risk, what's the problem? It's not illegal for me to leave my TV on the porch. It's stupid, but not illegal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-22 05:43:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nevermore!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-22 06:56:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oil</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-22 06:57:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Forest Grump. Life is like a box of... GET OFF MY LAWN!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can't go through six long weeks of puppy obedience school without finishing with an embarrassing graduation photo!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-23 18:53:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-26 08:38:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Here Comes the Sun"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rock Road Walmart never disappoints</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-30 04:17:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Skunk 1, My Akita 0</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-31 07:49:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Reenacted a 20-year-old photo with my siblings.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-02 06:46:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-02 07:42:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really interesting that people think I'm the guy in the foreground. I'm not. What made people assume that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-02 07:57:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yoder Meats! Best in town. Their main store is in Yoder (just this side of Hutch), but they've got smaller locations around Wichita. The one I go to is on Maize just south of Maple.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-02 08:01:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Apple earbuds really are surprisingly great for running. They fit (and stay) in my ears with no issues. I know there are better options out there as far as sound quality, but I generally listen to podcasts when I run, so it's not a big deal for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-03 07:39:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's with the "negative year" thing at the beginning? Is B.C. or B.C.E. not a thing in Japan? I've never heard negative years being used like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-03 07:54:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scroll to the bottom of that website and there's a map of the largest trees in Kansas. Just south of Lawrence, KS there's a mulberry tree that measures 24.5 feet in circumference, making it more than five feet larger than the one in the video. Interesting stuff. I had no idea there was even a registry for trees like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-03 07:54:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wind so loud that you can barely hear people talking? Yep, this is in Kansas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An employee at a Wichita restaurant tried to use his phone to film women in the restroom.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-03 22:19:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The president of Wichita State tweeted this, and now everybody's going nuts.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-03 22:27:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Three months' worth of growth for our 7-month-old akita. Westie for scale.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-04 21:53:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Half marathon distance?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-07 07:00:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I ran my first half marathon Saturday with the Garmin Vivoactive watch that I've been training with for about two months. I was pretty excited about my time, which was under my goal, but when I looked at my watch, it said I had only run 12.75 miles. What's more likely: the watch was more than a quarter of a mile off or the race course was that far off?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You might be from Wichita if... (What would you add?)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-12 17:11:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-12 19:12:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nailed it http://imgur.com/a/PlucR</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Showed my wife this cool new website. Reddit ruined Valentine's weekend.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-12 19:16:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-13 01:07:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>American Akita. She's still just a puppy, though (six months old), so she's got some growing to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-13 01:20:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I don't know as much as I should, but as I understand it the American Akita is 1/8th St. Bernard. Something like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-13 20:08:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>All I can talk about is my own personal experience, but my wife and I have loved AT amp;T Internet and Uverse. We compared prices when we moved to a house on the west side last April and AT amp;T was cheaper (by about 20 percent) than Cox. We get speeds easily above 25 Mbps down, and we've never had any trouble streaming Netflix while also being on our phones. My family was in for Thanksgiving, so we had 10 people in our house but the Internet was strong enough to handle the 10 smart phones and various laptops and tablets. We've been very pleased with their service.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-16 06:43:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>OK, I'll say it. Perhaps you meant Great Plains?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pete Rose's son to coach pro baseball in Wichita! Great move or silly gimmick?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-18 05:56:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I know the Oscar prediction show was a long one but...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-25 16:20:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who decided to pop open a cold one at the 1:43:48 mark???</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>After living in Wichita for 3 years, the only thing I think about when I hear a tornado siren is what I'm going to eat for lunch on Monday.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-29 19:05:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 07:34:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love how Reddit just assumes everyone is a Democrat. Here's the link in case anyone on here dares to be Republican: http://www.ksgop.org/#!caucus-locations/vopsn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 08:01:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>No offense meant against you personally. It's pretty widely accepted that Reddit users tend to lean more liberal than the average person. The link you posted was only prefaced with "information" so it would have been easy to assume it was information for all caucuses instead of just the ones for the Democrat Party. By the way, if you're not a Democrat, you can't participate in a Democrat caucus in Kansas. You have to register as a Democrat. But if you're willing to register, I'm pretty sure you can do it the day of the caucus. Either way, thanks for getting the conversation started. The more people who caucus, the better. Happy voting!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-29 15:41:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>All I can see is that apostrophe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-01 22:18:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Terrible idea. I'm running around making last-minute preparations, greeting people who are actually on time and trying to make everyone comfortable and you want me to step away, answer the phone because you're late AND remember what you were supposed to bring? I won't even answer that phone call.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-18 05:48:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bedtime policy when I was a kid: either turn the light off and go to sleep or leave the small lamp on near my bed and read a book. So I read. A lot. I fell in love with reading.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It appears they've declared that freshly mown grass is lava, and they're greatly concerned for my well-being.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-21 19:44:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 06:22:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>The traffic light at Maple and 119th is annoyingly short. When I was in college in Nashville, TN all traffic lights on north-south streets become blinking yellow lights between midnight and 5 a.m. while the cross streets were blinking red lights (must stop). It was so easy to get through empty streets without stopping at randomly firing traffic lights. I'll love to see Maple/Douglas, Central, 13th and 21st go to blinking yellow lights overnight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When old network news reporters confuse Star Trek with Star Wars.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 01:05:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wichita is now larger than Cleveland and New Orleans.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 23:19:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's that time of year!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-17 08:49:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My nephew DEMANDS domino perfection</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-08 04:22:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>For the Wichita redditor looking for roofing companies: do NOT use this guy. (But eat at Le Monde. It's delicious).</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-15 00:57:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Year No. 4 at my wife's family reunion.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-16 20:04:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-17 06:30:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! 20 bucks on Amazon with free two-day shipping. I'm more into the symbolism rather than the need for a high price tag.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My wife's family reunion wasn't all bad. Got second place in the disc golf tournament!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-17 16:03:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Jaax just turned 1-year-old. When should we move her from puppy food to regular dog food? We feed her Blue Buffalo.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-23 16:29:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When all the volunteers are searching for Will in the first few episodes why is it always at night?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-06 05:14:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wouldn't it make more sense to search during the daylight?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-06 06:41:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's 100 percent American Akita. She looks a little derpy in the photo, but she's a pure bred. We got her from Allen's Akitas in Mansfield, Missouri.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-06 06:45:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>My Akita just turned a year old and she's 70 pounds. We thought she would be bigger by now. Both her parents were 100+, but the vet says she's a happy, healthy girl, which is all that really matters to us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL: Wichita charges you a fee to have a garage sale. And somehow loses money doing it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-13 06:14:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Darryl Strawberry in Wichita this weekend</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-22 02:22:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Darryl Strawberry in Wichita this weekend. Free event on Sunday.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-22 07:14:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My hand soap got the Bible verse wrong, but technically it's still right.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-23 23:03:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My nephew being a bit cautious on his first s'more attempt.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-13 02:46:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 23:33:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just installed a new, no-slam toilet lid, and I feel like Richie Rich. There's no luxury like toilet luxury.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>These Australian guys broke the world record for highest basketball shot. And show some subtle Switchfoot love at the 4:12 mark.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 16:02:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When we let her inside she kept trying to open the oven and get to the turkey.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-24 17:17:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 04:44:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's an American Akita</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Our 1-year-old akita on trampoline guard duty.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 19:26:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 19:48:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. That's why we got an akita puppy to be in charge of safety. Right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-16 05:46:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>The 404 Show needs to be here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 23:44:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have a 1.5-year-old female akita, and she's great. Intelligent and stubborn, at times, but the patience necessary to raise her has been worth it. We expected her to be larger (her father was 120 pounds), but she seems to be maxing out at 75 points. That's plenty big enough for us. Here in Kansas it drops to 0 Fahrenheit in the winter and gets up to 100 Fahrenheit in the summer. She likes the winter more than the summer, but she's fine in either, though we keep her primarily indoors. When we got her as a 10-week-old puppy we introduced her to our 6-year-old male Westie. Both are fixed, which probably helps, but they get along perfectly well. My wife, a therapist, user our akita as a therapy dog. She hasn't passed the training yet to be an official therapy dog, so she's still just a "therapy dog in training" but my wife's clients love having our akita in the office during therapy sessions. I'd highly recommend some type of interactive training class for you and your akita. You'll need just as much training as your akita does. Hope this helps!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 04:20:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, our akita has been significantly more difficult to train than our westie. I'd say they're equally intelligent, but if the akita doesn't want to sit, she won't sit. She fully understands the sit command; sometimes she's just not interested in sitting. So she won't. Stubborn. My wife has had a hard time getting the akita to follow more advanced commands required to pass the therapy dog test, like sitting still while other dogs play near her or allowing children to touch her tail or head without trying to lick them. But she's only a year and a half old and we are making progress. But the important things like house training and leash walking were equally easy. Just start early and be consistent. My wife and I read about negative experiences with akitas, but we haven't experienced the aggression or destruction that others have, fortunately.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This author must have been so mad when that other book came out.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-24 04:11:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 16:38:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>The article is so poorly written that I'm questioning Its credibility. It's a grammatical mess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>These 22 places in and around Wichita will take your dead Christmas tree for recycling.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 07:44:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 03:14:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! I'll buy one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stop judging me, Netflix. It's been a long year.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-01 05:27:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 04:19:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was too late to snag one. Where do I buy one now? Looks great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is your name? Obergruppenf #252;hrer Smith</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 07:13:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This manly model on my underwear packaging is curling five pounds.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-09 17:00:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 06:14:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's so irritating when the media use Facebook comments as quotes in what's supposed to be a reputable news story. How much lazier can a reporter get?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-22 07:21:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Andy Griffith Show.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-22 07:32:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Attendant has been notified to assist you."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If Trump brings down American civilization, the wealthiest of people will be hiding out in a luxury bunker near Salina</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 15:30:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 21:01:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure why the reporter connected it with Wichita in the story. The bunker is actually about 140 miles north of Wichita.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 17:59:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I asked a German exchange student at my school if he knew what Black Friday was. "Uh, Martin Luther King Jr. Day?" Nope. Explanation time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-08 20:51:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Navy vs. Hopkins on a Big Ten field?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 06:18:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Man in the High Castle. Thank God Amazon only loosely based its TV series off the premise of that book and nothing else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-20 06:34:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've got AT amp;T and it works great. I live on the west side and work downtown. The only problem is it's impossible to get a signal inside Lowes on Ridge, but I think that might have something to do with its proximity to the airport.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is how she sleeps.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 04:50:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Oscars fiasco</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-01 08:00:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can we bring Jordan Hoffman back this week for just 10 minutes so we can get his take on the disastrous ending to the Oscars? He did such a great job setting it all up for us. I'd love to hear what his reaction was as it happened.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-04 06:28:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mom's spaghetti!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you want to destroy your diet but hold up at the last second.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-05 05:41:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you want to destroy your diet but hold up at the last second.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-05 05:53:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you're about to destroy your diet but hold up at the last second.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-05 05:56:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Homeowner turned his sprinklers on before leaving to escape a Kansas wildfire. He came home to this (photo by the Kansas Air National Guard).</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 16:10:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 16:11:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's the full story from The Wichita Eagle: http://www.kansas.com/news/state/article137518423.html</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My niece making a discovery</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 19:56:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My niece making a discovery</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 20:00:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This football field has an 80-yard line.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-19 06:54:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-21 10:46:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's interesting how we consider something on Netflix to be free. It isn't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 23:55:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>No slam toilet seats. Simply luxurious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 17:14:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>But isn't there an established order of dominance within the pack? Especially if this is a routine for feeding time, I feel like letting different dogs go first would disrupt the pack mentality. Not an expert here. Just asking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just a car with a bandaid.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 23:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"I'll tell you what happened next..."</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 23:33:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 23:46:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for sharing this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-30 02:50:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sigh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 07:08:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>How about a minor league baseball stadium?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 20:23:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what Tiger Woods did for golf. He changed the sport. So much, in fact, that golf's having a hard time recovering since he left.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 22:34:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scott Sterling would have made the save.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>John the Music of Williams</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 00:51:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When your dog walk takes you to the doughnut shop, but the doughnut shop says no dogs allowed.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 05:39:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 06:32:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>We've used Blue Buffalo on our akita since we brought her home, and she's been a happy, healthy pup ever since. After a year we switched from their puppy food to regular dog food. They have a pretty good variety.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>LPT: if a company brags about its Better Business Bureau rating in an advertisement, it's a scam.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-06 06:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why do I even listen to late-night AM radio anymore?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scientists have identified the 50-foot creature that washed up on an Indonesian beach | Baleen whale. Had to go six paragraphs into the story to find it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 20:19:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scientists have identified the 50-foot creature that washed up on an Indonesian beach | a baleen whale. Had to read through six paragraphs to get the answer.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 21:26:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just found this sub! Thought I'd share how I broke the good news to my siblings.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 06:12:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 06:14:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is certainly not a standard headline. A good newspaper editor would never leave out such a key detail. A standard newspaper headline would read: "50-foot creature that washed up on Indonesian beach identified as baleen whale"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 07:49:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Found the black box</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Welp. All we can do now is brace ourselves for some epic Papa John's garlic sauce akita farts</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 03:39:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 05:29:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>If a flight from NYC to Anchorage, Alaska would keep flying in the same direction it would eventually fly over Tokyo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 18:52:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Infant kid in the backseat? This looks like a desperate mom refusing to let her child be kidnapped.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I have three cottonwood trees in my backyard. This is what it's like to mow this time of year.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-05 23:41:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 06:35:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Augusta National Golf Club has the money and expertise to do this kind of thing. In less than a year they moved at least a dozen full-grown loblolly pine trees (all more than 50 feet tall) when they created their new driving range a few years ago. It's incredible what they do with trees, flowers and grass around that course.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My pastor got some adorable help to tell the Acts 12 story</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-21 07:21:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 08:25:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty much 90 percent of the car dealerships in my town.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 08:27:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>An hour before bedtime put your phone down and don't touch it until morning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 08:28:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't be an idiot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 08:35:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whenever I'm about to do something, I think, "Would an idiot do that?" And if they would, I do not do that thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 08:38:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those granola bars that crumble immediately upon opening the wrapper.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 08:42:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/instantbarbarians Videos and gifs that show something unlikely or interesting happening followed by the crowd going wild (turning into instant barbarians).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 08:45:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lord, beer me strength.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 05:37:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Falcons aren't the first. Augusta National Golf Club has even lower prices at the Masters Tournament.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 05:40:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>More like a cartoon map of Delano.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 08:48:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>When Squints puts the moves on the lifeguard. Wendy Peffercorn saves the day as I'm laying there all alone dying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 08:49:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>When a payday loan place opens up in your neighborhood.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 08:50:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're going to love r/crappyoffbrands</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 08:57:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a baseball fan, and everywhere I travel I look for souvenir baseballs. Not the expensive, autographed kind; just something unique (like a ball with the town's minor league team's logo) that I can pick up for 10 bucks or less. Even the most cliche souvenir shops usually have a ball with the state/country flag or something similar on it. I was at a junk place called Wal-Mike's in the Alaskan interior two weeks ago and found a baseball from a youth baseball league in Anchorage. Great find, cost me $9.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>As a 34-year-old, I've lived the same amount of years in two different millennia.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 21:23:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 14:53:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Come on, the catcher caught the ball. It's not that hard to see it. The replay guys missed this one. It happens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 17:37:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>OK, first, you can disagree while still being civil. Calm down, this is a fun discussion. We're all going to be OK. Second, all you need to overturn this is clear evidence. I'll concede your point that the side angle may be inconclusive, but you don't need the side angle. The first angle (the view from behind the pitcher) gives you all you need. You can see the ball go into the glove and not hit the ground. The catcher knew he caught it, which is why he threw it around the horn. And replay guys are very good. But they're not perfect either. Mistakes can be made.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hialeah man shoots out tires of AT amp;T truck outside home</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 22:09:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 22:25:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was an overreaction.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 05:30:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Java Salon. They have east and west locations, but I'm more familiar with the west one at Maize and Central. Ask for Christie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dwight???</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-02 20:09:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Two-years-old today! Meet Jaax!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-07 17:57:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 16:59:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>THE FAKE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-11 20:20:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vaping</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Jim Halpert dropped 28 points on TCU over the weekend. Meredith added 17. Andy had more fouls than points.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 04:34:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My nephew drew on the wall and got put in time out for the first time.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 07:34:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It costs a penny more per Twinkie when you buy two.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 03:37:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 03:15:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell me about it! https://imgur.com/gallery/a0RQg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-08 16:19:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Akita? Husky?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 09:13:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scott's Tots</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 07:28:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>This! Highly recommend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 15:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read somewhere that two of the opening shots, including this one, were shot by John Krasinski.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 16:54:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Grocery stores assigning their most extroverted employee to oversee the self-checkout stations.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 07:53:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or at least the ninth season of The Office</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When have you blown your wage on something absolutely ridiculous?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 20:57:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 03:39:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Two years old, 82-pound female.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 06:02:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>show no signs of intelligent thinking but can rattle off a dozen or more specific names of pain killer medication.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 05:45:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Calm down. It's a reference to an episode of The Office. You just assumed it was a comment about her breasts. It wasn't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 05:22:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>"hang up" the phone. They used to be on walls where people would hang them up when they were done with them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 06:31:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's grammatically correct to say, "I'm going to Steve's and Lisa's house." But all of us, including me, say, "I'm going to Steve and Lisa's house."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My sister-in-law didn't get the family photo she was hoping for.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 03:41:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not sure if I'm about to get some massive French toast sticks or the world's smallest syrup pitcher.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 18:17:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's the difference between frosting and icing?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 06:03:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 18:46:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not wearing a wire</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 07:02:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nelly in The Office. Blah!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 09:26:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>-Michael Scott</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 12:00:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Andy Bernard</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 12:05:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Up all night with a 1-month-old who slept the entire 5-hour road trip to Grandma's for Christmas, so I'm fully qualified to answer on this particular night. At least the discussions about TV shows/characters made for some interesting reading. It's better than seeing that guy slide down the escalator median in a dozen different subs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 12:08:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>America's Funniest Home Videos. After almost three decades, that show still gets me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 12:11:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Roku app lets me watch Netflix on my TV while listening to the audio through earbuds from my phone. As a new parent with a baby's crazy sleep schedule, that feature is amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 22:52:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>This time of year the cranberry version of Sprite/Sierra Mist/7-up is my go-to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 23:28:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. I mainly see it in two-liters. Great for Christmas parties.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 08:42:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>My wife has had that same teddy bear for 30 years! Her father gave it to her when she was two. He passed away a few years ago, and we have a daughter of our own now. We'd love to get her the same bear. Anyone know how we could buy one? A name? a store? a brand? Anything?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 16:04:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! Just bought one. My wife is going to be THRILLED!!! Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 04:12:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You sure you're living 'til 78 if you're eating 15 times a month off the dollar menu?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Saving my Christmas money to buy a freezer for my garage so my family can take better advantage of sales. What brands, features, stores, website, etc. will help me make the best purchase?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 04:29:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 17:16:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>What did it for me was the $20 price decrease for the dot AND the add-on of a $25 smart plug for $5. So now my wife and I can have Alexa turn on a light in the nursery when the baby's up in the middle of the night. If it did nothing else, that's worth $35 right there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 20:39:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please don't be that guy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The ideal cover for a spy satellite is that it was mysteriously destroyed during launch.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 08:12:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 22:25:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>The meteorologists seem to be really good at predicting severe weather and pretty rotten at predicting wintry weather.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 09:15:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>First-time parent here. I'd like my wife and I to be able to tell Alexa when we change the baby's diaper, feed her or put her down for a nap and Alexa responds by tracking the frequency of feedings, naps and number of diapers used. So I can ask, "Alexa, how many diapers did we use last week?" or "Alexa, when was the last time... we fed baby/we changed her diaper/she took a nap?" The idea is we can better judge when I need to order more diapers or if her sleeping or eating patterns are changing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 05:32:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man in the High Castle. Amazon Prime. Go. Now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 05:35:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Healthcare workers who smoke cigarettes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 05:37:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Injury. "Ryan, who is supposed to be DEAD!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 05:47:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The second before Squintz came back to life and kissed Wendy Peffercorn. Then... THIS MAGIC MOMENT!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 05:53:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>A garbage truck hit a patch of ice, slid out of control and ran over a woman in my neighborhood this afternoon. I drove up on it just after it happened. Horrible. Tragic. 911 dispatch and first responders were awesome and knew just what to do. She's going to survive, thankfully. But just be careful after snow or ice hits. Cities and counties generally do a good job of plowing and treating major roads and highways, but neighborhood roads are typically left untouched and can stay icy for days after wintry weather hits. Be careful out there!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 05:54:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well... Reddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 05:58:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not mine but my wife's. She and her family went camping in Yellowstone when she was in second grade. They saw moose and bear cubs and all kinds of fun wildlife. Doesn't matter what vacation or trip we take now, nothing in her mind can compare to her second grade-self's view of Yellowstone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This guy was voted best beard and mustache in the U.S. He says he uses regular shampoo on it every day. Is that good advice?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 17:50:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 18:58:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, everything I've read on this sub says no shampoo. So I was surprised to read this guy's advice. I'm a bit lost, to be honest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 05:15:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure you guys are getting the point. It doesn't matter if this is a fake award and it doesn't matter who sponsored it. What does matter is you can tell by the photo that this guy has an outstanding beard and he says he shampoos it every day. So maybe daily shampoo works for some guys. I don't know. I'm new here. I know this is just one example, and maybe he's the exception, but the validity of the award or sponsor is irrelevant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 05:32:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great idea! Is it available through a streaming app such as Stitcher or TuneIn?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 05:42:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>We've got an echo Dot in our nursery. Combine it with a smart outlet, plug in a lamp and tell Alexa to turn on the lamp before you change a diaper in the middle of the night. So convenient, and the baby isn't blinded by a brighter overhead light.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hurts Donut selling 'laundry pod' donuts</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 17:23:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 05:50:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>They can see which stories get the most clicks, and Wichita loves its restaurants.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 06:29:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>How is this "two for one"?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 07:04:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Podcasts. Usually "The Daily" from the New York Times. I highly recommend. Why settle for radio with all the commercials and lower-quality content? And once you discover you can pause/rewind/skip ahead on a podcast, you'll never go back to radio.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 18:12:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every time a large truck is shown, there's a horn sound. Every time there's a wide shot, there's an eagle screeching.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 16:01:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>But they'll build a new QT in three weeks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You're down 3, your rival has the ball, 20 seconds left.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 18:40:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 22:53:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't stop watching her!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 22:55:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>The girl (No. 24) hits a 3-pointer to tie the game then that same girl steals the ball and makes another shot to take the lead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is there a way to get Alexa to shuffle the start of a Spotify playlist?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 22:59:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I say, "Alexa, shuffle dance party playlist" or "Alexa, play dance party playlist." It always starts the playlist with the exact same song. Is there a command that will make it shuffle the start of the playlist? Anyone else had this problem?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 23:11:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>That'll work. How do I find a silent song?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 00:04:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're making it hard to be lazy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 06:26:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why are you singling her out... like a million years later?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 06:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just tried to book three nights at a hotel in KC. More than $40 in taxes  amp; fees. Nope. Thank God for Airbnb.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Eight years ago NFL draft expert Mel Kiper said he'd retire in eight years if Jimmy Clausen wasn't a successful NFL QB.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 18:38:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 07:02:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, still worth it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 20:01:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the best way is to offer an alternative idea rather than just point out how bad the original idea is. "Balloons would look great, but imagine how much longer planted trees would last."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 22:19:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, there's no need to distinguish between a pass and a shot. If a player is in the corner and tries to pass it to a teammate in the opposite corner but the ball accidently goes into the basket, it's still 3 points even though it was an intended pass. Same with an alley-oop pass that never gets touched but goes in anyway. A ref shouldn't (and doesn't) have to determine if an attempt was a pass or a shot. This was a 2-pointer because it was touched by a player inside the 3-point line.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 03:36:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meh. Maybe. But if a ball gets tipped it's not going in. I can't think of a single example of that happening. Prove me wrong, Reddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 04:59:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>That had to be the most excruciating gif I've ever seen! I'm yelling at him through my phone and then... Oh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lion meets a scooter</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 03:58:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 05:18:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. Sedgwick County Zoo in Wichita, KS. I guess they have a similar set up in Cincy? (P.S.: Go Shockers!)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 05:20:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sedgwick County Zoo in Wichita, KS.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 05:36:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, but did you tip your proctologist?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Parenthood.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 03:41:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 17:01:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ria Farmer. We've used her as our realtor twice. She's amazing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 17:58:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>During the Christmas shopping season last year, Amazon had these exact two items bundled for $35.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 05:32:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've got a group of guys I play with at my church's gym. Sundays 7:30-9:30 p.m. Wichita First Church of the Nazarene close to downtown (1400 E. Kellogg Dr.).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wait for it. Kid ends perfect shooting effort with epic staredown.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 18:39:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 17:22:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Office</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Redditors over 50, what's "The Office" of your generation?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 20:23:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 04:50:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Found Martellus Bennett</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This tool is being passed around at our family reunion, and no one knows what it is. It opens and closes like scissors and it's about 8 inches long. It looks like it's designed to hold or carry something. There's a small inscription just above the wooden handle that says "NEVCO JAPAN"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 21:27:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 21:39:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Solved! (I think)[campfire gripper](https://www.kitterytradingpost.com/camping-travel/camp-kitchen-supplies/open-fire-cookware/rome-campfire-gripper-65314.html)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>