<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject1914</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-09-27 07:04:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Played??? As in, past tense??? I still play it on my mac! Proof: http://imgur.com/qmM3h.jpg Love love love this game! It also love how anime it is. Like, in the future, bad guys will mostly fight with their kung-fu rather than with guns. Yes. This is the game I go to when I just wanna beat up some Strikers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-09-29 08:33:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely one of my favorite characters in the show! You probably won't get a chance to answer this since there are over 2000 replies but, do you talk about weird sex in real life as much as you do in the show? Cuz, if you do then that's awesome and I totally approve. Good luck with the new season!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-09-30 04:42:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Upvote for really good short story.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-09-30 04:52:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, but your character kinda reminds me of the things I talk about with my friends. Every so often we just start talking about weird sex or something so I always wondered if that's mostly the script or if there's a bit of the real C.S. Lee in it. *Ignore this part:* OMG! Masuka talked to me!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-10-01 07:40:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not a parent but I'll always remember what Dr. Membrane once said: "Video games develop hand-eye coordination and make kids into better human beings."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-10-01 07:45:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, that's the number that shows up with her texts and reply doesn't seem to work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-10-08 21:05:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Way to make it into my subconscious! After reading this topic, I went to bed and then had a dream in which there was a vending machine at my school that sold these!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-10-10 09:48:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Heck yes. But the only things I ever cared about that much were Animorphs and the software section.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-10-11 01:26:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that in Portland? I think I've seen it before...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-10-22 03:47:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Skin - gt; Sheetrock. Could someone explain that one to me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-10-22 18:55:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I heard somewhere that some kind of baggage handlers are called "Throwers" (a bit of a worrisome name). Is this true?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-10-22 21:24:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lost interest when it asked me to login/register. Seriously, do I want to register for something as simple as this? Also, there should be an option for using only 2 ingredients. Corn chips + banana.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-10-24 00:05:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's M 78 (Messier object 78). Looks like it was photoshopped to be extra awesome though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-10-25 08:24:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Take all the money used for pandas, give to tiger preservation. Problem solved. Fewer useless animals. I love tigers. I really want them to stay with us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-10-28 21:52:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every surface? I'll just paint it on my eyeballs!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-11-10 18:44:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It reminds me of the visuals in Bioshock. Tell me I'm not crazy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-11-18 06:05:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>YESSSS! Upvote for amazing idea!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-11-19 08:13:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nymphadora is her first name?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-11-19 08:14:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Randomly saw the same actor in The Island. That was a throwback for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-11-21 07:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please, please, please make a sign that says "God slashes tires".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-11-22 08:12:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's funny because all parts of your tongue can taste different things equally!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-11-23 08:44:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck yeah DNA profiling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-11-24 08:40:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is so freaking awesome and I'm not even that much of a Star Trek fan... New goal as a CS major!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-11-27 07:44:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Armored Core 4. Damn Gamestop would only give my 15$ back when I payed full price for it new even though it was only a week later.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-12-06 20:17:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Logged in to upvote this. Well said.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-12-10 11:56:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like I was in the same store in Italy once. Where was this? Did they happen to have Kama Sutra chocolate next to the tools?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-12-12 06:05:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>After being called anti-social: "I'm social! Just not when people are around..."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-12-14 05:23:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>The grass have their life; please have mercy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-12-14 05:43:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I must strive to talk like this in sexual situations... Nope. Can't think of anything bad happening.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-12-15 08:59:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is why I love my home town.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-12-23 08:26:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>CELEBRATE! CELEBRATE!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2010-12-30 23:41:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only just beats "Gay porn star assaults lover with samurai sword, gets tazered and jumps off cliff."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-01-02 04:30:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well you are supposed to change into a new one after 20 minutes of use so if they plan to go longer than that, then having an extra on hand is a good idea. Great advice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-01-11 10:31:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Impressive...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-01-19 07:25:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't think my dislike of Activision could increase but they proved me wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-01-19 07:27:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I laughed. Then I wondered why there weren't NSFW tags.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-01-21 02:01:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jeremey Soule does such great work. I really am looking forward to this game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-01-31 02:12:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someones been reading [this list.](http://www.lotsofjokes.com/supermarket_fun.asp)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-02-02 08:38:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! That poison!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-02-15 23:39:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vic: "This is Tex Babaganoosh, star of CSI: Baghdad". Ken: "He was also the lead role in Full Metal Burka." Jokes like that kept me coming back to this show. I'm glad I found a torrent of them since I don't think they are aired anywhere today.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-03-01 01:47:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Firefly (Awesome show) vs Larry (Horrible show). Give me the awesome show, I don't care where it is. I'd watch Firefly if it was on MTV as long as the channel itself had no say in episode content.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-03-18 17:02:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Republicans are also highly critical of the salaries of public broadcasting executives and used that to bolster their argument that taxpayer funds for their operations should be cut." The fact that they are not critical in any way of the salaries of multiple millions of dollars and stock that many corporate CEO's get and their insistence that we give these people even more tax cuts only underlines their BS facade of trying to help the economy. This is completely political. There is nothing fiscal about defunding NPR or Planned Parenthood or Unions. It's all about the Regressives trying to hurt us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-03-19 06:20:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL that it's "Hedgehog" and his middle name is "The".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-03-28 02:47:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's because we didn't have access to a credit card needed to order them from Acme.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-04-06 19:09:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I imagine a group of people in a very fancy kitchen toasting bread all day, flawlessly. Am I wrong?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-04-07 03:05:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Snow biomes are still broken. Seriously. They have been broken for way too long. I can deal without cookies and wolves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-04-14 05:24:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>My roommate told m this. Apparently it's a Russian surrealist joke. Try to imagine the accent. Bear and Owl are sitting on log. Rabbit comes up and asks "Do you guys have any glue?". They say "No." So Rabbit leaves and comes back with glue and says "Here you go."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-04-16 02:17:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can someone explain how this works? If the Democrats refuse to vote, wouldn't the repubs just gain the majority and pass the bill anyway?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-04-27 01:03:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I invented one that's higher. I combined "Bat-shit crazy" and "Crazy like a fox" to get "Bat-shit crazy like a foxbat".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-04-28 01:59:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who are these people?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-04-30 12:04:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember that. I also remember several years later, seeing an add on TV where you could get two for 30 bucks. Those things used to be a hundred each. Technology never stops moving.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-05-07 22:08:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seen a lot of these but this one is quite nice. I think the colors of the waves make it really stand out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-05-25 20:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I knew that Yahtzee generally has some pretty shallow opinions but I never thought he'd be one of *those people* who simply says that first person platforming doesn't work. It tells me that he obviously hasn't played Mirrors Edge for any substantial length of time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Arcade game, Warhammer 40K Kill Team, coming before Space Marine launch.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-06-04 09:19:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-06-04 21:29:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too. The power sword is way too cool of a weapon to be exclusive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-06-16 22:55:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've always liked the unreal tournament font. I even found it for download [here](http://www.dafont.com/unreal-tournament.font).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-06-19 23:32:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>"The Cloud." Mostly because it's just the new tech term that non-tech people love. There's one every couple of years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-06-20 04:49:20</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;The US District Courts have ruled that since oil is no longer flowing from the Macando Well, BP and Transocean are not liable for cleanup costs and damages from the BP Gulf Oil Spill since the  #8220;well has already been sealed and the injury has already been committed #8221;. That's like if I broke someones arm and he sued me, only to have the suit thrown out because I wasn't breaking his arm at the time of the suit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-06-21 01:40:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone played Skies of Arcadia? Great old RPG. Your home base, [Pirate Isle,](http://marsarcadia.doublemole.com/world/images/pirateisle.jpg) is pretty sweet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-06-21 07:28:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to hate reading when I was a kid. Jacques' books were actually the books that got me to start reading for fun and not just school. Thank you Brian for giving us such a great series.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-06-24 23:33:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Found it. [Nice haircut.](http://i.imgur.com/IKc7n.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-06-26 10:16:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>And Anvil. I miss being able to make my machine gun shoot rockets instead of bullets.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-06-27 10:27:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>The fuck? 14% say they support the bill while 85% say they don't with 0% undecided? Bullshit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-08 08:28:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I pulled this game out a while ago for some nostalgia. But when I tried to play it, it was like "please enter the code found on page 37 of the manual" which I did not have. Proof that shitty DRM has been around for longer than some of us imagine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-11 06:15:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm always like, "I'll keep this gravel and power mine it later to get lots of flint!" So now I have chests full of gravel that I never use.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-13 06:28:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, "Video Game Television" at it's finest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-14 01:33:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>How about a playground editor so we can make our own maps and such?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-19 03:14:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn it. I passed this game up during the Steam sale. I ask myself, "Why?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-20 05:59:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>As much as I want to see her drop out of the race, I don't think that drug usage for a real or debilitating problem should be seen as a reason for forcing her out. Let's focus more on the fact that she is bat-shit insane. It's a much more persuasive argument anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-26 03:57:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow. Anybody have a higher resolution version? Tineye gets nothing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-26 20:13:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>The biggest giveaway to me is that the FBI seized 5.7 million dollars and then wanted to give it to its rightful recipient.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-07-27 02:50:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Build giant pyramid on top of it. Create awesome tomb with traps and secret entrances.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-08-01 06:24:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is brilliant. I had a setup that connected a pressure plate to a piston that let water into a little ditch to pop all the plants. This is so much faster. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-06 01:40:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got a coupon for a two week free trial and gave it a shot. By the end of it, I decided it wasn't worth it. Maybe I've been spoiled by netflix's quick shipping time on dvds or maybe they don't prioritize people who are on trial accounts but I spent at least 75% of the trial period waiting for games to show up. I even called them once to find out what was taking so long and they told me that my game had just shipped today. The one thing I did like was that, if you like a game you get, you can buy it from them and they will send you the box. I dunno if they are any better now, since this was a while ago. If you can find some sort of free trial then try it out first. Otherwise, I'd say, skip it. Buy used.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-17 10:31:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uncle Mario?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-18 00:15:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every time I see one of these links I always think "Awesome! I'm gonna make a video game weapon/cool armor piece etc". Then I find out that I need a garage full of tools I've never heard of and technical know-how I've never gotten. There must be a site that has plans to make cool things like this with only an exacto-knife, saw, printer, paint and a maximum of 10 minutes of googling to figure out what to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-20 04:24:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I felt the same way. I kinda liked how it was designed, especially how the narration worked but it was way to short to really provoke a good reaction.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-21 23:09:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely Nutella. I used to eat it all the time but found out recently that I'm allergic to hazel nuts. I take the "no health effects" to include allergic reactions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-24 11:21:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm still hoping for a new installment. Call me a dreamer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-09-27 21:26:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used the Fancy Pack back in 1.7.3 to make all kinds of furniture. It was great. I don't know if there is an update available for 1.8 or 1.9 yet. It would be great if Notch incorporated some of the blocks into the main game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-03 00:09:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>The maps are really cool and look good but you gotta rename the levels of difficulty. Example: Basic - gt; Doable. Easy - gt; Fuckin' Hard. Normal - gt; Fuckin' Hard and Irritating. Intermediate - gt; Rage Quit Material. Seriously, the difficulty curve is way too steep.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-04 08:11:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't see anything in the article that supports your claim sir. It would seem that your ability to play PS2 games is not being challenged at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-07 04:49:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have taken that exact same plane tour! You started in Ketchikan right? When we took the tour we got really lucky and the weather was perfect. I got lots of shots just like that. Best moment of our entire trip.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-15 01:30:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can hold down the block button (if you've got a shield equipped or your weapon out) to cast spells faster.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-18 03:44:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>If one of those features isn't mod support, I'm gonna kill somebody's dick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-19 05:01:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish they'd release some more intel on this game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-19 23:37:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>They seem to be posting small bits of a single image over a period of time. I'm not sure what to feel about this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-22 21:05:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't you know? There are only two sides in politics today. So everything that one party wants must be the opposite of what the other party does. Trying to find any sort of "common ground" is just people not taking a hard enough stance on anything. Compromise and working-together is socialism.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-25 08:37:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Introduce your stupid friends to [this.](http://www.skippydisc.com/pgs/Home.php) And while you're at it, remember it for when your discs invariably get scuffed up. They've restored two of my games to working condition.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-26 23:44:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't tell if you're being sarcastic. I mean, some older titles I can find for 5 bucks or less *used*, but if you want a pristine copy you'll need to buy new. My Ninja Gaiden disc became unplayable and my choices were to buy another copy for 20$ or something (this was a few years back) or try these guys. I do not regret my decision.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-27 04:29:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I decided to wait until they stopped prereleasing so that all the big modders could catch up. Jeb wants to do prerelease 1.9.5. Guess I'm gonna be waiting for a while more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-10-31 08:49:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was a long read, but it actually restored a bit of my faith in humanity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-01 21:12:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is this in r/gaming? Perhaps r/worldnews would be better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-05 09:22:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm interested but I was really happy with R6 Vegas 2. I was kinda hoping that the next one would be similar. I can do without all the bells and whistles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-18 09:19:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone notice that a large portion of the businesses on the list were photography studios? I didn't really expect that when I opened the list. I figured there would be more organizations involved in video production.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-20 08:25:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Babushka dog!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-21 03:53:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh. Is it cool to hate on Daughtry now? Hang on while I adjust my opinions based on the tastes of other people. There we go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-28 17:26:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Either way, your weekend is ruined.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-11-28 23:41:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>From the same flikr account. [If Star Wars was a Disney movie:](http://farm7.staticflickr.com/6083/6160071934_bc0ef30da9_b.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-12-01 23:10:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It makes so much sense to give a good chunk for mining diamonds. Do you get experience if you use a silk touch pickaxe?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-12-02 07:27:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would love to have this in wallpaper size. Can't deck the halls until I deck my desktop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-12-03 22:06:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not going to read it because it's 700 pages long. I would love to understand it for myself, I just don't have that kind of time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2011-12-13 08:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Too bad he didn't have the [Iraqi Patriot Missile Defense System^(tm).](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NsVgiuZgShM)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-01-30 23:18:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love the ending line! What show is this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-02-19 19:35:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hope-you're-not-lactose-intolerant-because-the-next-part-is "dairy."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-02-20 02:27:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Wait for it!" would have also been an acceptable answer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-02-23 20:56:51</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;under-car flamethrowers they use to stop carjackings in South Africa [Holy shit.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fDrzMGdYWZc) [You weren't kidding.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blaster_%28flamethrower%29)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-02-27 09:34:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, Rick, I suggest you quit bitching, strike him down and take his place like any decent Sith would.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-03 08:59:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>An N64. Practically everyone I know from my home town had one. This is why I just smile and nod when something Zelda or Mario related comes up on r/Gaming.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-05 21:12:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice try, flip-floping X-play employee.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-07 02:58:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will I be able to plant a tree and watch it grow into a huge disappointment?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-13 07:20:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>This happens to me so much that there should be a support group for it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-03-16 08:10:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>What pisses me off just as much is the horrid site design. They can't even be bothered to organize their bullshit into pages. Instead, you just gotta scroll through it all. Reminds me of Timecube.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-03 03:15:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Guns don't kill people; people kill people. But I think the gun helps. If you went around saying 'BANG!' I don't think you'd kill many people." - Eddie Izzard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-09 00:10:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I find that offensive. You should use either "his penis" or "her penis" depending on how he or she would prefer to be referred to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-21 07:38:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>WHERE? Edit: Person deleted their comment which said they got to meet some tigers up close in Oregon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-04-22 05:40:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow. What country do you live in?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-03 00:36:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm pretty sure that line was the cause of at least one of my bloody rampages.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-12 23:45:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I recommend [BiomePainter](http://www.minecraftforum.net/topic/1119044-tool-biome-painter-08-edit-your-minecraft-worlds-biomes/).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-29 05:04:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>It took me a while to get used to the mouse controls (especially with regards to vehicles) but I definitely got there. I think the game support a controller if you have a USB one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-05-30 00:33:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks a lot like [Eldaria](http://www.planetminecraft.com/project/eldaria-island---custom-terrain-mc-10---end-portal/), a custom terrain that I've been playing on for a while.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-10 23:10:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>**"Proving atheists wrong with science!"** Okay! Science! Awesome! **"The Bible says..."** Aaaaaand science goes bye-bye.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-16 21:54:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Technically, he could just be Italian.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-06-21 02:50:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>What kind of dog is she?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-07-15 21:22:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, first we make it illegal to leak "sensitive information" (i.e. anything we choose to label as such). Journalists will then switch to online anonymous releases. Next, we destroy any sense of anonymity on the web. Who can guess the next step? If you guessed "arrest the journalists for doing their job" then you're probably right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-07-23 04:34:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Relevant](http://www.parkinsonstissuebank.org.uk/images/people/dbrain.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-07-25 07:22:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love this idea! I got tired really fast switching back and forth between Minecraft and those diagrams.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-08-04 22:42:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was a very beautiful and sad story. Thank you for posting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-08-12 21:38:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never had any idea that "Religion is the opium of the people" pretty much had an entire sentence ellipsed out of it. "Religion is the sigh of the oppressed creature, the heart of a heartless world, and the soul of soulless conditions. It is the opium of the people."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-08-27 09:06:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're all on RoosterTeeths' youtube. Here's [season 1](http://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PL49C4397CE9AC5260). Wasted the whole day in nostalgia land when I found this out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-08-28 20:48:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't see them. You stuck them inside your hat for some reason. What do they say?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Spoils of War?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-08-30 11:16:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello. I've been playing BLR for a few days but I'm really confused on this one thing. Twice, I have ended a match and something labeled "Spoils of War" pops up with a list of weapon parts. But I don't see these items anywhere in my inventory. Did I unlock them? If not, what's the point of showing me? Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-05 02:27:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Couldn't this be seen as harassment, perhaps even sexual harassment? If he still works at the same company you do (even if it's another location) you might consider talking to HR or the local manager.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-08 23:53:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks awesome but, how am I supposed to get this version?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-24 00:10:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great use of the terrain! I've always wanted to make something like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-28 09:03:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm voting this "Least helpful comment of 2012".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-12 04:41:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could you upload that somewhere that doesn't force people to register? I won't even let me make a free account! I really want to make this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-13 06:08:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unlikely that anyone will see this but one thing to remember about Best Buy is that if a local competitor is doing a sale but they happen to be sold out of the good, Best Buy won't price match it. So if you see that somebody is sold out locally, don't bother trying to get BB to price match their item.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-10-13 08:16:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel so silly. I clicked on everything on that page except the actual file name. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-01-19 01:14:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey! That's at the Lucca Comics and Games Convention in Italy. I accidentally stumbled into it on vacation there by accident a while ago. Didn't even realize what was going on until I saw the welcome banner. In hindsight, the large groups of people dressed as Naruto characters should have tipped me off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-01-19 03:00:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Season 2, episode 4 - Blood. Happy watching.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-01-25 01:46:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Computers, history and porn. A+ article.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First time playing: Whats up with weapon stat requirements?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-01-30 18:26:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm on my very first playthrough. I found a mace that has a strength requirement of 12 and my strength is 16. Why is it that my attacks with it are slow and laboring for my character? I can only do one strike which is very slow and I can't chain attacks with it. The same goes for this halberd I got at the undead parish. It has STR 16 and DEX 12 requirements both of which I meet. Can anybody explain why this is happening?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-02 04:50:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks everyone. I understand now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Whats the most souls/humanity you have ever lost at once?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-02 04:56:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've only been playing for a little while but I just lost 25k souls and 4 humanity due to Blighttown. Made me angry because most of that was the reward from killing the Gaping Dragon. Whats the most you have ever lost at once?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-04 23:49:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>List of people who aren't surprised: 1. Everybody</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-04 23:57:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I high school my history teacher asked us if we could tell her what Harriet Tubman's nickname was. That was the day I learned it was, in fact, "The Mistress of the Underground Railroad" and not "Tubby".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-05 08:02:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude didn't even have a goddamn voice actor! He was a non-character. He had no history with the player, no motivation, no nothing. Just an enemy to be fought. Part of the reason why KOTOR II could never live up to the first one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-05 19:29:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe I ought to do a replay then. It seems I missed a lot of important plot points. It's not that the game itself was bad. There were a lot of things the game did right (Like expanding the crafting system, for example.) It just felt unfinished and ended up leaving a bad taste in my mouth. But I want to enjoy it. That mod you mentioned definitely sounds like something I should try, especially if it ties up some of those loose plot points.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-06 21:14:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>As someone who graduated a few months ago and is about to move out of my house, I wish I was a freshman again too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-07 01:25:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>This'll get buried but I just wanted to throw this idea out there. I think that movies based on games are better off doing the expanded universe thing rather than trying to retell the story of of the game. The game has already told it. Trying to retell it all while changing everything to work in a different medium is upsetting to fans and new viewers alike. It's better to set the movie/game as a parallel, a prequel or sequel to the events that have already happened. This prevents them from being constricted by major plot points that couldn't be changed without ruining the experience or continuity. Somebody mentioned that the movie would be better off being about the 7-hour war. This is a perfect example. It's a set piece in the Half-life timeline yet it is completely open as to what happened (except for us loosing, that is.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-07 19:53:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't worry. "They'll be worth a fortune some day."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-07 20:20:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://rasterbator.net/ Take any digital image and blow it up to a huge size by rasterizing it (converting it to series of dots). It makes a pdf file that you can then print out and assemble. The only cost is paper and ink.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-07 20:44:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you. I've felt like I'm the only one who thinks that about unleashed. Although the Werehog levels got kinda irritating at times, I found the sonic stages to be well designed and interesting. At the very *least* it was 50% good and warranted way more that the measly 3/10 ratings it got. Honestly, Unleashed gave me hope for the Sonic franchise especially after the pile of all things dark and horrible that Sonic 2006 was. It felt like a breath of fresh air and the series seems to be moving in a rather positive direction now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-07 21:14:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since when does star sign determine career path and drug usage?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-07 23:45:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had the same problem. Uninstall DSFix. Run game. Disable AA. Reinstall DSFix. Hope that helps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-16 19:03:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. Starting your own farm isn't terribly frugal. It would be nice to have a smaller veggie garden for personal use, however.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-01 18:42:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was the first thing I tried. Sadly, did not fix anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-02 19:57:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks anyway. I fixed it by deleting the chunk in MCEdit and replacing it with the same chunk from a backup save.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-03 04:57:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>My CS professor always generalized that to "If it's tedious, you're doing it wrong."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-14 07:21:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never before have I seen such sensible advice downvoted so: that you only deserve as much respect as you give.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-22 08:37:09</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;It #8217;s just $20 a month. And if all of us do it together, it gets to be millions and millions and millions of dollars! ... that goes right into 'Ol Pats pockets.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-27 23:37:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with the fact that it may be years before a treatment using this knowledge even enters human testing. However, I don't agree with the idea that pharmaceutical companies do not want effective cancer treatments. It's likely that we humans will face a never-ending cycle of disease discovery, fighting, and curing. That's because evolution itself will continually throw new plagues and maladies at us. There will always be a market in medicine. You also discount the possibility that anybody who was presented with a cure for cancer would essentially be given carte-blanche to charge whatever they want for the drug, potentially making them billions or more, worldwide. Since cancer isn't transmitable, a company to patent the cure would still have a never ending tide of cancer patients to sell to. Further more, if they refuse to take advantage of such an opportunity, another more charitable company may beat them to the punch. And really, imagine how valuable your company would become if it was labeled as the company that beat cancer once and for all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-22 18:33:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't own a pair but I can attest to the sound quality. That is because whenever somebody is wearing a pair less than 15 feet away from me, I can hear everything they are listening to as if I was wearing them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-25 02:58:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you also disable the HUD or just stitch images over it? Also, would you consider making a video of the process? I think everybody would love if people made more of these.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-30 19:45:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read somewhere that some resolution was passed that would prevent the president from using funds to close Gitmo. But why should that be an issue? The real problem are the prisoners who are there with no trial or charges. Can't he pressure the justice department to do something, or even pardon them? Keep Gitmo open for all I care, but let the prisoners have their day in court.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-05-12 01:28:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>SERIOUSLY? I need to go play that! I managed to get into the localization beta a while ago and I had a blast. I had no idea that it went F2P. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-25 19:14:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't forget the Airtight Garage! I spent so much money playing the games there. I got so upset when I started working in the area only to find that my favorite time wasting place is just a movie theater and food court.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-29 07:42:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do remember that! The teams were broken down by where you were actually sitting. You had to destroy the shield generators or something. I don't think I ever had any success in that game. I can't remember what that game was called.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-29 07:42:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah yes. Hyperbowl it was called, I believe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-11 19:00:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fucking genius!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-16 22:40:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I miss that show.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-20 04:24:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>NEVER FORGET WHERE YOU CAME FROM.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-28 00:50:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've only ever bought the Humble Android Bundle. After that, I realized I may never buy an android game again once I discovered that I can just play old gameboy games on a free emulator.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-03 22:39:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://knowyourmeme.com/memes/interior-monologue-captioning I didn't know either until today.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-08 06:22:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just some "Make Money Easy! Just Give Us Money" garbage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-08 20:40:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>In what ways would changing the engine have made it better? If the issue with the game is poor execution or planning then a change in engine would not result in too much improvement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-11 17:15:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Redacted]</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-12 04:16:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the upload. I'd also like to take this opportunity to point out that this movie is weird and I don't understand anything about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-13 01:09:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>This a misleading title. The bill would have increased minimum wage for people who work for very large companies that are worth more than a certain amount (Walmart was one of them).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-13 20:42:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm guessing that these forms of payment are untraceable, right? Guess it would have to be since this pretty much fits the definition of extortion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-13 20:46:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is extortion which is illegal... I'd also like to point out that if the NSA wanted your money they'd have an easier time of it hacking into your bank account using your stolen credentials than using a virus which costs you 300 dollars.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-15 05:22:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>That too, but good luck with this congress...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-17 06:03:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>He knew that a vote would pass which is why he did everything he could to prevent it. He just lied through his teeth about what would happen and used the "that was different" defense when anybody brought up the 47 votes to repeal the ACA.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-19 00:22:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe you were thinking of ["Romanies."](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Romani_people)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-22 22:40:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I... I don't know... Here. This links directly to the image evanfury posted but without the sidebar. http://imgur.com/HRX86Nx.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-24 07:17:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That article made me so gods damned angry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-26 07:16:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Save me a wing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-26 07:22:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel the same about this as I do about Minecraft. Other people: I made a 1:1 scale Star Destroyer replica! Me: I made a house. It has a window...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-01 18:34:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>The article mentioned this book [Denying AIDS: Conspiracy Theories, Pseudoscience and Human Tragedy](http://www.amazon.com/Denying-AIDS-Conspiracy-Theories-Pseudoscience/dp/0387794751). It has mixed reviews and I was wondering if anyone has read it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-06 21:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>All I could imagine when hearing this was a Mutant Midget Psycho from Borderlands.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-11 20:55:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>As someone who has just begun to learn Blender and modeling, I'm sure this will be very helpful. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-22 03:11:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your post actually made me buy the game on GOG when it went on sale. Of course, I have only played about 30 minutes of it but that's high praise considering all the GOG games I have that I've never installed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-28 03:00:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could argue that it was filler but it is incredibly well done and wonderfully animated in Gendy Tartakovsky's unique style. Regardless, there's a scene where Mace Windu beats up an army of super battle droids with his bare hands and the force. At least watch it for that. Also, here's a youtube link to the full show: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XTmIwOLfUlM</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-05 21:45:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone else playing this on a Mac? I just installed it and the game is really dark (Visually I mean. Even with the brightness cranked up all the way I can barely see).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-15 20:09:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you provide some more detail on this or give an example?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-21 04:40:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone on Imgur posted this: http://erfrischungsgetraenk.minus.com/uploads. It's a page with some super high quality stills taken from a bunch of Ghibli movies. Some are large enough for a dual monitor setup.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-21 18:05:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Double whammy. Zenimax (The parent company of Bethesda) did the same thing to Mojang when they announced their new game "Scrolls". They argued that it would "cause confusion" with the Elder Scrolls franchise. So you gotta rework that title pal. And fast. Edit: Well, here I was thinking i was the only person to remember that. Wha-whaaaa.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-27 18:40:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can anyone explain the little mirror that the guy is wearing on his wrist?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-07 03:59:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can play it for free on PC (Controller highly recommended). Feel the nostalgia! http://www.schtserv.com/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-07 17:22:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe try their forums. You can't be the only one who's had technical issues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-11 19:49:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh yes. Most certainly. What gives it away is numbers 1 through 21.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-12 00:28:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is why they are often called "Smiling Sammys"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-24 02:11:02</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Wouldn't it be ironic if in the interest of global warming we mandated massive switches to energy, which is a finite resource  gt;  gt; switches to energy We're already using energy! What else could we be using!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-28 22:52:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thought that said "X-rayed amputee porn". Realized my mistake and lost all interest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-06 01:06:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, these concepts are simple enough that some Googling should get you on the right path: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/UV_mapping http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Normal_mapping The basic premise is fairly simple, so I'll try and summarize Consider a flat surface like a wall which, in Blender, can be represented by 1 4-sided polygon. Without increasing the complexity of the object, we can make it more visually appealing by applying a "wallpaper" to it which is defined in an image file (Like a .jpg or .bmp). So, if we apply a texture map of a brick wall to our wall object, the object will look like a brick wall. This is UV mapping. It creates a relation between each pixel in the image file and a location on the object which alters the render, making the object appear as if it was made of bricks. This is the same principle as putting up wallpaper in your house. However, as you may know, textured objects can be much more complex than just a flat surface. In order to properly create a relation between the texture and the object, the object must be "unfolded". Consider a paper cube. If you cut along the edges of the cube and then flatten it, you will get something like [this](http://www.breezesys.com/articles/photobooth/cube_net.gif) (Minus the text) Now, we can associate a 2d texture with this "2d" version of a cube. That's UV mapping in a nutshell. If you were wondering, the U and V work in the same way that X and Y work in graphing. It was just decided to use different letters to avoid confusion. However, even though the wall looks more detailed with a brick wall texture applied to it, it's still physically flat. If we place a light source near out "brick" wall, the light will behave as if the wall was completely smooth, ruining our effect! We could create a new wall that modeled all of the little cracks and crevices of a brick wall and use that. However, in programs like video games, we don't often have the luxury to use super high detailed models. These take up a lot of space and also greatly increase the time it takes to render each frame. Here's where Normal Mapping comes in. First we need to understand what a "normal" is. In 2d geometry, we can have a straight line, and then draw a line that is perpendicular to it (so that it hits the first line at a 90 degree angle. Expand this to 3 dimensions and we have a flat polygon (a plane) and a line that touches it at a 90 degree angle. Check this image for an example. http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/a/a5/Normal_vectors2.svg/220px-Normal_vectors2.svg.png Those 2 lines define the normal of that yellow plane. They effectively show where which direction the object is "facing". Note that each normal doesn't actually go through the object. In Blender, objects only have one normal instead of 2 like in that image. This allows us to know which side of a plane is actually the "outside". I should note that in 2d geometry, those two lines I mentioned are said to be "perpendicular" but in 3d geometry the term is "orthogonal". When the light in our scene hits the wall, what happens to the light is all dependent on the Normal of our object at each point that the light touches. Since the normals of the flat wall are all facing away from the wall at a 90 degree angle, the light acts like it is hitting a flat plane. But, since the normals of out object are just data, we can force them to change to something else! http://www.bricksntiles.com/textures/brickwork_normal-map.jpg That image is a Normal Map. We apply a normal map in the same way we apply a texture map, by unfolding our object first. The difference here is, instead of each pixel in the image changing the objects color, it instead changes the objects Normal at that specific point. The normal map may just look like a really weird UV Map, but each color is interpreted as a change to the normal instead of as a color. Now when light hits the object, in reads the normal data that we defined in the normal map and creates real shadows that fall across the object as if it were more complex. With a combination of UV Mapping and Normal Mapping, you can create more detailed renders without needing extra geometry. Hope this helps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-07 18:05:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>C'mon man. They're just local self-defense forces. Thousands of them who all went out and bought the exact same uniform at army surplus stores.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-12 20:39:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>What annoys me about referring to the founding fathers is three-fold: 1. People invoke the founders names as if they were some super-perfect figure that knew exactly what should and should not happen. Essentially deifying them. 2. People claiming to know exactly what a founder would or would not have wanted to happen. Interestingly this usually takes the contrary form. "I dunno what the founders would have wanted but is sure wasn't this!". 3. People claiming that the founders wishes are always relevant. Even today. They lived over 150 years ago. They had absolutely no way of knowing what our modern times would be like. We aren't required to apply their thinking to modern issues. (There are, of course, exceptions to this rule, with many ancient people who's teachings and ideas are still widely accepted. But Abe Lincoln didn't even know what a TV show was so the point is moot.) To sum up: You don't know what the Founders would have wanted, they didn't know what today would be like, and even if they did their opinions would just be opinions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-30 19:25:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have seen this comic several times but it always seems to be translated just a little bit differently. Am I crazy?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-04 20:23:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hands down one of my favorite comedians. If you like him, also check out Black Books, a short TV series he was in along with Bill Bailey and Tamsin Greig. [Episode 1](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4GDDl74cbYA) [Episode 2](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B_Vxnf9QwMA) [Episode 3](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GeOgfvaZzFY) [Episode 4](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1KEgwqDnJR0)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-04 20:58:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I quite enjoyed Invisible War. It was one of the first xbox games I ever owned. I wasn't someone who played the first Deus Ex before playing IW so maybe that has something to do with it but I thought the game stood well on its own.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-13 19:31:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>This happened to me once. The only solution was to download MCEdit (which is good to have anyway) and copy a chunk from somewhere else to fill the hole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-19 18:13:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you click "choose best available" it gives you a list that you can choose from. Each item in the lists says what is and is not included. Alas, it seems that all of them are missing the controller and the AV cable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-03 18:45:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Moonstone Cannon, Fire!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dOKc-wdbcQA)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-04 05:13:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like to know as well. I've heard that the people behind NifTools are working on a version for the more recent versions of Blender. The only way I've done this (and I've only done it once) is to export it as an obj then import it in blender 2.49b (the version that NifTools supports) then do all the Nif exporting from there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-05 06:11:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't even know it was a franchise until you said that. [According to Wikipedia the last Spec Ops game came out in 2002](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spec_Ops_\(series\)). Why even bother with franchising it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-05 22:16:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>The world is in chaos. Our governments and military have fallen to a brutal alien regime. Our natural resources have been plundered. Vicious creatures roam the wastelands and survivors live in abject slavery. So, my eye-shadow needs to look fucking perfect. Y'know, in the name of freedom and stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-08 04:59:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you have any timelapses that you can share with us? I really want to see what one looks like!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-08 18:31:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wonderful to hear. Now if we could just get this everywhere else... Arguably, civil forfeiture before any conviction is even levied should be completely unconstitutional as it fall under "unreasonable search **and seizure**". I can't imagine anything being more unreasonable than someone being forced to prove their *innocence* when the rest of our justice system is based on innocent until proven guilty. Alas, the supreme court seems to disagree with this line of thinking: See, [Kaley v. United States](http://www.scotusblog.com/case-files/cases/kaley-v-united-states/) These forfeiture laws have their origins in the war on drugs, and I think we can all agree that this war should have ended a long time ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-08 19:40:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Excuse me ma'am, I believe this was intended for you."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-08 19:52:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you explain exactly what is going on in a situation like this? What's causing the plane to lose altitude like that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-08 22:14:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude, "Build a Beer Workshop"!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-09 18:22:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Doesn't work for me either. Not the first time this has happened. Hope it is fixed soon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-09 23:09:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just saw this today while walking to lunch and came on /r/pics to post my photos. (But I'm a good redditor so I did a search first.) Very cool art that more people should see.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-14 01:11:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bad luck Moon Moon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-15 19:38:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ever had the Memphis Mafia? That's my all time favorite. That donut is on my top 5 reasons of why I miss Portland. Honestly, it may be reason #1.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-21 21:06:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I drove out of my driveway with this, it would get stuck. I'm guessing anything steeper than a flat surface would do the same.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-29 03:09:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>None of your complaining. You pick those off the floor and eat them like a man!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-02 20:38:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mexican-Italian fusion food is the exception. Mexican lasagna is awesome with olives.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-02 21:11:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wasn't a joke. Nothing to get.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-03 20:10:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>That show just got even funnier to me. Didn't think it was possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-03 23:07:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Couldn't we just send them an email?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-05 21:17:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>A complex and dangerous situation with no easy solution. But it is clear that if the Nigerian military is unable to protect their people then someone else must do so. Either and outside military or civilian militias. There was a report a while ago about a group of civilians who repulsed an attack so we know that such a thing is possible. I wonder if there would be a way to offer aid to Nigeria that isn't in the form of more guns/troops. Perhaps logistical support via communications systems and better transport would allow the military to communicate better with remote areas and arrive quicker in case an attack is imminent (Assuming they actually heed warnings from civilians in the future).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-06 00:56:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>[At least he enjoys his work](http://37.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m6viphlpUS1rpggm0o1_250.gif)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-07 00:54:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have wanted this for so long. So much of the 40K-verse could be an awesome series. I'd love a whole series based around the Horus Heresy for instance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-26 23:23:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>German government forced to pay million euro early termination fee.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-27 22:16:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>My roommate found out that if you get that 1-shot tazer gun you can hit Yelena over and over until she dies. The amount of time she is stunned is almost equal to the reload speed of that gun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-29 09:10:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blows my friggin' mind that homosexuality can be a choice but somehow requires special therapy to "fix". At least be consistent with your crazy, GOP.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-03 20:39:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually, I think that red rock was just covered in red leaves. I remember reading about it in a book of his work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-04 00:59:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Highly recommend that movie. It's really cool to see his process along with the finished work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-08 23:30:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, even *if* he was right (Big if right there), it's not like Mars is bursting with life. It's not like, "Hey! Mars is doing just fine! All it's rain forests and oceans and sentient species are happy and healthy." Not only is he wrong but even being right wouldn't support anything he just said.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-17 18:32:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who sees a school bus and immediately thinks "illegal aliens" and not "students"? Apparently this guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-17 21:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Sheriff Paul Babeu is credited with stirring up the anti-immigrant protesters through social media postings and a press release and by leaking information about the migrants #8217; arrival to a local activist. Ah. You are correct. I thought that that was referring to just anti-immigration protests in general and not specifically what Kwasman did. I was confused and didn't realize that Kwasman *was* that "local activist".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-18 23:42:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Chutzpah** - Noun - Yiddish That quality enshrined in a man who, having killed his mother and father, throws himself on the mercy of the court because he is an orphan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-23 06:32:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>In case anybody wanted a slightly less biased source. Ya know, one that doesn't use needless sarcasm to discuss a serious issue: http://www.wtae.com/news/teenage-girl-says-police-beat-her-after-curfew-violation/26992088#!bkfKOR</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-23 19:39:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>So they spied on a public event?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-23 22:35:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, maybe not "walk in randomly off the street" public. But were they required to do anything other than sign up for these events? One of them said that at least one event was listed on facebook. That's pretty public.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-27 08:25:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I respect your idea of trying to find a middle ground here. Unfortunately the law can be incredibly slow at times. If your assets are being held while charges are being pursued, it may be months before you can get them back. There's also the question of allowing someone access to their assets in order to pay for legal defense or court fees. I could imagine a tactic of "starving" someone of their assets until they relent and accept a plea or something. The biggest part is really just the fact that whatever the cops seize goes into their operating budget creating incentive to do it more. Thankfully this bill addresses that and also closes the equitable sharing loophole. Here's hoping that congress will stop being useless for 5 minutes and push it through, though I'm not too optimistic about that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-05 18:35:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that's actually a Bernese Mountain dog.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-07 18:49:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Attorney:** My answer is that the rational basis analysis is limited to the classification. Is there a rational relationship between the classification and the legitimate interests that the state's identified. And when you look at it that way all you're asking is 'is there a rational basis...' **Judge (Interupting):** What is the classification then?" **Attorney:** Classification is between opposite sex couples on the one hand and same sex couples on the other. And the only question that one asks is 'is there a rational basis upon which to distinguish between opposite sex and same sex couples?' and the answer has to be 'yes'. It always has to be 'yes'. And I understand the other observations beyond that and I think that's all the things that you're talking about. But they don't answer the strict rational basis question that needs to be asked and answered and that question has to be answered. **Judge:** Let me see if I can run this by you then. There's two different classifications here: same sex couples and opposite sex couples. And the thing that the state of Tennessee wants to do is to encourage the opposite sex couples to get married and have children. **Attourney:** That's not the legitimate interest. That's what I said at the beginning: that out articulation is narrower than that. It is specifically to ensure that when children are born by opposite sex couples that they are born into a stable family unit. Period. **Judge:** Okay. So why do you need to prevent same sex couples from marrying in order to have that happen? **Attourney:** Again, your Honor with all due respect, you are asking me a question that's not part of the rational basis analysis. All I need to say is they've identified opposite sex couples, does that explain why same sex couples are not included? And our answer has to be 'yes'. It does explain the distinction. And we're done. That's our only point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-07 21:07:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what i got out of it. "Stable Family Unit" kinda sounds like a replacement term for "Traditional Family" which has accumulated a lot of anti-gay sentiment since it started being used by "Pro-Family" groups. It seems clear that the attorney views heterosexual couples as the only valid type of couple to raise a child.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 01:43:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was really excited for this game when it was announced. Although I own the first, I didn't play very far into the campaign but I enjoyed my time in Ascalon. Is there anyone who owns this that can give an honest opinion about GW2?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-18 22:46:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>In a complex situation, cut away all of the unnecessary details until you arrive at the core issue. Then, Google it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-21 00:34:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>That story about someone being charged with murder for lending their car freaks me out. [Full story from NYTimes](http://www.nytimes.com/2007/12/04/us/04felony.html?pagewanted=all). It seems clear that something like that is disproportionate application of the law and doesn't take any intent into consideration, as the law should. It's why we have differences between murder and manslaughter. Some may argue that the Felony Murder law makes potential accomplices think twice about getting involved, but it fails to imagine the possibility that someone may be an accomplice unwittingly, in which case someone who could be considered blameless gets life without parole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-21 01:37:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>So charge him with accessory to robbery. Doesn't seem that difficult. He also claims that he didn't believe that those who committed the crime we actually intending to do so. Obviously, this could be true or false. The article doesn't say whether or not that question was addressed during his trial.  gt;  #8220;When they actually mentioned what was going on, I thought it was a joke, #8221; Mr. Holle added, referring to the plan to steal the Snyders #8217; safe.  #8220;I thought they were just playing around. I was just very na #239;ve. Plus from being drinking [sic] that night, I just didn #8217;t understand what was going on. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-21 01:51:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would you turn down a plea bargain if you believed yourself to be innocent? I don't have much sympathy for him either, but I just don't see the point of charging him with murder when the person who caused the death of that girl was someone else. Punishment should be proportional to the crime that he committed.  gt;  #8220;Whether or not the felony murder rule can result in disproportionate justice is a matter of opinion, #8221; Mr. Rimmer said.  #8220;The father of Jessica Snyder does not think so. #8221; The original article brings up *Lex talionis*, eye-for-an-eye. It talks about how people who are angry and grieving shouldn't be the one who make the decisions about punishment and that justice should be about application of the law, not about getting back at the perpetrators.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-22 19:20:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>What year is it? The last time I heard someone complain about stem cell research was when Bush Jr was president.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-22 19:34:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bad OP! Didn't source! No biscuit! https://www.flickr.com/photos/95572727@N00/5751526500</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-22 19:50:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kinda wish there was a mod that retextured all the weapons as being made out of money. Weapon repair would make more sense then. Although, there may be a net-loss of sense overall.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-24 03:52:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>SWORD AND SCABBARD 1 EA $100.13 Hey guys! Check out this sweet sword I got of the 1033!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Build Help] Ars Technica - System Guide Budget Build - August 2014</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-26 21:52:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ars Technica had a system build guide article today. I decided to look into their Budget Build as I am currently planning my own first pc build. Here's the [article.](http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2014/08/ars-technica-system-guide-august-2014/). They include several alternative parts in the guide, but I decided to stick with the basics here. And here is the listed parts in a [PCPartPicker](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/h4GZXL) list (not sure how to make this render on the page). It's pretty cheap as is: $724.74 before rebates. I don't even need all the peripherals so that knocks off about $200. The only obvious area of improvement to me is to include a larger SSD or additional HDD. This would increase the price by $30 (for an extra 128gb on the SSD) to $100 (for 512gb total on the SSD). Maybe around +$60 for a 1tb HDD. How functional would this be as a mid-high range gaming build? What sort of changes would be needed to make it viable as such if it is not already. Budget: $900.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-26 22:10:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Budget is $900. Should have mentioned that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-26 22:45:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Already got windows. Also planning to use our TV so don't need a monitor. Have keyboard/mouse already as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-27 00:12:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>No overclocking. (Man, I failed to mention a lot of stuff...)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-27 18:13:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Out of curiosity (sorry if this was asked before), how old are Tweedle and Whippy? In my head, they are teens but the fact that one asked to borrow your car has gotten me confused.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-28 01:36:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the suggestion. I don't intend to sound rude, but I was more interested with with the build that Ars posted and how good of a gaming comp it was. Not that I don't appreciate you designing one for me, but it doesn't answer my original question.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-03 22:36:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.forbes.com/sites/instituteforjustice/2014/05/07/minnesota-forfeiture-reform/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-04 18:36:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had no idea that they even had an affiliation. I figured that ALEC, being a clearly evil policy group, and Google, with it's "Don't be evil" tagline, would be like oil and water.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-05 22:09:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Simple (possibly obvious) question: I own the base game but not on steam. If I bought the trilogy, would i be able to access my old account alright?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-05 22:16:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>For 5.00? Oh yeah. Personally, I don't particularly like the Catwoman bits but the rest of the game is great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-06 20:11:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I assume that means that there is an end game and it isn't just like minecraft where you play for however long you want?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-08 19:14:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I recall reading somewhere that this game has a huge install size in order to deter piracy. Is that true?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-11 19:59:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I passed through TSA with [this](http://www.weapons-universe.com/Martial-Arts/Martial-Arts-Knives/Mtech-41.jpg) in my bag without even knowing it. I didn't find out until I got home and unpacked!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-11 21:34:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Funny, but I think you have the wrong sub.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-11 22:48:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, you never know what damage you could have done with a Nalgene (aka. Terrorist Container)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-12 18:25:51</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Can you show me where you learned this regarding their curriculum...or are you just giving me your opinion on what you think it's about? From the article:  gt; The Charles Koch Foundation expressed a willingness to give Florida State an extra $105,000 to keep Benson  #8212; a self-described  #8220;libertarian anarchist #8221; who asserts that every government function he #8217;s studied  #8220;can be, has been, or is being produced better by the private sector #8221;  #8212; in place. So, considering their strong support of someone who holds this view who is also a fellow "libertarian" and also happens to be department chair (of what I assume is the economics department. It isn't specified). I would logically conclude that this belief would play a part in whatever "curriculum" they concoct.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-12 18:38:25</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I will not write much about libertarianism, as I have published many papers and books explaining my views. The anarcho-capitalist position arises because every government activity I have studied (e.g., policing, courts, law, highways, regulation) can be, has been, or is being produced better by the private sector, **so I am yet to find a valid justification for the state.** [Source](http://mailer.fsu.edu/~bbenson/) I think this is pretty telling of his views on the purpose of government. No, I cannot cite all of the government functions that he has studied but it seems clear that, if he has found some that contradict his view that the state has no justification, he isn't saying which ones they are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-12 18:57:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>You'll forgive me for saying that he sounds exactly like the opposite of someone who is keeping an open mind. That being said, this quote was written in 2008. (Says so on the bottom of the page I linked). Also, do you really think he was going to enumerate all of the branches of government that he found useless? Suggesting that by leaving one out he proclaims that branch to be something that the private sector can't do better? More likely he was giving examples as evidenced by the **e.g.** before the list.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-12 19:15:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't call is a sweeping generalization. More like: Logic 101. Also, I'm not interested in if you agree with his findings or not. In fact I don't even care about whatever political philosophy you adhere to. The point I was arguing was that Bruce Benson has made himself clear that he does not believe that there is a valid justification for the state based on his examinations of various branches in comparison to private sector industries that provide the same service. And that, because of this belief, his department chair status, and because part of the requirement by the Koch Foundation that he stay on for an additional 3 years after his intention to step down in 2012 that it seems evident that this would play some role in future curriculum.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-12 23:19:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome. I've had the second one as my desktop on my dual monitors for a while now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-22 22:14:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow. #1 in that image happened to me in Rome. Slightly different in that, instead of having my pockets picked, the guy brought over his friend to "say hello". I realized later that this was his backup in case I didn't want to pay. So, yeah. I paid 5 euros for some fucking string.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-22 22:19:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You mean like [this?](http://youtu.be/Hch3HL8gPTk?t=1m59s)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-24 21:53:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone else reminded of the "Terrorist Fist Jab"?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-25 18:05:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally, I don't believe on God. That's just me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-25 21:59:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>So did I, but when I googled it, all the related stored called it a "jab". So I went with that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-26 18:58:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Talking to some friends a while back about 40K, they said that official tournaments only allow 100% official pieces. 3D printed ones are not allowed. Total BS if you ask me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-26 19:20:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>$18,000 in 1970 is $100,000 today http://data.bls.gov/cgi-bin/cpicalc.pl?cost1=18000 amp;year1=1970 amp;year2=2014</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-26 19:34:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bootcamp dude. My MacBook Pro is actually pretty decent at running games on Windows 7. For some reason, the mac version of the same game run like shit. Switch to Windows partition and it runs great and on mid - high graphics even.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-26 22:20:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does their pizza cost $400+?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-26 22:33:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't worry. I'm sure he won't be taking any of those many congressional vacations he'll be entitled to. That would make him a hypocrite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-26 22:49:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another insane aspect of our justice system that I've never even thought about until just now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 23:17:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hell to tha yeah!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 23:37:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like to take this opportunity to say how completely retarded it is to label one's self as "Pro Family". It's just code for "Anti-Gay". Find me one person who is against the idea of people forming a group based on relationships either genetic or legal, then you can call yourself Pro Family.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 23:44:12</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; "This is not Africa," Thompson said. "We have a great infrastructure to deal with an outbreak." We also have fewer people who believe that Ebola is some sort of hoax made up by doctors. So, that helps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-04 01:14:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Good for her there's no law or statute that requires state governments to follow the laws laid down by the federal government. That would make her insane and not very well-read.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Supremacy_Clause)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-07 01:47:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will this be visible on the West Coast at all?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-08 22:05:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the curious: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Orval_Faubus</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-09 01:08:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Texture mapping. It's like wallpaper. You take a flat piece of art and apply it to an object. You may have to fold it or stretch it a little bit to work on more complex objects.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-09 22:18:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>And welcome to Iran!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-11 07:12:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>"To learn who rules over you, simply find out who you are not allowed to criticize." - Voltaire</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-13 18:24:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I dunno about you, but I've always been cautioned to avoid [shotgun surgery](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shotgun_surgery) in my line of work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-15 22:42:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that how you did the deadspace ones? Just cropped Isaac out of the resulting shot?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-22 05:40:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish this dog lived on my walk to work. It would totally take the sting out of Monday mornings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-24 21:38:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of the few times I've heard my parents consider getting solar is during a power outage where we looked at our neighbors house and saw that all the lights were on because they had solar panels and were running everything off built in storage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-24 23:21:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spoiler alert: the lawmakers were in on it too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-25 00:23:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just want to warn people that the Mac version of AC2 does not run very well at all. I got about 15 FPS at minimal resolution. However, on my Windows 7 partition (using bootcamp) it runs great. Don't know what exactly the problem is. Just might want to be careful unless you have a supernew Mac that it might not work so well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-25 02:59:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I played it on the exact same hardware just with different operating systems. Mac: runs terribly. Windows: runs fine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-25 07:43:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure what subreddit you intended to post this too but I'm guessing /r/aww was not it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-27 19:22:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whether or not he's actually an asshole or it's just part of his character, I don't think he's the kind of person I'd want at a commencement speech.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-28 01:31:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Transcript of the speech.](http://origin.library.constantcontact.com/download/get/file/1109132129778-302/Transcript_Mumia_Abu_Jamal_Commencement_Speech_10_05_2014+%281%29.pdf) I've certainly read better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-28 18:56:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. http://www.un.org/apps/news/story.asp?NewsID=48672#.VBGYQvmwJ4c  gt; According to the experts, so far in 2014, at least 45 people have been executed in Saudi Arabia. Between 4 and 22 August, 22 people were executed, which represents an average of one execution per day. These included at least eight people beheaded for non-violent crimes including drug-smuggling and sorcery. Other offences resulting in beheading have reportedly included adultery and apostasy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-29 20:21:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought he was gonna climb the rock in the preview picture using "just a bike". Lies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-29 21:06:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you have a source? I've never heard about this view before. This article from The Atlantic seems to paint a picture of them actually viewing certain people of practitioners of magic, which may include the riding of brooms: http://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2013/08/saudi-arabias-war-on-witchcraft/278701/  gt; "Some magicians may ride a broom and fly in the air with the help of the jinn [supernatural beings]," The article has other examples of people being accused and punished for acts of magic including casting spells that bring sickness or damage marriages.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-29 21:26:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Quelle horreur!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-30 17:24:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I almost saw this happen. Waiting for my train to arrive, some guy decided to bolt across the train crossing while the gates were down. The train probably missed him by about 3 seconds. If he had slipped and fell, that would have been the end for him. Plus, the train that he was trying to catch was 5 minutes away. He would not have missed it had he waited.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-30 22:02:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh. *That* Paul Broun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-30 22:05:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trying2BaWiseGuy 2016!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-30 22:14:50</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; "Reznick even invoked the Muslim extremist group ISIS. He argued that releasing the names of the reservists could put them at risk of attacks by the terrorist group." I think the day that ISIS cares about some pay-to-play cops in a 300 person town in Michigan is the day that ISIS ceases to be a legitimate threat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-31 19:57:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd rather fight deathclaws. For some insane reason, cazadors seems to be randomly immune to certain things. By certain things, I mean grenade launchers. No joke. I've wasted many grenade on cazadors which did fuck all. I have no idea how you could ever get the Crackerjack Timing challenge because they seem to be immune to dynamite as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-31 23:19:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use bullet time in place of VATS so I can confirm that. The best way I've found is aim for the wings with a hunting shotgun. Once you've got some decent gear, they aren't so bad. It just throws me that a grenade launcher can be ineffective. Unless you are using incendiary grenades. Those actually work quite well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-31 23:49:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't call the graphics "horrible". I think "simplistic" is more fair. Minecraft is pretty but the graphics aren't "bad". See what I mean? Besides, I would imagine that they want to focus on gameplay features like crafting and shooting. Graphical updates are always a possibility.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-31 23:56:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's so insane that they want to prevent people from having abortions yet do not want their children to learn about preventative measures. Not all contraceptives are abortatives. Learn the difference. Get your head out of the sand people. Your kids are gonna have sex and there's pretty much nothing you can do about it. Teach them that there are safe ways. You can prevent them from becoming teen parents.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-05 22:25:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Best relationship in a TV show. Hands down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-06 03:58:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Psych.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-06 18:38:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe that possession of a stolen firearm is already a felony in California. Let me see if I can dig up a source. Edit: According to this, http://www.shouselaw.com/grandtheft-firearm.html, stealing a firearm is considered Grand Theft which is a felony.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-06 21:07:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>The relevant part of the bill: Section 490.2 is added to the Penal Code, to read: 490.2. (a) Notwithstanding Section 487 or any other provision of law defining grand theft, obtaining any property by theft where the value of the money, labor, real or personal property taken does not exceed nine hundred fifty dollars ($950), shall be considered petty theft and shall be punished as a misdemeanor Section 487 is where theft of a firearm is considered Grand Theft. Problem is, I have no idea what notwithstanding means in the context of a legal document like this. Does it mean that Section 487 still stands or that the new section overrides it? I wish bills like this would just use regular speech instead of needlessly complicated legal jargon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-06 21:15:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Perhaps one day, Christians will be able to worship openly in this country. An maybe, just maybe, we will be tolerant enough to elect one president.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-06 21:23:31</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; The last time city police officers were prosecuted for brutality was in 2008, according to the New York Daily News, when three officers were charged with forcing a baton into a man's anus during an arrest. A jury acquitted the officers. What the fucking fuck?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-08 03:47:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. Google lists the running time as 106 minutes but the youtube video is 132.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-12 18:10:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>As an actual Space Jew, I take offence that you would equate my noble race of interstellar mensches with the likes of those despicable greedy aliens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-14 19:46:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I concur. I mean, they didn't even make up a plausible name for the singer. "NeYo"? What parent would willingly inflict such torment on their children?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-14 20:05:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I ever end up on the street, I think "dignity" would be the least of my concern after "survival".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-15 17:03:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is on Netflix instant watch right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-17 21:17:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everything I've read classifies them as dolphins, not porpoises. Then again, I ain't no marine biologist. Some brief googling seems to suggest that the difference between the two is a matter of [physical characteristics.](http://oceanservice.noaa.gov/facts/dolphin_porpoise.html)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-18 21:00:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Considering how much money they seem to need to do their job, no, I would not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-18 21:03:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.linkedin.com/pub/jennifer-lawton/10/784/92</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-18 21:11:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow. The Cons aren't even Cons. It's like the equivalent of saying your biggest weakness is working too hard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-19 19:07:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Orcas are: Order: Cetacea Suborder: Odontoceti Family: **Delphinidae** Genus: Orcinus ------------------ Dolphins are: Order: Cetacea Suborder: Odontoceti And one of the possible families is **Delphinidae** ------------------ Porpoises are: Order: Cetacea Suborder: Odontoceti Family: Phocoenidae ------------------ So, Orcas are closer to dolphins in their taxonomy. \#Facepalm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-19 19:29:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>In protest, all UCD students should substitute the phrase in as many places as possible. "Pulled pork sandwiches for lunch today? I'm so hitting that." "Free movie night on tueday! You guys gonna hit that?" "Option for extra credit in my calc class. Gonna hit that like a mofo."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-20 00:36:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Then my work here is done.](http://www.satnat.net/wp-content/uploads/2013/08/Mission-accomplished.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-20 01:13:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Witchhunter Batman](http://www.figures.com/forums/attachments/news/6716d1274987052-return-bruce-wayne-action-figures-announced-1brucecover.jpg) [Wild West Batman](http://wac.450f.edgecastcdn.net/80450F/comicsalliance.com/files/2010/07/cowboy-batman.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-20 20:30:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's too bad. I love GITS but this doesn't look too much different from Blacklight Retribution but with more gadgets.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-20 20:33:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pay a visit to the next session of congress.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-21 23:11:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ensuring that people in the future will get boners when eating an actual peach.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-22 00:24:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck me sideways! An honest, not-in-it-for-the-easy-money DA who actually gives a damn about innocent people getting their money stolen! In Tennessee! Honestly, I feel motivated to try and contact him just to say "well done."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-24 18:55:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shoulda just [buried his head in the sand.](http://www.bbc.com/news/world-australia-30053739)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-29 09:20:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup. You had the option of creating a character as an online character or offline. Apparently, Actilizzard has suffered from a bit of amnesia.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-03 18:46:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope that it's down due to an overwhelming number of people trying to submit complaints.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-05 22:14:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your post made me actually look at my card progress. Is it just me or this the system very confusing? It seems like I've earned almost all my cards just by purchasing a game. Also, I've read that you receive booster packs randomly when someone crafts a badge but how does someone craft a badge without possessing a booster pack?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-06 01:50:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>How does the universe know it's the last time? What if you died the second time because someone said your name "for the last time" but then someone else said it again an hour later. Do you come back for an hour and then die? I don't get it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-12 18:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m fairly sure if they took porn off the internet, there #8217;d only be one website left, and it #8217;d be called Bring back the porn! #8221; - Dr. Cox</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-12 18:55:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.eeemo.net/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-14 19:00:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like to point this out:  gt; (36) The term `enhanced body armor' means body armor, including a helmet or shield, the ballistic resistance of which meets or exceeds the ballistic performance of Type III armor, determined using National Institute of Justice Standard-0101.06 It doesn't ban all armor, just armor equal to or above a type III rating. Not that I agree with the ban at all, of course.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-15 06:23:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see. I don't really know much (read: anything) about body armor but that is good info to have. I'm guessing that anything the police field is over type 3 then.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-15 06:25:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did something similar. But nothing happened. Because I have no friends.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-15 19:05:48</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; "We oppose ALL subsidies, whether existing or proposed, including programs that benefit us, which are principally those that are embedded in our economy, such as mandates." "Koch will continue to lobby for the repeal of subsidies and mandates, as we work to make people's lives better. We believe history has proven that this is the best course to foster job creation, opportunity and prosperity." The fact that the subsidies still exist is proof that they are lying. If they wanted them gone, they would be gone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-15 22:43:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm really kicking myself because there was a free weekend a while back. I installed the game but then it slipped my mind so I don't know if I want it or not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-15 23:16:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you nail it, you have the unprecedented opportunity to take an actual victory lap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-18 23:02:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had a friend (read: asshole I knew but hung out with anyway because I didn't have any actual friends) in grade school who had 7 names. One of them was "Kamahameha" and another was "Aristophanes". I still remember the his entire name because he always said the whole thing (he was quite proud of it)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-19 07:27:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know if I pick this game up my ships will be the equivalent of a dirt house in minecraft. Some people are just on a different level.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-14 19:20:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dear god. It's even worse than i imagined: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3rSWkXb7Kao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-23 03:08:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>The dwarf spider: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Erigoninae</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-23 03:37:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chow + husky?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-27 06:11:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck this game. http://i.imgur.com/EG0undB.jpg JK. But seriously, at least "Pebrine" sounds like a word.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-03 19:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sure their very expensive Harvard trained lawyers would be more than happy to elaborate the difference for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-03 21:18:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Too true. In my experience, whenever I get mad at a game I'll actually start to do even worse at it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-09 22:51:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>SP feels completely lifeless. The only enemies are training robots and the only people you hear are robot voices aside from some audio logs. There's no checkpoint system at all so death = mission restart. I died during both "campaign" missions and decided to quit rather than redo the same 20 minutes over again. I feel like what they have now could be a decent framework for a good game but this version just isn't that. I do have to hand it to them for not just making "CoD In Space". It's definitely going to be more challenging and tactical. Closer to Rainbow Six I'd wager.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-10 08:11:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nothing wrong with seeing for yourself. It's just my opinion anyway. And the install file is super small (I think it was 1 gig) so even if you don't like it you won't have to wait too long to find out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-10 08:24:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Couldn't even choose to play as a girl...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hangnail Apocalypse</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-18 01:21:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-18 01:22:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read that as "Miami Buffet". Kind like it better...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-18 01:23:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>NSFW: http://imgur.com/r/MURICA/X9DLci9</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-18 17:51:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>DVD extra deleted scene. Flashback where John Wilkes Booth is revealed to be the founder of one of the assassin agencies. Doesn't really add much to the movie, IMO.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-18 18:24:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sleep all night and I sleep all day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-19 19:14:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember mailing in 14 dollars cash to get my account upgraded. Money well spent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-20 18:09:36</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; A doula (/ #712;du #720;l #601;/, also known as a birth companion and post-birth supporter[1] and originating from the Ancient Greek word  #948; #959; #973; #955; #951; which is the feminine form of "slave") Huh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-20 22:33:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dunno. Let's ask Google Sensei: http://www.americanpregnancy.org/pregnancyblog/2011/11/what-is-the-difference-between-a-midwife-and-a-doula/ Looks like midwives have actuall medical training.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-23 18:07:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you confusing Wildstar with FireFall?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-25 07:38:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>REFRIGERATE!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-25 07:49:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>IT people don't get a lot of respect in their line of work. I imagine if a half-ton animal with massive claws told you to restart your computer, the answer would be "Yes, Sir" instead of "But that shouldn't fix anything!". Probably would be an asset to the department. Pay's not bad either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-25 07:51:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>This really makes me miss that show...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-25 07:53:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://explosm.net/rcg/FierceFlyCoat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-26 18:22:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>How is he more responsible for someones death than the person who fired the gun?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-26 18:26:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too man. Everyone here is like "55 years for attempted burglary? Yeah. I'm down with that. Fuck this 16 year old kid for being a stupid teenager."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-26 18:32:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only one person killed his friend. The homeowner. He did so in self defense on his own property so it is not murder (rightfully so). The kid in the article is being charged with making a decision that resulted in *someone else* killing his friend. And now he is being charged with murder? Nobody else seems to get how fucked up that is? People on here seem to be saying "He was committing a burglary so fuck him. Murder charges? Yeah, throw those in there too. 55 years is perfect for a teenager with bad judgement who had no intent on anyone getting hurt or killed."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-26 18:33:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is he more culpable than the person who fired the gun?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-26 19:55:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don't need to be an asshole because I have a different opinion that yours. Also, there's no such thing as "Societal Darwinism". You're probably thinking of "Social Darwinism". If you think that I don't deserve to pass on my genes because of something like a difference of opinion, perhaps you are the one who should be excised from the genepool. Just sayin'.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-26 22:01:09</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; If someone does have trouble with this concept, better they're weeded out now than before they reproduce and pass on more stupidity. It's classic evolution in action - societal Darwinism at its finest. I assumed that this was aimed at me. If that is incorrect then I apologize. Still, I can't claim to have been the smartest of teenagers though I never tried to rob a house. I think that simply resigning this young man to prison for such a long time serves little purpose. My issue lies with the Felony Murder law requiring simply a death to have occurred during the course of the crime taking place instead of being at their hands directly. In this case, the reaction of the homeowner determines what crimes they are charged with rather than their own actions. If the homeowner had not killed anyone they would only face burglary charges. If he had killed 2 people instead of just one, would the kid face double felony murder? As for Societal Darwinism, any search for that returns only results for "Social Darwinism". If that is just an obscure term then a good source explaining it would be appreciated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-27 05:47:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thought this sounded familiar: http://www.reddit.com/r/Bandnames/comments/2wruam/the_sax_offenders/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-27 06:23:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Followed your advice and the white does look a lot more blue than I had first imagined but the gold still looks gold.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-27 17:15:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope they do. PayPal is a horrible service and they've had a grip on the market for too long. Some of the shit they pull makes me wonder how they still exist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-01 06:43:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wasn't this a joke from Cow  amp; Chicken?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-01 06:47:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>All rise for the Honorable UncreativeTeam. This Karma Court is now in session. You may be seated. The People vs JHBlancs. 1 count fucking up with his ASCII arrows in the first degree. How does the defendant plea?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-01 17:05:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't plead mobile ignorance under the law.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-01 17:48:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Non-culpable?  gt; Sorority Sigma Delta Tau was placed on a two-year disciplinary suspension because its members "stood by at Treetops Resort and allowed others to vandalize the facility," according to the U-M sanctions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-02 00:10:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck it. Case closed. Bring in the dancing lobsters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-02 00:35:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've got some River Dancing Rabbits. Will that do?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-02 03:36:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not if I overrule those rules...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-05 22:53:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you have Ghostery installed? I've found that I need to pause blocking in order for the link to work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Halal, Goodbye. (All Muslim Beatles cover band)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-07 17:57:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-09 17:50:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://in2gpu.com/2014/07/27/build-minecraft-unity-part-1/ I didn't even know that was a thing. I might have to give it a go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-11 19:34:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>A map of the cave that shows you how to get to the exit from the one treasure chest in the cave.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-12 07:20:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Need to get 3 teenagers to stand in front of their local government building with signs saying "Fuck this Shit". While spitting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Capital Zero</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-13 07:03:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idea shamelessly stolen from /u/TechRentedMule from http://www.reddit.com/r/talesfromtechsupport/comments/2ysocw/capital_zero/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-13 17:44:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I prefer PICNIC: Problem In Chair Not In Computer. Rolls off the tongue better than PEBKAC.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-14 16:12:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've looked and I've only found 2 instructions by him to make guns. Halo pistol: http://www.mocpages.com/moc.php/294935 SOCOM pistol: http://www.mocpages.com/moc.php/222274 With a lot of patience and reference images you might be able to reverse engineer some of the larger ones using Lego Digital Designer...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-14 16:20:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually, the Lego Digital Designer (assuming Nick Brick actually uses it) can automatically generate step-by-step instructions from something you create. If he used the LDD he could have easily make instruction files and shared them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-14 16:22:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>But what you find out he's up against Hunters?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-14 18:37:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Back when hunters were somehow the least threatening enemy in the game. Good times. Hell, a lego version of the magnum would probably work just as fine as the real one on one of those guys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-14 20:25:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You forgot about the people making the guns and bombs. They're the real winners.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-14 20:30:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, it's not like a majority of other animals possess the cognitive functions to move beyond their baser instincts of reproduction and survival. They can't consider it "sacred" because the idea of "sacred" is an entirely human invention. It's the same reasons wolves don't consider certain books or symbols to be sacred either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-14 20:40:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Survival instincts that reward us for favoring more survivable conditions? I mean, I just made that up. I have no idea. Does that sound acceptable?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-14 20:43:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, but I'm pretty sure that some people somewhere have banged on top off a moving car. I mean, it would probably have to be a planned thing but I'm sure it's been done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-14 20:55:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did specify that it would probably have to be planned. Are you modifying your original question to be "why do animals seem to have indiscriminate sex without any introduction with other animals they have just met?". In that case, I don't know but some animals do mate for life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-15 16:42:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know much about space exploration but I imagine it would be pretty difficult to successfully launch a rocket without understanding the thing you were launching it off of. Wind speeds, atmospheric pressure, gravity... it probably all factors in somehow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-15 17:35:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>He should guest star on Walking Dead. Apocalypse = over.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-15 17:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>My secret is just dropping 3 bottlecap mines before I aggro one. If that doesn't kill it, it's pretty much guaranteed to cripple at least one leg. Without their insane speed they aren't even 10% as threatening.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-15 17:44:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>If people reading this are curious about where the Trejo face comes from, it's from a mod made by DragBody. The mod is only consistently available here http://vgunetwork.forumotion.net/ but the site requires you to reach a certain rank before you gain access to it. I'm sure some people have hosted the mod elsewhere but that is against the wishes of the mod creator. I do recommend becoming a member of the community. People are very friendly there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-16 01:34:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-16 01:43:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry you feel that way. But then again, it is not for you to decide what a mod creator does with their content. If they decide not to release it for the whole world then that's their decision. Additionally, part of the reason it's done is that a lot of the content that these guys make is ripped from other games. In an attempt to prevent legal action from being taken against sites that host such content, it was decided that the best course of action is to control access to said content. The funny thing is that it isn't even that hard to gain mod access. If you're active on the forums and chat it might only take a few days. But just by having that restriction, the community prevents entry to those who just want to download stuff and then leave. If you want free mods, go to the Fallout Nexus. It's not like there's a shortage of mods for games freely available.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-16 02:53:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you accept that money is equivalent to free speech then that means some people have more free speech than others.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-16 04:50:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unless you're in New Vegas.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-16 04:58:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meh. Honestly, I couldn't be bothered. The bottlecap mine method always worked fine enough for me. I didn't feel the need to install a mod that would make it even easier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-16 16:32:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. You're probably right. It's not like that guy would fit in anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-18 18:48:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>In Her Majesty's Secret Cervix</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Source files for Armor and Helmets</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-19 03:39:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been digging through the games source files trying to find the models for the armor and helmets (using UE Model Viewer). I've found the files for the outfits of the Hero characters which are located here: C:\Program Files (x86)\Steam\steamapps\common\blacklightretribution\Blacklight Retribution\Live\FoxGame\DLC\PCConsole\HeroXXX but I have not been able to find the files for the base armor and helmets. It's kinda driving me crazy right now. I feel like I must be missing something. This is kind of a shot in the dark but if someone has any experience with this I'd appreciate a hand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-19 17:08:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have. You'd assume that everything I'm looking for would be in the CH_Helmets_SF file but when I look for meshes, I only see the following: http://i.imgur.com/1UyYkAS.jpg http://i.imgur.com/U5o76Bj.jpg http://i.imgur.com/abGxEMV.jpg I did find what appears to be the face plate of the Dataluxe Slant http://i.imgur.com/UfBDnqg.jpg But that's it. It's like the other helmets are appearing in pieces. I'm not sure if I am doing something wrong when I view them... The Upper_Body files show what look like some very fragmented armors. Like, stuff is floating in space. http://i.imgur.com/K0PkT1t.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 06:20:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Keep your shirt tucked in, go down with the ship and never leave a man behind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 17:23:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I imagine you'd have to apply the normal way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 19:22:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought this was a pretty good low-budget movie. It's proof that you don't need ridiculous special effects to tell a good sci-fi story.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 19:26:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>We had witness reports and even rebel twitter accounts confirming that the plane was shot down but forensic evidence is something we didn't have. It's not like anything will change because of this. At least, not until the Russian backed separatists are arrested and held accountable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 21:42:25</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; The citizens in that part of Ukraine actually want to be part of Russia. I'll bet there are more than a few Crimeans who disagree with that statement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 21:46:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's really hard to tell what they really wanted when the vote for annexation was done under armed watch by Russian soldiers. Had it happened before the invasion it would probably be more accepted as legitimate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 21:46:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Potato potato.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 23:40:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>As opposed to it happening after the invasion and *definitely* being fixed by the occupiers?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 23:55:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just because 58% considered themselves Russians 10 years ago doesn't mean you have a guaranteed victory. That number could have changed significantly in that time. Additionally, is it guaranteed that everyone of those 58% will vote "yes"? Perhaps some have mixed feelings or are on the fence about it. Surely, some will have been upset over what could be considered a needless military intervention. Perhaps some of them will abstain from voting entirely. There's more factors at play that just what percentages there are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-21 04:17:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>360 No scope</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-21 16:26:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think "Shotgun Funeral" is great by itself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-22 05:34:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kinda already done: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gaye_Bykers_on_Acid One of their stage names was "Lesbian Dopeheads on Mopeds"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-22 17:47:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>It all depends on usage of course, but my phone is a Razr HD MAXX and I haven't charged it in 3 days and it's at 40% power. I don't really use it for much more than the occasional text and playing solitaire.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-22 19:18:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. So, i found out what was going on. For some reason, when opening certain files with UE Viewer, the first material that is selected if completely invisible. However, if you simply cycle the material by pressing M you should be able to see the object. So, I had found the correct files but just didn't realize it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What helmets are these?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-22 19:31:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, I've been exploring the games source files when I came across some helmets I had never seen before. None of them can be seen in the games armory so I'm hoping someone could at least tell me the names and if they are actually available in the game. 1. http://i.imgur.com/zZTkyR2.png 2. http://i.imgur.com/kzlJ6si.png 3. http://i.imgur.com/CIrorJ2.png 4. http://i.imgur.com/UdZSPti.png 5. http://i.imgur.com/9Mq2nnW.png (I only seen one person with this but still know nothing about it)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-22 20:22:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, it isn't The Onion so technically...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-22 20:23:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. Do you know the names of the other ones?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-22 20:36:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Much appreciated. That links keeps redirecting me to arc-games. This one seems to work though.. why is that? http://www.arcgames.com/en/games/blacklight-retribution/news/detail/9052503-prototype-helmets-weekend-sale</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-23 05:11:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's very shortsighted to simply maximize your pay at the expense of your employees. Like the article said, when the collective purchasing power of the people goes down the economy suffers. Through this, businesses suffer. If you're the top CEO at a firm and you make a million dollars a year and the board comes along and offers you a 100,000 bonus will that bonus really improve your quality of life? No you really need it? If you instead decided that you would use that bonus to give 100 of your employees a smaller bonus instead, you may greatly increase their quality of life. $1,000 may not mean much to you but to someone making $10/hour that's a huge amount of money. And that money will likely go back into the economy instead of sitting in some trust somewhere. If that option is on the table, then I would argue that increasing your pay in that instance is selfish.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-25 22:26:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was genuinely surprised in one of the later Modern Warfare games where you're riding a chopper and another one crashes into you. I'm thinking "Yup. Had to happen sooner or later." But then you don't crash and the pilot's like "I think we're okay!". Had to give the devs props for going against expectations.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-26 22:34:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Somethings up with the subtitles. The letters "fi" are all replaced with " #241;". Fire - gt;  #241;re. Finally - gt;  #241;nally.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-28 23:26:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Both of them did. I read it as two killers who just happened to be gay got married. I read it the opposite way that Teary did.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-28 23:29:26</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Mikhail Gallatinov was locked up in 1997 for the murder of Salford man Adrian Kaminsky who he had met through a gay chat line before luring him to his home in Moston.  gt; Goodwin was sentenced to life behind bars in 2007 for a  #8216;gay-bashing #8217; killing on Blackpool seafront.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-30 21:33:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Climate change is religion. Therefor it has no place in government. Except for Christianity. That's different.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-30 21:45:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>You heard it here first people: White Christians will soon lose the right to vote as they have far too much political clout. There's no way they believe this bullshit. It's a blatant attempt at logical acrobatics in order to throw another wrench in the equal march towards equal rights.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-07 17:55:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was just reading another article about the proposed law and it said TANF not SNAP. Unless they are the same thing then this article is wrong. Not saying the law is a good idea though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-09 21:05:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe those are how emergency blinkers work in Russia?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-10 03:59:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reminds me of a new feature I was assigned to develop. Our web application had customizable dropdown menus with 25 options. My task was to increase that number to 50. To my horror, the person who wrote the thing had somehow forgotten about loops. That's right: s/he had copied, pasted and modified the 25 lines to enable the functionality desired. In just one place? Nope. This was done in about 30 different classes. To make matters worse, it turned out that there were originally only 10 options and it was written like this from the start. But it was then increased to 15 options and then 25. Both times, whoever was behind it just tacked on more lines. Fortunately, going from 25 to 50 was not something I was prepared to do via copy and paste. Once I was done, the number of options was tied to a single variable which could be changed at any time. Like how it should have been.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-10 06:04:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Already beat you too it: http://www.endevr.com/balance-bracelets/purestrength/t1i-series-bracelet  gt; four additional components of health technology including a far-infrared bio-ceramic blend, a powerful 600 gauss magnet, pure germanium and naturally energized tourmaline. All for only $119.95 (Plus S amp;H)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-10 17:41:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It may not seem like a big deal if you only have 10 or so lines. But what if you need to repeat a task 100 or 1000 times? Modifying code that involves copying and pasting lines becomes a huge endeavor and is prone to errors if you forget to change one of the lines (And trust me, with copy and paste, that will happen.) If you have many lines of code that only vary slightly from one to another in a predictable manner, it's much better to use some sort of looping structure. This makes it much easier to read and modify. If you need to increase the number of times the code runs, you just change the loop conditions to run longer instead of having to copy and paste a bunch of lines and then change them to work properly. It also makes your code much shorter. A common rule of programming is DRY: Don't Repeat Yourself. Or as one of my professors once said, "If it's tedious, you're doing it wrong." Which of these looks like it's easier to modify or debug? Variable.setParameters(1); Variable.setParameters(2); Variable.setParameters(3); Variable.setParameters(4); ... Variable.setParameters(97); Variable.setParameters(98); Variable.setParameters(99); Variable.setParameters(100); or int i = 0; while (i  lt;= 100) { Variable.setParameters(i); }</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-10 18:49:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nothing has ever surpassed my original shitty xbox. It would constantly hit me with the "Game cannot be read. It may be dirty or damaged" error screen on brand new games. I finally lost it. I picked it up and almost threw it out the window but I calmed down a bit and instead carved the word "crap" into it with a knife. Nothing has ever made me rage harder than that and I hope it stays that way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-10 18:49:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have my sympathies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-10 20:43:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has the curriculum covered loops yet? If you haven't reached there it's understandable to avoid them but if you have, then I think your teacher is following some very bad practices.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-10 20:47:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually did that and it didn't help. I read later that a majority of the original xbox's used a certain type of disc drive (called a Thompson I think) that was prone to failure. The ones that used a Jasper drive never had this problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-13 07:06:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is why I unsubscribed from /r/gaming dammit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-19 01:18:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can someone explain why this is funny?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-24 04:51:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about Curio City?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-25 18:19:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>If they were truly Nokian they wouldn't wear down at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-27 06:08:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friends always called this show "Japanese Zen Ghost Busters". It's very accurate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-28 07:05:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>In soviet Australia...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-28 07:11:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I kinda want them to completely get rid of taxes on the rich, just to see what their next "solution" to the nations financial woes will be. I'm damn curious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-07 21:06:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>At this end of the room, the only thing of any significance was The Throne. Ultimas stood before The Throne and regarded the figure sitting upon it. Anyone else, even an Angel, would have trouble making out exactly who or what sat on the throne. Most saw what they wished to see through no action of their own. A gentle father figure, reassuring and smiling. A stern lecturer, wise yet impatient. A beautiful woman. But Ultimas saw the truth. The being who sat on the throne was old. Older than any being who had existed up until now. Save one. He did not sit up straight in the throne but was leaning back. His breathing was heavy which was odd for someone who did not need to breathe. Perhaps it was an affectation that he had adopted. His face was lined and wrinkled with eons. His eyes were glossy and half closed yet they saw more than any man could ever hope to see. His hair was cloud white and stretched to the floor. We wore nothing at all. Though he would be hard to measure my human standards, he could have easily been 10 feet tall. Of course, that was subject to change. Ultimas spoke.  #8220;You know why I am here #8221;. It was not a question. The being who was God open his eyes a fraction more and replied, simply,  #8220;Yes #8221;.  #8220;Then we should be on our way #8221;. With great effort, God sat up ever so slightly.  #8220;Must we go now? #8221; Ultimas almost smiled. The question that everyone asked,  #8220;Do I have to go? #8221; He always wondered where if it was just human nature. It was. And it seemed that it was inherited.  #8220;I #8217;m afraid so, old friend. #8221;  #8220;Are we truly friends, Ultimas? #8221; God asked.  #8220;But of course we are #8221; Ultimas replied, with no amount of insincerity.  #8220;Who but a friend would give you such a gift? #8221; he continued.  #8220;Who but an enemy would take it away? #8221; God said as he sat up even more. Anger was creeping into his voice. It #8217;s not fair. It #8217;s not right. How dare you? These were things that Ultimas had heard countless times before as well.  #8220;Have I been unfair to you? Have I treated you worse than any other? Have I not kept my promises? Even as you forgot yours? #8221; Ultimas was not angry but these were the facts.  #8220;It #8217;s too soon. There #8217;s still too much work to be done. I still have so much to do. #8221; God said now with Sadness. Ultimas had heard this as well. It #8217;s not my time. I can #8217;t go.  #8220;I #8217;m sorry. #8221; Ultimas said.  #8220;It is your time. Your power has faded. Your subjects are gone. And, what #8217;s more, #8221; and with this Ultimas gestured the clouds on the horizon  #8220;a Storm is coming. #8221;  #8220;I fear no storms #8221; God said Proudly.  #8220;You should fear this one. No wind no rain can compare to what is coming. A darkness of time and space. A shadow which will consume creation and all who remain. This is not something you wish to endure. #8221; Ultimas said these things calmly though the clouds were drawing nearer. Now God looked into Ultimas #8217; eyes and Ultimas saw what he saw countless time before. Fear.  #8220;I am afraid. #8221; God said. Perhaps the most honest thing ever to be uttered by such a being.  #8220;What lies beyond death I confess even I do not know. Human kind comforted itself believing that Heaven was what lay beyond death but this was only half of the truth. If only they had known #8230; #8221;  #8220;It would have changed nothing, sorry to say. These are the rules by which we exist. These are what you were made to understand when your power was given to you. #8221; Ultimas did not fear the coming storm. He would be long gone when it arrived. But he truly did not know if he would leave alone or with the old man in his company. God looked up from his feet.  #8220;Would you tell me what you have never told anyone? What lies beyond life? Where are we going? #8221; Ultimas had never told anyone. In all his time, every single soul he had claimed had asked this question. Peasants, and kings and warlords and other beings more powerful than could be imagined had asked this of him. Some had begged, many had cried. A few faced the uncertainty bravely. These he remembered the best. He was surprised that God would not be one of these. Ultimas looked at the self-titled Lord of All Creation and said,  #8220;It is not my place to say #8221; as he had said countless times before. The Lord of Man and Master of Heaven leaned back in his Throne and closed his eyes. The wind had begun to pick up now, and his long hair began to move in the air. The sun was shining not so brightly and it was getting colder. God reflected on his works. He saw that they had been good for the most part but he still lamented that is was all ending before he could see it finished. It had been ambitious, to be sure. When he had made the deal with Ultimas like others before him, it had been with the knowledge that the arrangement would be temporary. The young God had believed that with enough effort and care, he could avert the coming storm and put an end to this timeless cycle of creation and destruction. This existence that was, ultimately, pointless and doomed to end in nothingness. Ultimas knew all of these plans, of course. He made no effort to interfere in accordance with the arrangement. All power given was done so with no limitations save the inevitable.  #8220;In truth, I had hoped you might succeed. #8221; Ultimas said.  #8220;I have walked this cycle since time was merely an idea. I have seen a thousand empires fall along with their Gods and Deities. You were not the first to try and put a stop to it but, I must admit, you were the most ambitious. It is sad to say that you were too proud. You became too caught up in your lesser works to focus on the bigger idea. If you had #8230; well #8230; who knows? #8221; God was surprised to hear this from Ultimas. He ventured a question but, in truth, he was deeply afraid of the answer.  #8220;Once I am gone and the next arises, will you tell them of what I almost accomplished here? Will you set them on the right path? For all the lives that have yet to arise, will you help put a stop to this? #8221; Ultimas said nothing. The wind was blowing even harder now. A shadow fell across the throne.  #8220;It #8217;s time to go. We have lingered too long. Please my friend, do not let the storm reach you. Take my hand. #8221; Ultimas stood now before the Throne on the top step with his hand outstretched. Gods still yearned to hear the answer that he feared most.  #8220;Please. Ultimas I beg you. Answer me. #8221; The Lord of Man was begging him to violate every rule he was bound by. To cast away eons of adherence to ancient law and contract. Would it even be worth it? Would the wrath incurred to do such a thing even result in any change? Or would the cycle continue as it always had? He would risk his own existence by doing so. Despite the nature of his works, he too, feared the nothingness to which he was the sole gatekeeper and which he did not truly understand. But, in the end, the cycle was everything. It was the nature of creation itself. Everything that begins must end even if it is simply to make way for something new. Ultimas understood this but it had taken the failings of an ambitious God to make him see. One day, he could feel, the end would come for him. Something new would arise. But that day was not today. When that day came, would he face the dark bravely or with foolish questions? Would he take the hand offered or refuse and be doomed to whatever it was The Storm held in store.  #8220;I #8217;m sorry. It is not my place to say. #8221; God took one last look around what he had created. Then, he took the hand that Ultimas offered him. God stood from the throne and a black doorway appeared before them. Together, Ultimas and God stepped through the door. The doorway vanished. The Throne crumbled into dust. And the sun went out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-08 03:10:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can trash on these bootcamps as much as you like but it doesn't change the fact that they really do help students get tech jobs. They're quite clearly growing in popularity and they offer a much more modern curriculum than most universities. A friend of mine completely switched his career from neuroscience to web development after one of these camps. By contrast, I majored and got my degree in CS and I ended up losing my first developer job due to cut-back and downsizing. A few months before I accepted a new job in a different discipline for less pay, he was starting his first developer job. I was severely tempted try and gain entry into one of these camps since they really seem to work and I felt like my education hadn't really prepared me to find solid entry level work in the career I want to pursue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Banana Theocracy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-14 23:50:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-20 00:24:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whenever you are about to purchase something big, ask yourself how many hours of work it took (or will take) to be able to pay that. Then decide if what you gain from buying it is worth that amount of time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-25 18:20:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I cant decide if I should get Reaper of Souls on console or PC. I tried the Xbox demo and thought it was fun with a controller but I understand that only the PC version is getting the latest updates. Anyone tried both can give me a recommendation?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-25 18:35:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's another thing: the console version actually has an offline mode. Does the PC version still require a connection?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-10 18:08:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always thought Attorney General was a rank like Brigadier General.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-20 20:48:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do it even if you don't have a quad core. I don't and the .ini fix helped my game stability immensely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-23 21:07:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course I just bought the Borderlands GOTY during the steam summer sale for $8...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-25 23:18:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Blood is thicker than water, but not as refreshing."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-27 01:31:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>12 - Thats the number of times this has been re-submitted: http://www.reddit.com/r/Bandnames/search?q=Tequila+Mockingbird amp;restrict_sr=on</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-07 19:19:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't play Destiny so I googled "destiny thorn". There's a friggin Forbes article talking about how unbalanced the PvP is with Thorn: http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidthier/2015/06/05/bungie-needs-to-do-something-about-destinys-thorn/ Seems pretty telling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-08 00:17:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh. I didn't know that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-12 04:02:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought it was pretty funny too except for the fact that towards the end it just becomes a book of cocktail recipes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-14 22:38:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Texas Chainsaw Mascara</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-15 23:52:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like the use of negative space. Makes it look like a map of a city.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-16 22:28:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>... in a van</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-17 18:28:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I honestly found it far too cliched to watch. I feel like I've seen 10 other shows about Mecha piloting teens in space. I only watched 2 episodes before I stopped. Does it get more interesting?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-15 18:45:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh man! I had no idea! I'm super stoked now! http://www.starburstmagazine.com/features/interviews/10356-nader-alikhani--pixel-hero-games-xenos</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-16 02:06:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post is 5 months old but I just wanted to say great work and thank you for sharing it with us to use!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>UEModel Viewer no longer works with textures for BlackLight</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-16 03:58:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>For a while now I have been extracting models and textures from BlackLight to try to bring them to other games. I was using EU Model Viewer and TexMod. But, after the parity patch any textures I extract with EU Model Viewer are just black. Models come out okay but without textures its kinda pointless. Also, since you have to login with the launcher which in turn launches the game, I can't extract textures using TexMod anymore. So now I'm stuck and my project is stalled. I know this might not be the best place to ask but I thought I would in case anybody had any helpful hints.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-16 10:30:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry but I didn't get any of the receivers or gun parts. I was focusing primarily on armors. Before the update, I had extracted upper and lower armors for male characters (hadn't gotten around to female) as well as all the helmets. I didn't get any gun parts (didn't know where to start with them) but I did get the tomahawk so you are in luck there along with the Katana as well. I also have the machete, combat knife, sonic knife, ninja starts and throwing knives. I also have all the heroes except for MARS. Right now, the issue is really just with textures. I can extract models just fine but all textures come out as completely black. The issue could be solved through the use of texmod but I have no idea how to get it to work when the game uses a launcher. Typically, you specify the game executable and run from TexMod which is what I did before, but now you need to login through the launcher or you can't get past the opening screen and TexMod can only rip loaded textures that are currently on the screen. If I could get around that somehow, I think everything would be fine. It'll take a while to upload all my extracted stuff since it's over 1.5 gigs total. Let me know if there's something specific you want. Here's the tomahawk and katana to start. https://www.mediafire.com/folder/68vwf9733dm4f/FoxGameContent_DLC4_SF</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-16 17:33:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry about the goof with the files. Here's a zip of them for others: http://www.mediafire.com/download/a1uu6ul29neae4y/FoxGameContent_DLC4_SF.zip I'll make sure I zip any others I upload. That's a great idea about the torrent. I honestly didn't think there would be any for a F2P game but I just found one from February which I am now downloading. Also, this is probably obvious but I saw some blacklight models in the Garrys Mod workshop on steam. Seems like there's a decent variety of characters and even a weapon: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=257932465 amp;searchtext=blacklight Anyway, let me know what you would like me to upload next.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-16 20:36:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I downloaded a russian version of the game from before the patch, but the exact same problem is occurring. No idea why. It seems like the creator of the UE Model viewer is aware of the problem but that doesn't guarantee a fix in the immediate future.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-18 06:53:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just want to take the opportunity to say you suck, Mediafire. You wanna verify my very last upload for an hour for no reason? Get outta here. I'm going back to dropbox. This link will be used for all future Blacklight source files: https://www.dropbox.com/sh/pt5f8modqlbecus/AACRxo3603-uyUL8IdF9a5aAa?dl=0 The knife and machete along with some other odds and ends are in the FoxGameContent_WPNG_SF file Sorry but I can't help you with converting models to Source Film Maker, that's not a file type I have to deal with. I have converted from valve models to .obj if you need help with that though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Multi-ethnic rap group called "Mixed Grillz"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-29 22:25:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-12 03:20:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man, I really aught to finish the first game and the DLC.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Aloha Snackbar</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-16 03:57:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.reddit.com/r/Teleshits/comments/3jabt5/the_fbi_claims_he_was_on_their_radar_for_years/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-19 04:16:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've never played Battlefield but I image if I found myself in a similar situation I'd miss every shot and then get run over. Then I'd probably get spawn killed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-19 22:20:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>May the fleas from your couch enslave your rhubarb!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-18 07:54:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>First heard this track on Siberian Jungle Vol 1. If you like this you may find some of the other tracks enjoyable as well. http://music.tunguskagrooves.com/album/siberian-jungle-vol-1 I'm quite fond of *Surface of Doomed Planet* and *Big Wonderful Thing*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-21 07:51:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Put in 7.25. Found out that "Nipple Shields" are a thing: http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/B000067PQ0/ref=nosim/krisssoccersi-20/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-14 07:08:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, technically it's Mishas voice as well...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-15 05:08:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello. Non-fist-clenching-Liberal here. Just my 2 cents but I think that minimum wage should not keep someone in poverty if you are working 40 hours a week. Even working hard might not always be enough especially given social circumstances that might contribute to poverty such as children or medical costs, the later of which is a huge contributor to poverty. Luck can play a huge part in if you get out of poverty or not. I do not see the minimum wage as any sort of handout. It's supposed to prevent a "race-to-the-bottom" approach where businesses attempt to see how little they can pay someone to do the same work. After all, there will probably always be someone a little more desperate that you willing to take a 25 cent pay cut for the promise of employment. It will have to be raised some day, otherwise there's almost no reason to have it. Minimum wage should be enough to live on. So yeah, that's my American Dream.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-15 22:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>This isn't your dog. http://karmadecay.com/results/u6198365</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-23 04:26:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nobody has made a "call of nature" joke and I am extremely disappointed by that for reasons I cannot understand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-28 07:03:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. Different person: https://www.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/3u5hm5/tried_to_take_a_family_photo/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-28 08:00:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>No worries.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Build Help] GPUs - I really don't know how to tell how much power I need and how much power I will get. Benchmarks are confusing...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-21 08:49:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone got me Fallout 4 as an early gift so now I need a computer that can actually handle it. I'd like to be able to handle any other such games at high quality with decent framerates (gettin' real excited for Just Cause 3). Problem is, when choosing a graphics card I really can't tell how to translate benchmarks to quality of gaming so I get the best value. I looked here: http://www.videocardbenchmark.net/high_end_gpus.html and saw that GeForce GTX 960 had a rating of 5,968 for only around $199. The one in my pcpartpicker build has 4GB with for $214. The same list shows GeForce GTX 950 with a rating of only 5,264. But that one only seems to come in 2GB varieties but are as low as $150. So, I can't really process how this is all supposed to work out. How can I take into account the amount of memory? What's good for good to high quality gaming and what's overkill? Which makes more of a difference: better chipset or more memory? Does having a larger or higher resolution screen require more memory? Any help in clarifying all this technical mystery would be greatly appreciated. Also posting my tentative parts list for the curious. [PCPartPicker part list](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/Xz7QmG) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/Xz7QmG/by_merchant/) Type|Item|Price :----|:----|:---- **CPU** | [Intel Core i5-4460 3.2GHz Quad-Core Processor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/intel-cpu-bx80646i54460) | $174.99 @ SuperBiiz **Motherboard** | [ASRock H97M Anniversary Micro ATX LGA1150 Motherboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/asrock-motherboard-h97manniversary) | $67.99 @ SuperBiiz **Memory** | [Kingston HyperX Fury Blue 8GB (2 x 4GB) DDR3-1600 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/kingston-memory-hx316c10fk28) | $38.99 @ SuperBiiz **Storage** | [Samsung 850 EVO-Series 250GB 2.5" Solid State Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/samsung-internal-hard-drive-mz75e250bam) | $87.99 @ Amazon **Video Card** | [MSI GeForce GTX 960 4GB Video Card](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/msi-video-card-gtx960gaming4g) | $214.99 @ Micro Center **Case** | [Cooler Master HAF 912 ATX Mid Tower Case](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/cooler-master-case-rc912kkn1) | $39.99 @ Newegg **Power Supply** | [EVGA SuperNOVA GS 550W 80+ Gold Certified Fully-Modular ATX Power Supply](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/evga-power-supply-220gs0550v1) | $69.99 @ NCIX US **Wireless Network Adapter** | [TP-Link TL-WN781ND 802.11b/g/n PCI-Express x1 Wi-Fi Adapter](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/tp-link-wireless-network-card-tlwn781nd) | $14.69 @ SuperBiiz | *Prices include shipping, taxes, rebates, and discounts* | | Total (before mail-in rebates) | $769.62 | Mail-in rebates | -$60.00 | **Total** | **$709.62** | Generated by [PCPartPicker](http://pcpartpicker.com) 2015-12-21 02:35 EST-0500 |</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-22 05:32:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>That honestly kinda seems like overkill for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-22 05:54:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just by virtue of me feeling like I won't really need Ultra 1080p. Not that it wouldn't be nice but I don't really see myself as super highbrow when it comes to graphics. Know what I mean?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-22 06:11:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the site recommendation. It's really nice how they talk about GPUs in comparison to others from the same year and in respect to price range. I get the feeling that those benchmark numbers aren't really that useful by themselves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-22 07:05:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely sounds powerful, thanks for the suggestions. My one hesitation with the card is that I see a lot of review complaining about crash problems and driver issues as well as heat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-22 07:16:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe you. Out of curiosity, what other parts are you using it with? And, random question, what operating system?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Build Ready] "Merry X-Mas to me" build. 1st time builder looking for feedback/opinions before I start.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 21:41:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello! I recently got Fallout 4 as an early gift and my macbook pro running Win7 is just not up to the task (no way!). I've been thinking for a long time to build a gaming computer and now I'm actually going to do it! Purpose: Gaming. Budget: 750 - 850. I'm a little over what I was hoping to aim for but I've got lots of cashback I want to use. Plus jet.com has 20% off with "ANDROID20" so I'm gonna get my GPU from there. I've been gaming on laptops for so long I want to see what a nice GPU can do so I don't mind spending more on that. But I still need to buy a monitor and all the little perhipherals. In regards to GPU, /u/raydialseeker suggested the Asus Radeon R9 390 8GB but the MSI version had much better NewEgg reviews so I went with that. The Sapphire also looked good but seems less popular. Any first hand experience would help. They are all available at the same price currently. Thanks in advance for feedback! [PCPartPicker part list](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/zdqqGX) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/zdqqGX/by_merchant/) Type|Item|Price :----|:----|:---- **CPU** | [Intel Core i5-4460 3.2GHz Quad-Core Processor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/intel-cpu-bx80646i54460) | $164.99 @ SuperBiiz **Motherboard** | [ASRock H97M Anniversary Micro ATX LGA1150 Motherboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/asrock-motherboard-h97manniversary) | $66.98 @ Newegg **Memory** | [G.Skill Ares Series 8GB (2 x 4GB) DDR3-1600 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/gskill-memory-f31600c9d8gab) | $34.99 @ Newegg **Storage** | [Samsung 850 EVO-Series 250GB 2.5" Solid State Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/samsung-internal-hard-drive-mz75e250bam) | $81.61 @ Amazon **Storage** | [Seagate Barracuda 1TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/seagate-internal-hard-drive-st1000dm003) | $45.88 @ OutletPC **Video Card** | [MSI Radeon R9 390 8GB Video Card](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/msi-video-card-r9390gaming8g) | $319.98 @ SuperBiiz **Case** | [Corsair 200R ATX Mid Tower Case](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-case-200r) | $47.99 @ Micro Center **Power Supply** | [EVGA SuperNOVA NEX 750W 80+ Gold Certified Fully-Modular ATX Power Supply](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/evga-power-supply-120g10750xr) | $79.99 @ NCIX US **Wireless Network Adapter** | [Asus PCE-N15 802.11b/g/n PCI-Express x1 Wi-Fi Adapter](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/asus-wireless-network-card-pcen15) | $16.89 @ OutletPC | *Prices include shipping, taxes, rebates, and discounts* | | Total (before mail-in rebates) | $919.30 | Mail-in rebates | -$60.00 | **Total** | **$859.30** | Generated by [PCPartPicker](http://pcpartpicker.com) 2015-12-24 15:36 EST-0500 |</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 21:55:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Understood with the wifi. But the PSU is already EVGA 750. I don't really see what the difference is between your suggestion and what I have. Sorry if I am misunderstanding you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-25 03:35:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Got it. Good to know. Updated build: [PCPartPicker part list](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/4hnT23) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/4hnT23/by_merchant/) Type|Item|Price :----|:----|:---- **CPU** | [Intel Core i5-4460 3.2GHz Quad-Core Processor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/intel-cpu-bx80646i54460) | $164.99 @ SuperBiiz **Motherboard** | [ASRock H97M Anniversary Micro ATX LGA1150 Motherboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/asrock-motherboard-h97manniversary) | $66.98 @ Newegg **Memory** | [G.Skill Ares Series 8GB (2 x 4GB) DDR3-1600 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/gskill-memory-f31600c9d8gab) | $34.99 @ Newegg **Storage** | [Samsung 850 EVO-Series 250GB 2.5" Solid State Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/samsung-internal-hard-drive-mz75e250bam) | $81.61 @ Amazon **Storage** | [Seagate Barracuda 1TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/seagate-internal-hard-drive-st1000dm003) | $45.88 @ OutletPC **Video Card** | [MSI Radeon R9 390 8GB Video Card](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/msi-video-card-r9390gaming8g) | $319.98 @ SuperBiiz **Case** | [Corsair 200R ATX Mid Tower Case](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-case-200r) | $47.99 @ Micro Center **Power Supply** | [EVGA 750W 80+ Gold Certified Fully-Modular ATX Power Supply](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/evga-power-supply-220g20750xr) | $89.99 @ Amazon **Wireless Network Adapter** | [Gigabyte GC-WB867D-I 802.11a/b/g/n/ac PCI-Express x1 Wi-Fi Adapter](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/gigabyte-wireless-network-card-gcwb867di) | $29.99 @ SuperBiiz | *Prices include shipping, taxes, rebates, and discounts* | | Total (before mail-in rebates) | $902.40 | Mail-in rebates | -$20.00 | **Total** | **$882.40** | Generated by [PCPartPicker](http://pcpartpicker.com) 2015-12-24 21:35 EST-0500 |</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-26 06:28:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. This is based off a completed build on pcpartpicker. the board as it is seems like a pretty good deal for the money. I think I'll stick with that one. Thanks for mentioning it though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Build Ready] Just want some opinions on my first build. Very nervous but anxious to start putting this thing together.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-26 06:30:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>###Build Help/Ready: **Have you read the sidebar and [rules](http://www.reddit.com/r/buildapc/wiki/rules)? (Please do)** Yes. **What is your intended use for this build? The more details the better.** Gaming. **If gaming, what kind of performance are you looking for? (Screen resolution, FPS, game settings)** High quality or better. Don't know much about resolution. I really want to experience gaming in awesome quality. **What is your budget (ballpark is okay)?** $850. I have a promo code which will get me $50 off the GPU easy to bring me under budget. **In what country are you purchasing your parts?** USA. /u/CamperJeff has already provided some very helpful suggestions on my build but I would very much appreciate a second opinion before I get started. [PCPartPicker part list](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/4hnT23) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/4hnT23/by_merchant/) Type|Item|Price :----|:----|:---- **CPU** | [Intel Core i5-4460 3.2GHz Quad-Core Processor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/intel-cpu-bx80646i54460) | $164.99 @ SuperBiiz **Motherboard** | [ASRock H97M Anniversary Micro ATX LGA1150 Motherboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/asrock-motherboard-h97manniversary) | $67.99 @ SuperBiiz **Memory** | [G.Skill Ares Series 8GB (2 x 4GB) DDR3-1600 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/gskill-memory-f31600c9d8gab) | $34.99 @ Newegg **Storage** | [Samsung 850 EVO-Series 250GB 2.5" Solid State Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/samsung-internal-hard-drive-mz75e250bam) | $81.49 @ OutletPC **Storage** | [Seagate Barracuda 1TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/seagate-internal-hard-drive-st1000dm003) | $45.88 @ OutletPC **Video Card** | [MSI Radeon R9 390 8GB Video Card](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/msi-video-card-r9390gaming8g) | $319.88 @ OutletPC **Case** | [Corsair 200R ATX Mid Tower Case](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-case-200r) | $44.99 @ Newegg **Power Supply** | [EVGA 750W 80+ Gold Certified Fully-Modular ATX Power Supply](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/evga-power-supply-220g20750xr) | $83.99 @ NCIX US **Wireless Network Adapter** | [Gigabyte GC-WB867D-I 802.11a/b/g/n/ac PCI-Express x1 Wi-Fi Adapter](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/gigabyte-wireless-network-card-gcwb867di) | $29.89 @ OutletPC | *Prices include shipping, taxes, rebates, and discounts* | | Total (before mail-in rebates) | $914.09 | Mail-in rebates | -$40.00 | **Total** | **$874.09** | Generated by [PCPartPicker](http://pcpartpicker.com) 2015-12-26 00:22 EST-0500 |</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-26 17:21:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wasn't really planning on overclocking. If I have that option though that would be cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-26 17:28:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know why but this image makes me think of Metal Slug. Now I want a sidescrolling game with orcs as the characters...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-26 21:42:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright, I'm going for it. Thanks for the input!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-01 00:23:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm wondering about the ports that appear on the MoBo. I see an ethernet port. Does that mean I don't need any sort of internet adapter (unless I want wireless)? The graphics card I bought (MSI R9 390) has HDMI as well as DVI but the MoBo has VGA: Will the video ports on the MoBo work as well as the ones on the GPU?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-01 07:58:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wasn't planning on a dual monitor setup but that is good to know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Build Help] Trying to do out-of-the-box build. Won't even turn on. Don't know what to do.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-14 06:14:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Finally assembled all the parts according to this: http://pcpartpicker.com/p/4tzT23 I'm trying to follow along with the video posted on the sidebar: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VIF43-0mDk4 I've put together the mobo, PSU, CPU, GPU and ram. Plugged them in and tried to "short" the mobo but nothing happens. I'm freaking out because the PSU makes no sounds, has no lights and the fan doesn't move. How can I tell if I have a dud somewhere?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-14 07:15:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for telling me about that paperclip test! I have confirmed that the PSU is working. I'm gonna try reconnecting everything using the built in power switch for my case and see what happens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-14 07:23:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup. I experimented with flipping the eco switch on and off and it works as you say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-31 03:22:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, in the book, they sent four to kill Horus so you'd have to be at least half as dangerous as him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-31 03:28:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish I could find this in wallpaper size.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-31 19:24:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Word for word repost from 3 years ago. Didn't even give credit: https://www.reddit.com/r/gaming/comments/pwrwv/found_this_gem_at_my_local_5_guys/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mini-cupcakes should really be called "Shot-cakes".</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-09 06:50:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since they'd be more at home in a shot glass. Then again, people would assume they had booze in them if that's what they were called in bakeries.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-24 04:44:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>A friend blew my mind when he told me "Samurai" is both singular and plural. Makes much more sense than a white guy being the last of a warrior culture and instead simply witnessing the end of an era.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-28 18:24:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Potential hobbies: * Zentangle * Knife making * ~~Astrophotography~~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-29 00:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>The fucks that I give about these camo jokes must also be wearing camo because I cannot find them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-16 02:43:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>The punishment is supposed to be deprivation of liberty. You don't need to add malnourishment/potential sickening through bad food to it. That's just cruel and unusual.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-17 22:01:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Second album: "Labels hate them!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-22 18:07:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome! I was just gonna ask that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-07 06:51:19</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; WARNING: This book contains action. Lots of action. Dinosaur-fighting action. Jurassic Park meets Transformers.  gt; Raptors wage war with their dinosaur foes across the galaxy, and they've set their sights on Earth. If they can't take the planet for themselves, they plan on destroying it like they did 65 million years ago.  gt; Human-friendly dinosaurs team up with the United States military, forming the Dino Squad. Their goal? Repel the raptors, save the planet.  gt; Or die trying... Well, I'm sold.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-13 07:02:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Poor Fischig.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Giraffe Dodgers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-21 22:05:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 07:15:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Iron within!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 06:09:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Superbad. Shit was not funny. In fact, I found the whole thing utterly depressing for some reason.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-04 19:19:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>DuRAMdal?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-19 17:00:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amateur. I once knifed a dude from behind and then survived for 12 whole seconds before being machine gun sniped from across the map. Beat that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-06 03:10:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wondering if you have a source or more info on the economics. Couldn't solar assist considering the price is dropping pretty quickly? Just slap a bunch of solar panels on the roof.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-06 05:41:54</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; you wanna put solar panel on roof to get electricity so you can use the electricity to power the light? Uhh, yeah. That's how solar works.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-06 07:32:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cuz you wont be able to stack those plants vertically. You'd have to lay them out flat and now you've just got a normal farm.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-07 03:23:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you know what an internet troll is?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-07 03:37:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, thanks for actually providing a source. It definitely seems that the cost of electricity really limits the energy efficiency of the vertical farms. However, this could be solved eventually with improvements in solar tech. Also, it seems like the main selling point the video was trying to make was reduced water usage, so that could be seen by some as a reasonable trade-off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-21 03:30:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Utter craziness. From my experience, children are about 80% noise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Due to all the health hazards surrounding the Rio Olympics, I figured they could use a new logo. [OC]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 04:16:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 04:42:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm cool with it. I figure that must mean I'm talented or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 04:44:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 04:46:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meh. I figured a watermark would detract from the image. If people wanna use it I don't care that much. The process of creating it was so simple someone with a few minutes and photoshop could recreate it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 05:19:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go for it. I thought about doing it with zazzle or something but those guys would probably take it down for copyright infringement or something. Then again, I am also lazy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 06:01:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fit right in. Well done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 06:07:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for your support and appropriate pun!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 06:09:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ports get closed?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 07:36:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, here it is if you are interested: http://www.zazzle.com/riohazard_2016_shirt-235391842564096356</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 07:39:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, I made it into a shirt. http://www.zazzle.com/riohazard_2016_shirt-235391842564096356 I dunno. Some comments expressed interest in having it in shirt form. So, why not?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 07:41:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had to google it but that's pretty clever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 07:47:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. http://www.zazzle.com/riohazard_2016_shirt-235391842564096356</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 07:50:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like the gasmask idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 07:53:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 07:53:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mkay: http://www.zazzle.com/riohazard_2016_shirt-235391842564096356</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 07:54:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like it too. A different aspect perhaps but great in its own right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 07:55:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>You image stealing whore!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 07:59:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kay. http://www.zazzle.com/riohazard_2016_shirt-235391842564096356</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 07:59:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://i.imgur.com/mMlHSII.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 08:03:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay. Thanks for informing me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 08:07:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Years long legal battle over 30 minutes of photoshop? They can have it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 08:08:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.zazzle.com/riohazard_2016_shirt-235391842564096356 All proceeds go to feeding my cat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 08:09:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>0 so far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 08:10:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since you asked... http://www.zazzle.com/riohazard_2016_shirt-235391842564096356</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 08:11:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not surprising but I made my own anyway http://www.zazzle.com/riohazard_2016_shirt-235391842564096356</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 08:18:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll go boil some water.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 08:19:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd be honored to have my work used for a subreddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 08:19:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, stop it you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 08:21:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you like. I already did it though but feel free. http://www.zazzle.com/riohazard_2016_shirt-235391842564096356</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 08:22:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you kind stranger.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 08:23:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow. Has it really been that long? Man. It totally has.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 08:24:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>B'okay! http://www.zazzle.com/riohazard_2016_shirt-235391842564096356 http://www.zazzle.com/riohazard_girl_tee_t_shirt-235273241130099798</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 15:56:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>WHAT! That's awesome!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-02 15:58:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wont be quitting my day job anytime soon. That's for sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 03:59:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like it. If you want the full resolution image check here: http://imgur.com/gallery/yp7by</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 04:01:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some reason being IOC threatened them. If you happen to want the full rez image I've got it here: http://imgur.com/gallery/yp7by They can't stop the signal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 04:01:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 04:02:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>A whole village of people far away from home under immense pressure to perform who are at their physical peak? Yeah. I can see that happening.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 04:02:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Zazzle took it down after IOC complaint. If you happen to want the full rez image I've got it here: http://imgur.com/gallery/yp7by They can't stop the signal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 04:03:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey that's really good. The use of the same font was smart.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 04:04:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great choice of photo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 04:04:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell your dad I approve!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 04:05:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just imgur I'm afraid. Share away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 04:05:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>They already forced Zazzle to take down the shirts. If you happen to want the full rez image I've got it here: http://imgur.com/gallery/yp7by They can't stop the signal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 04:15:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's the full resolution: http://imgur.com/gallery/yp7by</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 04:16:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. I'm not a graphic designer at all. Sorry to disappoint.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 04:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Full rez of the image. http://imgur.com/gallery/yp7by Go crazy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 04:17:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shirt is gone now. Full rez of the image is available. http://imgur.com/gallery/yp7by</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 04:18:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Send me a pic of the end result! Here's the full resolution if you want: http://imgur.com/gallery/yp7by</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 04:20:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Full rez if you want: http://imgur.com/gallery/yp7by</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 04:21:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, it's gone now. Full resolution of the image if you want: http://imgur.com/gallery/yp7by</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-03 04:49:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. They claim it infringes their trademark blah blah blah.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-04 03:20:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice to know though I never saw it as I don't make a habit of browsing the MIT website.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-04 03:23:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the record I have not seen that one until just now. Not that I can prove it or anything, but I don't watch football and have had no reason to visit the subreddit where that was posted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-04 03:24:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had the idea about 2 weeks ago and I made the image about half an hour before posting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-04 07:48:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely true. Wouldn't be the first instance of multiple people coming up with the same thing independently. I'm glad you like mine though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-04 07:53:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really, it's more that I don't want to open myself up to legal trouble from the IOC. They are notoriously famous about defending their trademarks. If I were to try and monetize it I could wind up in trouble.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-04 07:53:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow. TIL.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-05 06:23:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>You made this? I made this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-06 08:11:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-06 08:13:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love the Colbert one. Genius.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-06 08:20:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's available here. Not mine but it's only 14 bucks. https://www.teepublic.com/t-shirt/615104-riohazard-2016</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-28 23:22:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>"The following footage is 100% rendering in real time." But it's a movie...? Not a game...? I'm confused. Aside from that, awesome work. I think the design of Terran architecture was really good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-29 03:01:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. Courage is not putting a headphone jack on your new phone. For fucks sake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-30 23:27:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reminds me of Fallout New Vegas. 2 guys try to mug you in an alley when you get to Freeside. They have a tire iron and a switch blade. Usually by that point I have a shotgun. It's quite satisfying if I do say so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-01 18:15:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>"And how long do you plan to be staying on Cadia Mr. Abaddon?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How can I tell if my Power Supply is bad (even if my computer turns on).</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-17 00:41:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>PC that I built about half a year ago stopped working today. I can power it on and see lights on the case as well as fans spinning but no sounds come from the speaker and nothing is being picked up on the monitor. I disconnected the GPU and removed the RAM from the MOBO to test but it didn't change anything. Googling says this might be a bad power supply. There was a power outage this morning so maybe it got fried somehow? However, the monitor and speakers are plugged into the same power strip and both still work. Anyway, I'd like to know if theres a way to test if it's actually delivering enough power but I don't have any electronic testing tools or another machine to test it with. Appreciate any suggestions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-17 05:29:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright. Looks like I'll just have to buy one. Thanks for the diagram though. That looks like it will really help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-18 03:14:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love that show even more now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-29 18:02:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>It seems totally crazy to hire someone just based on a score on what is essentially a site for practicing coding interview questions. At least, that's what I see it as and that's the reason I signed up for it along with leetcode.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-29 21:11:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never went further than the first 2 questions since it seemed to be aimed at people who are much more math inclined that I.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-30 02:37:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The person behind the decision was Ohio Secretary of State Jon Husted who is a republican.  gt; Husted #8217;s separate purge of registered voters due to voting inactivity was deemed an overreach recently by a federal appeals court.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-30 15:41:30</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; "Two out of every three smokers does not die from a smoking related illness and nine out of 10 smokers do not contract lung cancer" I'm assuming this statistic is bullshit but 1 out of 3 is still pretty bad odds if you ask me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-30 16:38:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think there's a pretty huge difference between eating foods which might be safe on their own but in larger quantities would be unhealthy, and "we literally put toxic chemicals into our product which would trigger a recall if it was found in any of the food you see in the grocery store". See https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1989_Chilean_grape_scare Other fun ingredients include: Arsenic, ammonia, formaldehyde and lead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 16:23:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Having done OOP my whole career, I really don't think it has given me any points towards set theory. Databases too. To me, their only parallel is spreadsheets.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-10 03:09:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone put a wall in my way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-15 07:31:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>One thing that's really helping me learn javascript is TamperMonkey. It's a chrome addon which allows you to run little bits of code on certain specified websites. A while ago, I got sick of this one forum I frequented because there were no rules on the size of a users signatures. People were adding huge images and gifs with flashy crap and I hated it. So, I wrote a little scriptlet which automatically hid all user signatures on coming to a page. I even found out how to use local storage so that I could "whitelist" certain users signatures. It's so satisfying to make something where the reward is something you actually want.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 06:05:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>He did. He lost the popular vote. They aren't saying he didn't win the election they are pointing out how the system is broken since Clinton got more votes but still lost.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 16:20:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another aspect of this skit is that the writers are actually trying to make Bill Hader (the guy playing Stephan) crack up on screen. So they make his lines as ridiculous as possible. They actually succeeded really well here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=otT53ANCfR4</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 05:07:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Repeat a lie enough and it becomes the truth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-14 03:09:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was one of the first free books I got from this sub and I really enjoyed it. I ended up buying another book of the authors recently (though I haven't read it yet).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-20 03:04:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Emperors Little Helpers Chapter?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 17:56:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>My understanding was that Mussolini's claim to "making the trains run on time" was actually a myth. Snopes agrees: http://www.snopes.com/history/govern/trains.asp EDIT Missed a letter when copying the link. My bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 07:57:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can get CS2 for free (legally) http://www.techspot.com/downloads/3689-adobe-photoshop-cs2.html It might not be as advanced but it's got all the essential tools if you just want to mess around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-06 07:54:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I often wish for the same thing, brother.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 04:32:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck that noise. I dunno if my $20 will really help but it can't hurt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 06:28:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been needing some new wall art. Now I just need to find a way to print this... What do you think the maximum real-life size would be?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 03:09:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically it means he won't be involved in any legal proceeding due to potential conflict of interest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-09 03:39:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>There doesn't happen to be a subreddit dedicated to polite political discourse between people of differing stances, is there?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 16:42:54</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; The journey was no trip to the beach. Bertish #8217;s $120,000, 20-foot-long paddleboard, dubbed the ImpiFish, was a solar-paneled board that included satellite weather forecasting gear, GPS, an autopilot system, satellite relays to the internet and a tiny cabin where he slept at night. Whoa.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-16 02:21:31</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; At the end of the video, he added:  #8220;I wouldn #8217;t give nearly such good head if it weren #8217;t for my priest. I just don #8217;t see the big deal. #8221; I'm sorry but that is some messed up shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 05:45:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't really know how much this matters but when I started doing some research on VPNs I heard about http://thatoneprivacysite.net and they list PIA as an "Enemy of the Internet". I've heard a lot of people say that PIA is good but this gives me pause. https://thatoneprivacysite.net/vpn-comparison-chart/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 05:47:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>A little while ago, I really dove into http://thatoneprivacysite.net to see which VPN would be best. Long story short they're all flawed in some way but Nord came out in the top 5 so it's the one I'm really considering.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 02:10:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whoops. Good catch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 02:10:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't tried any of them but all the free ones have a lot of red marks on that site.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 16:47:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow! I knew something was up! Everytime I get linked there on reddit, the site refuses to load to the point where I just don't even read their articles anymore. I thought it's just because my browser is super old and not updated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 01:46:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>My 6th sense is telling me this is BS. But hey, it's free so at least you can't feel ripped off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-01 17:42:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like to go on record as saying that "Cyberpunk 2077" is about the least creative title I've ever heard. Honestly, they might be doing other developers a favor by forcing them to actually come up with a creative name for their games which isn't just the genre of the setting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-02 00:44:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah. I was not aware of that. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 21:29:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh man. Any chance there will be plans or kits available for that? I'd buy that so hard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 21:36:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I once saw them described as conservative fanfiction. I think that's the most accurate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-04 04:59:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 17:09:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry you lost your friend but excessive amounts of bullying and discrimination are most likely the biggest cause of high suicide rates. Also, from what I've read, gender identity is likely associated heavily with brain structure. Doubtful that something like that can be helped with therapy. You can argue that it's a "mental illness" but there's a lot of stigma associated with that term and it probably harms more than it helps. On the other hand, if gender reassignment surgery can help someone feel more like they are put together correctly then that's a good thing. It's possible that the trans community sees transitioning as the best solution in all cases which I would disagree with because everyone is unique but, as I'm not part of that community, I don't actually know if that is the case.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-08 01:53:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. Kinda gives it away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-10 18:10:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, if this rule gets killed, does that mean there will no longer be such a thing as a fiduciary?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 00:46:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just read the first one and it came of as very sober and reasonable to me. Not "VPNs are just as bad" but more "They have downsides and not all of them are good so be careful" which is completely true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 06:04:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always eat them over the sink for just that reason.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 22:52:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you mean to post this here?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 16:58:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Karl Pilkington pitched a movie idea similar to this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 17:39:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since at least WWII: https://youtu.be/wfOrez6q7WM?t=25</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 18:48:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a magical place.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 20:06:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Ignorstance** *Noun* An opinion or belief which is held despite lack of knowledge on the subject</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-08 17:12:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then please, link me to a post promoting hillary 2020 on T_D for which the author has not been banned.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 07:35:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just left a comment with the FCC. www.gofccyourself.com Click on link which says "express"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 16:26:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Favorite comment  gt; CERN has not destroyed the universe, or jumped us to a "parallel" one.  gt; The truth is, CERN has been working on time travel by creating wormholes initiated by micro singularities, and while they can not yet send someone back, their experiments cause waves of particles to go back in time which still cause disruptions.  gt; These cause usually subtle alterations to reality (spelling variations etc.) as they attempt to learn how to control it in order to institute a global fascist dictatorship with themselves in control. Yup. All those millions of dollars and super advanced physics and educated scientists gathered in one place for one reason. Advance our understanding of the universe? Nope. Fascist dictatorship. Every time. You can't throw a rock in the conspiracy house without hitting a theory where the end goal is "fascist dictatorship".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-19 01:09:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah yes. The fishy-fishy grind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>/r/jokes has gone private temporarily to show "solidarity" with T_D</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 17:27:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 20:02:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great. I was starting to worry that my main source of jokes on reddit would be gone for good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-22 08:19:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then Mk V is higher tiered armor. You can tell because of the asymmetrical shoulder pads.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 17:35:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too. I always watch this video when that happens. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sBFqzL11QVM</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 05:26:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Poe's law in action.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 17:19:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>See! It does happen! Thats why we need to suppress minority voters just to make sure it doesn't happen again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-26 08:00:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Well, it'll be $500 to fix it" said the mechanic. Annoyed, the penguin mutters a curse under his breath. "Come again?" said the mechanic. "No! I told you it's just ice cream!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 16:33:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, respect people for their choices unless said choices involve murder? Sounds alright.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 17:24:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I though "Political Correctness" was just code for "not being prejudiced". You always hear complaints about PC when some terrorist attack has happened. PC is blamed. Based on context, it means that if we weren't being PC then it wouldn't have happened. Then it starts to make sense. "If we weren't so PC this wouldn't have happened" now translates to "if we could just recognize all muslims as terrorists we would have prevented this somehow"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 17:32:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go easy on the guy. It's hard to keep so many lies and half-truths straight in one head. Who knew lying could be so complicated?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 17:40:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>The folks on /r/cyberpunk would probably love this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 17:50:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. But I've always thought that the oversensitivity which is visible sometimes is a reaction to the push back against racial equality emanating from the new right. I see this as something that will start to fade once we make more progress towards equality.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 03:46:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I missing something? I read the original article and it didn't say anything about the attackers political leanings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-24 07:59:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do people with money and power want more than anything else? More money and power.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-25 21:20:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. Because then it would be *their* money.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-27 07:03:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Proof: It's literally impossible for me to give you proof.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 18:28:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a "weed-whacker" here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 18:29:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>10 minutes of research shows that they didn't use air conditioners but rather cooling suits which work via sublimation. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Apollo/Skylab_A7L#Liquid_Cooling_Garment https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Liquid_Cooling_and_Ventilation_Garment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 03:53:02</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; he said he is not going to repeat this ugly behavior on social media again. In addition, he said his statement could serve as an example to others not to do the same. CNN reserves the right to publish his identity should any of that change.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 06:23:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Subtle! I didn't even notice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 04:40:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's even more people. Check the top left corner. Looks like a mirror.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 17:41:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was under the impression that Kaplan acquired them after they had set up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 17:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those Heretics. #NotMyGodEmperor</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 07:51:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also wondering this. It's probably relatively simple to create a one-to-one copy of the blueprint, but what about the underlying structure?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 05:01:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like the design. Elegant yet simple. How long did it take to build?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-02 07:20:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I vaguely remember a quote about propaganda that goes something like "The enemy must be portrayed as both so powerful as to necessitate action yet so weak that victory is assured."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-08 04:15:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is the skull actually their face or a mask?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-08 06:24:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's basically a religious belief. I took a look at the front page of the subreddit and there's a sticked post about evidence for a flat earth. It includes this gem: http://i.imgur.com/ZyLDSBE.png You also see a lot of references to "the firmament" which is a biblical term when it comes to flat earthers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 17:46:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had to search the whole page to find ONE person who mentions Marathon! Love that whole series. You can still play them on modern macs with Aleph One.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-25 02:33:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Concept of the completed tower](https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2017/02/leeza-soho-architecture-beijing-china-news_dezeen_2364_col_2.jpg) looks even more cyberpunk. Article with more info: https://www.dezeen.com/2017/02/16/leeza-soho-zaha-hadid-architects-beijing-tower-worlds-largest-atrium-architecture-china/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 07:05:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never! It's clearly the Deep State in connection with George Soros and some cabal of (((Satan Worshiping Pedofiles))). /s Maybe someone can explain why George Soros is at the center of every conspiracy ever devised?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 17:22:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you ever wonder why the Szechuan Sauce went away? I won't say it out loud but it rhymes with Meep Spate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 00:26:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like the current administrator is actually qualified for the position given his background: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brock_Long Totally uncharacteristic of this administration but I guess it's a pleasant surprise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 00:29:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. It's part of their long con. Operation Do Good Stuff Whenever There's a Disaster Like Our Original Founding Mission Says So. I mean, they've been around for 40 years or something so I'm sure all the evil concentration camp stuff is just around the corner.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 06:29:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ya know. Places...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 07:22:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe we'll get lucky an they'll both duel for it. And then maybe we'll get really lucky...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 00:15:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>~~I vote satire.~~ ~~ gt; government to keep its greedy paws off our medicare!~~ ~~I think this is the key giveaway: Medicare is a government program.~~ I take it back. People really are that stupid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 00:24:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>PC just means "not being openly racist". White nationalists think that everyone else is just as horrible as they are but don't want to show it. They claim anybody speaking in calm rational tones about racial equality is just faking it and is really as bad as they are on the inside.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 00:38:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>He just grabbed it because it had his name on it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 00:55:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>One issue is built in styling which varies across browsers. This causes a lot of issues but can be solved easily with a good CSS reset file.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 05:13:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>"The good die young but pricks live forever". - Lewis Black</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 19:54:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I vote for Cards Against Humanity. You could spend hours searching for hidden meaning in the cards chosen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 03:04:02</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; "Two out of every three smokers does not die from a smoking related illness and nine out of 10 smokers do not contract lung cancer" I'm assuming this statistic is bullshit but 1 out of 3 is still pretty bad odds if you ask me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 22:41:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow. He was against a needle exchange program too?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-08 12:51:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>So what's this guys deal? He's trying to use solar flares to predict earthquakes? You'd think some real scientists would have caught on to something like that by now if it was actually a reliable indicator of seismic activity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 00:52:41</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I know many very good Jews Oh good. I was starting to worry there that we might be dealing with somebody who has an irrational hatred of a certain group of people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 05:54:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm tempted to have my first tattoo be the final 5 lines of that poem just to piss of white nationalists. Kinda like an anti-swastika.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 07:05:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wasn't aware that he was also behind the most racist law in the US: https://www.dailykos.com/stories/2016/11/10/1595617/-The-architect-of-the-most-racist-law-in-modern-American-history-has-been-named-to-Trump-s-team</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 23:15:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>This should be higher up. It's very well put together and concise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 05:49:33</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; This is not true not one bit, shit like this gives jones a bad name and his followers a tin foil hat Really? It was *this* that made Jones look like a loon? *THIS?*... I mean... I just... *THIS?!*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 05:27:12</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; 33 deaths is a shockingly low number. Not really: http://www.nws.noaa.gov/om/hazstats/resources/weather_fatalities.pdf Katrina was the worst in recent times with over 1000 fatalities. Chronologically, after Katrina the second worst is Harvey (83) and then Irma (33). But after 2005, there are 5 years where casualties from hurricanes only reached single digits and 3 years where there were 0 deaths at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 07:32:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit ya'll. The sub just got banned. Like 30 minutes ago. Was this the cause?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 07:32:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wonder no longer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 08:17:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Herders too. And Nerf.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 08:21:29</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; They say that the only thing holding matter together is our consciousness and between each vibrating sub atomic particle is a void Can confirm. I stopped looking at my car for a second and when I looked back it was just a pile of dust. On a more serious note, who the fuck is "they" in this context? Deepak Chopra?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 08:26:27</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Well, we're all living in a simulation or something so we don't even exist really and therefor can't die. - Somebody on /r/conspiracy probably</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 08:44:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://i.imgur.com/nibk9Pn.gif</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 08:47:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nerf you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 08:53:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>She's also against suffrage for women.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 07:54:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shit man. All this North Korea stuff is really driving up my nuke insurance premiums. At this rate, I'll have to drop my civil war insurance just to break even.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 07:56:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>MOSSAD = Israel = Jews = Soros. Get with the program.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 07:58:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>"All our satellites have been the haxored! What do we do?" "Uh, they have no standing army and we still have guns and radios." "Oh yeah."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 02:39:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basic propaganda. The enemy is everything horrible (including ugly) and our side is everything good (including handsome).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 03:57:04</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; BASED Butterfinger goes for the jugular and the NFL BTFO of the century. RIP NFL. My vote for "Most Overstated Thing Of The Century". Can I also just take the opportunity to say how dumb "based" sounds as a compliment?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 18:26:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>The biggest takeaway is that she's dead and can no longer defend or clarify her own statements or intents. So she's a prime target for being made into some symbol representing whatever it is they want. See: Seth Rich.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 20:07:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>They have neither the depth nor the warmth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 03:33:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>They'll take credit for your icecream falling off the cone if it would further their goals. They aren't picky.  gt; "Americans died? Yup! That was all us!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 04:43:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm pretty sure its "Grandfather say".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-07 08:00:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>The truth is that legit flat earthism is basically religion. There's no point in debating it because they accept it as absolute truth and reject all evidence to the contrary. Hence the insane logical hoops that are needed to jump through in order for any of it to make sense. And all of it is grounded in biblical representations of Earth (see 'Firmament') not actual modern knowledge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-07 08:13:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apparently, some of the cultists killed their own including some of the children. Of course, t_d thinks the FBI just murdered them all for no reason other than 'gun control'.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-07 20:20:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this a shot from the movie?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 06:23:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't follow superhero story lines. Can someone explain why Harley is on the Justice League side?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 06:44:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't forget that light from the sun comes from another dimension.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 19:15:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 17:47:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>This may seem like an obvious question, but when it comes to liquid cooled computers, do you need to use special parts which are built to withstand being immersed in liquid?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 07:51:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I swore at the Blue Shield representative who called and told me that my rates are going up by $200 dollars next year. Not her fault but I was so angry. I mean, I can afford it but why the fuck is it going up so much so soon? I've been enrolled for only 2 months! Once I got off the phone I just kept asking myself, "How the fuck do people making less than I do even afford decent health care?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 19:36:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everytime I run the superhot shortcut it created, it runs the Twitch client. Any way around this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 23:35:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was installed through the twitch client, yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 07:35:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just the icon it made on the desktop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 21:26:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I honestly doubt it. Trump and the Republicans have cultivated an environment of distrust in anything that goes against them. Any news story painting them in a bad light is "fake news". Now the FBI is "corrupt" and "planning a coup". Look at all the "deep state" conspiracy BS spewing from the far right. It doesn't even mater what Mueller uncovers. Trump will deny it, the party will deny it and everyone who voted for them will eat it up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 04:21:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>You put stock into this mystery 4chan poster because of what he said was going to happen. If you just explain it all away when it doesn't pan out it seems more likely that you want it to be true despite all evidence to the contrary.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 04:22:30</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Clowns listening Maybe Q was talking about 4chan users?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 04:25:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like sourcing from Flex's own subreddit is too easy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 04:28:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ironic as I consider referring to Trump as God Emperor is the ultimate heresy. http://warhammer40k.wikia.com/wiki/Emperor_of_Mankind</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 04:42:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>They also reference this random stream of consciousness ramblings: https://i.imgur.com/ugZ08e3.jpg I mean, can't you see how the phrase "Disney is a distraction" totally predicts a power outage at Disneyland?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 18:24:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate your compliment but the fact that you keep saying "do your own research" or "look at the facts yourself" instead of actually presenting them in a convincing fashion makes me very doubtful that any actually exists. I think that you don't want to present whatever it is that supports your claim in your eyes because you are afraid that people will see it as weak evidence. So, you say "do it yourself" and if we do and come back saying "I didn't find anything is support of your claims" you can just say "well, clearly you didn't look in the right places or at the right stuff."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 18:35:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Give it up amigo. He won't present whatever it is that supports his claim in his eyes because he is afraid that people will see it as weak evidence (or BS). So, he says "do it yourself" and if we do and come back saying "I didn't find anything is support of your claims" he can just say "well, clearly you didn't look in the right places or at the right stuff." There must be a term for this... How many excuses has he thrown out to avoid summarizing the evidence?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 05:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Saturday Night Live (Dead) 10/10 humor</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 18:50:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait, what is this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 20:17:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of the developers of Plague Inc contacted me after my flag post and asked if they could include it in the game. I agreed but I don't play the game so I never saw it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 17:43:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's my proof of round earth. In Call of Duty Modern Warfare, Captain MacMillan says that you have to take the Coriolis Effect into account when sniping Zakhaev. And those games are super realistic so there you go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 17:49:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>LMFAO. Government Shutdown != The Purge</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 18:02:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>You inspired me to donate $50. The blatant corruption is just sickening. https://imgur.com/HmVDPrg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 18:30:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this a photo? Those rocks look strange...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 03:09:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>It can be hard to tell but the World Weekly News is actually satirical. The Inquirer is real fake news.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 21:56:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know what's really amazing about Time Cube? If you scroll to a random location on the page and read it is equally crazy as any other location. Time Cube is uniformly crazy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 20:07:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Already done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 05:23:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Batman: You must have been a good man once. Owlman: No. Not good. Never good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 05:39:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck it. Take my money. Nunes is a disgrace. https://i.imgur.com/ccKnV8O.png</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 16:19:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>This reminds me of a story a while back about a fake news creator/writer in Romania (I think). He said that Conservative fake news makes him more money in ad clicks but the same is not true for Liberal fake news because the users tend to question it more quickly and catch on when it's exaggerated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 17:40:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that like Johnny Bravo's less handsome conspiracy theorist younger brother?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Help] First time printer. Prints are coming out slightly thicker than designed.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 18:21:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I recently acquired my first printer. A Monoprice Maker Select Plus (Rebranded Wanhao Duplicator i3 I think). Heated bed. 1.75mm PLA filament from Monoprice too: https://www.monoprice.com/product?p_id=10552. But the first problem I've encountered is that prints are slightly thicker than how they are designed. This is causing problems because the first thing I wanted to print was a replacement part for something which requires millimeter accuracy. For testing purposes, I created a 10mm cube with a 3mm hole in the center in Blender and printed it. The result being a cube with length and width being closer to 10.25mm and the height being 10.5mm. The hole in the cube was 2.75mm across. I used 50% infil with 0.2mm resolution. I've included the Cura project file below for all the details as well as the original STL file. Other small prints I've done have had similar issues. In the end, I can always just compensate for the extra thickness by sizing down but this will make it hard to get pieces to fit together perfectly. I know this is a lower end printer so maybe accuracy offsets like this are just going to be a fact of life but it's still frustrating. Any help would be appreciated. Cura Project file: https://www.dropbox.com/s/rfnxlu213203nio/Test%20Cube%2001.3mf?dl=0 Test cube STL: https://www.dropbox.com/s/ba9edwmg4dz4fb5/Test%20Cube.stl?dl=0</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 21:36:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I follow. But what determines line width? Is that the same as the extruder nozzle size? Mine is also 0.4mm if that's the case.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 04:09:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey this worked great. I was able to get the width and length to 9.91 and 9.92 respectively. Height was 10.4 and inner circle diameter was 2.75 so that's still an issue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 02:44:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Too be fair, I feel that the world would be a much better place if people weren't so uptight about sex.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 18:38:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think we need to be very careful about who and what we refer to as Terrorist Organizations. It devalues the word. People call Antifa a terrorist organization despite having killed 0 people. The NRA isn't a terrorist organization. The NRA is a gun industry mouthpiece. They don't care about anything so long as people buy guns. Mass shootings are great for business because it scares people and makes them buy guns. They are 100% profit seeking. Greedy motherfuckers sure but not terrorists.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 07:38:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bigger issue is gerrymandering. I've never hear it suggested that voting machines were rigged.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 07:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>The budget slashing this program came out *before* the shooting. Totally not their fault. /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 18:08:01</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; dropping atomic bombs was the greatest crime against humanity in all of history Even if you don't count the 6+ million dead from the holocaust it's hardly the worse. We got loads more genocides to choose from.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 03:39:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bombing_of_Tokyo ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Bug] Random textures look messed up when far away, fine up close. Happens after playing for a little while.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 20:10:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've had this bug since I first got the game over a year ago. Now it's like it's getting worse. It used to be that after a few hours playing it would begin to happen. A restart would fix it. Now it happens after only minutes. [Here's a screenshot.](https://i.imgur.com/7BcxX37.jpg) Running Windows 7 (yeah, I know it's super old) with AMD Radion R9 390. Plenty of installed mods for the game. Has anyone else experienced something similar?  #160;  #160;  #160; Modlist below: Fallout4.esm=1 DLCworkshop01.esm=1 DLCworkshop02.esm=1 DLCworkshop03.esm=1 SettlementKeywords.esm=1 Homemaker.esm=1 ArmorKeywords.esm=1 DD_Columnsandstuff_1_0.esp=1 DD_Floor_brace.esp=1 Workshop_Planters.esp=1 AlternateSettlements.esp=1 More armor slots.esp=1 Move that Workbench!.esp=1 BetterSettlers.esp=1 BetterSettlersNoLollygagging.esp=1 DD_TRUMP_2016_MAKE_MODDING_GREAT_AGAIN.esp=1 Movable Power Armor.esp=1 SkjAlert_RS+.esp=1 Better Vendor Stalls.esp=1 Northland Diggers.esp=1 This is MY Bed (Extended).esp=1 WindowBoards.esp=1 AnS Wearable Backpacks and Pouches.esp=1 AnS Wearable Backpacks and Pouches - Ballistic Weave.esp=1 Crossbow.esp=1 StartMeUp.esp=1 SanctuaryParts.esp=1 Repaired Roofs.esp=1 Scrap Everything - Core.esp=1 Scrap Everything - Far Harbor.esp=1 Scrap Everything - Nuka World.esp=1 AnS Wearable Backpacks and Pouches - AWKCR.esp=1 Homemaker - Streetlights Use Passive Power.esp=1 Homemaker - Settlement Keywords Compatibility Patch.esp=0 EvilViking13_WastelandWalls.esp=1 SurvivalOptions.esp=1 DD_All_the_COncrete.esp=1 More Smarter Companions Mod.esp=1 DOOMMerged.esp=1 P220.esp=1 P90.esp=1 P90NPC.esp=1 SCAR-L.esp=1 M2216.esp=1 R91M.esp=1 FO4Hotkeys.esp=1 My_Minutemen.esp=1 EndorsCustomCombatArmor.esp=1 EndorsCustomCombatArmor_WATM.esp=1 EndorsCustomCombatArmor_BoSKit.esp=1 SlowTime.esp=1 BlackLight.esp=1 K9TacticalHarness.esp=1 PipeShotgun.esp=1 PipeShotgun-AWKCR.esp=1 dinoshelf.esp=1 dinoshelf_extra_ammo.esp=1 dinoshelf_retex.esp=1 OCDecorator.esp=1 OCDispenser.esp=1 tenpinesshruberycleanup.esp=1 TimerPowerSwitch.esp=1 Power Conduits and Pylons Overhaul - SKE.esp=1 IMP.esp=1 mso_sms.esp=1 PWR.esp=1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 00:44:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, that's gotta be a pretty old version since this issue has been occurring for more than 1 year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 07:43:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Country #110: Jews weren't kicked out of 109 countries for no reason. Country #109: Jews weren't kicked out of 108 countries for no reason. . . . Country #2: Jews weren't kicked out of that country for no reason. Country #1: I don't like Jews. Lets kick them out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 17:50:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you have any more information on this myth? It seems like I keep hearing it. If there was a Snopes article on it or something that would be nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 01:47:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your skill in Numerology has increased by 1 point. Your skill in rational arguments has decreased by 5 points.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 01:48:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like to see him apply his awesome code breaking skills to the Voynich Manuscript.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 16:57:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of their top mods *is* named after an amphibian, the axolotl. That can't be a coincidence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 05:24:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Orange isn't a race.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 04:12:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>You make a good point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 20:16:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't wait for the next one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 01:16:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't forget the path itself. Asphalt is black but in the photo it's tinted pink.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 01:11:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 01:47:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>First job out of college had a coworker who as super smart (previous experience at NASA according to my boss at the time) and I looked up to him. He had a copy of The Secret book on his desk. When I brought it up he was all like "Yeah man. Quantum entanglement" or some such nonsense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 16:03:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anymore?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 19:17:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>When we first adopted our greyhound you could count all her ribs. Now she's been fattened up on cheese and tuna fish and you can't anymore. Still has the saddest face though and a thousand yard stare like she was in Nam. Not much we can do about that. Also, this is our new favorite comic. Please keep making them!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 19:39:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>But what about that time Jesus fucked a porn star after his kid was born? Or when Jesus bragged about groping women? Or when Jesus lied about literally everything?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 22:19:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I lost it when he brought up how Alex had not yet tried to sell him supplements.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 07:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't forget his use of chili as a legal defense. That's gonna be what law students study pretty soon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 07:54:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>What if it affects you whether you "tune it out" or not? Like if you get death threats after losing a child to a school shooter because some whackjob with a web show calls you a fake?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 06:56:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very good article. The best words.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 03:30:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>What'd he get banned for?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 05:44:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Question] Contemplating a bed upgrade. Glass, PEI sheet or both?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 00:37:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a Monoprice Maker Select. The print quality is decent but the biggest problem is with adhesion and bottom quality. I often get warping on some prints always in the same quadrant of the bed. Additionally, it often takes a few strokes for the filament to catch on the bed and I have to babysit all my prints through the first layer to make sure nothing goes wrong. Heard that a glass bed is better than a metal one. Not sure if I should print directly on the glass bed as opposed to whatever plastic sheet came with the Maker Select. Also heard that PEI sheets are great but should I just use PEI with the basic metal plate or do I need a glass bed too? What does the glass bed do that the metal one doesn't? Thanks for any advice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 17:53:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for your answer!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 20:29:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Source missing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 20:31:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen that episode of Kitchen Nightmares. I don't think it was ever even mentioned that they are a Jewish family? Where did that even come from, anyway?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 06:26:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought the same. "No wonder it's so long. The man doesn't seem to understand editing." All the same, I would like to watch it. Preferably in small chunks over a week maybe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 23:23:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have no idea why but the addition of "ORANGES" has made me start laughing like an idiot. I literally had to scroll down the page so that I couldn't see it in order to write this comment without laughing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 18:06:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bone spurs, remember?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 03:27:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>There were 9 departments that had to signoff on the deal. Fox News (of all places) actually had a segment with ~~Matt Sheppard~~ Sheppard Smith debunking the whole thing: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uAWtb7McNvQ</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 03:29:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like that a report on Fox News of all places debunked the whole thing in 6 minutes: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uAWtb7McNvQ</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 08:33:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you get to make up secret meanings derived from tweets, everything can be related to the deep state.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 21:56:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good catch. I dunno why I was thinking Matt Sheppard. That does explain why it was so hard to google the clip I was looking for.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 17:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I call BS. Those IG lasrifles are waaaaay too effective against those Orks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anyone remember or have their Swedish Flag shirt?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 18:42:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw once, long ago, that they had a merch shirt which was done to look like the Swedish flag made up of their catch phrases ("Pre diner mayo", "good for you"). I was never able to find it after that and not I'd like to remake it for myself. Was hoping maybe someone owned the shirt and could take a picture of it for me. Thanks ya'll. Stay Swedish.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cura is creating a dent in my model where there should not be one.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 04:22:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 04:22:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>[The model as it is in Blender.](https://i.imgur.com/6RmmhJO.png) There are no interior faces or duplicate vertices as far as I can tell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 05:45:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think so. It prints the other edges just fine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 05:46:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Doesn't seem to have any effect, sadly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 06:44:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since I got the printer, all the prints turned out too be slightly wider than they should be. It was suggested by someone on this sub to set the horizontal expansion to be slightly negative. I played with the setting until I was able to print a 20mm cube with only a little margin of error on the size. [I set it back to zero out of curiosity and the problem still exists, though it looks like the print would fill the outline a bit more than before.](https://i.imgur.com/uVuQbFT.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Has anyone tried chemical welding PLA with acetone?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 18:31:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw the video that Tom did here https://www.reddit.com/r/3Dprinting/comments/5hfuof/does_acetone_also_work_for_welding_and_smoothing/ but when I tried it for myself it didn't seem to work. I'm skeptical but there are 2 things that I think I might have done wrong. 1. I didn't use pure acetone but rather a nail polish remover which had some other stuff mixed in. 2. The two pieces I tried to weld were different brands of PLA. One was Hatchbox and the other SoluTech. If anyone else can confirm that chemical welding of PLA is possible that would be very helpful. Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 20:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Dogenald. Much collude. Such Russia.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 03:34:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>OMG. Are you the genius behind these? [https://imgur.com/gallery/9yGzq](https://imgur.com/gallery/9yGzq) If yes, please do more of them. If not, please do more of this. Also, was the monkey wearing the aardvark suit or the kid?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 06:18:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for a straight answer. That is strange because the Tom video seemed to show that it creates a very strong bond \(he couldn't break it by prying it apart.\)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 06:20:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 21:05:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>The most lawsuits. The best lawsuits. Believe me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 07:11:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>When the government admits that something bad is happening there's no conspiracy because everything the government does is bad/evil/lies/coverup by default. See: Flint MI water quality. They admit that the water quality is bad. It doesn't mater that nothing is being done. The conspiracy crowd has no interest in that. When the government says that something is fine and okay \(or just not as bad as people think\) it's a conspiracy because same reason. So, why are they lying and what is the actual truth? See: fluoride, moon landing, homeless encampments.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 06:02:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm more impressed with the fact that the whole thing printed perfectly without supports.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 05:24:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trump loves dictators: Putin. Kim. Jinping, Duterte. Trudeau? Merkel? May? Leaders of modern stable democratic nations? Nope. Not a fan. This is scary shit. It almost feels like the runup to some major event where we abandon all the progress we've made and just go full dictatorship. I know that sounds crazy, but cozying up to dictators while distancing ourselves from our oldest allies? Where else does that lead?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 16:01:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>For flat earth to work you basically have to abandon all of physics. I think I recall reading someone argue that the speed of light is actually really slow. Also, that gravity doesn't exist and the only reason we don't fly off the Earth is because we're accelerating upward at a constant rate. Nevermind the hundreds of insane things *that* implies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 16:15:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nicely done! btw, I think I see something fly off the front when you pull the large mag out in the gif. Dunno what that is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:24:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Must be for handicapped mermaids or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 00:41:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're not making the Marker. It is making us make it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 15:45:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>How does one learn how to do this? Are you self taught? Are there classes you can take?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 18:31:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't forget setting the stage for our eventual annexation of Canada.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 18:31:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Garbage person; garbage president.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 16:24:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking "Jurassic Bawk"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 03:30:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a shitty God you must have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 17:34:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only insomuch as their stock is traded publicly but that has no bearing on their policies or what they owe to the user base.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 02:05:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're doing stair sliding now? I guess Warframe is next up...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 16:38:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Similar vibe to the "I watched Muslims celebrate 9/11" lie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 16:39:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty sure he means it as a compliment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 15:58:15</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;r/TopMindsOfReddit Why did you ban them? They didn't break any rules.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Trump says he predicted the results of the Brexit vote... they day after it happened.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 07:16:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 09:29:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>4 lies in 140 characters. A new record!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Display Purposes Only</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 17:30:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 20:56:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Random memory: Cartoon called Cow and Chicken. Chicken at one point plays a game called Immortal Wombat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 04:28:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>More like Derp State</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 17:42:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, the bar has been lowered. What's next? "Some of the letter magnets on my fridge fell off and I rearranged them to spell out a secret message which reveals the deep state."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 19:40:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Almost. Qulists be taking randomly capitalized letters from tweets and rearranging them to form "secret messages".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 06:34:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least nobody is bashing him for using Atom. I was legit expecting that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 07:01:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Read my mind... like 12 hours before I even saw this post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Volunteer SWAT Team</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 17:33:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 19:32:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have the same issue. The only thing that helps is using a support interface in Cura with a gap between the support and the piece. Sadly, I've only improved the bottoms from 'terrible' to 'not as terrible as before'. If I print without a gap at all then I have a hell of a time removing the supports and it looks even worse. I've researched this problem a lot and I fear the best solution is probably multimaterial printing where the supports are a different material which would prevent bonding thus allowing supports with no gaps and better quality. Sadly my printer doesn't support multimaterial printing. What I can do is cut the models into parts so that the bottoms will not be seen or get glued to other pieces. It's not much of a "solution" but it is a work around for most of the things I print.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 17:56:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're listening to 98.6 FM! Bringing you the same songs you've heard a million times before!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 17:35:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>What benefit does the glass bed give and also can you link to the hotend and bed if you can?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 18:11:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the tagline for the Flat Earth movement should be "Do your own damn research."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 01:34:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>My brain autocompletes the phrase "When I die" to the template version of this joke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 17:44:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great idea. I will also do this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:05:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a good point. Don't you have to signup for the SAT like months in advance? Not 100% sure since it's been forever since highschool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 17:43:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Jesus may rise, but Lucifer lifts"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 17:51:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have to wonder, have any Qultists decided to never eat pizza again out of fear of being seen as a pedophile?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:22:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what she sang.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 17:49:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>[https://politics.theonion.com/giuliani-insists-breaking-the-law-not-a-crime-1827979622](https://politics.theonion.com/giuliani-insists-breaking-the-law-not-a-crime-1827979622)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Whywolf</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 18:04:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 19:07:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personal favorite is **Hasidic Gridlock**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 19:09:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I dunno. While some are good I found myself mostly saying "meh" while reading the whole list. It's clear these are all the ones he's thought of rather than just the good ones.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 21:11:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't realize Adventure Time had beaten me to it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 17:56:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you tell me more about the Ska and Punk Rock thing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 18:29:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jones is human garbage and Cruz is a spineless coward. They make a great couple.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 08:50:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can someone explain to me why everyone on reddit is obsessed with this childrens television show?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Psychopomp Circumstance</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 17:07:56</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8203;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 18:02:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can save yourself a lot of headache in the long run in regards to adhesion problems by installing one of these: [https://www.amazon.com/Gizmo-Dorks-Printer-Surface-Adhesive/dp/B074XF3NGP/](https://www.amazon.com/Gizmo-Dorks-Printer-Surface-Adhesive/dp/B074XF3NGP/)  #8203; Trust me. The basic build surface of the monoprice printer is awful. I had no end of problems getting things to stick and I tried most of the suggestions you are getting in the comments: slowing down the first layer, increasing heat, leveling, leveling and more leveling. Even with all that it can there's an upper limit to how good the adhesion can get. I know it seems ridiculous that you should have to spend more money after you just bought an expensive piece of hardware but it's totally worth it in the long run. I've wish I'd bought one of these first thing after I got my printer.  #8203; Also, based on the picture so seem to have discovered that the thing used to hold the filament spool is much too short to hold a 1kg spool. Thingiverse has a number of extenders that you can print to fix this problem. I have this one: [https://www.thingiverse.com/thing:1805457](https://www.thingiverse.com/thing:1805457)  #8203; PS: You seem to be replying to the whole comment thread instead of the individual comments that people are leaving FYI.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Mock Giraffes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 01:24:26</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8203;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Advice for waisting some IRS scammers time?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 18:16:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Got a call this morning from unrecognized number. Voicemail said that the IRS was pursuing legal action against me and to call them at specific number. Not thinking it would work, I actually just dialed the number that I got the call from instead and got an Indian guy calling himself "Sam" thanking me for calling the IRS and how can I help you? I've since called them back twice giving myself a fake Indian name each time (I sound like a generic white dude and I find this funny, especially since one guy who answered has a thick accent and called himself John Williams). They seem to catch on pretty quick and also have reverse call lookup so they actually have my real name. None of the calls have lasted more than 90 seconds. I think I'll feel satisfied if I can waste 15 minutes of their time but I've never done this before. Advice? \-- EDIT -- Or maybe there's some service I can sign their number up for that will get them to be called a lot?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 05:45:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had better luck after leveling but there were certain things which would always fail to stick. One thing I printed had the print head take a very sharp and rapid turn on the first layer and the filament would curl upwards from the plate each time, even when leveled and with the speed slowed down. That print failed on me 4 times and it's what made be buy the PEI sheet. I just got fed up with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Salami Bandits</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 15:09:31</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8203;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 16:08:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>He never "pivoted". At best, he had a handful of moments where he wasn't a horrible person. That's not pivoting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>