<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject4505</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>first time poster</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 21:12:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm planning to start keto on Saturday. I did it a bit last year and did pretty well till I fell off after about 3-4 months. My doctor recommended me going back on it since it works well with PCOS and seems to be the only thing that's worked well for me in the past. I kicked and screamed against it at first, mostly because I binge on carbs when my depression hits. But I know I need to make a change and I want to commit myself to it this time. My question is about sustainability. For those of you who've been on this awhile, how do you stick with it? How do you keep doing meat, cheese, and eggs after three months when you feel like if you see another piece of meat, you'll throw it? lol Also for those of you who deal with binging and/or depression, what are some keto foods you go to on order to quench the urge? Do you have easy stuff to prep for days when you feel like you don't have the mental energy to do anything at all? Thank you guys. I look forward to working more with you starting now!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Day 5 check in</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 20:15:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I'm finely past the headaches of sugar withdraws, thank God. lol I don't seem to be losing as much as I was last time I started keto, which is a bit discouraging. But it's only day 5 and maybe my body's just reacting different this time (being on my period probably doesn't help). Last time, I lost about 10 lbs in the first week. This week, I seem to be stuck at 2 lbs, so maybe I'm doing something wrong? Did anyone else have the same issue when they started? ~ #9734;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I messed up...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 09:18:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been going strong on keto for about a week and a half. But today when I got home, I felt my old urge to binge come up again coupled with this feeling of anxiety that I couldn't shake but didn't know why. I tried to fight it off as much as I could but I ended up eating more than I should have. And even though they were keto sweets, I still went over my carbs. I know I'll pay for it in the morning. I know I'll look down at the scale and have regained some of the progress I made. Though hopefully not all of it. I guess that's part of what makes me scared, though. I don't want to go back to old habits. I want to fight this. I want to keep going. But I'm scared that if I see the scale close to where it was, I'll want to give up. Especially after failing to stop myself from binging after only a week and a few days. Did anyone else struggle like this? Could you maybe offer some strategies to deal with binging urges? Or maybe just words of encouragement? I'd really appreciate it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 09:42:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you - I really appreciate this! When you say real food, do you have a no/low carb food that you can reach for? Especially if it's towards the end of the day and your carb limit is pretty much reached?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 09:47:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much! I do like eggs so I'll try to keep that handy!  #128512;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 20:58:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! Yea, pretty sure I'm gonna need to just bail on sweets. They're too big of a temptation right now for me to keep around. Better safe than sorry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Help, please?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 05:52:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I started keto about three weeks ago and...I think I must be doing something wrong. From when I started, I lost about 7 pounds in the first week and then just screeched to a halt. And now, even though I'm sticking to 25 carbs or less, I'm starting to gain weight. I've been using keto recipes that I've found online, drinking plenty of water as well. I will say that I do indulge in that zero Green Tea that Arizona makes as well as zero sugar/carb vanilla syrup for my coffee. And I occasionally use slim fast shakes (the ones with 1 carb) in the morning. I will admit that I'm doing lazy keto right now and not counting calories, though I keep my portions pretty in line. My job has me on a 12-9 shift so I generally eat dinner really late. Maybe I shouldn't be having dinner and should just stop after lunch? I don't know. I feel like I'm missing something. I've compared notes with other people and yet I still either stay right at the same weight, barely having lost anything after three weeks, or I gain weight. It makes it hard to deny all these other things because I'm not seeing results like I did the first time I did keto. In fact, it's going the totally opposite way. Could someone tell me if I'm doing something wrong? Please? :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 00:29:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>OMG the salt and vinegar almonds are TO DIE FOR. they're SO great whenever I want chips and need a substitute!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 00:40:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look at you go!! Well done!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 01:00:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>First of all - CONGRATULATIONS!!! That's so fantastic!! Also totally agree - why no grilled nuggets??? Rude much?? haha Second of all - holy crap, thank you so much for posting this. I was having a really weak moment after a doctor's visit and was feeling down on myself. It felt like all of my struggles to do this were amounting to nothing. I was literally in the Burger King line with a "f*ck it" mentality when your post came up on my phone. I opened it while I waited and when I read what yo said about saying "yes" to who you were becoming, it really made me sit back and think about what I was doing. So I got out of line and went to Food Lion instead and got some burgers to make keto style for tonight. So thank you for posting this. And thank you for saying yes to yourself. And thank you for being an example for those of us who are trying to do likewise.  lt;3 I appreciate it more than I can say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 01:13:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>My lunch break is generally at 5pm, yep. Do you just do coffee with no heavy cream in the morning or would it be ok to incorporate that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 01:16:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! Yea, I think I was looking for the same ~whoosh~ that I had when I started last year - the 10 lb gone thing. But this time, it's like... hit and miss or a gain and it doesn't seem to go as naturally as it did the first time. I didn't do as many artificial sweeteners last time so that might be a thing.  gt;_ gt; I'll have to check into that. But thank you.  lt;3 I appreciate the encouragement!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Coke Zero</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 19:54:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, so I have a question. I was looking at the label for this soda the other day and happened to notice that there were no carbs and no sugar but there was aspartame. Does anyone know if that kicks you out of ketosis? Not that I want to make a habit of drinking it. But I was wondering if it would be something that would be okay to drink maybe when you're out with friends or as a very sporadic "treat."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 16:44:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd be up for this for sure! :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>IF and Keto question</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 17:41:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been looking more into IF lately, and I think the 16:8 schedule would work really well with my work schedule if I moved the hours from 10am to 7pm and fasted around that. The problem is, the articles I've read haven't really talked about doing keto in conjunction with this, so I'm a bit confused. I know that IF aims to improve your body and mind as well as create a deficit. That being said, I'm confused about how I'd meet my macros with IF. Am I supposed to try to cram that much fat and protein into two meals?? Or is it acceptable to have deficits in my macros as well? I've seen people mention that meeting your calorie, fat, and carb macros are really important (and not to go over your protein). I can do the carb macros on IF, no problem. But the fat and protein I'm not so sure about. I'm already having issues meeting my calorie macro each day because I just don't wanna eat anymore and my macro has me at like... 1900 calories. Which may be why I'm stalled? Idk. Sorry, I'm rambling. Anyhow, any help you ladies could give me would be GREATLY appreciated!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 17:48:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some people said going over protein meant it would convert to sugar and kick you out of keto. Is that not true?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 18:40:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 19:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I put my deficit at 20 but it still had me at like 1900 cals, I think. I need to check mfp. Stats are 31, 5'11, 303.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 19:31:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, sorry shoulda mentioned I'm F not M (technically nonbinary but I figure it counts in the calculator). Ah, okay, considering fat as a limit makes much more sense. I kept thinking each macro was a goal, not a mix of limits and goals. Thank you so much!! I've currently got my MFP set to 1770 for calories. Do you think that would be too much of a deficit with IF?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 19:41:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just started keto about 3 weeks ago. And you're absolutely right - most of the time when it was "meal time", I still felt full from my last meal but would eat something because I felt I had to meet those goals. Seeing them as limits really helps my understanding now - thank you. :) Yea, I looked into IF this morning on the advice of another ketoer and the 16:8 seemed like it woukd fit my schedule and how I feel most of the time. Usually I wanna skip dinner anyway, lol. Thank you so much for the example! That helps a lot! Do you find that works well for losing as well as maintenance?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 19:50:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah okay, that makes sense. Would going that low on calories trigger the starvation mode I've heard about where the body just holds onto everything? Or is that more of a play by ear thing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 19:54:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>honestly, that's a big part of why I want to do it - not just for physical health, but for mental space too. I have an eating disorder I'm trying to conquer (binging) and I want to train my brain not to go to food for everything, especially when I'm not hungry. So that's excellent news!! And CONGRATULATIONS!!! look at you, kickin ass!!! :D Thank you so much!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 20:47:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Got it! Thank you so, so much. I can't tell you how helpful you've been!! TT_TT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Small victories!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 23:20:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Three weeks on keto and I finally hit the 10 lbs lost mark! It's not as fast as I'd like, but I keep having to remind myself... It's a marathon, not a sprint.  #128522; Thank you to everyone who's guided and encouraged me so far! I hope one day I can return the favor to you! KCKO!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 23:26:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's great!! Keep strong!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 23:28:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>My clothes are beginning to fit a little better! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 00:18:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>that's a good mindset to have - I'll have to remember that! 9 pounds lighter is fantastic! And it's better than where you were! Don't give up! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 06:55:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're doing so great!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 18:42:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! That's super encouraging - I appreciate it. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Whoosh!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 15:57:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had my first whoosh and I'm finally back into the 200s!! 299.8, so just barely but it still counts! LOL I am never, EVER going back into the 300s again. Just need to keep strong and KCKO!! YOU GUYS ARE THE BEST. Thank you so much for everything so far! I can't wait to keep going with you guys!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 17:07:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!!  #128537;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 01:07:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Way to go!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 05:27:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 09:46:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats to you, too!! :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 16:41:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the encouragement!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 20:38:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL exactly!! Hahaha THANK YOUUU!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 23:30:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea... friend of mine had an account and asked a simple question about sushi once. Someone told her she was "making excuses for her weakness" and was weak-minded because she wanted to have sushi with a friend from out of state. Literally one meal does not make you weak minded or weak willed. She broke into tears and ended up leaving reddit. People who do this shit know the only person they're helping is themselves and their own ego. They don't care about who they mow down as long as they feel superior. And it's bullshit. If you're concerned, *be concerned.* Don't be an asshole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Protein help?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 21:17:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>My legs started getting a bit wobbly lately so I started tracking my protein. It seems I'm usually hitting about 20g under my macro when I eat. :-/ I'm trying to find more ways to work it into my meals - I eat meat in each meal. I'm on 16:8 intermittent fasting though and I don't find myself hungry between meals, so I'm not sure what to do. Should I eat anyway to meet the macro? If so, does anyone have any low carb/high protein snacks they could suggest? Thanks! :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 01:40:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess wobbly is wrong - more like really easily tired, then wobbly. IE - Im not getting winded going up the stairs, but I get halfway up and my legs feel like I just ran a lap or something. Really weird. I have not been supplementing; maybe that's the problem? I wasn't aware we needed to. Would taking a multivitamin help that? I usually drink quite a bit. I have a glass or two with breakfast and take a jug to work that I fill up twice. I've been trying to get better with my water. Current stats are - F/5'11/292.6/mostly sedentary (office job. Need to start working out.  gt;_ lt;). The macros i have are 1917 cal goal (with IF, I'm usually under that), 126g protein and 146g fat. I try to keep my fat lower than that, though. Protein goal on MFP is 111 but today I'm 34 under so far. I'm at 77g.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 01:41:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll look for that! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 01:42:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah okay, that sounds like a plan. A friend told me about Isopure. Maybe I'll try them. :) Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 01:44:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm usually under in my calories, but not so much that it would be detrimental. I usually do 16.8 OF because I'm not hungry in the evening. I can't say I've been doing supplements. Didn't know that was something we should be doing. Oops... I'll look into that now, thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Finally, a better checkup!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 18:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Went back to the doctor yesterday and she was really proud of what I've achieved so far (about 20 lbs lost and my blood pressure is down but not perfect - but 144 is better than 164!). She encouraged me to keep on with keto and to stay on my antidepressants. I'm down from 314 to 289 overall so far. She's been very supportive and even suggested keto to me. Though she did warn me that it's "difficult to sustain long term" which made me a bit scared. I have done keto before for about three months and fell off and I don't wanna make the same mistake again. :-/ Has anyone here been on this for awhile? If you have some tips for how you've maintained it long term, I'd appreciate the input! Thanks! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 14:09:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your response was super helpful - thank you so much! I do have a stationary bike and it has some 30 minute routines programmed into it. But if you're doing specific and don't mind sharing details, I'd totally be up to hear them!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>NSV!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 18:39:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>So at work, we have a union and thet gave us these shirts to wear for solidarity and whatnot. Before I started keto, I'd stuffed my shirt in a drawer and made excuses not to wear it because it was too tight and I was self-conscious. Friday, the union rep came around and asked us to wear our shirts for a meeting Monday and my stomach sank, but I took the shirt out of my drawer thinking I'd at least take it home. Today the big day came and I figured I might as well try it on and holy crap - it fits! I mean, it's a blocky, cheap t-shirt so it's not exactly flattering, but it fits!! KCKO!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 22:03:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right back atcha! :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 22:53:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh man, that's so badass!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First attempt at a Varric Inquisitor</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 01:39:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because why not? :P There are some things I'd like to change but I thought this was pretty close for my first attempt. https://i.redd.it/i54jlx9358711.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 02:18:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much! :3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 20:58:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh yea. The first time they stood together, I cracked up. XD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 21:01:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apologies - I got a bit over excited and must have skipped that attachment. Thanks for reminding me nicely, though! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 01:32:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I'm planning to when I get home. But reminding someone nicely instead of yelling might have saved the snark, if that upsets you so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Question about biting</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 23:00:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to cut and still struggle sometimes, though not as bad as I used to...but since I can remember, I've always bit myself. I bite chunks of skin out of the inside of my cheeks or peel pieces off of my lips. Sometimes it feels like it "just happens" - like I space out and when I come to, there's chunks of skin missing from inside my mouth. Sometimes, though it's intentional and seems to happen more when I'm anxious. Does anyone else do this, too? Is it considered self harm?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>