<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject4198</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-09 07:51:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>*swims in reddit waters for first time* Hey guys its true we are porting GGE on Linux and Mac (I wont lose my head if i say Mac here?), and yes in the past as we were a small team and the porting did some other people and they didn't deliver. But now its different and its coming, and i hope your bodies are ready. I wont say and dates or time because as I sad on steam forums you never know what problem can pop up, but it should be soon (as the devs said 90% of job is done). So yea bring out your chickens, cute fluffy rabbits, penguins, zombies or whatever you wanna smash with your car and be ready! =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-10 08:05:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cars and guns? And the awesome community? We would never give up on that one!! Just when there is a proces that takes several months it kinda doesn't make sense that every 3-4 days devs come and say "hey guys soon" Id be pissed as well hahah. But yea we will always keep an eye on GGE to give you guys the best experience possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-19 08:57:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>SCUM wont be a battle royal. Ofc you can go around a try to kill everything but SCUM will be more Survival/RPG oriented.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-19 10:02:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Online games are a 2 sided coin. The sooner you accept that you will see yourself improve ^^</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-19 10:04:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>All the he said and for me sometimes it helps to change to role I play. I usually rotate between mid, adc and jungle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-19 10:09:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>If someone would put his dick as a scale you wouldnt see it from the balls that would ocupy the whole room</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This game is awesome, and i wonder about 1 thing..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-19 11:04:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey everyone I got this game few days ago since its free (been wanting the game since the release but $$ is a problem). As im playing the game I enjoy the hell out of it, tho didnt try the MP aspect of the game yet. The thing that gots me wondering is in the end game when you take the top cars and the cars you start with (atm mine is 370Z) if you tune them all up to the max. Are they on par? Like from a real side of view all cars should be able to be equally fast but from the gaming side progress and unlocking should maybe have an advantage. I ask this because i see few cars in the early game that I really really like, and I would have no problem driving them for the whole game just want to know if its even worth doing that, if later on they will just fall off performance vise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-19 11:10:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to see a diamond player who does that unranked to diamond but that he starts from bronze 5. Just so to see how much can he do with a bad team. Yes there will be games when he can solo win but i really really really think that wont happen a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-19 11:12:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>But lets say i enjoy SP and im not playing MP. Does it matter then?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-19 11:51:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>The devils biggest victory is making you believe that he doesnt exist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-19 12:03:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the feedback I appreciate it big time ^^</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-19 13:46:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>The mob doesnt exist? Either he is an idiot (from your story id say he is a lot of things just not stupid) or he makes jokes about it because he is actually in it. Tho the italian mob isnt really "working" anymore most of them went legit. Id say 70% for a cult and 30% for mob, adn 100% you are fucked =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-20 11:27:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dont think think you can do anything here. The only thing is purifing the whole land and that means digging up all 71 corpses (or how many are there), and burning them. Get out as soon as possible. Its a miracle you lived there as long as you did. But if you feel things are taking turn for the worse you should get out as soon as possible. Go to the grandparents for time being literally anywhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-24 10:39:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>We had some talk about VR but nothing is set in stone. I think we should first make the game haha =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-04 16:26:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>As we are working in UE4 its supported and a possibility. But as we are a smaller team at the release the game will be windows only.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-03 15:51:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its gonna be 1P and 3P, AND its gonna be MP and SP =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-03 16:42:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>You will be able to change from 1 person to 3 person in game not depending on server.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 17:33:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep we grew up on those games like a lot other people and when we sit down and talked what we could do we noticed that there are no games like those anymore so we gave it a shoot with GGE and even the game genre is not on the hype it was well received! =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 17:39:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>All th DLCs we made are included in the game so nope no microtransactions or dlcs anymore =D Tbh I kinda lost track of that about year and a half if you dont take DLC in count. Hahah about 4 times we came back with the DLCs (tho there are only 2 DLCs the rest were just updates)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 17:42:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nostalgia for some epic old school car carnage haha I answered that on the first post ^^ about year and a half</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 17:45:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sadly I didnt get any copies to give away =/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 17:51:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>From DLCs we had only 2. Full metal frenzy:  #8226; Zagreb arena: a totally true-to-life depiction of the old downtown area of the Croatian capital, where the developers of this game reside !  #8226; Cowboy arena: a huge wild west map where dirt rules and anything goes.  #8226; Two new cars: the Stallion and the Rhino JTL. For that extra muscle.  #8226; All new female announcer.  #8226; Two new power-ups, Invisibility  amp; Stun Grenades (who threw that???).  #8226; Three new games modes: Dominator, Destruction Derby and Domination Derby .  #8226; New police skin. No-one drives like the Feds... And Full metal zombie:  #8226; A total of 22 zombie variants, from plain old regular zombies to ax wielding maniacs, to giant undead zombie animals carrying explosives, plus a minigun boss.  #8226; All new arena: Warburg, a huge new city map.  #8226; New car: the Kaiju GTR, a fast iconic Japanese sports and drag racing car.  #8226; Two new game modes: Defend the Base and Survival.  #8226; New military skin. Bust those Zs like GI Joe... And we had lots of updates with minor addons that we didnt want to charge for because as said they were minor =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 17:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>PS4 is coming next year deffo. And right now we are working on a totally new project but after that is done, yep chances for GGE 2 are big because it was our first game and we love it and see lots of room to get bigger and better</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 17:55:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh boy im not good at those but ill give it a try. Khm...Blow of some steam after a hard working day by shooting mini nukes at cars with a blow up doll as your co-driver!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 17:57:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>The thing that I love is the humor and the vibe you get from it. Yea you blow up stuff with tons of weapons but still kinda have that funny chill vibe if needed...and zombie buffalos we have zombie buffalos that are annoying as hell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 17:59:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah yes the Mp thats a huge set back we wont deny that one. As I talked with the tech team and what they said to me is that the Xbox One is a pretty closed platform, and that we just couldnt make it work with the dedicated servers and the experience that we have on the PC.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 18:01:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>As most small teams will tell you the biggest foe is time. Deadlines, tensions, mistakes all of that gets much bigger when time presses. I dont know about that as i was not in the team at that point and forgot to ask that sorrryyy...but will try to find out the answer!! Pizza? where? give me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 18:03:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Should I take it as sold? =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 18:11:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay got the answer. We wanted to add cockpit view and a dynamic day night cycle but at that time we were just a too small team to make it happen in time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 18:39:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Today! =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 18:46:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im not sure if you can compare those 2 games x)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 18:47:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/store/p/gas-guzzlers-extreme/brqh5gkv7912</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 19:40:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>No there isnt a split screen option =/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 19:40:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the nice words means a lot to us! ^^</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 20:05:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Xbox couldnt handle a split screen without a drastic visual degrade</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 20:06:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I dont think so hahah</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 20:08:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh dang it. gonna survive somehow =/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 21:42:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>We also work on a new project and time is also a big factor and manpower. Gas guzzlers was made by 6 people so I assure you laziness and inexperience is not even close to why there is no multiplayer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 21:43:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmmm hard to decide but if I had to pick one id go with the local developers that made Serious Sam 1 =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 21:47:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sadly not only SP =/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 21:52:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope splitscreen wont be a feature sadly, and we also dont have it on PC.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 21:58:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im not trying to offend anyone or downgrade the Xbox. This is what I have been told. Im sure the team had a reason why. Yes time, resources and manpower were the biggest factor. And also there was some other technical issue. Sorry if i sounded rude =/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 22:00:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well our new project will have that and it looks stunning. but thats a topic for another time and place ^^</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 23:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You paid the first rent..what about the second?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-04 23:57:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ayyyyy thanks everyone who was a part of the AMA I had a blast time with you all hope to see you all again on another!! Take care everyone!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-24 10:12:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>We will have some testing before the release next year and when that time comes trust me everyone will know. But Ill put a post up here as well so you guys can be informed =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Steam page is up and running!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 17:32:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-20 08:24:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its not really gonna be the main focus. Regarding firearms, you will be able to find them and have them for a long time (if you take care of it) you will be even able to craft some improvised guns, and bullets. When we say prioritize we mean that in most cases you would want to reslove a situation with melee as its more conviniente in a hostile world filled with enemies. But hey if you wanna go guns blazing dont let us stop you =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-20 08:27:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm if we will have it will be after relase some time! I think the community on reddit is still small so its okay if we have just you as a mod that drops in from time to time. If then things start rolling in the future big time its gonna be easy to pick some people from the community to moderate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 12:15:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>We still didnt decide that one. But when the time comes for testing everyone will have all the info needed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-05 15:00:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Our lead game designer answered this question (and lots more) in detail on our steam forums! So check it out for more infro! http://steamcommunity.com/app/513710/discussions/0/152390648075150883/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>CHARACTER CUSTOMIZATION</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 16:45:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SCUM - Next gen survival</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 16:59:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good day fellow survivalists! My name is subject4198 and I'm the community manager from Gamepires the studio behind SCUM. Maybe some of you stumbled here and there on SCUM and some of you see it for the first time. I'm here to tell you in few short sentences what its about and leave some links that you can check out if you get interested! SCUM evolves the multiplayer open world survival game with unprecedented levels of character customization, control, and progression where knowledge and skills are the ultimate weapons for long-term survival. Players will balance base level needs with knowledge-based skills to manage everything from nourishment, metabolic rate, and body mass to weapons proficiency, combat style, and security systems hacking. Dominate the island with your skills, cunning, and strategies to achieve higher levels of game and receive powerful gifts from corporate sponsors and, if you happen to slip up and die, get resurrected by the show #8217;s producers with all your valuable skills still intact. SCUM is built with Unreal Engine 4 co developed with Croteam and published by Devolver Digital. Its set to launch on PC via Early Access in 2017. Feel free to ask any questions and I will answer them as fast as possible! (A lot of gameplay question have been answere by our Creative Director and Project lead on SCUM on our steam page.) [Reddit](https://www.reddit.com/r/SCUMgame/) [Steam](http://store.steampowered.com/app/513710) [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/ScumGame/) [Twitter](https://twitter.com/ScumGame/) [Blog](https://scumgame.com/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 17:25:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its gonna be a persistant world (you can find some info on the islan you are playing as well on our blog that i forgot to link but will do now hahah) There are still no gameplay videos as we are still in development. Yes it will be an early access game as we are trying to break the EA hate and prove to the people that there are developers who will update the game and give people more content and most important community based content. The release date is around Q2 2017. If a person will have the courage he will be able to survive the whole time without killing or any violence at all. If he builds his character that way as we will have a RPG style skill based mechanic (more on that soon!!)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 17:58:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are still working with the log out, at the moment you disappear, now we have to make that work in a way that you cant just log out when you are in danger and return few minutes later because that makes no sense in a survival game, its still all WiP =) About stashing loot and keeping loot we talked about in one of our posts on our blog so check it out! Base building is in our minds and we talked a bit about it but its nothing sure yet and if we decide on it its gonna come in later stages</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 11:17:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the nice words =) we are trying to make a game that will stand out. And yes, if there will be base building it will be more like fortifying current constructions than building bases from scratch, as in our world i doubt youd have the time to build a bunker haha. *cough* booby traps will be a thing *cough*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stamina update 2  #8211; S is for Science</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 17:21:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stamina update 2  #8211; S is for Science</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 18:18:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stamina update 2  #8211; S is for Science</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-19 10:34:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do players perceive the complexity behind a game?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-19 10:49:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello everyone! I'm new here and hope I will not break any rules with the stuff I say ( i have read the guidlines several times) =D. Back on topic, the game we are currently working on is a survival game, and we are really trying ti bring a real feel to it, and the thing that bothers me is that on the surface (lets take stamina system for example) 2 games can have similar systems and work in a similar way but the technical part behind them can be light years apart. How do you show the player that the difference is bigger and impactful. Yes i guess you can say that the gameplay will show it and thats true, but as I saw in a lot of games the better you do it the more "oh yea i guess its good" it gets.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Our Stamina system</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 09:31:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Ti5LgSMKWQ Hello everyone! This is a short presnetation of the stamina system we have in our survival game SCUM. More info about it you can check on our dev blog. I will try to answer everyquestion! =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-21 08:50:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>[SCUM - Stamina update 2 - S is for Science](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Ti5LgSMKWQ) Hello everyone! Our latest update on SCUM is the stamina system, and everything behind it! In short few notes what is it about: There are several crucial parameters that are taken in consideration for Stamina level determination: * Max Stamina - the initial value * Current Stamina * Maximum Stamina * Stamina Change Rate * Stamina Reserve * Maximum Stamina Reduction [Blog](https://scumgame.com) | [Steam](http://store.steampowered.com/app/513710) | [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/ScumGame/) | [Twitter](https://twitter.com/ScumGame)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Inertia</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 14:58:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Our inertion system</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 15:08:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SCUM - How does inertion work in our game!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 15:21:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-28 09:19:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes they will, as it is in real life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-28 09:30:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Inertia](https://scumgame.com/2017/01/27/inertia/) Hello everyone! Today we have a little video showing the inertion system in SCUM. We recommend also checking the full post if you want the fancy explanation (we used science terms) =D https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_QbNSS3wbC8 [Blog](https://scumgame.com) | [Steam](http://store.steampowered.com/app/513710) | [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/ScumGame/) | [Twitter](https://twitter.com/ScumGame) **Bonus question** Yes I play them and love them haha. The first one was Rappelz in the old days it was really fun but now i became P2W =/ now Tera is my favorite</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 07:22:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha you will save some thousands of bucks whent he game comes out =D. The release is around Q2 this year so just few months ahead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 12:22:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You cant be more correct sir, and we agree with you. But thats why we also have a first person camera mode, and we balanced out the "peeking" with use of skills. You can read about that in our blog posts. More precise the post about stealth https://scumgame.com/2016/12/20/stealth-skill/ tho the 1 and 3 person angle is still under work and we are improving it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 18:02:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>In the later stages of development we plan to put in some transporation device, bycicel, motorbike, car, dragon (joking but that be awesome). Tho it wouldnt just be find it and drive it. There would be some fixing needed probablly depends on the damage of the car. Some skill could also help you fix it faster / fewer parts needed, and maintain it easier and even drive it better. Once the time comes for that we will make sure that the community gives its oppinions so we can go in that way. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 07:57:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello. Regarding base building, we have fixed bases located on the island, and when you capture them you get bonuses like food, weapons, ammo etc. But we are also considering the solution that the player builds his own base. Although its not planed for EA, as we want it to be more than just a box and a door on the level.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 11:01:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!! If you have any more questions just drop them here or on steam forums and we will answer it as soon as possible =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 09:57:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is an awesome suggestion, tho i see some problems regarding twitch and streaming sites. But the concept of players being the audience to other player and themself is quiet interesting. Thank you sir for this suggestion =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SCUM - Unarmed Combat [Pre-Alpha]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 09:58:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-18 12:29:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>We will give our best to give you guys the best game possible, and we will work with the community closely and listen to what it has to say and go with their wishes as much as possible</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-18 12:38:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello everyone! Today im back with more SCUM news more speciffic our unarmed melee combat and we explained in the basicis how it works. For any questions feel free to ask =D [Video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=52AwfWOFbBg) [Blog](https://scumgame.com) | [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/ScumGame/) | [Twitter](https://twitter.com/ScumGame/) | [Reddit](https://www.reddit.com/r/SCUMgame/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SCUM - Unarmed melee combat</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-18 12:39:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello everyone! Today im back with more SCUM news more speciffic our unarmed melee combat and we explained in the basicis how it works. For any questions feel free to ask =D [Video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=52AwfWOFbBg) [Blog](https://scumgame.com) | [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/ScumGame/) | [Twitter](https://twitter.com/ScumGame/) | [Reddit](https://www.reddit.com/r/SCUMgame/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-20 07:28:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imagine if the devs would actually talk with the commnuity that be amazin right =D as the video says in later stages of EA we plan to add more martial art techniques and some of them would have some kind og grappling/submission system (im no pro in this just guessing it)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-20 07:34:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>All of this you see is still WIP and if we and the community notice that its not working as it should we will change it to something better. As you will have combos, dodging, blocking, counter attacking on top of that add free control to hit a person it gets pretty hard and frustrating. As said for now in testing this system worked really good and was fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-21 07:39:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can expect it around Q2 this year</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Missed out on something? We got you covered!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-21 16:23:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 07:43:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>For now its going to be PC only, after we exite early access we will see about consoles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 08:13:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the suggestion I will write that one down =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 18:26:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.reddit.com/r/SCUMgame/ evo za one koje vise zanima imamo i reddit =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-06 07:33:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the nice words, we have so much in store for scum that you guys will love, and when the community ides come into the picture as well this will be the game of the century!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-14 08:15:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well we are working at a fast and strong pace and it takes it tool, but comments like this make it worth all the trouble and sleepless nights. We will give our best to make this gener alive and popular again and show how much potential it has. And ofc we will try to keep the bug level to a minimum =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 08:30:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>A new video is coming out soon =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>For our russian friends!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 17:33:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>A small update for all our friends in Russia. You can now read about SCUMs story on Russian on our blog.  #1044; #1083; #1103;  #1056; #1086; #1089; #1089; #1080; #1080;- #1084; #1072; #1090; #1091; #1096; #1082; #1080;! https://scumgame.com/2017/04/06/ #1080; #1089; #1090; #1086; #1088; #1080; #1103;- #1084; #1080; #1088; #1072;-scum/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 08:20:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are aiming for next week if we dont hit into any problems =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 08:05:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just a small one haha tho its not a problem really we are waiting for some thigs and then it can go live.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 14:09:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://scumgame.com/2016/09/29/encounters/ Here you go, all you need to know about them!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New video? fuck yea its a new video</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 14:11:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here it is guys, a new video on SCUM. Check it out and give me your thoughts and comments!! https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dn-qfKPnKtk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[SHOW OFF] Shooting skill in SCUM!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 14:27:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>How we made shooting in SCUM real and awesome! =D https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dn-qfKPnKtk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 07:45:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kudos to the post its pretty on point. I will try to show you the developers side of this year long problem. Its kinda pretty easy, I really doubt that there are developers with an attitude that goes "meh we make games for PC no need for a controller, those console pesants should pick up KB amp;M". Mostly the problem is the number of key bindings. If there are more than the controller supports you have a problem. You cant drop out some functions just to put controllers in the picture it would be unfair big time, and balancing out the aspect of functionality between KB amp;M and Controllers is kinda impossible. We in Gamepries didnt exclude the option for controllers in SCUM we would love to have it really. Just we need to finish up the game and the controlls for it for KB amp;M first to see what we can do for controllers. If its gonna be possible to make the game for controllers rest assured that we will if it wont be able we will tell you guys why we werent able to make it. On a side note I have huge respetc for people who play FPS like game on controllers, as i have no clue how can someone be so precise with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 15:28:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just want to say one thing before it gets out of controll as i saw it many times before. KB amp;M is not supperior to a Controller or vice versa its all about personal preferences so lets stay at that and not go into a whats better competition. I personaly love controllers for racing games (a steering wheel is even better but the good ones are shit ton expensive|). We will look into controllers and consoles as well just for the time being its not our priority. Im not saying that it matters less just we dont want to jump on other things while having for example: gamebraking bugs, big fps drops, lag problems etc.. We are alwayas as transparent with our community as possible, and you will be always in loop of whats happening or whats not happening and for what reason its not happening =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wrong game name in description</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 10:02:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello evryone. I have a issue, on our latest update video of the game SCUM after some time in the description showed up that the game is Wildlands, and i cant find a way to remove it, and our game is not on the list. So i wonder what can be done in that regard. Here is a screenshot of the issue http://prntscr.com/f0y3jz Thanks in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 10:34:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tried that already, and its not working.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 10:51:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright. I did that, and i didnt notice any new options really and when i tried to change the name again it didnt work. Is there a way that we can add our game to the list?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SCUM - Camouflage preview</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-06 10:19:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7ZRY4mJzLN8</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 08:15:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>We will try to bring SCUM in every part of the world =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 17:49:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Gamepires =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 09:47:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey mate we have no problem with that. From the recent games that i saw that went to EA and overall, gamedevelopers are popping out more than weed with a mind set "Lets make some fast money". But then few months into development suprise suprise making games isnt as easy as the thought. Gamepires is not a new studio we are here for aprox 5-6 years, and the core team are old school vets in the industry. Check out the game that they made with 6 people. Gas guzzlers Extreme, and as you all know by now we are really open with you guys so you are always in the loop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 12:20:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope that one sadly cant do. You have to understand that we arent a 60 man company, 14 people are working on SCUM, and you never know what problem can pop up that will halt the development. So we rather dont say anything regards that than say a relase date and the fail to make it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-22 08:21:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>+1 from the Devs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 12:39:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>We hope and believe so. I really dont want to misslead you guys because before being a community manager im also a gamer, and I know the feelings and the position you are comming from. In this industry no matter how much problems/situations (good or bad) you expect there will pop up 3 times more that you just could not predict. But I assure you that we are giving our best and max to deliver SCUM as soon as possible and in the best state as possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 12:43:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>In SCUM everything you do gives you experience and goes into some skill/status so there will always be a feel that you did something. Regarding item spawning etc... There will be servers with various rates (community made servers) and lots of other options. Everyone will be able to find the perfect server for him. If not well you can always play solo the way you like with the rates you like. =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 08:07:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea, you buy the game, you can join on other servers (or get your own) or you can play on our own local server alone and chill, and all paramters that we will put in to be adjustable you will be able to change. Item spawn rates, weapon spawn rates, enemy spawn rate etc.. (those are just examples of what might be in)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 08:07:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thats a top secret, if we tell you we gonna need to kill you =/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 14:32:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>All of the devs understand that, they are just lazy and time to time money hungry =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-09 07:50:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>yup =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SCUM NEEDS YOU!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-15 12:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://steamcommunity.com/games/513710/announcements/detail/2917618592648837941</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Help us improve our metabolism formulas!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-15 12:46:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-15 15:17:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure you can, there is no hurry =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 08:11:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>its an email you need to send the chart to</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 08:32:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy..this is a nice read. Thanks for your input. Not sure how will you take this, but most of the things you said we already know and most of them are already in game (some need tweeking but are in). I hope that you dont think it was a waste to write this as it was not, and there is a lot of info that we will write down. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 14:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>We still dont have ny date set, as soon as there will be we will let you know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-08 09:28:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here ya go mate. Some of the basic info about it you can find here. =) http://steamcommunity.com/app/513710/discussions/0/2132869574256298533/?tscn=1502175451</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New vide live!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 18:19:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>See what we did with our new video update!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 18:22:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Show Off] How we tackle TPP problem in survival games.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 18:35:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 23:02:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>In the video it was extended just to show it of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-17 08:49:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>We will see about that, we had to make it longer for the video as the naration was about 30 seconds so people can see what we are talking about. But it wont be gamebraking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Small update on player feedback of sCAT video.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-17 12:42:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 08:32:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every action in scum has a counter balance in some way. When you die you lose all your gear but skills will stay intact, as we dont like to punish players that much. Thats our point of view, but of course there are players who like a hardcore approach to the game and we respect that one as well thats why people will be able to make their own servers and mod them in the way they like them so everyone can find something that suits them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 08:33:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here you go guys http://steamcommunity.com/app/513710/discussions/0/2183537632736507701/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Some eye candy while you guys wait for the new video</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-11 15:35:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Promise we are working on a new video aswell =D</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 20:08:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 12:53:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>And what did exactly happened? I don't really understand it from this what you wrote?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SCUM - Headbanging into the sunset time lapse [Pre Alpha]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 17:03:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New video live!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 16:09:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 18:04:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Skills and fame points wont be transferable between servers (at least not for now). 2. We will have certain event types in the game, and for now its only that we did not look into mechanics like paring the most/least popular players ect.. 3. Fame points (you can look on that like a rank) will be one of the core mechanics in the game so it will be on every server.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 08:00:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>There will be official servers. I guess you can take that as vanilla.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Awesome article on scum from venturaBeat</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 13:03:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 23:38:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the nice words. For now we still dont have the sleep mechanic worked out. But once we do we will let you guys know =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 10:11:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Feed me suggestions and ides my minions muahahahah =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any clans still active?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 14:02:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gonna try HoN again after few years. Wondered if there are people who would like to play?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My first 2 games after 3 years.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 08:01:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, yesterday I played HoN after some good 3 years, and I really need some confirmation from you guys here if its the case for all games. So my first game was a normal game (not for the leaderboards), and the moment we entered hero select screen shit went south, really really really fast. The last time (3 years ago) when I played there were heroes for mid, jungle, suicide, support, carry or sometimes duo top. Depending on the communication what people want to play. Okay so we enter the hero select screen, and the only thing anyone wrote was me "Can I please support I didnt play the game in a long time" ofc no one responded but hey who knows they will get it when I pick Glacius. I was on a lane with Ra, mid was pyro, top were polly and cant remember the last hero. Overall I didnt mind the weird picks as people can go anywhere with anything and make it work if they know how to play. But you know those games where it feels that everything is just all over the place like nothing makes any sense of what the hell is going on? Yea multiply that by 5. Then I went to play a game for the leaderboards as I thought maybe people take that more serious than casual games, and boy was I wrong. Exactly the same stuff happened. I tried to communicate with my team of what to do where to go ect.. but nope like im talking to a wall. I mean even for a player that played this game before and has a lot of games under his belt. I dont feel like playing anymore at all. How does Frostburn expect to gain people when the game is in such a chaotic state. Okay I get that its not really their fault for me getting "unlucky" with my games and teammates. But i bet 90% of new people who would like to try to get into the game wont look at it that way but will just uninstall the game after few games. So my question is. Is that really the state of the community/game right now or did I have bad luck and those are like 2/10 games that happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 08:37:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am from Eu and I play on Eu servers. Guess youre right. But that takes the question how far can you get with such teammates.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 09:09:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good point good point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 13:55:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everything you need to know is written on our discord under the christmas event section.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SCUM - Merry Christmas from Gamepires</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 15:28:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New video live!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 13:18:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 08:18:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thats totally fine and if its your opinion we respect it. Not every game is for everyone. =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 14:58:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>No worries we already looked into that and have ideas and plans for it. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 14:59:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>But thank you for your opinion and suggestion nonetheless!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 10:42:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the input we shall look into it. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 07:27:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>As we (the devs) cant really influence reddit as its community driven. But can you try to keep it civil. And thank you for the input.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 14:26:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ill just say that we will have fun events that you can chose if you want to participate or not. =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 14:29:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oPhjvMIfkH0 amp;t Did you watch this video?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 08:04:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>NVGs won't be easy to find. So about 90% of people will need to rely on alternative vision sources. Like flashlights and torches.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 08:06:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, thats an interesting idea for sure x). But for now, it's not planned, maybe later. Tho we do plan to have interactions/taunts that are not gender specific.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 08:08:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>It will be closer to the end of Q1 or beginning of Q2, than to the end of Q2. The main reason is that we decided to add some extra features that were not planned for EA release. These features will separate SCUM from all other survival/BR games and also will provide new players with some new game mechanics that are fully unique to SCUM. This was hard decision to make but at the end, we decided to do it before the release. It is our opinion that we have only one chance so it #8217;s better to do it right. Also, these elements will provide players with enough things to keep them occupied before we make the first update of the game. This first update after release will be crucial since the game will be tested by huge numbers of players and we will have to patch/fix issues ASAP. Because of that majority of the team will be probably working on the bugs and not gameplay related things. So even if it seems that we are being late we are actually planning to be more effective after the release. Hope you understand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 08:12:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://i.imgur.com/HkPOzEH.jpg?1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 16:02:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes we will have VOIP in game =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New video live!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 15:55:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 07:58:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn it...*Crosses out pony hats raining from loot boxes" Jokes aside, we dont plan to have any p2w mechanics. If we will have something that can be bought with extra money it be skins like you said. I personally love the system RUST has but we will see which way we will go if we will go that way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 08:13:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes we will make it able to you will keep your character preset that you made. =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 07:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, thats an awesome idea. And sure you can use all assets you need for it. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 07:17:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>0.35 euros and a wallet aint enough atm =/. Next time try with your soul.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 08:49:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>You mean in character creation? If that then yes we will have character customization.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 13:33:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are fixing them already =D, and ofc we will fix them all the time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 12:43:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you and fuck you too =D  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 09:38:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>And we agree 100%. That's why we look into the option to disable and enable the outline option (also other various mechanics). So people will be able to play in their own style of game. We are not sure if we will be able to get this running from day 1 as it includes more parameters *insert some tech stuff talk that I did not understand*. But we heard you guys on that topic on more than 1 occasion, and we will do our best to make it satisfying for everyone. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 09:39:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Sad pepe*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 10:09:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea I mean server wide. =) Regarding servers we will see if there will be official servers that will have that disabled. (Cant promise anything) But once its available (as said mentioned that wont be available from day 1) you will be able to set it up for your own server. Now regarding your own server, there will be 2 types of "your own server" 1. You can buy a server from our official server provider G portal. And you will be able to do that from day 1. 2. Once we release server files that will enable you to host your own server. But that wont be from day 1 as well but later on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 10:34:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice ideas all around this thread. For now, we will have some time frame that will start a countdown before you log out. But yea we will improve that later on for sure. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 10:39:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>The thing with the fame system is to draw attention from the new players that are just starting to the ones that are..well more famous. I mean we still want make our game that way so everyone can do what they want. So its up to you how you want to play, where there be bullies that will aim to camp new players? Probably yes, but as said with the fame system we want to throw the focus of from that, but yet not so much so that the choice of "do what you want" is removed. Its all about the balance, and we will give our best to get to that balance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 10:40:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>We do not have a set price yet. It will depend on the state the game will be released and how many features it will have. Take this as a definite answer. =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 10:41:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Q2 is the release. And all videos are ingame made. =D https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G8J7N_dQbcs Newest one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 10:43:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good point, with a fair sense of doubt. +1 =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 10:44:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its been mostly quiet as I have been sick for the last week, and I'm the CM. So sorry for that, as we pride ourselves on community interacting. But I,m back now!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 10:45:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup, this is totally true. But also take into account that Rare (SoT devs) have around 200 employees. And we have 16! =D Tho we are trying our best to be here with you guys!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 10:48:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, stuff like that is planned. But atm we have some bigger priorities than that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 10:54:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, we would like to have it to such a degree. The only problem with that atm are animations, we need a lot (and I mean a LOT) of them to have most of the wound situations. Like if you miss an arm, finger, leg ect... We will have hit zones on the body, to simulate real life as much as possible. We have some ideas for healing that will be located in safe zones, but all that is still in the works. So can't say too much as it could all be changed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 10:55:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't be haha. Nothing wrong with a small dose of healthy scepticism. =D Thank you for the nice words, means a lot!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 13:13:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>We will see about that. First it will be for SP. If it will work for MP we will add it in. Ofc depends on the community and what they would like.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 07:33:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>As @Magor57 stated. In a game like this, you cant punish people for doing anything really (besides cheating ofc) as you can do whatever you want. Regarding freshspawn people and the "famous ones," we can try to make it so it's uninteresting to hunt them. And yeas you will lose fame points on death. Before that you will be able to use a certain amount to maybe get some gear back, skills ect.. And this is all still in the works, the whole fame system. We will make it as good as possible with the input from you guys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 07:36:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Interesting idea. Not sure how much we can do as this takes a lot of work, and we are kinda busy with the game. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 12:07:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Valid points, I'll write them down. And as said, all of this is still in the works. I said a rough outline of the idea ofc its gonna be tweaked and balanced as much as possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We are at PAX East!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 17:49:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>For all you reddit people. This year we are at PAX east, so if you want to try some SCUM drop by! And have a chat with us if you want!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 18:10:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes we plan to add that. Not from the day 1 of Ea as we are limited by animations, but we will add it in the future.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 07:52:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have our own both besides the devolver one. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 08:39:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are doing some work on it thats why its down. We will update once its live!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 08:39:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry totally top secert, cant say we are changing everything so it looks better =/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 08:40:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>The old site is up, there were few problems that the web team encountered. They are Canadian, don't want to tell you all the excuses we got from them. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 08:42:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ayyyy we do not know about the wild west but east Europe, now living here that's some real survival. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>screenshots!!!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 15:12:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 14:04:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>All settled!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 14:12:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Guys Q2 is a 100%. This can be tomorrow or June 30. Sadly we cant go more precise</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 14:14:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Regarding modes. We will see what we can do. We will try to add the ones most wanted by you guys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 11:56:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey Eli, yes we are active everywhere (or at least I try to be as much as possible). A lot of answer can be found in our FAQ (jace posted it). But before that, I highly recommend to watch our videos. https://www.youtube.com/user/TheGamepires/videos From Inertia till the end.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 16:51:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ayyy time that I pop in here. SCUM is inspired by a lot of games. But we are not trying to make a better version of DayZ, EFT, PUBG, H1Z1, Ark ect.. We are making something totally new something that has not been seen before. You can find online our interviews that we gave on PAX. I'm pretty sure that we and dayz found the same good inspirations for items and made them by it. Even if we did copy it or even if they copy something from us in the future. I really do not see it as a problem. If devs upgrade their games with good features and mechanics and improve the game overall I would never see it as a problem. You still choose what game you want to play no one is forcing you to play something else. But that's my personal opinion. A similar situation happened with AC: Origins. I met a person who was "They have totally no originality they copied Witcher 3 questions marks on the map for undiscovered situations". I asked him does it work like in Witcher 3? He said that it does, and then I asked him again if he likes that system in Witcher 3 he also said yes. So where is the problem? You got another game with a system that you're familiar and on top of that it works and you like it. Isn't that a win for everyone? SCUM will have more than enough of original features (it already has tons of them). If someone can make something totally new that was never seen before and make it work well, great, respect to that person. But also I do not see the problem if you see something that works and people like. Why not use it? Its a win for everyone. I'm starting to repeat my self SO final verdict. We are not copying anyone, we see what you guys like and add it to SCUM, we also have tons of original stuff that we hope will attract new players. For any more questions, I'll be more than happy to answer. =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 16:54:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Obv the best ones were with me. ;D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 17:03:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you talk about the drone hovering over players, that was just an idea that popped into my mind at that point. Ofc if it can be made possible so it's balanced we will make it. We are totally open to suggestions as well. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 17:04:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://prntscr.com/j7vl1r Here you go. Some of the current benchmarks from our testers. Ofc they are prone to changes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New round of screenshots!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 14:48:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 08:22:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, you will be able to get stuff from events. But it wont be crucial to join them. We like to balance things out so everyone can find their play style =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 08:23:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe, who knows. If people will ask for it we will see in what manner we can add it. But survival is still our main focus.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 08:24:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea as people said. For now, they are just a few presets. But we will try to add more customization in later stages. I have in mind already an awesome tattoo artist who is hooked for our game and he would like to do some custom ones just for SCUM. So we will see what we can do about that. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 08:25:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://scumgame.com/en/news/encounters You can check more here about our "zombies".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 17:54:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can tell you that I never heard of NDS. And we are not affiliated with them in any way. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 08:32:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Deathmatch mode where everyone is naked and has crohn disease, and the only weapon is the one you shit out? 1 hit 1 kill?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shout out to our reddit SCUM</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 08:34:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just a small shoutout to all you guys who follow us here. As we are the least active here. But we did not forget you guys we love you all the same. Thanks for supporting us  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 09:01:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for letting us know. I think they are good for now pvtjace is the boss here so he takes the shots for for staff and everything =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 17:24:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its gonna be pay to play =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New screens!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 13:31:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 08:12:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yo guys, there won't be any hidden release dates. We will announce the release date. When? When we announce it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 08:15:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have benchmarks on our official discord server. =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 08:02:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Interesting idea for sure. I will write it down. =D even tho we had some ideas around fear already. But thank you nonetheless</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Discord is over 5000!!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 13:47:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Today we broke 5,000 members on our official @discordapp server. Big thanks to our whole community and much love from the whole SCUM team. https://discord.gg/scum</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 15:03:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>As soon as we will have an official date you guys will know it. We do everything transparent with you guys. =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 07:45:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you and we will. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Video Sunday!! Check out this awesome flyover made by our tester soBr0kEn!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 14:44:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 07:32:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5tTFP2Fg2OI amp;t here you go. 7h of shooting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 08:42:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://prntscr.com/jngzmr</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 08:43:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair enough, what does not look good to you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 16:24:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are aware of some of the UI problems. The UI is being reworked as well, and one thing to consider is that youtube compressed the video a lot and it's much darker than it should be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 16:25:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/444216579941466112/451010743190552576/unknown.png How it really looks. But as said it is being reworked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 14:35:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're fired 5/7 =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 16:43:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ohh good that you mentioned I mistyped as well...fired 100/10 =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New screenshot!!....kinda...love you all!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 10:03:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 17:58:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>.-.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 14:10:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey hey and welcome to our subreddit. We already have in mind (and did some testing with hair growth) facial hair and hair growth. We would love to make it able that you can rock different haircuts and beards. But for now, it's not a priority. But thanks for the suggestion nonetheless hope to see more of you here. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New vide live!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 17:12:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 08:43:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>God damn why do I always miss the o in the video....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 08:44:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its a shuriken =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 08:06:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>U igri se trenutno ne moze okretat janje no mozda jednog dana ubacimo i to u igru. =D https://www.reddit.com/r/SCUMgame/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>HAPPY B DAY DICK!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 15:20:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 13:45:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey guys just to chime in to clear possible confusion. Nvidia will be giving away codes that can be activated once the game is released not sooner. And the price 30$ is just an approximate from their side due to legal reasons. So 2 main points. 1. The game WON'T be one sale on E3 2. The game price is NOT confirmed. 3. The game release date is also NOT confirmed until told from official sources.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 13:46:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey guys just to chime in to clear possible confusion. Nvidia will be giving away codes that can be activated once the game is released not sooner. And the price 30$ is just an approximate from their side due to legal reasons. So 2 main points. 1. The game WON'T be one sale on E3 2. The game price is NOT confirmed. 3. The game release date is also NOT confirmed until told from official sources.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 13:46:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey guys just to chime in to clear possible confusion. Nvidia will be giving away codes that can be activated once the game is released not sooner. And the price 30$ is just an approximate from their side due to legal reasons. So 2 main points. 1. The game WON'T be one sale on E3 2. The game price is NOT confirmed. 3. The game release date is also NOT confirmed until told from official sources.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 09:07:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Guess its time to put my head on the chopping block =D. The robots were here from day 1. You can see Mr.Smiley on our first art screen posted in 2016 (he is on the right behind the fence). And the whole game is about a TV show, that's with the drones and stuff (We also had drones in some of our previous videos). And there are things tied to the lore that we still did not reveal yet. SCUM is still a survival game in its nature, just there will be a lot of other goodies going on on the island to keep you entertained..or the people watching =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 09:10:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>The decision for the delay was made on Friday. And because the people who want to get the game we do not want to release a game that is filled with bugs and problems under the cover of EA, at least keep it to a minimum. Also what we forgot to account for is Steam summer sale that starts soon, and E3 itself. We took a call that it's not the best time for a release. And as said the decision was made on Friday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 09:12:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope, still a survival game, and it will never be a BR game. The closest we may get to BR is a BR mode inside the game...in the company with many more modes like TDM, Deathmatch, CTF ect..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 09:14:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>We did not lie, the decision was made on Friday. We are still working hard on the game to make it as good as possible. You can find more info in other posts and steam regarding this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 09:15:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, much love  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 14:02:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't go into too much detail about it. But on the release day, you will know exactly what your getting, and we plan to publish a roadmap on release.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 14:21:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I totally agree with you on that one. But as said I can't go too much into detail, but you will get all the info you need to make sure if the game is for you or not. =) and ofc the info that you will get will be unbiased.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 15:51:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope, totally our fault. We are a small team, and we do not have any management just for that. So kinda everyone does everything. Ofc most of people are just in the development. I'm as well in development but also a CM, PR and some other stuff as well. We are doing our best to make SCUM as good as possible for release. But in Game dev even if you account in problems there will be some that you never expected. So its really really reaallllyyy hard to make a set date if you are a small studio. We made a mistake we learned from it. And big thanks to everyone who understands  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 16:28:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ummm...those 2 are different types of genres. And we won't be a BR game but a survival simulation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 16:46:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean thats also a viewpoint. But if we go by that every game where you can die is a survival game? Maybe go with the notion that survival games tend to backtrack when you die? E.G you lose stuff/progress when you die? Edit 1: Its a big area I think. But regarding SCUM or main focus is simulation and hc survival. Not arcade shooting, if that makes sense</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 08:23:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice work there, just 2 things. 1) You wont have a map like that in SCUM when its released 2) This is the most outdated map of the island from 2016, it changed regarding hot spots, cities ect.. But nice work non the less!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 13:05:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>The shape of the island is the same, roads are different, village positions, a lot of POI are not here as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 17:50:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey guys. I'm here to shine some light regarding the stream. First of all, you need to know that on E3 where only 2 SCUM devs, as the rest of us are heads deep in development. We were aware that 2 people are wayyyy to less to handle all the meetings but we just couldn't spare more people. Saying that the only time able to stream was that 1h window on Friday where the press meeting they had cancelled it. And they did not go catch a breath or rest for a bit but they went to stream. "But why couldn't you put someone from devolver to stream the game" yes we could but that person could not answer any questions really. They guys were flat out tired and exhausted. We all have only the best intentions for SCUM but mistakes were made and will probably be made in the future, as we are all people and we make mistakes. We will try to make up for it with streams from the office (we plan to start that next week with a Q amp;A) and try to do them as many as possible, also we will publish the longer version of the trailer that you saw on E3 in the next 2 weeks, as well with the price of SCUM. Thank you all for your understanding, much love from the whole SCUM team  lt;3  lt;3. And please please please, try to avoid trash talking anybody, we always welcome constructive criticism and advice. But venting and trash talking over spilt milk won't do anything. Again thank you and much love  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Taking merch to a whole new level</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 18:03:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 08:07:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was not pointed towards anyone specific. And we are well aware it could (and should) been better, and we will give our best to make it so. In the next streams, you will see my pretty face and we will go through Q amp;A gameplays or anything you guys would like to see. =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 08:04:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi new guy I'm dad. In case you log off your gear goes with you and reappears when you log back in. Cooking will be optional, you will be able to find cans of food ect..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 11:55:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, it is possible. I mean depends on what food you eat. If you eat just candy all the time ofc no. But most canned food has a good nutritional value, mixing it with some fruits as well for vitamins (there are a lot of fruit trees) you should be fine. But some basic cooking like meat, vegetable ect.. will not be too hard to come by.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 11:55:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>For now no, and we did not really think about that. But if people would want that we can take a look into it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 07:06:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>There will be a party mechanic we will see how much of "friendly" visibility we will have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Game development at its finest.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 13:41:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SCUM price reveal!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 17:18:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excited to announce that SCUM will have an introductory $19.99 price when it enters Steam Early Access this August! The price will increase throughout Early Access as new content and features are added. Wishlist here: https://store.steampowered.com/app/513710</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 09:01:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol same</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 09:04:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>And as it pans out Spielberg does not take a beer as a payment option =/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 09:13:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>My 2 cents on this. So yea we will have fortification in the game (not from day 1 but it's being worked on). Regarding storing stuff, you can already put your stuff in cabinets that you search/loot. Ofc there is always a possibility someone will come and loot it and find your gear. If we will make storage that you will be able to lock in some way we will need to make it in a way that ties into skills, and also have a counterpart of it that would be lockpicking. So it's not just make a storage of some sorts and you are set.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 09:14:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because of reasons =D Just a small clip to show you guys how the song animations were made. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 07:17:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>As soon as we will have more info on it we will let you know!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 08:03:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not yet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 15:45:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://prntscr.com/k0emg2 *flies away*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 07:44:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just to make it clear we are already pushing the boundaries of UE4 regarding map size. I do not promise we will expand the map. But you never know what can happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 08:37:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just to chime in for a moment. The skill as in the red outline/red blob or call it whatever you want it is removed due us reworking the whole awareness skill. The red outline was just 1 feature of that skill.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Official gamepires curator page!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 12:50:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 14:53:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>We will see what we feel works best.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Interview with 80 level</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 16:35:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 14:18:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Props to you and your dad for being in our game =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 16:16:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imma try to answer that one. =D 1) Yes, also the idea is that the buildings you fortify give you more than just a place to stash your loot. Maybe if its a workshop more tools to craft better items to maybe repair broken ones etc.. And not all building will be the same. You will be able to have from small houses to big bases. (some of them you wont be able to fortify alone) 2) Its gonna be various, from a simple try to lockpick a door, and youre in a group of players trying to break in a base where is another group of players to various means like maybe brute force, or stealthy. 3) SCUM will also have a clan like system, for starters it will be basic but we will upgrade it later on. We will also have in-game missions. Raiding I explained above. Look if I told you that we have every little detailed planned out to the dot for SCUM id be lying. Ofc we know what we want, and we have an idea how to get to that, but thats a trip, a trip that we will take with our community together. Thats why it will be an EA game and its costs 20$ in the start.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 14:11:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really good suggestions. Ill write them down. For the map tier system, the idea is that the player can go anywhere. But going in the mountains in summer clothing or in a radioactive area without a hazmat suit...well it wont end well. But you can always try if you want to. All in all really nice suggestions. =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 14:12:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cant promise anything about it. But we will take a look into that for sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 14:14:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a casual gamer regarding survival games, and have no problem playing the game. Yea, I also make the game that needs to be accounted for. But I know few testers that are casual and just chill and have a nice time. SCUM is made for casual players and hardcore ones.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 14:14:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nahh youll be able to play with him =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 14:17:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will this make the post to flare up?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 14:17:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope, it wont xD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 07:28:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>More closer to later August than early. You have benchmarks on our official discord so you can see how your system will handle it. =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 17:44:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry for the silence guys, we are tied in development big time, and don't catch all the socials. We plan to announce the date really soon as well. So stay tuned. If you want to join on our discord there you can catch all the news faster.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 11:43:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 11:44:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are doing our best, and your support means a lot ^^</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 11:44:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Preach brother!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 13:53:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep yep, you will be able to stash stuff. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 14:44:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>We plan to add psychological effects. From happiness, anxiety, fear etc.. Tho we will add it later on, as those will require a lot of work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 14:45:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahahah those would be indeed fun aspects of the game with an impact. I will write that down. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 14:49:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>As Phlex said, that would take a lot of time for a person to do that. And someone can just come after him and remove the things from furniture. For now we will stay on that feature and see how it pans out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 14:49:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>=D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 14:50:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I chose the name Batman.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 15:17:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you will fortify a building and make it yours, items wont respawn in it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 09:58:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have event modes that give you the possibility to shoot your heart out, also maybe we can add some BR type event in the future.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 14:39:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>For now, we have basic wound patching. But the idea is to upgrade that system from heart massages to surgeries that can only a person with high medical skill pull of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>small update!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 15:03:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 08:11:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just imagine to get hit by that gives me shivers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 08:11:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just by crafting this thing you prove a point not to get close to you hahah xD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 08:14:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>=o noice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 08:18:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like the idea of shooting a dose of adrenaline in your friend that is injured and is not close to you. Good job!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 08:19:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are a mean person =(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 07:22:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>No DLCs confirmed, lets not spread fake info ;).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 07:24:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey hey, valid thinking for sure. But im happy to say that youre wrong ^^ The game will come out this month, and we will announce the date any day now. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 09:07:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure we would like to expand the island and the game overall. But lets first finish this part of the game and then look where to expand. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Release date!!!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 16:00:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>throwback time =D</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 09:45:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 14:30:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey guys just to touch on the spawning mechanic. Its still in the early days, we will ofc fine tune it as time goes on so its balanced out. All that you saw in the stream is NOT the final version (maybe some things are if the work good). Nothing is set in stone, all is prone to changes, and all of the changes will go towards that, that the game feels balanced and good to play. =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 14:31:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will talk with the reddit mods to set up a possible Q amp;A for you guys so we can clear everything out, and remove the doubts and worries you may have =D in the end the game is for you awesome people  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 11:30:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>We already have our menu set with all the dishes, tho the customers will be able to add their suggestions what could improve the meals. And we can see and try it out, and if its better and the customers like it, why not keep it. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 12:55:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gogogogog play with the man!! Id love to but will have hands full with a community after the launch. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 12:59:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well to be honest, the idea is to escape the island. But for what will happen when you do we still need to see what scenario we will pick. We will tie it with missions once we add them to the game. Also with rewards that will come with that etc..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 13:21:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh damn. We in the bussines part tho. Hall 4.1, booth E40</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 13:44:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need to have a business pass for it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 09:13:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha this is awesome. But boy oh boy you will get messed up =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SCUM - Developer Stream #2</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 11:15:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 11:42:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imma take those 2 cents =D. Fair enough, tho that sound happens only in the events. And you dont need to join them if you dont want to. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 11:46:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>How about we give the option to have it or not to have it? So people who don't want it can remove it? Through options?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 11:47:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>The team up system will be upgraded. This is not the final version, and ill take your input into account. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 12:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ayoooo wheres my mayooo. Thats our bad guys, we have some of those stuff in our builds that we make for easier and faster testing. But stress not it WONT be in the game.  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 09:06:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>What he said. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 11:47:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Soooo...map change incoming? =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 12:44:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>+1 to this. We will look into it once we gonna expand our medical skill to the next stages. Thank you for the suggestion  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 12:47:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tbh we made our game for moments like this.  lt;3 Cant wait to see what you guys can come up with =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SCUM is live on Steam Early Access! Welcome to SCUM Island, prisoner!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 18:06:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 15:34:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The cube is of big importance of the island. In the early days of mankind when the island was still shaping, the gods used those small cubes in finding problems and issues to they can fix it faster....In short we use it to find the exact place of a bug on the island, and time to time we forget to delet it xD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 16:27:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>If anyone is a god here, its you guys that play SCUM and support it.  lt;3 You are the real heroes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 16:29:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahahah the whole office was looking at me while I was laughing my ass off. GGWP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 16:31:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>At one point you will forget to refound it and we will make a BBQ together in our game ;D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 16:33:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just normal people who take care of their game, and the people playing it as best as they can  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 16:35:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>We might have to tweak that a bit. But yea, please do not drink a whole bottle of absinthe in real life it will kill you most likely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 16:35:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are aware of the issue and are looking into it right now. Thank you for your understanding  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 16:37:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>hahahah guess we messed up a ragdool. We will take care of it. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 16:38:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you everyone for the nice words, it means the world to us  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 16:50:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>...If she leaves you Ill jump in so no worries, and thank you for the nice words and suggestions they are noted  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 16:52:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>...this may be a bug. Noted it down and will look into it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 16:53:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>For now you can not. But we will add that later on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 11:46:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dont think i dont see that wooden chop board that you are ready to throw into his head if things go wrong...totally not talking out of experience..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New patch coming in hot!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 13:19:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 10:01:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, we appreciate it from the bottom of our scumy hearts  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 10:07:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey guys, thanks for the feedback. Ill shoot this thread to the people who work on them, we will continue to work on them to balance them out as good as possible. Thank you for your feedback  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 10:09:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>What have we done .-.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 10:18:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nono thank you for playing our game  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 10:19:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmmm the meat should spoil after 2 days, we will take a look into it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 10:20:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dad could beat up your bear with your dad...am i doing this right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 10:21:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>We were just trying the mute button and for us its working. We will have a deepr look into, and keep you posted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 10:41:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Duly noted! Thank you for the suggestion  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 10:43:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>That one is on our todo list!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 10:58:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>No worries thats why we are here to answer questions! We have a roadmap on steam, but we can't really say a certain timeline of what will go in regarding those. We will level ourselves with what people would like to see next and also what takes longer time to add.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A big thank you from the devs  lt;3</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 12:40:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello reddit folk! Just wanted to say a big thanks to all you wonderful people who help us with suggestions, bugs, feedback and the awesome funny moments. It means a lot to us. Please, keep posting here as you are as we are looking here as well and responding to your comments (we cant catch all but trying as much as possible). Also feel free to tag me in questions, suggestions etc.. and I will do my best to answer as many as possible. Again a big thank you and without you SCUM would not be where it is now.  lt;3  lt;3  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>