<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject4762</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First Draconic Visage on an Ironman account!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-05 18:03:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>After the visage drop: got the dfs made! :)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-06 23:11:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>They say I'm pretty fly, for an iron guy.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-07 19:19:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First there was visage. Now i got zerker ring in 17 total kills!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-13 20:55:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Random dc, hidden PvP testserver?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-20 16:24:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nice achievement - 1600 total on my ironman</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-23 23:50:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>14 kill rex trip on ironman : 3 warrior rings + rol + half key + clue</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-01 13:16:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Was bored so went to chaos ely for a bit.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-17 21:34:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Streaming hardcore ironman day #1</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-13 13:12:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cockatrice head drop on Ultimate Ironman in 20 kills</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-26 13:18:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Before  amp; After - Fremmy trials warrior part</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-28 02:16:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why are spectral SPIDERS not a beast?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-26 10:47:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sorry about that. How to beat handlock as druid.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-30 14:27:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Saw it building up and decided to record it. Turn 7 wombo combo with druid vs handlock. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KieuhxljYrQ</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Here goes nothing.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-25 02:23:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First try on a 1 def account! 57 combat</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-26 00:18:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Progress after 1st month - 1 def everything 50+</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-31 23:36:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can someone quickly give me info about this?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-05 13:20:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm at work and can't check but I'm realy curious about the reqs for hard achieve diary in western provinces. Could someone list me the things needed real quick? :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>1 Defence progress - Everything 60+</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-16 23:19:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hey Jagex, I'm the man for the job and it's time for you to employ me.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-07 15:03:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right so I've been thinking this through and I've decided it's time to dedicate my life to OSRS and improving it to the game we all enjoy and want to keep enjoying in the future. Now I know there's this thing going on about hiring a new QA tester, well shit, I'll QA test everything possible. I'll be stabbing a goblin in the depths of lumbridge hours upon hours with a bronze dagger while using a new shield to make sure it doesn't glitch out. I'll be getting 99 runecrafting twice in a month to make SURE that this new runecrafting altar thing works 100% as planned allright? But wait there's more, if there's no QA testing left to do (yeah right, lmao, ofcourse there'll be testing 24/7 right), I'll just hop on Ash's glorious back and assist him into coding the god damn best new features you could possibly think off! Coding knowledge? Mate, I know the basics of C#, Java, etc etc I'm all set to learn along the road and bam I'll be a professional in notime! Community activity? Holy shit is this like a description of me? I'll be active on reddit, twitter, youtube, hell even Google+ if you find the odd person using it to make SURE we get all the information across that's needed to keep up a healthy connection with the community. Currently I'm living in Belgium but hey fuck this shithole, Cambridge is where it's at right boys? Damn right, can't wait to be laughing at the random questions we'll be getting on the Q amp;A streams and boy o boy am I looking forward to telling Ronan how beautiful his hair is looking today as he steps into the office. Hook me up boys, I'm your man. See you soon! EDIT: I considered taking a look at the actual job application, but it seems like the application is closed! This is the only way boys, now we wait and pray.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Welp boys, we dun goofed!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-08 21:42:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So this is legit right? So OP.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-19 19:58:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z4ceKJgY8aE Using AHK to make super combat potions. Seems 1:1 right? This feels so OP when using. /// CODE \\\  amp;:: Click right return  #233;:: MouseMove 0, 70, 1, R return ":: Click return ':: MouseMove -50, -70, 1, R return</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>10 Defence progress - Everything 70+</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-25 12:19:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>AHK-script for anti-venom+ [Still 1:1, very OP]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-25 16:24:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi, so I just finished this script which basicaly makes anti-venom+ super fast. The code: http://pastebin.com/cvgSx2SQ Sample video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GLFb6d466DY So I start with A Z E twice to withdraw the ingredients, followed by P O I to close bank and go to inventory. Then I spam Q S M L to make the potions, each iteration adding 1 to the counter so I can change the MouseMove action at the end of each row to go to the next row. Then I manualy make the last pot while going to the bank to repeat the process. So what do you guys think? Clever use of 1:1 AHK or abusing 3rd party software?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So this guy just came in with cannon...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-08 23:43:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MildlyInteresting - Fremmy trials: Lyre performance text applied my herb level</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-10 21:48:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>MildlyInteresting - The troll stronghold exit has both a use and leave option</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-11 18:33:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>God fucking damnit...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-05 02:12:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sooo I had this great idea of trying to speedrun a f2p ironman to dragon slayer completion (starting on tutorial island). I tried flinching it with mith scimmy on 12 str but didn't work out as planned so I tried suiciding with an invent of wines to go with fire strike. But I forgot something important and didn't notice until making this highlight. At this point I realized I should just stop. http://www.twitch.tv/imheatstreams/v/5816332 7 hours well spent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The walk of shame...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-06 16:19:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is this what talented pures look like?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-11 21:08:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"Quality Time with Mog"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-28 02:58:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman progress - 1st month</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-30 21:28:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Went from diamond 1 promos to master without a single loss. 12 win streak. - Hi guys I go mid</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-19 08:14:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Went from diamond 1 promos to master without a single loss.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-19 08:26:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ended up with a 12 win streak. IGN is "Hi guys I go mid" https://gyazo.com/36db6ba4989569171e04bbeea948edac</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I hacked into a testserver again /s</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-21 13:48:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The power of graves jungle</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-13 23:58:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Been recently playing a lot of graves jungle on several master accounts in EUW. This is one of those kills that showcases the potential it has. For reference, check match history of 'Salll' on EUW. https://gyazo.com/2f7e5e6796583e1fb15051f90e513bf1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Carried 4v5 game in master with graves jungle. AMA</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-21 15:48:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great banter. https://gyazo.com/172b9e92e8b204e59fde54c811914bc1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Jungle graves highlight - Master soloqueue game EUW</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-11 01:25:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Showcases some of the burst potential with jungle graves. This is on my master account around 100LP, but I've reached challenger on a different account maining jungle graves. https://youtu.be/TJgLv9zgp2M</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why are easy  amp; normal clue bottle both green when hard is blue and elite is purple?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-09 00:33:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TFW you cba to fix something.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-18 12:51:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The tease is real.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-27 13:32:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I tweeted Ash about the nmz changes a week ago. Some info for the people that don't quite understand the points system.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-10 14:34:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When people complain about not being able to do stuff cause of bots.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-13 20:25:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>2000 =] Big achievement for me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-19 15:33:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[DMM] So it seems like the poisonous gas will cover THE ENTIRE area at the end of the tournament.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-23 18:31:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[DMM][Suggestion] Make every season unique.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-28 13:47:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think DMM would be very interesting if each season there'd be rules / restrictions set, unique to each season. Maybe like 1 season where you can't get defence experience, or one where you can't access a certain area on the map. Just a quick thought, feel free to discuss. EDIT: maybe also make the seasons shorter? 3 months sounds like a long time for something that you'll lose at the end which might stop a lot of people wanting to put in the effort</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is it just me or does the fremmy boots image look out of proportion?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-30 21:44:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Please tell me this is a troll? You had one job Jagex.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-03 12:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Screw the meta.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-10 15:40:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Proposed change to the arrangement of the bank options.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-14 14:13:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Suggestion] Xeric's talisman for lvl 3 skillers.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-17 13:02:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Currently, the only way to get to Zeah for lvl 3 accounts is by boat, and the continent is massive without any way of teleportation or travel apart from running. Compared to the mainland, this feels rather inconsistent as you have access to a lot of teleports. I think there should be a way to get the talisman other than killing lizardmen. My suggestion would be to offer it as a reward after completing 100% favor in all the houses, as this already takes a long time to get, and it's not much of a privilege to have one. I'm open for discussion or opinions on this one, but I feel like there's place for this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Suggestion] Change the points mechanic in MTA enchanters chamber</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-19 12:22:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Currently, the most efficient way to get points for enchantment is by hopping worlds and enchanting the dragonstones you find. The problem here, is that this method is the only way of getting decent points, but the area is heavily botted. Result of this is you're just competing against a hoard of bots to get the dstones, and you get prompted by the login limit quite often when you keep hitting empty worlds. My suggestion would be, to make other methods in the room worth doing over hopping for dstones. Make it high effort, slightly higher points, while keeping the dstones method in. If it inherits a somewhat difficult mechanic, as in the alchemy chamber, it wouldn't speed up the bots either. This way, normal players can actualy have a sufficient points gain when they put in the effort, instead of having to resort to battling bots over dstones. You might not think this is a big issue, but it's been months if not years that the area is littered with bots, and it's really frustrating when your main issue is having to deal with bots, which is more the case here than anywhere else as they directly influence your personal gains.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Literally unplayable</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-21 16:39:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sometimes items are animated caused by certain placeholders. Maybe this could be permanent? It looks nice.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-03 13:09:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>No it's not :(</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-08 16:20:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Now you see me... now you don't.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-09 12:26:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I like how the mods are on different streams at the same time. They really go the extra mile!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-15 13:34:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>OSBuddy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-16 12:25:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only Ironman - Intro</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-17 14:02:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rescuing M'lady</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-17 17:18:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-24 16:13:57</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;without actualy looking into the account rather than just the information on it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-25 12:21:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think those are immune to magic? KBD and Chaos ele should be taking damage from mage, they dont have as high of a defence as the others. Any source on this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-25 13:01:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm interesting, I'm doing a mage only ironman atm, I've tweeted ash/kieren to see if I can get more info on when monsters become immune to mage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-25 20:52:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Feel free to :p Just remember that there are alot of restrictions you end up with, such as no ancients/lunars/fairy rings/miscelania/... My current [stats](https://gyazo.com/8891b7a840efd7e2c145b230d93832a7) Also starting progress series, look for mage only ironman on youtube if you want to see when they come out ;p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-25 20:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right click the ingame report button and click "Report game bug".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 16:23:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>this gives a good option to lvl 3 skillers, apart from that I agree</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 20:23:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>but the LOL xD bO eh memes Cx</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Managed to get a person's right click options x3 when right clicking him after completing a rooftop obstacle simultaneously.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 01:37:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 01:54:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>There were quite some ideas in the post. I'll put my reaction to it here (which got alot of support).  gt;**Easy** * Wieldable fishing rod, similar to barb-tailed harpoon * Feathered boots, lowering the fail-chance on rooftop courses * Archery trousers, to match ranger boots, robin and tunic  gt;**Medium** * Steel (t) and (g), to complete the trimmed metal sets * Golden hammer (possibly wieldable), purely cosmetic  gt;**Hard** * Elite black armor and dagon'hai robes, as suggested by /u/smexylure * Divine robe set, requires 80+ prayer, can be cosmetic or high prayer bonus  gt;**Elite** * Barrows ornament kit  gt;**New Tier** * Samurai armor as suggested by /u/NoSleepReader * Axe and pickaxe, same tier as dragon, based on the samurai style of the armor and katana (like third age suggested by /u/dsftgbujio) * New BIS strength bonus boots for 1 defence, for example +3 compared to the +2 of climbing boots (Waraji?) * Magic robes, requiring 75 magic and 40 defence, with similar offensive stats and weaker defensive stats than ahrims, also based on the samurai style  gt;**All tiers** * New tier of stackable food, much like purple sweets, healing 0-5 * Variation of spices, when used on raw food, the cooked version will give a relevant skill boost based on the type of spice upon consumption Edit: formatting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 13:46:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well you need 80 mage for them to be 'very OP', at 60 mage ibans is much stronger</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tedious Mage - Mage only ironman progress video #1</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 16:03:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 17:46:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty sure you took a wrong turn to get there in the first place, can't remember ever having to be there :p but yeah it seems weird</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 18:35:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It requires fremennik trials, which gives attack  amp; strength exp reward iirc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 18:42:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I'm staying 1 att 1 str 1 range :) I do get defence levels through defensive casting though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 20:21:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>:\^)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-30 20:57:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe you mean graceful? You get them by getting marks of grace on agility rooftop courses, and trading these in at the Rogue's Den in Burthorpe. http://2007.runescape.wikia.com/wiki/Graceful_outfit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-31 01:16:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've had this alot aswell, where I play 2 accounts in the same world, and I completely lagg out on one of them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-31 16:07:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>easily, and u only need 85 herb if you're going to boost +5</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-31 22:19:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought that place was dead now that nieve cave exists.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-01 20:53:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>ja want anders zout gij wel gaan woodcutten :\^)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-01 23:34:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>zotjes! kben favor ant hale atm me mn 95 wc :v</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Something doesn't seem right</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-02 13:17:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-02 14:32:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I checked my logs, [but I didn't find anything suspicious](https://gyazo.com/9a3bfcf522200029ef10ac17554f56c6)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-02 14:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>afking a 90 tree is better than afking a 35 tree, god forbid!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-03 01:56:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Support.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What even is the point of a summer special offer for bonds?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 13:27:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cause of the summer special, bonds go up in price up to the point where you're basically paying the same amount as you would before the special offer. So what exactly is the benefit of doing this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 22:57:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't mind me, just gunna cook some kawambams in arganoog.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm insanely confused and paranoid right now.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-07 11:21:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>So tonight at around 3 AM, I received a text message saying someone got onto my email account. Now this was my first ever hotmail account, linked to my first ever osrs account that hasn't been played on in years. All of a sudden I can't log in to a few very old osrs accounts of mine, and got the message another one got locked cause they suspected sth. Now these are all accounts I haven't played in months or even years, and have absolutely nothing on them. Haven't been touched whatsoever. At this point I'm confused but didn't think much of it, maybe I lost them a while ago or maybe I just forgot the passes who knows. But this morning I logged in on my current active account at around 10:30 AM. I went to check who's online in the fc, and I see my main account in the list. Now this is where I get insanely suspicious. I went and tried to log onto it, and didn't even get a message saying it was already logged in, and could log in without any issues. The account was where I left it when I quit on it, and has no value left + is f2p. Authenticators are still in tact, email wasn't comprimised and the password wasn't changed. Someone in the fc said they saw me online a bit ago aswell on the account. How is this possible, what is going on? I'm not an idiot that goes around doing stupid shit, the accounts I lost were very old without anything, pretty much dead. I'm just very paranoid about seeing my main in the fc, without really having it comprimised in any way. Is this a graphical glitch? What's going on. Let me know if anyone has experienced anything similar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-07 13:19:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think 9 EST is exactly the same as 3 AM CEST.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-07 14:21:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know why this is relevant? Like I said the accounts I cant get on are very old accounts that I dont use and dont have protection. All my active accounts have every single best protection apart from bank pin which shouldn't be needed, and they aren't compromised. The only confusing part is that I saw the name of my main online, while nothing about it is compromised and I had no problems logging into it, with password and authenticators still in place.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tedious Mage - Mage only Ironman - Episode 2</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-07 14:29:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-07 14:42:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great to hear! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-07 15:04:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>As you can see I already have ahrims top, so yes, ahrims isn't too difficult to kill :p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-07 21:09:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like having my att,str,range at 1. I know it limits me out of alot, but otherwise it wouldn't really feel like mage only to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-08 19:45:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>#ModTractor2016</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-11 01:29:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Makes alot more sense like this. Support.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-11 16:19:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Need 72 mining for that in the first place.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-11 16:24:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>nor is another 100 nuggets</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-11 20:33:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah its 1/(500-monster HP)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-12 00:15:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Come hang out in "Iron Faux' friend chat, lot of helpful and friendly people there :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-12 01:34:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, I don't know you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-12 12:58:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gratz Kevin :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-12 16:09:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>nmz prod :\^) gz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-12 18:32:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but they don't get assigned.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-13 21:00:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>hahaha big xD never seen before LOL great banter !!1!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-14 19:47:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-15 01:36:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>This happens so often, for months now. Even when I have 2 accounts in the same world, one would just randomly stop doing anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-15 13:00:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never play on US worlds, always happens on UK/GER worlds for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-15 14:48:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>thats not how it works  gt;The chance of obtaining a clue bottle of any difficulty is 1 in [X/(100+Y)], where X is the base chance and Y is the player's fishing level. For example, a player catching anglerfish at level 99 fishing will have a 1 in 395 chance of obtaining a clue bottle, with decimal values floored.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-16 22:07:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am in favor of wieldable fishing rods / hammer, but I think they should come from something else, rather than just randomly putting stuff in zeah for the sake of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-16 23:00:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>some skilling minigame based on stealing creation wouldn't be too bad i think</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-17 15:13:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>But why</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-17 15:24:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>what's so bad about having to open notepad? takes as long as going to the notepad tab you'd want</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-17 15:41:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't feel like there's a need for this to clog up more of the UI, personally never felt like 'wish i had an ingame notepad at this point'.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-17 16:17:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>that's how social media work for anything, if you want to solve it yourself you're always free to do so</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-18 00:29:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>cons is hardly a grind, and anyone with a decent acc will have the money for med lvl construction, also gotta remember you're able to build stuff 8 levels under the requirement</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-18 14:50:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>you cant make spicy stews on lvl 3 comb cause of the quest reqs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-19 12:08:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>tags won't affect exp rates cause you still have to withdraw all, people wont bother using tags for skilling cause they put everything together anyways, only if you'd be able to withdraw certain items in 1 click it would change things</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-20 16:49:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>throwback to no warnings in trade screen so you could pass noted iron off as rune, full guthans with leaf bladed spear, veracs with black skirt, ... good times</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 00:19:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>They should've clarified they're doing this for bot prevention. People are probably voting no just cause they don't see the point of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 00:59:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're not the brightest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 12:38:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have both Quest cape and Achievement diary cape, but I support this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 19:12:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Petition to rename red topaz to pink topaz.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-21 19:13:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe dice are used during death plateau quest to obtain the IOU from the guy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-22 22:59:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah like brutal blacks not changing dfh THAT much?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-22 23:00:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>hardcore ironman = rs3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-24 02:09:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>[pet chompy](http://2007.runescape.wikia.com/wiki/Chompy_chick)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-24 02:14:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think 4 more skilling spets would suffice, being fm, thieving, agility, runecrafting. Firemaking - Phoenix - Lighting fires. Thieving - Raccoon - Pickpocketting, pyramid plunder. Agility - Monkey - Any obstacle of the full courses or completing a course. Runecrafting - Wisp - Every time you craft a rune, maybe make the chance count per essence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-24 03:13:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>that wouldn't be very consistent in any way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-24 12:19:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>other skilling pets not coming from just 1 minigame activity, but rather most active training methods</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>UK left the EU with a margin of 2%. Jagex can't slow down green dragon botters without 75% of biased voters agreeing.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-24 12:51:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-24 12:52:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's phishing streams, same like the double exp streams. They link to a fake forums that'll phish your login details when you enter them. They use viewbots to get high up the list and get permbanned, make new channels all the time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-24 15:45:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not so much on about the outcome, more that for such a change they need 75% yes voters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-24 17:27:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's people saying they vote no cause it won't change anything, then there's people saying they vote no cause they don't want bots to stop affecting the economy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-24 21:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be fair, that's something entirely different.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-24 22:08:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who do you refer to as 'you guys' and why are they butthurt?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-25 12:16:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I made a similar post 2 months ago. [Mod Ronan reply in the comments](https://www.reddit.com/r/2007scape/comments/4c9t9w/dmmsuggestion_make_every_season_unique/d1hg7t3)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-25 16:37:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ironman .. Fe-male</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-26 22:40:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>if you look at last clue, I don't even think the yellow respresents water, just like the little parts u see don't represent anything, and I think those things will allign up at the end for the final clue</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 16:57:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>that was interesting to look at lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 17:01:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>To infinity and beyo^o^^o^^^o^^^^o^^^^^ond</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>These guys aint wounded, they just chillin'</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-30 14:02:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-03 16:10:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>but what do you expect jagex to do about this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-04 19:09:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>that was a jmod</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-05 23:27:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>unid herbs are the thing i still miss the most, loved that part of herblore where you could merch your exp</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-06 11:46:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>it was the easiest thing to anti-scam though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I have no idea on this one, help NEEDED</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-06 15:32:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Suggestion] Make bird nests go in inventory, rather than dropping on the ground.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-07 21:38:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Currently, alot of bird nests get lost cause they drop on the ground and despawn rather quickly. With woodcutting often being a rather afk skill, you miss out on many nests. I think it would make sense to have the nests just go straight into the inventory, much like everything else does (especialy with the clue nests now compared to the clue bottles from fishing). As an alternative, the despawn time on them could also be decreased so it's less likely to miss them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-08 23:17:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>you can fake email addresses though, just a heads up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-08 23:19:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's also [this](https://gyazo.com/178ec8148d6f028ebefb98a1f7227acf)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-08 23:26:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>just check [this](https://gyazo.com/178ec8148d6f028ebefb98a1f7227acf) lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-14 01:38:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imagine swapping RSPS gold + RWTing and then making a thread on reddit about your locked account.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Juicy reinhardt setup for my genji POTG</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-18 13:33:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-18 22:27:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>UIM's cant have butlers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-19 18:07:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>hey it's me, your irl friend</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-20 12:15:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>At first I thought you were the one on the right lol. Gratz.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-25 00:58:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nobody in this thread is bashing him, it's just memes and banter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-25 21:46:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>prob the 8th pet that was gotten by someone using their fc</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Genji team-kill</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-26 02:47:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Genji penta on the rift</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-26 03:42:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks to the guy who posted the genji skin! [Ry #363;jin no ken o kure!](https://gfycat.com/GrayDelectableBanteng)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-26 16:52:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>wtf is animal husbandry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-26 18:28:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>well wouldn't that be a better thing for a farming extension then rather than a new skill? doesnt sound like it would be an interesting one lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-26 19:21:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>but if they WOULD add one, what WOULD you choose if you HAD to choose</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-28 03:28:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>the video is blocked for my country for some reason lol, screenie from setup?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-30 17:19:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>So basically you're just clicking your mouse with a toe instead of a finger, how revolutionary</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-30 17:55:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>but how is this different than just putting your mouse on the ground and clicking with your toe?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-30 20:21:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd advise you to get ibans blast rather than slayer dart. Gratz on the loot though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-31 22:54:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Way ahead of you](https://gyazo.com/05a01e94ee8eb368d1859b6beeae8cd4) (in D1 EUW)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-01 00:22:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah [these are my most played, all on mid](https://gyazo.com/dcc0d67d00c077f9b99b144a8495c51e)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-01 01:12:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anything can work in up to high diamond or even low master. Or even in general any rank in soloqueue. Cheese is often strong cause people don't know what to expect, at the ranks your saying people barely have an idea how normal matchups work so it can easily work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found this old pic of me, don't know how to feel about this one.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-04 22:22:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-04 23:04:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>[yes](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CpBCuySWIAAATS3.jpg:large)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-04 23:36:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>omg i think you're right, didn't even notice lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-05 00:30:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>don't think ive ever been a mod on any server :p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-07 21:29:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a spicy one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-08 12:27:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>those are different people talking</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-09 02:17:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got MM2 PTSD from that "!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-10 16:38:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>apart from the fact that they literally announced they're delayed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-10 16:42:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>[here](https://www.reddit.com/r/2007scape/comments/4x1emf/australian_servers/d6bn60o)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-11 20:53:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>but that would be salty water you'd be getting though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-13 20:30:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>why would he cover something up that he's openly said he did, on top of him already having dropped maybe 100m stuff over time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-13 21:07:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's talked about it on stream a long time ago</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-13 21:10:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could be, I'm indifferent on the case, if anything I don't think he should do it, but I don't really care too much about it. Just stating what I've seen from him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-14 15:05:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's still one more hand than the average player.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-14 15:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>just missing a comma  gt;and you, what were you ...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-14 22:49:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well shit how do you know my password</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-14 22:59:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>If only you could do that ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-15 19:47:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's just that a big part of it is dead compared to areas on the main continent, where almost every house has its purpose, has some activity bound to it. Zeah for a big part is just filled up with empty pointless stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-15 20:04:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah, but CURRENTLY that's why most ppl dislike Zeah</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-15 20:47:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah i know, i dont have anything against zeah and i dont play currently, just pointing out why people say it \^\^</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-17 13:56:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL the payload heals you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-19 14:18:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess the 24 in his name stands for the amount of chromosome pairs he's got.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-19 16:10:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's playing hide  amp; seek, you're cheating in building mode :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-20 16:22:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree, but they probably should've thought about this at the start aswell. Either way it should be a rule imo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-22 15:51:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>set prices, like he said, as in a gigantic store in essence</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-25 21:11:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you do 70 agility on gnome course?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-26 23:48:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vlaamse world dan?  #175;\\\_( #12484;)\_/ #175;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-27 01:41:14</DATE>
    <TEXT> #175;\\\_( #12484;)\_/ #175;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-27 18:13:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, a clear case of harassment. Time to issue a bug abuse major.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-02 15:19:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's like saying you got 99 cooking in 1 second cause thats when u got the wine exp drop lel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Suggestion] Change of minigame hiscores lables.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-03 12:25:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-03 12:38:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>How are you supposed to know what LMS means?  #175;\\\_( #12484;)\_/ #175;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-03 18:35:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you wake up after a night of being a high rank ironman.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-09 20:47:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You called?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-10 14:12:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>not on ironman</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-01 22:58:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure, but that's no reason to DQ someone, hence why rules are made.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-01 23:01:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rules are made for a reason. Woox did not break any rules. They can ADD to the rules, for in the future, but you can't just DQ because someone did something against the spirit of the game. Why bother making rules if you're not going to follow them anyways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-01 23:08:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>As long as you comply with the ruleset made I see no reason as to why you would DQ someone for doing something within that ruleset. You can use this to adjust the rules for future tournaments, which would be logical as it's still a fairly new concept, but I don't think it warrants a DQ, especialy when it comes to such a big thing with a fairly decent prize.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-01 23:09:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the integrity of the gamemode, they need consistency and adjustments in the ruleset based on cases like this. They cant just go about and make decisions on the go every time. Have clear rules, adjust these while the concept is still somewhat new, to build up a strongly supported gamemode with set rules covering all bases.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-21 23:14:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Mage only ironman?](https://gyazo.com/7687e7adc200bd6e1692965e6688b757)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-27 19:31:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like toothpaste.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-29 11:57:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a mage only ironman, I need something like this in my life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-30 15:29:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 18:48:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>[And now we wait](https://twitter.com/ImHeatLoL/status/793147495455027200)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-01 14:39:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whoa gz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 21:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>and would not be used*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-06 14:48:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>gij leeft ook nog x-jes sander</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-06 16:12:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>DMM in 2016 LUL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 18:19:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL there's a subreddit called ironscape GZ</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 18:19:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL there's a subreddit called ironscape GZ</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>For those interested; Loot from 22k fire bolts @ Twisted Banshees</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 23:00:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>For those interested; loot from 22k Fire bolts @ Twisted Banshees on Mage only Ironman</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 23:00:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 23:10:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I dont have tome of fire, let alone burnt pages, on my ironman.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 23:12:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah, that's mage's book.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 23:39:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd say around 600. Keep in mind fire bolt isnt the best to kill these, with decent range you'd get 1k+</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-12 00:09:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah srry didn't price check and banked everything, back at them with more runes now. :x</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-12 00:23:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>i think about 25 hours, very rough estimate though, didn't really keep track of time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-12 01:28:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didnt gain any levels, but I got like 80% of 97 - gt; 98 i think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-12 01:37:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>happens to the best</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Didn't know Lynx Titan had a girlfriend.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 23:26:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Call it a hunch</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 19:22:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-21 21:27:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-24 11:55:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Should be next week](https://twitter.com/JagexMaz/status/801735351580684289)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-24 12:43:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uhm yeah, they're not going for the feel of accomplishment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-24 12:58:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>If that's not what it's doing then what does it do?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-24 13:00:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>How about making it 100% spec and draining the enemy defence by 2x the hit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 13:47:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ice trolls are great, but you need to go to a spot where the guards north of neitiznot are fighting them. Then you can just attk them while out of their aggro range. You probably went to the wrong spot. :) Apart from that the other suggestions are probably the most common places to use fire strikes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 15:46:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Completely agree, the only thing that I think might be an issue is that when someone comes down the ladder and takes a hit and leaves, would make it so the ironman doesn't get the kill. Unless I'm missunderstanding the mechanics.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 20:32:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>1/10 effort on the cropping of that character</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Suggestion] Move the MTA points overlay so the XP counter doesn't overlap it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-25 20:36:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wonder what she puts in those sandwiches.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 09:44:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Suggestion] Change the point system for the MTA Enchantment room.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-29 18:29:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right now the only feasable way of obtaining enchantment points is hopping worlds and picking up the dragonstones. The problem is that this place is riddled with bots and you pretty much have to try to work around bots to be somewhat efficient at getting points here. It would be nice if actually properly playing the room, using the blocks and such, would be a better way of high effort high points gain, rather than having to compete with bots over the dragonstones. This has been an issue for years now, cause it's such an easy to bot activity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 09:59:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been chilling on rs3 for a few days doing divination on the side now. I have to say the game has a nice feel to it, runs ALOT smoother than osrs, even on max settings. No need to hate on either version :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 10:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah that was me. :c</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 10:54:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I play on the jagex client on both versions if that's what you mean.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 11:01:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>RS3 runs smooth as hell, I play league on max settings with 200-300 FPS, but osrs runs like a wheel through mud  #175;\\\_( #12484;)\_/ #175;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 11:52:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can the MTA Enchantment points be made more consistent to get? Right now it's very dependant on bots and I feel like that's not how it should be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 13:51:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah i'm aware of that :p it's a shame really</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 14:10:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>But there's no zeros there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 15:29:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes you are retarded, but you're probably just looking at the messages, you're just seeing the other guy's name, OP's name is way at the bottom ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 19:40:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>No worries, I'm not one to be pissed over such a trivial thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Loot from 10 minutes of MTA Enchantment room.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 21:11:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 21:40:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's like impossible if you have a full time job to do this properly lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-06 13:46:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, you could also start of by not hoarding any useless quest items :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-06 13:48:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Calm down now mr wyvernspwner</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 21:05:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>one month actually</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-08 10:39:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spicy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-13 14:53:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I found Hardcorn pretty clever/original :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-13 16:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-14 12:00:52</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;ok  gt;ok</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-17 23:13:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just cause it's single combat wont make it any better for solo players.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-18 15:40:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Season late on this meme bud</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-19 11:36:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>U laggin?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-19 11:38:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck am I looking at lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-19 11:42:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're trying to do 2 things that have nothing to do with eachother, and you're also not understanding how this would actually be used.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-19 16:52:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The real end game is getting front page and RWT to get banned.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-19 23:45:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>The shotcalling in that RoT F2P fight is so insane.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 13:38:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then there will only be RoT players left and people that didnt log in until the final hour.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 17:06:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also charging some sort of staff with it to get x amount of casts that are strong vs demons.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-24 10:19:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/cracktheclue the plot thickens</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 10:34:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agility potion hidden damage boost vs Zulrah?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 12:37:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I know, just pointing out he's a pleb.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 14:03:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tobias can.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-01 19:13:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>it will</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Don't know if this was known before, raids update will come with a new single-combat lizardman shaman spot.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 18:25:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 18:28:13</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Don't know if this was known before Ok thx</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>No longer possible to reset stat boost by logging out and back in.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-05 15:28:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 15:54:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Changes to smite prayer mechanics remove the ability to prayflick" would be a funny title to read tomorrow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 11:04:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>where?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 15:58:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favorite part is the report button saying 'Snitch'. Ngl though I'd love to play that haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-14 22:53:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the hover texts for prayers are just a bit of a clusterfuck overall. My suggestion would be to make it something like followed: Level 77 - Augury Magic attack +25% Magic defence +25%</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 13:05:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've played 100+ games in master/chall this season and it definately happens alot even in higher elo :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 16:01:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>And the #1 UIM for Vet'ion, Venenatis and Callisto is all the same guy :p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 11:35:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>well tbf he's not saying he created skull tricking, just the skull tricking using the skeleton</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 13:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Again, as adwaam said, he's not implying he conceived skull tricking, just the branched off version on the skeleton, which COULD be possible. I don't know jack shit about it, just saying that you're defending a different point than he claimed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 16:52:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god I found mine aswell : [Link](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=njYm4VSOaxM)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>And so it begins.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 19:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 15:34:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>something engine-related</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My take on hiscores categories. Note I used a placeholder icon for the clues section + I added the stats graph for overall.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 18:12:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-27 10:25:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was just a quick mock-up with inspect element. It's not like it's any drastic changes to the code, just a bit re-organized.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Suggestion] Ocean Kraken skilling boss</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-28 13:27:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>So this is just an idea that I went to sleep on yesterday and I thought I'd share a general idea on it. Citizens of Piscarilius on Zeah have constructed a ship to set sail and look for distant fishing environments that they can set up camp at. They're looking for adventurers to join them on the journey to aid them in possibly challenging situations. As you leave the docks, shortly after the crew notifies everyone on board that there seems to be something attacking the ship. This is where the battle starts, as it seems that there's a huge kraken clinging his tentacles around the ship. There's 2 ways of helping out to defeat the kraken. You can run bellow deck and look for items in supply crates to help construct cannons. These cannons can be loaded with either harpoons or fishing explosives and can be put both bellow deck as on deck in certain spots. Making the cannons would require 40 smithing, loading harpoons 40 fishing and using fishing explosives 32 slayer. As the kraken swipes his tentacles you might get hit for a %health much like at wintertodt. By shooting the cannons you will weaken the tentacles until eventually the kraken will forfeit and let go of the ship so you can continue your journey. Once you've been able to overcome the attack, the crew will decide the ship is too badly damaged to continue on the journey and will retreat to Piscarilius shore to repair the ship. This'll leave you with some bonus fishing / smithing experience dependant on what you've helped with on the ship. There should also be some minor loot you can receive, which I'm not sure what this should be so I'm open for suggestions. One thing I think would be nice to add as a rare drop would be a fishing rod add-on of some sort, which when added to a fishing rod will improve fishing much like the dragon harpoon does. So yeah like I said I was just thinking of this, it's a very random broad idea I've got and any suggestions are welcome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 10:48:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Barb fishing definitely doesn't need / won't get a buff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 12:55:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not too bad with tithe actually.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 12:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Get 99 magic - gt; 50 combat - gt; PC 99 HP - gt; Other combat stats one by one (STR - gt; ATT - gt; DEF I'd assume with range whenever)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 14:05:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only if it's animated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 15:44:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I wasn't thinking about being able to just continue ranging after 99 that's why I did it like this. That's probably the best way, that is if he has the money to get 99 range with cannon (I dont know how much this costs).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 10:51:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just call them 'Dragon', with nothing else to it. They're the OG's.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 15:02:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 16:01:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't read this and I definitely won't, but I can see you have put effort into this and it probably makes sense so support +1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 10:04:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Doesn't make any sense + would probably clip the fuck out if they'd try to combine the 2.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 10:08:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tried to do tutorial island - gt; dragon slayer completion on ironman once. Didn't quite work out. [Link](https://www.twitch.tv/videos/5816332)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 15:09:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just remember that they once said something about how the engine works when you want to make an item combined from 2 others. Either way it's make 0 sense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>99 Magic on my Mage only Ironman</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:15:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>99 Magic on my Mage only Ironman</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 22:15:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-04 09:38:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mostly from crafting (orb charging / alch) + slayer / general combat + mage training arena</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-06 09:27:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>You not lucky.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-08 20:20:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Like so](https://gyazo.com/6130ddc64a87a0f3af4bf006e5612ecc)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-09 16:10:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Crikey</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-09 16:12:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's LIT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 15:50:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vuile vieze khhankerleier</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 16:23:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>or dont die</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mod Smash</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 16:31:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 22:30:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>jokes on u, i have an azerty keyboard</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 09:44:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think there's much reason to kill him, even if you're high level, unless you're an ironman or going for pet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 10:23:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>You get those from zulrah/wintertodt aswell</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 16:20:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>psh, you're clearly not oldschool enough</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 21:31:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe that's just how they like to play?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 10:26:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>How about we divide it into 4 "houses" and have each house be a square?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 11:35:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any reason as to why we'd not have the cyclopse drop the next defender without having to re-enter? I feel like it's fairly pointless unless there's a reason for the code not being able to do so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 13:08:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean I guess so, just for collection sake then, it's not realy worth using over other off-hand slots on accounts with limited def</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 13:09:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>One could only dream of a different way to obtain bulk bstaffs on ironman apart from hopping shops. This'll help a bit though I suppose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 13:18:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 14:48:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even so, you'd need varrock elite diary done, which requires very high stats in other skills. Then it'd still take another like 140 days to get enough battlestaves for about 85 crafting. Now I don't want to sound like an ironman bitching about it being too hard, I've got 87 crafting atm on my ironman, using even worse methods than others because I have a limited account build. The main annoyance while trying to get bulk bstaves is from the login limit that triggers quite easily when hopping to buy. Just wanna say it'd be nice to have a different sustainable method to obtain them, e.g. for seaweed you can buy from stores OR collect from piscatoris, buckets of sand you can buy from stores OR collect from sandpit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 14:52:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Back in the days, they were showcased on the page where you'd select low detail or high detail before loading up the game in the browser.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 14:57:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I know about all those. Maybe I'm just looking for something else cause I've such a limited acc build (IGN = Rank 1 Mage, don't have access to zulrah / lunars / most diaries / ...). Just making the login limit a bit more forgiving would be a nice thing though :p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 14:57:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Put it on the wall.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 15:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, doesn't even have to be removed (cause it's used to stop certain malicious activites I think), just made a bit more 'loose' so it doesn't effect normal gameplay that involves hopping. Then again, this is from a user perspective and idk if a change like that is easily done/possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 15:23:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>100k+ was also yellow, instead of the current white. So you must've been a very big pleb then :p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 16:33:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't, sadly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 18:44:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>So basically only get membership in months that last 31 days? Surely this is a silly system.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 22:12:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just saying it's weird that you're essentially paying the same amount of money for less days? I'm not complaining, I buy membership all the time without worry, this post is just pointing out something that's odd imo. No need to be aggressive :p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 09:12:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Having a discussion =/= complaining.  gt;Now I don't want to sound like an ironman bitching about it being too hard, I've got 87 crafting atm on my ironman, using even worse methods than others because I have a limited account build. The main annoyance while trying to get bulk bstaves is from the login limit that triggers quite easily when hopping to buy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yay gilded hasta... :c</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 10:18:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 15:51:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>there's a difference between a client that just provides the game launcher, with tools outside of the game, than a client that straight up alters ingame mechanics/interfaces</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 20:35:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>All the combat I do is on defensive casting, so I'll get it eventually.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-18 09:16:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like to think my acc is unique. What's the purpose of an ironman with a normal build? :p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-18 18:01:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe they should make fossil island the shape of Australia, the forgotten continent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-20 09:29:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Skilling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-21 10:41:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's quite the gear you're rocking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-21 10:49:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd love that on [my ironman](http://services.runescape.com/m=hiscore_oldschool_ironman/hiscorepersonal.ws?user1=rank%201%20mage)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-21 15:08:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 13:13:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Getting hit by moss giant can be avoided, and stronghold isn't multi. So If you die doing either of those, apart from dcing, it is entirely your own fault.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Question about guthixian butterfly</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 22:10:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey so I'm a complete noob at RS3 but screwing around a bit to pass the time. Mainly doing divination on a lvl 3 acc, and I loved catching the chronicle fragments for a little hunter exp on the side. Now I did this random tutorial/miniquest or w/e it was, and the chronicle fragments are replaced by guthixian butterflies. These things are useless for me cause I wanna stay lvl 3 and just get some bonus hunt exp from the fragments. Is there any way to have it changed back to where I get fragments instead of butterflies while doing divination?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 22:22:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah okay, do I have to wait a week? Cause it seems to be locked for now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 23:01:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-24 10:20:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha instantly knew it was this clip without clicking the link, priceless</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 14:40:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>More like: ( #8226;_ #8226;) (  #8226;_ #8226;) gt; #8976; #9632;- #9632; ( #8976; #9632;_ #9632;) YYEEEEEEEAAAAAAAAHHHHHHH!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 21:51:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>u could have gotten third age 500 times</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 10:19:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice try with that phishing link smh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 11:41:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty sure the lines you said were as retarded if not more retarded than what the other guy said. Your capitalization of the title of this post also triggers me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 11:49:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>so do that on 2 normal accounts not everything has to become an official mode with a special symbol ironman was already a fun mode before they officialy introduced it, so why can't this be</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 11:50:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>No they didn't, ironman community before the mode was already pretty fun. But making it an official mode sure made it alot more mainstream and I'm sure they profitted alot from it. I don't think a duo-mode needs to be made, though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 11:52:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>He obviously means new thread in addition to the thread you're referring to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 11:55:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>In theory it sounds fun, but I doubt it would last very long compared to normal ironman, and imo we dont need any more 'modes' any time soon...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 11:57:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ehh not worth the discussion, nothing against you though we just share different opinions. Have a good one! PS didn't notice you were the same guy, just scrolling through threads :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 14:38:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>They had an unofficial ironman (self-sufficient account) before the mode. So did I, and trust me, it DOES feel like an accomplishment. Sure, it might not be 'official' and you can't show off to random people or whatever, but it's still the same challenge if you just do it on a normal account, and people u play with alot will admire your accomplishments the same way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 14:46:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>She could still get scammed by being told to drop stuff or w/e. And yeah sure, with an official mode everything is more set in stone, but how soon until someone will ask for group ironman? 2 man - UIM? 2 man HCIM? etc etc, we can't just keep making new modes every time someone wants to do something differently than the normal gamemode.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 15:21:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty sure most unofficial ironmen quit because of the official release, which in a way devalued their accounts even though their accomplishments weren't neglected before. I'm not saying releasing ironman mode was pointless, it was a great bussiness move and made alot more people try it out that probably didn't feel like doing it on their own. But I think you've got to draw the line somewhere, or soon we'll be having 20 different modes, cause people will always come up with new challenges and what not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 22:31:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>The hiscores page can only contain so many modes before looking like a complete clusterfuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[MildlyInteresting] You get this message when trying to do the air guitar emote on the fishing trawler.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-04 16:22:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-04 17:08:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>it means MELEE phase - gt; Pray whatever it says behind 'pray'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-04 18:25:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>no I can do all other emotes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-04 20:18:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-05 11:28:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah skill cape emote also doesn't work. didn't have one on me at the time so I didn't check that one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-05 18:54:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post is actually pointing out that the videomaker is in on the scam.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-06 21:19:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great idea (although mta is far from dead content imo).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 13:46:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Couldn't agree more. I've done loads of stuff on my ironman, I'm mage only and have over 16m mage exp, and having a rune pouch would've benefitted me in alot of situations. But I don't like the fact that I'd have to boost kills in order to get it, cause I think it's BS for ironmen to be able to do that, so I simply don't get rune pouch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 14:19:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go do it on normal accounts. Don't need new modes for every different challenge someone wants to play. This has been suggested several times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 14:43:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just make a new account? What's the point of having someone spend time to provide you with useless information just for the sake of it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 14:44:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah neither are KBD or KQ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 16:09:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok but just a heads up: this is not jagex customer service, but reddit. Not the place to find such trivial information I'd say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-07 16:09:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-08 09:36:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>B A N K P I N A N K P I N</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-09 11:26:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why are all the names censored apart from one time lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 20:34:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you have 2 step on the email?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-11 16:16:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>whips (and i think dragon items) in north middle part of park (at the fence thing) and the superrares (phats etc) north of fally</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 09:10:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Used to pimp out a new ride each day on RobotRage before loading up RS.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 20:43:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>not really seeing as he maxed his comb stats he can just do random pvm or whatever while hes getting his other skills up to the same level</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 21:30:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-14 11:43:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about the mr no sleep copy pasta</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-14 11:47:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>hah bless you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-14 11:50:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like a challenge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-14 16:10:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yikes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why do they want to paste The Inferno randomly to Zeah again, instead of adding it to the current TzHaar area that is very much open for expansion?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 19:45:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 19:54:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>They don't have to be though. Surely they're more related to the TzHaar area (considering they require a fire cape to take on The Inferno challenge) than Zeah? The other part of the city might be deeper down into the karamja volcano, where no1 has ever gone before because the TzHaar's were guardians of the city, but since you gained their trust they allow you to venture further into the volcano discovering the Kahlith tribe. Surely that sounds more suitable than 'oh lol another new random lost tribe at Zeah somehow connected to a distinct area on the mainland'.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 21:38:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>they should really improve the current state of Zeah, by adding lore and questlines to it, rather than just adding new areas each time that completely stand alone and have no correlation with the rest of the continent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 21:41:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>A small expansion to the fight Cave - gt; a new area discovered upon further venturing down the karamja volcano after being trusted by the TzHaar tribe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 21:42:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can play the game without ever really needing to do anything / go anywhere. I don't think that warrants plomping down such characteristic content in a non-related area.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 21:45:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not arguing with your opinion, arguing with that statement. It shouldn't be the reason why they're doing it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 21:52:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>How is an entire new area to be explored not standalone content? Standalone doesnt mean being put somewhere as a seperate piece on this map.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 21:59:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every single bit in this update screams correlation with TzHaars. They presumably use tokkul as currency, cause that's being offered from both the skilling activities. They require a fire cape to convince them of your worth. The outfit you can aquire boosts damage done with obsidian weapons. It makes so much sense to be an addition to the TzHaar area, it's a joke that this would be put so far away from the origin of this content.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 22:04:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Expansion of fight caves didnt pass - gt; so make it an entire new area underneath the tzhaars, previously guarded but as you gain their trust they let you procede. Makes no sense to randomly transit the entire idea onto Zeah just for the sake of cramming content onto Zeah.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 22:07:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you always do that little twirl on the way?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 22:16:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do agree to some extent with the points you're making. In my opinion it's like they have 2 pieces of a puzzle that just need to be put together (there's always been room for an expansion at Tzhaar as shown) and they're trying to force the piece into a different puzzle where it doesn't belong. I think you make a very good point that if they do want to put it in Zeah, it should be more unique in the way that's it not completely related to TzHaar's as the current proposal is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 22:30:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can the dev blog of The Inferno be revisited? I think the correlation with TzHaar, and the fact that there's very much room for expansion in the TzHaar area ([Relevant](https://www.reddit.com/r/2007scape/comments/5zl9q5/why_do_they_want_to_paste_the_inferno_randomly_to/)) makes it the most logical thing to implement it there. Thinking of: new area to be explored underneath the TzHaar area that has always been guarded by the TzHaars. But as you gain their trust they let you venture into the depths of the volcano, where you find a new tribe (the Kahlith). And then expand from there on with the current ideas laid out in the dev blog. Edit: I know it's been polled before as "an expansion onto the fight cave", but this is entirely different, as it's not just added on top of fight cave but it's an entirely new area to be explored, effectively making it standalone content.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 22:32:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Expansion on Fight Cave minigame =/= completely new area of a different tribe imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 22:42:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I doubt it would be a big problem code-wise, as the fenced off area has no interaction with anything else, the NPC's near it are just telling players they can't pass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 23:01:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Relevant Tzhaar City map on RS3](http://vignette1.wikia.nocookie.net/runescape2/images/a/a5/TzHaar_City_map.png/revision/latest?cb=20141210200743)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-16 13:44:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just cause they paste a big new area to zeah doesnt mean it improves current zeah, you'll just have to walk through the same empty and soulless zeah to get to the place u want to go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-17 13:08:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>$u(|{ My [)!(|{</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-17 13:39:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>**TOGGLESCAPE**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-17 20:09:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>**WE** **DID** **IT** **REDDIT**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-17 20:15:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for listening!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Could we make this happen if it's not too big of a job?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-17 23:04:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-17 23:28:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>For those that seem to be missing the point, I moved the skills so the Total level box is more alligned and the top  amp; bottom bars are also more symmetrical.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-18 00:03:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can see your ocd doesn't apply to your writing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-18 00:04:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe it'd be even better to increase the small gap in between each of the skills so that the entire area is nicely filled up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-18 13:43:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-18 16:34:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's talking about the slayer cave in relekka  amp; the slayer tower.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-21 16:51:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>The drop rate for any unique is 1/128 though, but yeah I agree.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 12:52:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why though? You're only going to spend them when you're at a slayer master so why do you need to know how many you have at random times?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 16:36:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you also run around with your cashstack all the time to plan how much cash you're going to invest into the next skill or how much you need to buy your next gear upgrade? Pretty sure you only check your cashstack when you're at a bank.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 19:03:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go get em champ. http://i.imgur.com/SJgRTzs.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 11:04:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>'Would help tons' seems like quite the exaggeration. And your final comparison doesn't make too much sense. The change there was going from multiple chat options to a faster right click option, but at the end it still worked the same way, you still need to bring the item to check. Also, knowing how many kills you have left on task while doing task is surely more valuable information than the amount of slayer points you have stored, as it directly impacts your current activity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 11:14:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 13:12:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>How dare you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-23 14:22:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Saw this happen a couple of times in previous seasons aswell :p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 13:58:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this the new way to farm karma?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 21:33:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>M E T A E T A</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 11:32:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Match aswell</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 11:35:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want this zapdos now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 10:21:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's an old meme but it checks out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 10:31:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>The classics :D Gratz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 13:12:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 13:12:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 15:37:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>That beautifull wall west of varrock bank.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 15:38:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>So don't go from edgeville to the fairy ring! :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 16:13:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>FeelsOhWait #178;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 10:25:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>When the snake popped out I was like oh shit he's fucked, seconds later he's twirling the bastard around lmao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 11:22:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>How did you manage to type it different again here lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 11:48:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the actual fuck dude</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 14:20:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've noticed there's a gap between 75 [Gargoyles] and 80 [Nechryaels], maybe add a new monster for level 77 or 78 slayer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 18:07:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why not both! 77/78 + 95 + 97/98</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 11:13:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Having both gaps filled is an option :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 23:14:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Lincoln Park](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C8HXZXQXkAATbgf.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-30 11:46:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha ikr, I lmaoed my ass off at this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 10:18:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>wwel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-01 10:40:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>why do people want to be rewarded for not playing as much? that's the whole point of the game, accomplishing stiff by putting in the work</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-01 14:55:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pickpocketting men is like 24k xp/hr when u stop failing right? Do you know when you stop failing or have u already stopped failing? Sounds rough but looking forward to you completing that. :) gl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 15:29:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>rune scimmy on ironman is highly overrated and doesn't really go far at all</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-03 16:02:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>What I did way back on my unofficial ironman was questing all the way to barrows gloves without training melee, pretty sure that got me 50+ Attack and I then bought ancient staff after completing DT to train up to 60. Even if you don't do that, just buying a rune sword from the store will suffice and you'll barely notice any difference, getting 60 attack really doesn't take long at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-04 14:22:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>You mean dividing by 25 and calling it close enough</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-04 16:55:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Time to make a grandmaster quest that enabled Menaphos and unlocks a new better viable keris?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-04 22:18:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mainly cause the bank settings interface is absolute aids lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Faux risking his HCIM at mole</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 19:53:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 20:44:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>that was the best thing I've read in a long time hahaha thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 22:36:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Diary cape has a teleport to shantay pass, granted that's not available for most players</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 16:12:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>white:wave2:selling my respect  #8364;180 - subject4762</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-08 16:45:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>big if true</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-08 20:39:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>if he had full invent he wouldn't have been able to pick herb therefor not been able to roll for pet in the first place if he would roll succesfully on the last herb that would fill his invent, the pet would take priority over the herb I guess 1 way to be able to roll on pet and have full invent is if u spam clicked the herbs to pick quicker, cause I think it can do 1 extra pick after full invent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-08 22:28:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>"However, when skilling, the pet is prioritised over the resource gathered, where it will be placed in the last inventory slot available, while the resource gathered will be dropped underneath the player."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 10:11:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Closing doors was the shit man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-10 11:49:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alot of my coworkers do this and it bothers me so much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-10 14:36:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>#FAKE NEWS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-10 16:47:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems like the actual question is deleted but here's the answer: [Link](https://twitter.com/JagexAsh/status/682127301304279041)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 16:24:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most Valuable Parents</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 16:27:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was basically the only tactic allowed back when ironman wasn't an official mode yet. The good old days where people played within the set rules, rather than doing stuff like having people help, boosting pouches etc that go against the ironman spirit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 16:34:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Big if true</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 15:10:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Quite disturbing how some of the characters are facing the other side.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-12 15:21:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's also loads of streamers that have done subscriber giveaways and what not. It's a shitty grey area.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-13 16:27:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>[You don't have to find a decent Defender if you become the decent Defender.](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C4R7-x8VMAE9pQW.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-13 16:34:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>In my opinion now that there's (what I assume to be) a viable method for ironmen to farm mysterious emblems, they should make BH boosting against the rules for ironmen. Have it result in de-ironing/prevent the posibility of doing so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-13 19:44:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-13 21:20:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Give me a fair reasoning behind why my idea is dumb and I'll consider a discussion. Note that I'm not trying to bash ironmen, I have an ironman myself that would benefit alot from rune pouch but I value the integrity of the gamemode.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-13 23:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>not hard to find a good team to do runs with if you put in the effort though :) learning ba and joining the Casual Ba CC goes a long way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 09:50:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Self-confidence on the low b0aty</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 15:05:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>what?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 15:28:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>If anything it should just work like an antifire potion, not just be used on the shield to have the permanent effect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 15:29:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why did you blur out your defence?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 15:31:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, guess I misinterpreted that. I mean sure, why not. It's a fairly niche use though so idk if that warrants the need for a new potion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 15:48:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>right, u just caused confusion with doing that :p easier to figure out you're 1 def when it's not on your hiscores page</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 15:55:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's now directly implemented into the game, where you pay the dwarves to do the work that the clans would do previously.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 00:56:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah but there are plenty if you know where to look :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The ironman hate :( They got frustrated when I started boxing a shadow spider so they logged.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 09:27:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 09:59:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>2 mains in semi-max logged in on me but got them pjed by the spiders so I started boxing a spider and they started talking shit cause they couldn't get on me and then they logged</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 12:05:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's down the stairs [here](http://i.imgur.com/SzjXR0L.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 12:52:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>the full map is on the wiki page of wilderness :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 16:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I play a mage only ironman (basicaly staying 1 att 1 str 1 range). IGN = Magique</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 20:09:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah when I was 12</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 23:10:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like to think they made this especialy for [my ironman](http://services.runescape.com/m=hiscore_oldschool_ironman/hiscorepersonal.ws?user1=magique)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 11:27:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks sick!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 21:33:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now that mysterious emblems can be obtained through wildy slayer, can you make it so ironmen are no longer allowed (or make it no longer possible) to farm/boost emblems in bounty hunter? It goes against the integrity of the gamemode.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 12:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>*grabs pitchfork*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 14:44:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know there is a def pure (or multiple ones) with prayer that have done some jad grinding for pet. Not sure if any has gotten one yet though. either way that's pretty neat, gz :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 17:20:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like you don't realise how time works lol. Take it as being a 1.3m xp/hr method straight up, cause the activities you'd do during waiting time can theoreticaly be placed behind the time from hunter added up over time. So what would you choose if that's the given options, 1.3m xp/hr without profit and low effort or 130k/hr with profit and high effort?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 17:24:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're so thick. jfc</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 17:28:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just did and explained exactly how it works but you're too ignorant to even try to understand such a basic thing. So why should I even bother?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 17:33:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I legit can't comprehend how you could possibly say my logic is flawed when you're spouting absolute nonsense? You're talking as if you're going to be standing there waiting to collect your hunt exp. How can you not see that you're getting the same experience as chins IN WAY LESS TIME WITH MINIMAL EFFORT? You'll literally be spending 10x as little time on getting your hunter up as you would with chins, if you'd have a similar method for each skill in game you would max in 10x as little time. How can you possibly say it has similar xp rate just because there's a time in between the xp gains where you're not training hunter (YOU'LL BE TRAINING OTHER SKILLS).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 17:44:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just gunna hope you're trolling cause this is beyond retarded. It's like you're arguing that 1 + 1 =/= 2</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 15:01:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I' like to see more, but pls not in this format, cause this was utter aids lol. Way too many pictures + not in order.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 15:13:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It very often didnt follow the levels, like range lvlup 2 - 3 - 9 - 10 - 4 - 5 - 11 - 12 - ... (not exactly like that but u get the point).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 09:45:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's like every month there's a new iteration of rune memes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 10:02:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was the last Successfully Retired American Whale, they're now extinct :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 10:06:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uhm?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 11:57:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Expected better of you, sir.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 13:11:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would the cat playing on the account need a catspeak amulet to talk to cats? Or would they need a humanspeak amulet to talk to people?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 17:19:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's weird that they changed it to have 2 different wyverns, but they didn't put the boots drop on just the lvl 82 wyvern. Would've made more sense. Also, I realy want that arc staff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Infernal Cape</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 20:27:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-28 18:35:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>[this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C6GeEjDxu-U)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-28 22:19:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah go make a throwaway reddit to try to circlejerk about autumn elegy making valid points that you have 0 arguments against.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 15:48:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I suggested [this](https://twitter.com/subject4762/status/858290743017951234) as some sort of middle-ground solution on the case. Ash seems to like the idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 17:54:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thoughts about [my suggestion](https://twitter.com/subject4762/status/858290743017951234)?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DonationMan Mode - Day 1 Progress log</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 23:45:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 09:33:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Clever](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C4R7-x8VMAE9pQW.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 09:34:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, I can ofcourse still get better items from donations, I'll use whatever the best is that I can get.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 09:35:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll see if I can get somewhere by only taking items / resources I need. If it shows to be too hard I'll take cash and use it to buy store supplies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 09:36:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do not take responsibility if this happens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 10:49:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Can't kill yourself if you're already dead on the inside](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C4R7-x8VMAE9pQW.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 11:26:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I agree, decided to take cash aswell and just use it to buy stuff from stores. Someone gave me 10k and I bought some runes with it just now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 14:34:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>That will happen indeed, and has happened already today. But I don't think that defeats the purpose of the account, I'd say any donations are welcome if I want to get somewhere with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 18:10:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I respect that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DonationMan Mode - Day 2 Progress log</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 22:26:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 22:27:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>In case you missed it, here's the link to Day 1 Progress log: [Link](http://imgur.com/a/xzlAM)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 23:23:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Support</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 23:59:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're right, I can't find any screenshot either. Must've forgotten a trade somewhere I'm confused aswell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 01:10:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I think it's fair to be able to just buy random things that I need for quests from stores and what not. For the real grinding of skills / obtaining gear etc I'd still need to get everything from donations. So the cash won't really do too much imo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 01:11:34</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;This is not the place to accuse players of wrongdoing. Report abuse in game and contact Jagex for serious issues. Feel like sharing? Please censor names wherever possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 01:16:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It shows someone's name in a botting client. Could've censored his name to not try to make him out to be a botter. Indirect accusing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 01:21:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congratulations, well deserved!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 01:38:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's true, I did need runes at the time to do quests though. But you're right, and I won't be spending cash anymore on runes. Some big donations just came in and I'll be set on those :) Right now I think I'll be using cash to do stuff like unnoting planks while training construction and unnoting food while blackjacking etc. I think those are fair places to use the cash I get at.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 01:57:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>*woosh*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 02:11:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha nice one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 09:55:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>No I can only use those to get cooking exp. I'll drop the cooked food afterwards.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 09:55:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yesterday I played like 10 hours, during weekdays it'll be like 4 hours max per day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 09:57:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll definately show my character more when I'm actualy doing something that envolves my gear, but until now that wasn't realy the case apart from when I did the few quests with fire strike (as shown @ fight arena, don't realy have any specific mage gear yet)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 09:58:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I know, read the other comment I made below this one, I'll use it to unnote items during skilling where it's useful and I'll use it to buy stuff like rfd gloves down the line.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 11:24:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd say dropping it is the same as donating, right? :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 11:24:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only time will tell :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 11:56:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha, nice :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 18:16:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've actualy been given plenty of potato seeds by now haha, and alot more :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 10:02:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're right, and I've been thinking about different stuff all the time. I'll try to set out some exact rules by next progress log (this friday). Right now the way I think about allowing myself to do these things: - Use ore donations to make bars + use those bars for more smithing exp - Use grimy herbs to get herblore exp from cleaning + making potions Things I'm not going to be allowing myself to do: - Use herb seed donations to farm herbs + use these herbs for potions. - Use flax donations to make bowstring + use this bowstring for bows (I said before I would do this but I've decided against it). - Use uncut gem donations to get crafting exp from cutting + using the cut gems to make jewelry (so I'm only using uncut gems for the cutting exp).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 10:16:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only if this also applies to real life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 14:13:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would this apply to my donationman account? Alot of people have already chipped in cause it's a fun refreshing project.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 14:17:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I have spent alot of time at the ge, essentialy asking for stuff to help build the account. I also go and ask people for random quest items constantly, which don't have much value most of the time but I just need to get them from other people to stay within the rules of the account. Alot of people have personaly came up to me to donate stuff ever since I made the reddit posts about it, but there will still be moments where I'd be back at the ge asking for stuff. Would be a shame to have to shut down such a promising project, although I agree that alot of actual beggers are cluterring up the ge (alot of which are bots aswell btw).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 14:27:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I started saturday evening and my bank is 10m+ right now. Whereabouts is your bank? Just checking if I'm in the clear or not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 14:32:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good, feel free to donate some supplies :\^) #donationman</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 11:55:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>How about Crying Heaviliy on the floor laughing, or Causing Harm on the floor laughing, or Creating Heart problems on the floory laughing, or Considering Health insurance on the floor laughing, or ...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 11:56:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>we woke</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 13:00:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thoughts about adding death rune packs to the wizards' guild rune store? If that can't be a thing, the second best option is probably a Buy-50 option as asked by others.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 13:36:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>We got him cornered now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 13:37:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those are usualy bots that will hop when u give them 1 gp.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 15:58:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus christ he's trying to be so smug about it, looks like a total douche.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 13:29:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You dun goofed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 14:19:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, cause he applied it in the same exact situation: to create - gt; to created to find - gt; to found</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 11:30:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>why would you go east of ge for oaks though?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 20:46:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's 2 oaks right outside seers village bank</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 21:59:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah didn't consider f2p, although I think the draynor spot would still be better? Might be botted though, I don't come in f2p so not sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DonationMan Mode - Week 1 Progress log</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 22:40:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-07 23:50:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice, KC for the heads?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-07 23:55:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn sweet. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 13:48:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I'd rather lose my account after a long break cause of my own incompetence than having it at risk cause of flawed recovery procedures.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 13:51:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's a quick little fun fact for you: you can actualy use the official exp trackers and set '102' or something as level goal, and it'll start tracking towards the exp that level 102 would be. I do this on my mage only ironman with 18m mage exp aswell. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 14:05:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah you have to enter it yourself but that only takes like 10 seconds, which isn't too long seeing as post-99 levels take a bit longer. I just prefer the vanilla client overall cause of the simplicity, but that might be an unpopular opinion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 19:01:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh I'm glad you asked! I am in fact, a mage only ironman. This means that I have 1 attack, 1 strength and 1 ranged. Oh and have I told you I'm an ironman? Cause I am.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 19:41:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck LOL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 21:54:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't start one before it's too late. Look at my stats "Magique", realise I"m going to get 77-99 rc with bloods to have enough runes for 93 slay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 23:29:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did the first part of slayer with fire bolts that I bought with the money from crafting (im 88 crafting atm). Apart from the combat stuff I don't think I did anything special compared to normal ironmen. Long time since I've started the account aswell. Basically just got 83 hunter at start to make some cash  amp; get 1 glory to mount in house (cant charge glories with this build). Then got agility up with alching bstaves I crafted (to 85 crafting). Also did quite some twisted banshees to get pure ess  amp; herbs + seeds (mostly after I got herb sack from slayer).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 20:09:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I need this update on my [ironman](http://services.runescape.com/m=hiscore_oldschool_ironman/hiscorepersonal.ws?user1=Magique). Massive support!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 19:31:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey it's me, your players.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DonationMan Mode - Week 2 Progress log</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-13 18:51:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-13 21:14:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>The way I like to see it is that this account is a community project where people can invest into and I put in the hours to get work done. So I suppose those people like the concept and want to see the progress. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-13 22:17:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn't really follow a specific list but here's my quest list quickly thrown together in an image: [Link](http://imgur.com/a/5jkeN)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 01:58:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>But that's basically the same as making money and using that money to buy stuff, which goes against the entire point of this account.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 02:05:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Rules](https://i.gyazo.com/afa063d5b728422d86589b0ea31cf8d9.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 09:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can assure you anything I get on this account won't interfere with my personal account. If I ever do end up quitting I'll think about what I'll do with the bank then. Maybe like a big drop party or whatever, not sure as of now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 09:46:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd rather have it where everything that's in my bank is purely from donations. Makes more sense imo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 10:04:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was a fairly long one cause of all the quests I did, pretty sure next week won't be this many images but I do get your point. Other people have told me to make vids or even stream aswell before. That's alot more effort than just making screenshots though, not sure if I can put the time in. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 10:10:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You actualy did normal tzhaar tasks instead of jad?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 11:17:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair play, I take it you just did whatever you felt like :p Pretty much what I do aswell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 20:12:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Usualy my home world is 351 but I hop around alot. Feel free to pm me though my private is always on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 22:11:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey that's me all the way to the left in the red dhide.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 10:46:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, not quite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 16:39:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>This response was patronising and unhelpful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 16:44:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like how you didn't plan out the space needed to write runescape so the e kinda falls off. Reminds me from back in the days where It'd start writing vertical when I made it to the end of my paper.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 20:03:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really like the idea of this actually. Can't help but feel like someone will find an exploit for this though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 16:25:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>The competition is fierce. Who will get the furthest?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 16:57:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're going places, I know of someone else who started out closing doors and now he's rich and famous!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 15:46:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>and the most fun one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-19 13:12:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>You gotta decide man, either QoL or bug abuse minor. Can't have both memes at once.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-19 13:46:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>"From Benly: Nigger" ffs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-19 14:23:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's because you get in contact with so many people in x amount of time. Let's say we compare it to league of legends. In league, you get in contact with 9 people / game (assuming no1 dodges a lobby) and this will take about 30-60 minutes in total. Now on runescape, in that amount of time you might have been in contact with 50, maybe 100+ people. Logically speaking, you'll also run into toxic people more often because of this, and people tend to remember negative experiences more than positive ones.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-19 16:43:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kryptonite shards, long locked away from humans guarded by dwarves, just now available for the high level miners! Works like redwood, just find a use for it now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 19:59:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Noiz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DonationMan Mode - Week 3 Progress log</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 22:28:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 22:48:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's impossible to share progress on an account like this without having people donate me and ask what I specificaly need etc. You can see that already after I uploaded the progress logs of day 1 and 2. This way I'll be able to get places with this account while still having a 100% donated bank. The only times I went out of my way to ask for specific items at the grand exchange is when I need random things for quests. As far as contacting friends goes, not a single donation is one I've asked people I know for. Everything is given based on what people wanted to give themselves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 23:05:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I see what you mean, but that's kind of how this account goes. Just seeing how far I can get with having a bank that's 100% donated items. Ofcourse what you're proposing can also be nice to follow, but a different account purpose because that account won't really get far. (From the times I've been at g.e. asking for random quest items I can tell you there's loads of people giving you shit for being a beggar and what not).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 23:07:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's somewhere on the screen but because there's so many people it often stacks on top of eachother causing it to dissapear / be out of vision. Basicaly just how it works I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-21 01:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>This way every single item I have in my bank is donated the way I have it. Otherwise it'd be me 'adding value' to it in a way. So people would either donate cooked food that I can use as food, or raw food that I can use to get my cooking up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-21 09:34:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah the only reason I added it was because last week almost every person that got in contact asked what I needed. Just trying to avoid having to give the same explanation each time really.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-22 14:13:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just because you shouldn't doesn't mean you can't. (  #865; #176;  #860; #662;  #865; #176;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 18:25:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Believe it or not guys this is not B0aty" damn got me good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-27 14:06:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love these :D found the little bugger after a minute or two.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-27 20:23:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think a mute is better than a ban in this case. I'd keep banning for actually breaking game rules, not for toxicity in chat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DonationMan Mode - Week 4 Progress Log</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-27 21:49:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-27 22:03:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>A beginner's mistake!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-27 22:44:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I give the loot away to random people as stated in the rules. You also don't see it in my bank do you :p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 22:56:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah ok this definately needs a way around it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 23:03:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 23:27:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, but I think it's fair to say 'having zulrah unlocked' shouldn't be a requirement for a skilling outfit. I'd say this was an oversight that they should fix.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 19:39:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's a legend. [Twitter conversation](https://twitter.com/JagexWolf/status/869517954605608960)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 13:51:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Friendly reminder that Quint is the one abusing corp glitch + has been a known bug abuser for many years. [Link](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7hvmDXiJBm4)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 18:34:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with the start of cannon 99 range - gt; 99 hp with range, but i think it might be better to just get 99 str then into 99 att into 99 def. not sure though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 20:53:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>How come you guys turned up with this out of nowhere, with the only background you have is from botting  amp; bug abusing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 21:26:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just think it's weird that they popped out with this client out of nowhere. I know we've seen previous progressions of HD clients before, but I've never heard anything about this in particular.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-05 10:32:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>LISHA WHAT TIME IS IT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-05 12:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>As much as I'd like to play in HD, it's fair to say MMK's assumptions are based on facts and it's a problem system-wise, not something like ticking a box that says 'OSHD client is fine to use'.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-05 13:49:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's fair to say none of us have any clue of how bot detection works, or how these clients are built. As long as it's built in the wrong way meaning it triggers bot detection, obviously they can't say it's fine to use. I've already seen people say they've been banned by playing on it. As far as the 'rumours' you're talking about, that's more than likely referring to the fact that Quint has been a long time bug abuser/botter (crf corp  amp; pc invulnerability) and them coming up with this client all of a sudden without any information leading up to it surely does seem a bit weird. I think Jagex (or Mod Mat K, however you want to look at it) is handling the situation as best as they can.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-05 13:54:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>But that's the entire point, everyone has members access? Not sure how you interpret this lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-05 16:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't compare an undetected botting client with a client aimed at non-malicious activities. It obviously needs to comply with certain things in order to not be picked up as a botting client (again, we don't have any insight on what this exactly entales). I've seen different iterations of HD clients before yes, but not this one made by these people. Nor have they had any communication about this before release (new twitter acc, first communication was through a friend's promotion vid). Again, I'm not trying to pick sides here, just trying to say that it might not be as obvious as people think without having proper information/insight on everything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-06 23:44:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>These are the real life issues the community doesn't need to be reminded of when trying to enjoy playing their mmorpg. That's the beauty of an mmorpg, you can be whoever you want to be without being put into boxes. That's what you're doing with events like this though, putting people in boxes / "forcing" them to voice their opinion on a controversial topic they don't want to necessarily be confronted with in this environment. My 2c, I don't care too much either way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 12:30:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is your name refering to the independance day of mexico? Gratz on the loot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 09:52:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>LISHA WHAT TIME IS IT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We're in the clear!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 14:54:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 15:44:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, guess we're not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 20:00:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup  gt; https://www.reddit.com/r/2007scape/comments/6f0mmf/a_friend_shows_off_oshd/dieilzz/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>OSHD devs right now.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 23:22:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-13 10:21:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>No need for giant testicles. All he did was buy out feather limit, then put up a sell offer of a feather for 1b, then bought it from himself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 15:32:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>It increases your magic attack  amp; defence bonus by 25%, and your defence level by 25%.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-24 22:34:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would be a great addition for my cart ride only ironman. Support.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-26 00:14:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chances are he's part of those wyvern service cc's. Those people turn up in the wonkiest gear you'll see.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-26 21:49:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I tried](http://i.imgur.com/OYO6sue.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 18:21:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would you put a one-time drug user in jail for a longer time than a drug dealer?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 18:24:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It does if you apply a decent analogy though, which yours isn't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 22:25:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>ok</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-30 09:13:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>there's still new players that start as p2p u know</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-30 14:38:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>What sleep thing, homie?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-30 15:25:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Terrorism is a term used in its broadest sense to describe the use of intentionally indiscriminate violence as a means to create terror or fear, in order to achieve a political, religious or ideological aim* Idk man, sounds exactly like what DDOSing does to people in RS!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-30 16:11:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're literally killing other people in game after they DDOS them man, how is that not violence?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 15:29:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>LISHA WHAT TIME IS IT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 09:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>UNIDS *sheds a tear*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-09 11:24:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>How about just adding this little fella as the 'slayer skilling pet'. RS3 has some sort of gargoyle as theirs, it's not a buyable. People will argue slayer already has pets (kraken, smoke devil, hellpuppy) but if anything that sounds like a more acceptable idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 15:24:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah, these people usually tell you to add them. Then they pm you to go to a youtube video or w/e and comment on the thread in description.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 15:25:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 15:58:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm woke</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 15:59:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The thread is a phishing site looking like rs forums prompting you to log-in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 13:53:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds good to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 16:52:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking of lightning spells in a different way. [Something like this](https://twitter.com/subject4762/status/872852894588030980)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 23:59:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>LISHA WHAT TIME IS IT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 21:57:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>LISHA WHAT TIME IS IT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 14:36:59</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Dusty is just some mom Idk why but that made me laugh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 14:39:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's some insane players out there for sure. [Rank 1 UIM Slay/att/str/hp - 200m Attack - 1 Defence](http://services.runescape.com/m=hiscore_oldschool_ultimate/hiscorepersonal.ws?user1=Yumemi) [Rank 1 UIM Crafting - All done on entrana - also 200m agil](http://services.runescape.com/m=hiscore_oldschool_ultimate/hiscorepersonal.ws?user1=kepi42) [Rank 1 F2P UIM](http://services.runescape.com/m=hiscore_oldschool_ultimate/hiscorepersonal.ws?user1=disziple) Just to name a few I can think of right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 15:33:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>First you kill the mammoth, then the chaos dwarf descends and the fight continues!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 15:34:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Should be fixed now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 18:13:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>UIM, mind you. I think it's from running boneyard in wildy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 20:17:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's in the wilderness, running back and forth picking up bones  amp; burrying them. [Wiki](http://oldschoolrunescape.wikia.com/wiki/Boneyard)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 18:44:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>And we can offer them to the West Ardougne locals for 100/200 Blood runes!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 21:38:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm interested in your comparison. Will it be uploaded to both subreddits?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 21:52:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd assume so. You can make the post on one and link to it on the other aswell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 13:19:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty sure I've seen them there when I started my ironman, which based on my post history is back in june 2015.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 20:54:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>As an osrs player that's trying to learn about rs3, can u give me a tl;dr of what I'm looking at?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 21:05:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>And I'm assuming he's setting up for a hard voyage that can give great rewards? Or am I wrong?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 21:48:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay cool. Thanks :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 21:52:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>To add on to this, can't call while repairing a trap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 20:29:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well yeah obviously, but it'd be nice if you could call while repairing is what i'm saying :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 16:29:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>You mean [like this](https://twitter.com/JagexMaz/status/892025368256933888)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 14:48:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>By making the green slightly darker it's more distinguishable with the yellow afaik.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 15:58:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gotcha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-05 15:19:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's just cause u dont stand next to the edge, and u cant stand at corners. Simple as that lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 14:32:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh wow so the guy whose name I really want is a complete moron. That sucks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 17:00:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I know but it'd really fit my [ironman](https://gyazo.com/4003becbe0f40b6d99e9af0235ca33f3) :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-08 18:41:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, and if i remember correctly it's short for Thursday Afternoon Personal Project. Even thought the osrs team does it on Friday, they kept TAPP as the term cause otherwise it'd be FAPP. hehe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-08 22:07:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen alot of RS3 players asking for osrs updates to come in RS3 aswell, goes both ways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 19:56:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The attacks aren't delayed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 21:24:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not really cause I believe it has a 7 tick attack speed. So technically it's possible if u can swap to right prayer every tick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 22:52:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brother?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 23:23:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't remind me ;-;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 19:40:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>As far as I know, Mod Stone is their marketing guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 11:40:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>All they have to do is capture the UI parts seperately through OBS or w/e they're using and scale them up. It's so easy to do... No need for actual ingame changes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 16:47:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's on RS3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 14:53:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>but he did draw a hand</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 19:30:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you know: on RS3 the cooking pet is called Ramsay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 19:31:45</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Gooi op reddit  gt;Hoe werkt dat Haha :D sick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-25 21:24:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>So like wintertodt but 10x worse?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-25 23:21:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>wintertodt is super afk and there's no need to get rid of unwanted fletching products</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 15:43:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, [my ironman](https://i.gyazo.com/1d0a12c1420624795114c1cc977bb258.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 23:29:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>... fool ...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 23:31:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>AFAIK the number you see for RS3 is actualy both games combined.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 16:47:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well yeah but it's not that people don't want the rework to happen, they want it to be the one update rather than having a half assed addition right now and then having the rework of current content in batch 2. People already voted on the actual rework a while ago as far as i know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 16:49:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been playing as a lvl 3 skiller on a new account for around 2 months right now. Obviously not unlocking alot of the content, I've been enjoying it. A big part is still the same grind as osrs, but there are alot less tedious methods for most skills + alot of OP promotional content to partake in. Definately more focused towards end game (PvM I suppose), but it's enjoyable imo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 21:11:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi shauny, I'm getting another spammed task in menaphos: [You are half way to completing: Class Crown](https://gyazo.com/fe82c17dd2eb94b13d05db2fe5ac3b52)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 21:36:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>for real. My friend and I tried antiscamming with different stuff, like bringing fletch cape + bolt pouch but no1 took the bait :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 21:45:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>But "no" is passing for the M amp;S rework, so invention batch 2 will be released in 2020.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 12:56:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just sped up the process of losing the 1b in duel arena anyways</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 15:24:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell you what mate, drop your sgs then talk to me again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 17:59:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right click world map icon - gt; Skybox/Filters</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 21:53:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>ge moet op curtain gebruike, ni op u kat :\^)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-01 23:37:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's flemish, dutch dialect from belgium. Has some similarities with Afrikaans though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 11:59:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, as a skiller I'd like to see more tools to be available for different skills, now it's basically Fish/FM-vention only. I guess they're adding a divination tool if I understood correctly, so that might be cool even though it's basically just daily caches.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Used 2 deathtouch darts from the raffle on my skiller.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 12:22:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 16:44:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you think it would register for that? As I can't quick chat the kill count either (it's still at 0).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 16:44:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha sweet :D thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 16:45:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used 2 darts on KK, still kept 1 to do family crest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 16:45:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's worth 18.9m actualy! It'd be worthless on an IM skiller :\^)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 19:15:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I'm not 99 cooking yet, so it'll help a bit with that. I'm assuming cooking cape perk is u stop burning then?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 19:16:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>From what I've seen here they've only talked about a divination tool, but who knows, we'll see on release I suppose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 22:53:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>No what I meant is if loot from DTD would count, after the update, as the kill also doesn't count towards kill count quick chat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 22:54:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be fair I might aswell use the 3rd dart on KK aswell, already 85 cooking so it's not that big of a deal to have cooking gauntlets I suppose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 23:04:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah yeah good point, never know with Jagex though huh :p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 15:12:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>It only kills 1 phase according to wiki.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 19:18:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think what OP meant is people that are maxed on both games, as in 1 person having a maxed account on both RS3 and OSRS.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 20:00:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Comment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 13:54:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh fuck sake so it does actually work with DTD loots. :( I got an off-hand drygore long from 2 kills on my skiller this weekend before the update. Now I'm sad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 16:45:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not 100% sold on the main screen, but I REALLY love those swords through the skulls + the fire holders.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 23:15:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can see the guy casting the spells right outside the bank</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 18:47:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the greatest karma farm of all time. God speed brother.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 18:46:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>3 actualy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 18:50:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would most likely be about xp records.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 10:30:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's fine the way it is. Would look a bit silly if there was this 1 little circle in the middle of such a big open space.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 10:56:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You probably do, just not for damage done on the pheasants, but he's just splashing anyways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 10:57:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like the examine option on players in RS3? I really like that feature, I constantly find myself examining random players to check their outfit/stats etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 11:09:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only item name I've had was Beacon Ring, as it's my go-to ring on my mage only ironman. But that was kinda boring when you can't even see it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 11:14:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, but most don't diss them, atleast I don't. I'm a skiller too and since I get plenty of cheaper invention exp from fishing/smithing/firemaking there's no real reason to waste money on dissing d hatchets.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 11:25:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make them 2x2 safespottable and I'll be happy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 11:26:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is actually a good idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 11:38:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>But he won? I'm confused.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-04 12:02:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too, I got confused by this at first.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 19:15:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>making them 2x2 size rather than the 1-tile sized ankous so I can safespot them :v</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-07 09:44:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a good looking range</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-07 15:30:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>They actually did this for April fools</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 11:30:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think it'll reduce numbers of them to be honest. Maybe it'll put in a dent after release, but after a period of adaptation they'll be able to go through it and it'll be back to where we started.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 12:03:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>200% support. Would love to just have broadcasts from Friends/Clan aswell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 22:27:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>You unlock all previous rewards if you complete an event.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 13:56:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bruh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 14:00:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haxunit Roy rocking the lvl 3 fire cape :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 14:44:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh hey. For what it's worth, after reading the post, I personally don't think they should be banned for tick manip here as I don't really look at this as a bug, just a QA oversight that allowed a widely known method to be used. Yes it was mentioned in the release blog that tick manip wouldn't be possible, but that doesn't really make it a bug, nor would people know of it if they hadn't read the blog.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 20:42:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone on oldschool did this and got pretty far. [Stats](http://services.runescape.com/m=hiscore_oldschool/hiscorepersonal.ws?user1=SlayNCombat)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 11:37:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Killing imps in wildy gwd for ecu keys + alching random item (like air runes or w/e) while doing so. Has 60 agility to get in the gwd, 37 prayer to get zammy cape + monk robe as zammy/sara item. 1/50 droprate, alchs for +- 300 nature runes worth of gp so it's sustainable to constantly alch something in between + have leftover cash to buy combat runes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 12:32:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah pretty sure he's as good as done, arcane tommy started other acc cause he wouldn't make it. 2 others will be or are already DQed for scouting arceuus books on other account. Most if not all others are just lava dragon campers and won't get high.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 22:01:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>10x xp in KotS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 11:02:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fire strike imps, alch while doing so, buy more runes with the ecu keys money. Around 5000 mage xp per 30 second login session or so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 11:04:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>While I agree, it'd kill alot of methods people are currently using. But that's not a bad thing as there's plenty of methods to figure out. It'd be best to have it where it only burns off a minute if you've been logged in for  lt;5 minutes or so, to prevent people from having to do long sessions to not burn a minute.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 20:20:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Revolution, you can set your combat style to full manual/revolution/legacy. With revolution it uses the abilities u set on your action bar automaticaly when they're available. It's changed recently to be fully automatic where before it'd not use certain types of abilities automaticaly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 15:50:46</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;out of nowhere</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 22:21:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>just make it so you can only stake cash / plat tokens</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 22:19:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't watch/read the whole thing, but quick pointer that u dont always get str exp when pushing wheat on low lvl and it scales on lvl I think. I've got like 20 str exp on my mage only ironman while doing plenty of hours in puro-puro pushing alot of wheat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 23:27:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh yeah for sure, was just pointing it out cause u said somewhere he pushed x times based on his exp :P I agree completely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 18:31:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>stavfefe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[DMM] Congrats Manked</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 22:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 17:42:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>what do u mean? it was vengence, casted before he got hit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 15:20:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>His chathead looks like the flipped genie head</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 19:08:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got rank 2 magic, even if he did use alt for steel plates I'll give it to him cause thats still alot of irl time spent collecting them with +-16min spawn timer :') Oh well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 00:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm curious what it is, I came 2nd in magic so if it doesn't suit me I might be interested. Do you have twitter? DM me @subject4762 if you do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 12:00:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>But then what's your opinion on people like Woox and B0aty using alts to scout the % at wintertodt so they know when to log out on their actual account to get the best rates? They didn't get DQ'ed and gained much more from alt usage than Caboucha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 12:20:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't watch woox do it, but b0aty certainly logged in and out of his second account. Either way the rule also didn't state that the "alt" needs to be controlled by the same person. So using friends (or in this case viewers) is pretty much the same thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 15:44:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I know, I'm not saying Cab shouldn't be DQed, but they should enforce it on everyone then. And while todt is a group minigame, people like B0aty still pushed it for even more gains by using an alt to see the %  amp; only doing part of the kills for even more exp.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 16:35:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm impressed, very interesting read.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 16:57:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Following these numbers it's like 50k xp/hr at lvl 50 scaling to 100k+ at lvl 99. Sounds really good but you probably need a similar set-up like his to track etc and might not be sustainable for long periods. Probably won't change the meta but it's very interesting + useful for builds that already need to use library for early rc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 17:00:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>nvm, thats mage exp, rc is lower.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 17:13:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>We all know that's not happening.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 17:23:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the few Zeah Only ironmen out there, this is very interesting. Thanks for the information, and as #2 kots magic (#3 counting u) I hope you get the prize.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 18:07:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's realy cool, never seen that post before either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 19:04:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>- Got money from thieving (blackjacking, got rogue outfit, in hindsight not the best way) - Bought law runes (+- 3k total) - Used law runes to telegrab nature rune spawn at annakarl (1 Law - gt; 4 Nature from the northern spawn). This involves hopping between the 6 worlds and waiting on the respawn +- 1min 20sec to avoid login limit. - Mta alchemy room with the nature runes (which is like 1.3m xp/hr on kots)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 19:10:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Quite late on this response lol :) I've not done it myself but I assume he had zammy + sara item (he had pray so he can have monk robe + zammy cape from mage arena) and there's a way to be safe from the 2 others.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 21:31:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got 625k cash to buy +- 2500 laws at first, then got like 100k more or something near the end when I ran out of natures. Not sure on the timing anymore as it's been a while. I finished rogue set at 20h42m left, I think I finished first thieving at like 17-18h left and then finished telegrabbing at 12-13h left. +- 500 telegrabs/hr ingame.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 01:49:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are you doing? You literally copied my old post lol. [Repost](https://www.reddit.com/r/2007scape/comments/5e5kms/call_it_a_hunch/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 20:18:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or you know, it's a weekend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 23:59:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Woohoo we both win. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 23:59:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm glad I still get to keep my #2 place prize. :) Happily surprised by the decision made.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 16:30:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm happily surprised, now I get to keep my prize! yay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 21:37:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>but they do refund pizzas if you get hacked and your stack of pizzas get stolen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 11:53:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree alot on this. Pre-GE was so much fun, merching at vwest bank was the most nostalgic feeling I've had ever since OSRS got released. Back in the day all I'd do would be standing at fally bank merching unids, and that's what I did at the start of osrs aswell. GE really killed alot of interaction as you said, nowadays so many people are just trying to play solo as much as possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 14:25:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I play exclusively on the official client and I don't see any problems with it. The only thing that'd be nice is a metrics system like RS3 has (in essence just have xp trackers).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 16:50:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>No thanks. We don't need official modes for every restriction people choose to put on their account (I myself have a mage only ironman aswell with 1 att, 1 str, 1 range, dont need an official mode for that). Next you'll have official lvl 3 skiller ironman, official 1 defence ironman, etc etc. Please no more modes for a while.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 17:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>So essentially the same as any normal ironman account, just cant lose as much health. I don't see why this warrants a new gamemode honestly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-26 00:11:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks sick, the RC emote + hooked ones are my favorite :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-26 16:41:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Zeah only lvl 3 ironman - [Current stats](http://services.runescape.com/m=hiscore_oldschool/hiscorepersonal.ws?user1=Landmass)  gt;77 Runecrafting  gt;73 Agility  gt;99 Fishing + Cooking  gt;70 base stats (- slayer) Mage Only Ironman - [Current stats](http://services.runescape.com/m=hiscore_oldschool/hiscorepersonal.ws?user1=MageOnly%A0BTW)  gt;99 Runecrafting  gt;93 Slayer  gt;Find team for raids and go for kodai/ancestral</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 12:08:49</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Completes queen of thieves quest  gt;Notices there's a fire and a store that sells raw sardines  gt;Hmm wonder what'd happen if I buy some and try to cook them on the fire  gt;Oh huh that's weird, I'm going to screencap this and post it on reddit Something along those lines I'd assume</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 11:11:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 14:56:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think death mechanics should involve some RNG-based mechanic. Just make it so you have to pay a % or something to get your items back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 10:02:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to find a squirrel while picking up toy mice on my zeah only lvl 3 ironman. #MakeToyMiceGreatAgain</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 15:32:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's colorless so Da Vinci would smuggle it without using it, as he can't paint with something that has no color.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 01:04:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you do a search to go to a profile it won't have the user in the URL, but if u then go to one of the stat pages and click back to his profile it'll have it there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 15:48:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's nice and all, but I hope you realise that the deadline to send it in was yesterday. Still fairly well made though, I like the different style all the videos have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 15:57:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tweet of Ash [Slayer purposes](https://twitter.com/JagexAsh/status/945614010094899200) Edit: also Wolf confirming it [Tweet](https://twitter.com/JagexWolf/status/943121042108829696)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 16:55:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah makes sense. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 13:08:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mage training arena really could use some love. I've spent alot of time there myself on my mage only ironman to get full infinity n what not, definately some frustrating things to it. Some other small tweaks I'd suggest for the alchemy room: - Don't have the npc's with talk option wander near the cupboards - Have the cupboards open by default, the closing  amp; opening often cancels your action - Be able to perma ignore the warning message when reaching max cash in the room - As you've already said, be able to see the message of the change-calls in the entire room (to add on to this, would be nice if the price-table would update on the same tick as the actual prices change)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 13:15:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will wrath runes be obtainable on an ironman account without the completion of Dragon Slayer 2 (in any way)?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 13:28:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what I'm asking, if they implemented them to come from elsewhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 11:58:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've used vanilla client for the longest time, just using konduit for like the last week to track my xp rates on my zeah only skiller. Apart from the xp rate trackers I don't really feel the need for a 3rd party client (it provides loads of features that are nice to have but very unnecessary)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 16:51:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Still works though](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8fACNBAQdjI)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 23:57:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>partner slayer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 10:55:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah so he can use his alt to kill his task monsters after he did damage to them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-05 14:09:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would definately like to see dhc  gt; blowpipe on this boss.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 23:30:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>just give them both components back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 12:44:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>You definately just fucked up yourself, no reason you would've been targetted in any way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 13:00:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you enter your credentials on any site that looked like a runescape site?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 13:03:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>No not at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 11:28:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>The main counter-argument for Artisan was that it'd force people to do skills through Artisan to not feel like they're wasting time not doing Artisan, much like how most people would do combat through slayer nowadays (- afking nmz).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 16:20:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or you know, just remove him from the game. Fuck him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 15:28:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>On his new years eve stream, mod mat k said he'd like to see it being released late 2018. He said everyone's behind the idea of it, but it requires engine work which can only be done after the release of mobile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 21:37:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, and no message back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 14:34:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be rather silly as you can fail at making wine until level 68(?)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Long term goal completed on my Mage Only Ironman. Trident on 4 KC.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 22:23:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Long term goal completed - 4 KC Trident on my Mage Only Ironman</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 22:31:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 00:00:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Heh yeah, also no wrath runes, ancients, lunars, black mask, etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 00:00:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 00:55:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can't boost for trident because you can only kill krakens on task</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 00:57:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depends on what you'd consider hard. Combat/Slayer was ofc very slow with fire bolts/fire waves. Crafting can't be done with lunars so I had to manually make molten glass (+ cook seaweed into soda ash).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 11:16:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I made 2 vids a while ago but I quit shortly after the 2nd one came out and never bothered continuing when I started again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 11:16:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>It would be possible to kill zulrah mage only, but I can't get there because I can't do underground pass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 11:19:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Heh, low levels is a long time ago  amp; can't remember much. Started this acc in 2015 and took alot of breaks, but I know I got 83 hunter at the start for implings to make money  amp; get a glory for my house. I'd say the main thing is crafting for cash  amp; just runecrafting aswell. Killed twisted banshees med-lvl to get ess  amp; herbs/seeds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 11:20:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't think I will, it's alot of effort and I don't have as much time nowadays with work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 13:20:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've got ahrims top  amp; bottom. It's actually not hard to hit on ahrim with mage. Mostly used flames of zamorak, which also lowers his magic lvl by 10% or something like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 13:37:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks :) not quite sure, I think I was just trying to come up with a unique concept and just went with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 00:37:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty much up until like 87, last few levels from blood rcing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 16:17:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>All brothers, it's not worth killing 1 brother.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 10:39:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don't get amazing rewards, but it's still good enough to set up your account early on. You get like 800k cash + a bunch of low level supplies from lvl 99.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 11:10:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fun fact: you can use the official ingame xp tracker to put a virtual level as your goal. For example, you can give in start level 106  amp; goal level 107, and it will work with the exp you'd need for those levels.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 11:14:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome, hope I get lucky on this one once I get to raids</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 16:28:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>good bot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 16:28:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was honestly surprised how many bots there are in this place when I was getting some ash on my ironman</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 15:48:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really liked pre-ge, the trading/merchanting aspect of the game was very enjoyable even through zybez.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 16:52:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, I genuinly enjoyed it. I stood at vwest all the time merching unid herbs etc</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 21:45:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 11:18:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You mean like they specified in the game integrity post from [November](http://services.runescape.com/m=news/a=58/protecting-game-integrity?oldschool=1)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 00:44:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tweeted mod Sween about it, [his reply FYI](https://twitter.com/JagexSween/status/956844859553394689)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 10:46:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let's go :D the hype is real</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 10:27:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>So what you're saying is that you'd like for different PvP situations in the form of minigames/skilling/Pvm? In essence offer competition in other ways than fighting eachother right? Any concrete ideas?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 11:53:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I personally don't see the need for it to hold runes, and the analogy you're making doesn't make too much sense as kodai is essentialy an empowered staff of water. Which 'nice niche' would it fit?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 11:54:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't see why this needs to be a thing when you can just create a new account.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 23:10:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>the email u use to login doesnt have to exist, all my accounts have a random email that never existed to login with, and then later are connected to an actual protected email (different from the login email). essentially they're just a username in email format</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 23:11:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>but I think it can already be considered that? why would it randomly have to be charged with runes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 23:38:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't see a situation where adding the option to charge the staff with runes would add incentive of using it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 10:27:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you create a new account, where it says "enter email here" or whatever (the one you use to login with), you can enter whatever you want as long as it's in email format. For example, you can fill in lvl3skiller@gmail.com without it having to be an email you actually use, or it even existing. Once created you can go into your account settings and change the registered email to an actual email you have, for example AnokataX@gmail.com . Any emails will be sent to AnokataX@gmail.com, while lvl3skiller@gmail.com is simply just sort of a username you use to log in with. It adds an extra layer of protection aswell, seeing as if they get access to your actual email it won't be the same as the one you use to login with. Same goes for the other way around, if they find out your login email, it won't be the same as the email used to protect your account.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 10:29:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where would you use the staff in a situation that warrents a weapon switch?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 16:37:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>So like an ironman with boss tasks unlocked who doesn't have a trident yet and has done a bit of wildy slayer so they could consider using slayer staff (e) as opposed to iban blast? Cause apart from that situation I still don't see it being the case.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 13:13:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like boots + book + b2p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 14:57:52</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I'm not scared  gt;Proceeds to write a long reddit post taking screenshots of every part of the conversation. Idk why you put this much effort into some random kid just throwing a hissy fit lol. Why would you think he can hack you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 16:25:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, Jagex can't do rollbacks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 16:28:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're a new hardcore iron man, chances are you don't really need a rune pouch to begin with. And boosting emblems on ironmen is immoral.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 16:32:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>People do though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 23:20:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol you have to actually put down the cannon, it's not going to shoot out of your inventory</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 11:56:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it would be a good solution, but it would also change skilling alot. You would most likely be forced to use these catalysts for all skilling activities as it'll trump all skilling without them. People might not like this as it's pretty much how RS3 skilling is, just with alot more different things u need to use.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 12:58:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>On my Zeah only ironman, I'm grinding 200m fm right now before doing anything else while I'm 18 hp (max to still take 1 damage from base attack). So yeah kinda silly but I dont mind the mechanic tbh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 16:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, the only difference is that you have to use less food. I wouldn't compare that to 6 hour nmz.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 16:17:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think having to use less food is a game breaking mechanic, hence why I don't mind it (as you have to restrict yourself to do so). I've also done ardy knights on my main to 99 thieving, which is a mechanic I do mind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 13:54:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can we get an update on the game integrity changes that were communicated about a while back? I tweeted Sween about it a few weeks ago and he said there'd be an update soon, but haven't seen anything so far. (this is regarding the things like quest req for using box trap etc.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 15:24:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheers boss.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 15:29:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Heh, I remember posting something similar. [I moved all the skills rather than the total box though](https://www.reddit.com/r/2007scape/comments/600mgy/could_we_make_this_happen_if_its_not_too_big_of_a/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 01:26:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I tried something like that once lol](https://www.twitch.tv/videos/5816332)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 21:52:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're an idiot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 10:30:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's for 1 exact clue, not any exact clue. He's not dismissing the first clue, it's just that the first clue decides what the next 2 clues have to be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 10:53:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>If the first clue is different from the last 2, then only the last one has to be a certain pre-defined clue, based on the second one, which would be 1/60 (using the numbers given).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 11:04:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a difference between griefing and partaking in PvP in a PvP environment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 23:20:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sailing got polled as a skill, as did Artisan. Both failed the poll. Edit: Sailing failed with [68% yes](https://services.runescape.com/m=poll/oldschool/results.ws?id=1273) Everything in the Artisan poll failed, with the skill itself only reaching [56.6% yes](https://services.runescape.com/m=poll/oldschool/results.ws?id=1035)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Plusle - 200m Smithing everything else lvl 1 - One 200m at a time</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 16:54:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 16:58:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>A</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 22:04:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>0n gp, with 200m cook like u said. It seems like he's still actively playing and currently at 93 agility as his second skill.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 22:51:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean you cant get 1750 total as a lvl 3 but yeah</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 10:24:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hah nice, this isn't me btw, I just shared it for him. I did add you ingame and saw you logged in. :) Do you play alot on it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 14:01:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>The fact that your reddit username is 69Dick_Butt69 doesn't help your case tbf.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 14:35:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not saying it does, all I'm saying is that it shows a certain level of immaturity, which makes me lean towards believing the mute is justified.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 15:41:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Suggestion] Stop trying to turn runescape into an esport with new gamemodes that only sound nice. Instead, if anything, try to build a competitive environment in the game we currently have, be it castle wars or a ranked ladder for PvP.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 15:00:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>3x random cosmetic item for me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 10:38:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>[SUGGESTION] Accept the fact that Ardougne Knights don't have to be the go-to braindead thieving method, much like how it never was in the past.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 10:39:40</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Slayer's enchantment have been dead content since day one. Say that to my mage only ironman on kurask tasks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 11:09:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah there's no way such a mechanic is possible to implement atm without a big overhaul.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 18:33:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not for me  gt;:(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>93 Slayer on my mage only ironman</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 19:13:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 19:37:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>A bit over 38m - ign is Smorc Devil</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 19:58:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unique accounts are much more fun than doing something thousands of others have done before you imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 20:49:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haven't done anything special as far as questing goes. I only really got just over 100 QP so I could do swan song to fish monks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 22:49:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Update](https://twitter.com/subject4762/status/976565271094841344) - Got smoke battlestaff on 47 KC but can't wield it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 08:45:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's a progress pic of [1 month on the account](https://imgur.com/a/1kqBu). Now everything you see in this pic was dropped when I quit at first, but then I restarted later on (and took more breaks over the years). Very early I rushed 83 hunter and that was my main moneymaker. Did mostly mage training arena at first for infinity. I then got 85 crafting for fury, and used that money to start slaying with fire bolt (and chaos gauntlets for damage boost). Kept using fire bolt while rcing more, camped some twisted banshees for ess/herbs, also mined a bunch of pure ess iirc. Once I was 77 rc, I crafted bloods instead and used fire wave for slayer (got 92 rc atm, used up all those bloods), when I got to 87 slayer I started using trident. Trident is fairly expensive, but I'm currently following a slayer list where I mostly get my money from kraken tasks, to maintain the costs of trident, note that I didn't start tracking from 87 but a bit later on [link to google spreadsheet](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1jsnWsxCZR2ZKjIr0VEr8xRTgkWwpgT48ZJkJsfrsQyc/edit?usp=sharing). Yes, I've always done defensive casting for all my def levels. Future plans are getting the occult now, doing raids for ancestral+augury(+kodai), getting seers from Prime (49 KC, 2 D axes), eternals from Cerbeus (11-14 KC or something, very supply draining kills, had to suicide a pile for most of them), and imbued heart through slayer. Then also just rounding up my skills in general, and eventually try to complete all the bosses I can do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 09:05:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't worry too much about it, expires in a few weeks anyways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 09:39:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not quite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 09:52:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>It expires in 2 weeks, which means it won't count towards his account's offences anymore. It doesn't mean he's muted for 2 weeks, it probably only lasts 1 or 2 days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 10:33:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha thanks, I do also have full ahrims but not worth using at most slayer tasks. Hopefuly I can get a bit lucky on Ancestral once I start grinding raids. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 11:19:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hah, definately wouldn't say I play super efficient, just got a few things done early :) I did do glass - gt; bstaves until 85. Here's an old youtube progress video [episode 1](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3YVx99uhwzs), only ended up making 2 and quitting again shortly after. Didn't start recording again when I continued playing after like 6 months.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Got the occult :) 100 thermy + 70 small ones</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 12:35:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 14:10:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>+3 max hit is very welcome :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 15:36:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it was, better than mystics + good mage training early on @ mta. And it looks nice :) As far as ahrims goes, I only use it on certain tasks where gear matters more, but I generally use infinity for most normal slayer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 18:31:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably taking a break from slayer for a while, but would love to get lucky on that one :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 23:33:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think its like 17k molten glass into bstaves to get to 85.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 10:04:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not saying it was justified, I was just trying to say it wouldn't have a big impact on his account. Seems like that was a bad idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 11:18:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my god</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 09:19:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't use void</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 10:02:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe he streams and donated it to himself, surely that's no problem :'D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 10:30:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're probably better off mining essence @ gnome stronghold rather than ardy (closer to bank). :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 13:12:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>He was already at ge. He saw people talk in chat (look screenshot), he added him to see where exactly he stood around at ge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 09:13:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still waiting on someone to play a range only ironman long term. :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 10:33:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mate. Relax. Breath. You have an hour to get your stuff back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 11:58:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>If the server went down, he'll also have immediately logged out on dc, which means he won't be dead if he wasn't at time of dc. If the server didnt go down, but instead, just kicked all connections out, he'll be able to log back in within the hour and collect his stuff (assuming he died).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 14:03:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's the thought process behind training the gathering skills when you're not going to use the supplies gathered? Might look nicer on such an account to keep gathering skills at lvl 1. Or are you doing them for quest (are u allowing yourself to do quests?)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 14:12:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone else is doing a slayer only ironman right now, "404 skill", who also completely limited himself from any non-combat stats. That looks very nice in my opinion, but obviously restricts the gameplay even more. Someone else also did this a while back, and he basically maxed out "Slayncombat". But ofcourse, if you want to do a different take on it by allowing certain skills etc, that's up to you to decide.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 14:57:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm pretty sure you don't need any non-combat skills for dks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 15:03:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah you don't need a quest to go to dks, it just costs 1k to take the boat then (I'm in the same situation :) ). Gl either way with the account!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 16:23:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>jpegg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 18:13:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jad wouldn't be too hard melee only :p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 19:13:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can just step back every attack</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hut hut</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 22:05:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 22:05:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>H</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 09:21:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh man if only there was this thieving minigame that you could benefit from doing with others... Like something in the desert idk lol...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 09:28:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi Dad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 10:22:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are plenty of teleportation methods! Minigame teleports are huge for getting around the map, aswell as unlocking slayer rings  amp; getting a mounted glory in POH (and then putting that POH close to one of the teleportation methods u have, for example yanille with nmz minigame tp). I'm sure teleportation will be the least of your worries :D I'm not sure how viable doing it as UIM would be, but hey, I'd love to see someone get far on a range only ironman, so let me know if you start one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 12:02:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.reddit.com/r/2007scape/comments/31qrzn/hey_jagex_im_the_man_for_the_job_and_its_time_for/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 14:35:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dragon implings</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 23:07:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck you, gratz.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Seers Ring</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 12:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Trident  #10004; #65039; Occult necklace  #10004; #65039; Seers ring  #10004; #65039;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 12:37:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 12:37:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>A</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Trident  #10004; #65039; Occult necklace  #10004; #65039; Seers ring  #10004; #65039;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 12:39:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 12:43:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kills took about 10 minutes each just camping trident, probably spent about 8m in trident supplies to get this prime KC.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 12:59:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cant get torm cause of the quests, will do raids mainly for chance on ancestral/augury as Kodai wont be too useful for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 13:25:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Took about 10 minutes/kill</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 14:28:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>[So lazy smh](http://services.runescape.com/m=hiscore_oldschool_ironman/hiscorepersonal.ws?user1=Smorc%A0Devil)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 15:25:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never really made constant progress updates, apart from 2 old youtube videos. I mostly just put updates on my twitter. (@subject4762)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 21:22:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes I know that, and I also don't use Osbuddy, nor would that make me want to put together progress logs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 21:23:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 21:23:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>A torn? Not sure what you're referring to. Also, I can't have veng.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 22:19:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't do all those quests</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 22:20:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah does ring a bell</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 01:32:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>My guess is, compared to other mineable rocks, this together with essence mines are larger than 1x1 square. So you start a mining cycle on one part, and then tick manip into a different square, it probably triggers 2 squares at once that are somehow programmed as different entities (but visualy belong to the same source).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 10:32:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah that's correct</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 10:33:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like Savtoz pointed out, I can't get to Zulrah because of underground pass quest, which requires range + gives attk exp reward.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 10:36:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would change the game too much as far as pures etc go. It's a choice you make that restricts you from certain content and shouldn't be changed imo. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 20:50:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>They go to all the big open cc's it seems. Was also happening in iron faux, I just left for another cc cause couldn't be bothered anymore. Kicking them does nothing because they instantly leave after the message got sent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Imbued heart from first smoke devil superior</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 22:01:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Imbued heart from first smoke devil superior</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 22:01:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Imbued heart from first smoke devil superior</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 22:02:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 22:14:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Crafting got me money that I used early on for fire bolts. 77-92 rc bloods were used for fire wave. 87+ slayer I used trident and got enough profit from kraken tasks to sustain rune costs for other tasks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 09:11:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reddit was bugging out for me, the first upload I tried didn't go through (and directed me to my user page) so I tried again with different format of image. Looks like the first one then got posted later on, deleting this post now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 09:12:07</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Reddit was bugging out for me, the first upload I tried didn't go through (and directed me to my user page) so I tried again with different format of image. Looks like the first one then got posted later on, deleting this post now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 09:13:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not gunna lie, after the screenshot my reaction wasn't as calm :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 10:47:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uncharged orbs - gt; Air battlestaffs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 12:45:34</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Crafting got me money that I used early on for fire bolts. 77-92 rc bloods were used for fire wave. 87+ slayer I used trident and got enough profit from kraken tasks to sustain rune costs for other tasks. Not really, I have like 250 barrows kc in which I completed all the items I needed, but as far as runes go, I basically went break-even on death and got 2x return on chaos. Not really worth it to grind out for runes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 13:35:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Belg* :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 13:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ik ben belg :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 13:53:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Swel jammer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 20:57:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmao that's awesome haha :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 11:36:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my god I love this aha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 11:44:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>- Lower price of rock thrownhammers - Add death rune packs to mage arena rune store after completing MA2 - Remove the confirmation message when paying farmers to protect/remove trees etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 16:43:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sinister Key</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 09:24:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I can see this being a good change. Won't do any harm, alot of people probably have plenty of white berries from kurasks so this'll just help certain accounts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - First cerberus unique</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 18:14:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 15:34:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I made something similar once](https://i.gyazo.com/862115dd923074f355a808937349ef76.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 09:36:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a few people doing this. 199atatime - 1atatime99hc - OSAAT Newn - Pckaxe I also started as OSAAT on my acc Sinister Key, but shifted the goal of the account at 85 agility.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 10:12:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>idk about this one mate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 11:32:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I personally liked the idea of having to build certain houses based on a blueprint alot more. Sort of like this: - you go to person X - he gives you a blueprint that shows which rooms/furniture u have to build etc - you build a house following this blueprint (seperate to your POH) - you get a reward for completing it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 14:01:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>doesn't need special rewards imo, just a competitive alternative training method</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 10:37:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Slayer Helm is easyscape anyways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Some info on my first completed Cerberus task.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 15:58:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 23:59:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>* Yes on Eagles peak * Yes on barb rod, I also got it on my zeah only (I think I was like 82-83 fishing when I did) * No on impling jars, not rly necessary, seems like a stretch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Hellpuppy + Pegasian in same kill</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 15:12:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Hellpuppy + Pegasian in same kill</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 15:12:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 15:12:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>A</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Hellpuppy + Pegasian in same kill</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 15:13:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 15:17:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fire bolt - gt; Fire wave - gt; trident</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 15:32:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have it look pretty in my bank</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 15:45:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>105</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 16:28:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fire bolt - gt; Fire wave - gt; trident</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 16:55:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>U can ask w/e u want, I'll reply to any.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 17:00:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gradually over time, combination of lava dragons at start, dbones  amp; baby dbones from slayer/d imps, and ensouled heads from slayer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 17:09:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fire bolt - money from crafting Fire wave - rced my bloods Trident - combination of rcing more bloods  amp; selling them and just slayer in general. If you look at this [spreadsheet](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1jsnWsxCZR2ZKjIr0VEr8xRTgkWwpgT48ZJkJsfrsQyc/edit?usp=sharing) you can see on tab "Task tracker v1" that I was able to sustain the costs of other tasks through kraken mostly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 17:29:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>105</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 17:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.reddit.com/r/2007scape/comments/88pz0x/mage_only_ironman_trident_occult_necklace_seers/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 17:32:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>A rcher started a range only UIM. There's a few others that started one before but only played for a few days. I want to see someone get far on one :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 17:34:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would have to revert to selling to stores for lower price, wouldn't be too bad I don't think. Less costly to sustain range supplies than mage supplies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 18:44:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been killing cerberus  amp; prime, surely Ahrim is the one you'd be the least surprised about? :p His mage stats are fairly low compared to cerb/prime. Wasn't hard to hit ahrim at all, used flames of zamorak before I had trident, just trident afterwards.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 19:39:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's on my keyboard above tab / next to 1.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 19:49:03</DATE>
    <TEXT> lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 19:59:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's a french azerty keyboard</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 20:25:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>1 kill/trip - about 8 kills/hour Average of 107 trident casts - 17 potion doses - 11 sharks per kill</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 20:37:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. Hope I don't go too dry on the eternal crystal. Only have enough potions atm to finish this task :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 20:38:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not long at all. Ahrim doesn't have that high mage lvl/def, compared to prime or cerberus (or other bosses).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 21:48:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>All defence is from magic on defensive casting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 22:07:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Prims would be as useless as these pegs :D now if only it was an eternal...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 22:25:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Defence through maging  #175;\\\_( #12484;)_/ #175;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 23:16:27</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Fire bolt - money from crafting  gt; Fire wave - rced my bloods  gt; Trident - combination of rcing more bloods  amp; selling them and just slayer in general. If you look at this [spreadsheet](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1jsnWsxCZR2ZKjIr0VEr8xRTgkWwpgT48ZJkJsfrsQyc/edit?usp=sharing) you can see on tab "Task tracker v1" that I was able to sustain the costs of other tasks through kraken mostly. Lack of lunars/zulrah makes certain things harder I suppose (I hate manually making glass). Also the fact that u have to funnel all the money u ever make into supplies for combat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 23:46:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't get to those cause of all the quests.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 00:06:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only have 111 QP, nothing special worth mentioning. Will probably complete all quests possible sometime in the near future to get more slayer blocks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 08:56:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imbued heart boost</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 08:56:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I made 2 videos, after which I quit for a while and didn't get back into making videos when I started again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 08:57:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a few others out there atm, but I'm most certainly the most progressed one. :) Second up is "Iron Mage" as far as I'm aware.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 10:32:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm really digging that scene setup. GZ :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 22:03:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Traveling really isn't too bad. Minigame teleports, mounted glory, chronicle, slayer rings, ... There's plenty of ways to get around the game. Lvl 3 skillers do just fine, as a range only you'll have more options than that :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 15:52:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think so, but ppl seem to have been killed in a few occassions during the short time that this occured. And they've lost bank  amp; stats because of it ON THEIR NORMAL ACC because the server was switched to DMM without logging out the people first. The guy from the linked tweet allegedly has 98 herblore with a herblore cape now, and his killer got a bank key that he can't use.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 15:59:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>occured</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 16:00:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>good bot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 16:25:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>CML does NOT lie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 17:25:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That pic wasn't from today/the issue at hand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 17:27:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's more that it simply creates data points pulled from the hiscores at a certain time. It's logical that it resulted in negative xp because of the difference between 2 recorded data points. Not necessarily built an exception to handle negative xp I'd say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 18:13:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think he said he lost about 35-40m, which was most of his bank. He also lost his mining pet (that I assume he had out at the time of death).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 18:40:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it was only during max 2 minutes during countdown of system update. The guy got killed when there was like 10 seconds left.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 16:18:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think dropping to 4 hp using a full invent of food on elvarg is how you're supposed to play any acc type, but I get what you're saying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 20:43:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gimme dat. also gz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 18:32:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>11$</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 12:15:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>They made it like this because too many people selected permanent and then had to ask jagex afterwards to downgrade anyways. This way people have to get 1k total first before going perm.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 14:14:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>damn wish I got those eternals that early :D currently 400 kc on my mage only iron with 1 stone, 1 jar, 1 pegasian, 1 pet. Can't complain but hope I don't go too dry on eternal :) GZ !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 08:30:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amazing progress. Those barrows items are also sick to get :D Can't wait to see more! I love how slayer is possible through temple trekking, never considered it for a mory only. As far as those agility tomes go, how much stored exp is that atm and how many are you going for?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 10:28:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Makes perfect sense :) gl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 11:47:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is possible to get 60 agility using toy mice. I got to like 48 or something on my zeah only until I gave up and made a 1-off trip to get barb rod to train further to 60 agility. From 60 onwards, the agility method @ wintertodt is pretty decent. I wouldn't make too many exceptions, just stick to Zeah only.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 12:03:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn I had about the same thing [just 11 days ago](https://www.reddit.com/r/2007scape/comments/8dng7z/mage_only_ironman_hellpuppy_pegasian_in_same_kill/). :D GZ</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 13:20:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>if u turn your camera so the clickboxes of the 2 nets allign u can spamclick to fill an invent without looking</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 13:42:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>As it currently stands, Zeah is pretty viable for every skill apart from slayer. But enjoying yourself is ofc important, that's also the reason why I ended up getting barb rod, I couldn't stand doing toy mice any longer. They're also planning to put a quest req on box traps, so if I were to still play my Zeah only I'd also make an exception there to complete Eagle's Peak so I could still catch the grey chins on Zeah. There's been several Zeah only ironmen out there (also a few UIM) and most have some minor differences in their rules. EDIT: Here's a link to a [Zeah only website](https://zeahproduct.github.io/zeahonly/) that Zeahproduct made. I think it's pretty scuffed atm but it can give u an idea from the accounts that were made so far. Mine was Landmass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 14:49:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whatever u bank on tutorial island gets lost when going to mainland anyways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 11:07:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>LMAO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 11:59:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Cpt SCHNIPAA](https://www.reddit.com/r/UniqueIronmen/comments/8eg4du/piratecoastal_only_ironman/) is jealous of you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - 99 Hitpoints</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 11:15:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - 99 Hitpoints</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 11:15:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 11:22:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Currently slayer is sustaining my rune costs. But that's only for normal slayer, bossing etc drains alot of supplies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 11:32:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>/u/FBI</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 17:14:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>No supplies for Cerberus, just doing more slayer atm. Will try to get some thieving in towards 99 so I can have a reliable rannar seed source I guess. :P</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 19:41:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I've done priest in peril  amp; recruitment drive with recoils  amp; defensive attk. EDIT: to specify, priest in peril with recoils  amp; defensive attk, recruitment drive just on defensive attk (which took like 20 minutes and I had to pray flick or I'd have died)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 20:29:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably like 300 more hours for def/slay roughly :p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 20:49:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mage only as in staying 1 att 1 str 1 range.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Chaos elemental pet</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:48:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Chaos elemental pet</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:48:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 23:12:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is that a rethorical question? Clearly it does, otherwise I wouldn't be able to kill it :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 23:35:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It does alright, about 80 casts / kill.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 08:16:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would be able to do zulrah mage only, but I simply can't get there because of the underground pass quest requiring range + giving attk exp reward.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 08:16:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boss slayer task, pet/d pick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 15:28:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alot of clan accounts are UIM aswell to have an icon to stand out n stuff. This is again just a stupid oversight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 15:32:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Leave me alone :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 11:29:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's because you're killing the wrong shades. The ones in the security stronghold are the old random events, which always gave reduced exp (much like the tree spirits u can kill for rune axe). The ones you want to kill are in mort'ton.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 13:50:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just checked on CML, he hasn't gained exp since [29/04](https://i.imgur.com/mhq75Y9.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 15:00:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Working. But once I get home the plans are: - RC bloods on my mage only ironman (might get 95 RC today) - Fishing trawler on my hardcore ironman (got 81 fish yesterday, can get manta rays now) - Hunt tortles on my RS3 lvl 3 skiller</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 15:05:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>2-3 Current activities while playing 3 at a time: - OSRS Mage only ironman - gt; AFKing Zeah RC - OSRS Hardcore ironman - gt; AFKing barb fishing - RS3 Skiller - gt; Hunting tortles</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 21:46:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>But you sell per 50, it literally takes like 1 minute manually spamclicking to sell for what I assume to be an onyx.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 22:24:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>No? there's literally a sell-50 option</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 09:18:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're missing what I'm saying. You can spam click the sell-50 option. [Here's a sample](https://youtu.be/3YVx99uhwzs?t=6m22s)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 11:17:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>FYI, u said the dropped wool didn't show up to your other account. Did you multilog for it or did u log out - gt; log in to other account? Dropped items only show up for people that were logged in when it was dropped AFAIK. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 13:29:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>This always happens on a game update cause it resets the spots. Then it takes a few changes until it occupies the spots again and it stops shifting cause it has nowhere to go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 10:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think there's 3 types of add-ons u can identify: - Not interacting with game window (hiscores, xp trackers, price checker, ...) - gt; completely fine - Shows information on game window (hunter overlay, timers, ground items, ...) - gt; fine but gives advantage while playing - Changes certain game mechanics (shift click options, left click pickpocket, left click use bones, ...) - gt; not fine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 10:57:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Halve it yourself by doing it manually.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 11:50:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd recommend [fruit stalls](http://oldschoolrunescape.wikia.com/wiki/Fruit_Stall).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 12:01:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's slightly faster when u run in between both stalls. It should be the best method available to you, upwards of 40k xp/hr</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 12:46:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah lock the dogs in the house. Can even be done on 10 hp, or you can hop around to other worlds to try and find them trapped.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 13:24:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm talking about npc's with talk-to options, like HAM members  amp; BJ NPC's. I'm aware u can left click knights etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 13:50:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Live  amp; learn :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 14:53:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Color me surprised</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 16:18:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I dont think this is necessary as the F2P-only community is very active, they even have their own [hiscores](https://www.f2p.wiki/ranks)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 11:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's also my third pet at 25 kc :D gz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 19:02:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>5k bonus pts for beating the challenge time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - tentacle #10 for the trident upgrade</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 23:22:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 01:16:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>gz on the piusfhs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 10:09:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I use trident for everything (apart from kurask tasks). Slayer on its own sustains a lot of the costs, but when I run out of cash my current method is just craft bloods and sell them for 200ea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 11:29:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>UGH gimme that. Granted I'm lucky on kraken/hellhound/chaos ele pets so far, the useful items would be nice to get :D gz on all</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 14:28:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Smoke devil pet</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 18:31:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Smoke devil pet</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 18:31:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 09:27:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very :) was on my first smoke devil superior</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 13:34:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You and me are on the same team here. We can make this happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 00:12:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>recoils + attk on defensive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 20:52:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bonds is more money for jagex than normal subscriptions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 14:04:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Skill releases were so exciting. Preparing farming before release cause u were already able to get seeds before the skill was out. Taverley slayer master being insanely packed with people spamming their slayer level, everyone super amazed when someone said they were 30 slayer. Good times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 14:47:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very true. I remember rushing home from school to my friends' house and we'd load up 2 pc's racing eachother for the first hunter levels. Good times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 13:31:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cor blimey mate, what are ye doing in me pockets?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 10:20:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/madlads</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 14:33:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Salmonest</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 13:39:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I prefer the name of Oziris' new hardcore, HcSoloIronFe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 14:07:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh wow that's prety cool :D never knew about this. Apparently using food on the white ones also gives cooking exp instead of herblore exp.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 00:00:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's been polled before but failed with [68% yes votes](http://oldschoolrunescape.wikia.com/wiki/Poll:Sailing_Skill)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 10:52:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>If a skill were to be polled, I doubt it'd be one of the 2 that've been polled before (being Sailing and Artisan).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 10:55:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chances are this is just ghostmouse</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 00:32:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Join the 'Iron Pure' cc and ask for directions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 12:06:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only druidic ritual. Can make exception to get skillcapes  amp; barb fishing rod.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 16:11:25</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Soooo much clicking Just got out of the starter building.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 22:57:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Legend, all these new updates are so great for your account :D Definitely up there on my list of favorite accounts to follow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 14:02:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh hello there :D I take it this is just the skill restrictions then, not fremmy area?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 18:45:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Construction: buy house from estate agent on zeah - gt; train to 25 at wintertodt Agility: toy mice (made in poh) until 60 - gt; wintertodt agil shortcut to 99 // make exception to get barb rod on mainland and do mice to 15 - gt; barb fish to 60 - gt; wintertodt agil to 99 // also possible to make summer pies to boost from 55</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 08:55:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah what SarcasmScape said. Don't need rune mysterys, you get knife on Zeah. Use client of kourend lamps on slayer, otherwise you're stuck with not doing lovakengj favor for ages (look me up, "Landmass"). Train 9 hunter in raids.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 19:07:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Getting 9 hunter doesn't require you to 'do' raids. You simply keep entering until hunter is the first room (just on your own) and get lvl 9 and leaving.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How I made 1.5b in just 2 weeks - Intercepting RWT</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 19:17:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 19:18:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>V</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 19:26:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>My video isn't even monetized. I'm just legitimately sharing what happened in the past 2 weeks. It's not clickbait when the title literally reflects what happens in the video.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 22:14:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm intrigued</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 22:23:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idk, that value would have to be fairly high, seeing as I got a 9m from the ground in this video (and have seen other drops on ground, of which I don't know the value of).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 22:40:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, he was someone else that was doing the same thing so now he's salty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 23:31:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Using the exp lamps on agil + hunter really wasnt a good idea imo. Like I said, I used them both on hunter cause I was following a pre-raids starter guide, and I'm still only 7 slayer on my zeah only "Landmass". Much better to use them on slayer and do 9 hunter in raids, but if your reasoning to not do it is 'just cus' than that's your choice I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 00:15:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>500 xp on agil is pretty negligible if you plan to do mice to 60</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 13:30:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haven't thought about it much, but if cons  amp; craft is possible u can make toy mice in poh and train agil that way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 13:43:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a plank spawn at barb assault, idk if u count that area within your limitations. Can also buy limestone bricks in keldagrim iirc, not sure what lvl u need to start using those. Also don't know about the accesibility of construction tools for u. Can use house tele pre-lvl 30 if u allow that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 16:22:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>See I loved doing stuff like this. It was a skill on its own to do this well. Also full guthans with leaf bladed spear  amp; full veracs with black skirt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 18:06:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's only been 3 days since my video got on front page. Might be a bit too early to repost bud.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 11:57:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Might aswell give it directly to me :\^)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - 99 Woodcutting</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 13:03:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 19:18:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes ofcourse, through slayer. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 08:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>OH shit ;s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 13:15:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>You cant just hold down alt and press the little - that comes up next to it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 11:30:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you go into the Ground Items setting, you can give several values to have different tiers show in different colors. Should be self explanatory :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 11:47:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm at work right now so can't check, but I think there's options for both? Not sure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 09:59:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess it's rather common, but still comparable to raids 1. I'm not too familiar with average points in group raids in raids 1, but lets take a group of 5 people that get 25k. A drop in raids 1 is averaged to be every 700k points iirc, so it would take that group of 5 people about 5.6 raids to get a drop. If you consider the same for raids 2, getting any unique is a bit more rare than raids 1, granted there's less of them on the table.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 11:18:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very nice :) gz again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 11:19:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oof that's a rough one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 15:49:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Finally. Gz :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 16:03:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's true, haven't been following enough to know death counts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 08:31:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's amazing haha :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 14:38:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>RS3 graphics and UI are great, that's what got me to play it for a while even though OSRS is my main focus.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 23:57:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't sleep on Robot Rage</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:50:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I went ahead and tested it, [for science](https://gyazo.com/b15c9a7e285cc8d53abfe5464b1c6fa7). Oof OP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 08:54:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just looked at a previous post of him, someone mentioned it but apparently it required 30 agility to use it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 10:43:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thats nice and all, but is that a quest cape you're slaying in? :x</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Episode 3</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 18:56:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Episode 3</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 18:56:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Episode 3</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 18:57:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 18:57:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>V</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 17:28:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or even better, how about a laptop!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 20:34:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can't reset a task you got from turael.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 12:48:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>That'd be [him](https://www.reddit.com/r/UniqueIronmen/comments/8xaaak/nudist_man_ironman_that_cannot_equip_any_items/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 11:08:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>It hurt me to see you use the books on magic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 14:00:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>absolutely, it's not bad with the library helpers out there, I believe Zeah Leesin was the first zeah only to get 77 rc with it, I'm 50 on mine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 12:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's too much brown to the left side of the river, just north of the white line.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 01:01:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Huge</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 23:41:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I received mine [a couple of weeks ago](https://twitter.com/subject4762/status/1020243255819194368)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 23:34:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a way to bypass the camtasia watermark by disconnecting from your internet connection and then entering a fake key, it'll give an error and then u can just render without watermark (shouldn't be too hard to google for that to find example vids).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 21:36:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>wtf!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 23:31:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Merching on the streets was the most fun I've had in RS period.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Skotizo method</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 13:25:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Skotizo method (Bug or feature?)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 19:00:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 19:44:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>V</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 20:43:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't see why not, not sure if you'll have an easier time with trident compared to other methods though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 21:59:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im not entirely sure if their speed is quick enough to do it the same way I do it with trident. Prob not better than range for the full kill either if u plan on just using god spells.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 01:51:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>increasing xp rates in any form or shape =/= QOL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 21:52:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>gz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 23:57:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>been considering this for a while too for osrs, seems fun :) gl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 17:19:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>good luck on your account, feel free to pm me ingame with questions whenever I'm on :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 01:17:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mid</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 14:19:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well there's others aswell. Plusle is currently 150m fm after 200m smith, and Zulohh is currently 43m smith after 200m cook.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 18:03:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well if you saw the vid, you'd know that he quit his 19 combat idea cause he won't be able to recoil the 180s, and the new account he started also won't work cause he won't be able to kill the 360s with poison.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 18:14:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah but like i said, it also wont work</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 20:34:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because it takes too long to hit them, you have to repoison them but they'll heal too much. [Rendi input](https://gyazo.com/a95e0325ea3defff9c3ef2cc554dbef2) Edit: Noticed Rendi commented himself on other reply.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 22:16:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know, KempQ didn't say that, I'm saying that part.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 19:49:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's true, RS3 has some nice sailing-themed content. As far as uncharted islands go (or the arc in general), that's mainly end game content so you'll have to reach those high levels first in other ways.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 19:56:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>you did put an "m" at the end though, which you should change to gp :p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 01:01:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>On average, you'll receive a drop every 700k personal points. Doesn't matter if you see items gained by other people, the average will remain on your personal points for personal drops.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 10:14:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>But yeah like /u/jesse1412 pointed out, referring to the last part of your post, the points don't "count up" to 700k overall and then you'll get a drop. It's just all about averages, so joining FFA's when you're around 700k personal points total will do nothing for you. Averages will only show with big enough sample size, so it's perfectly possible to go 2m+ personal points dry of an item, where it's also possible to get 3 items within 700k personal points.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Eternal crystal</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 12:09:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Eternal crystal</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 12:09:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 12:10:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Other loot: 3 pegasians 2 stones 2 pets 1 jar 1 of the pegasians were together with my first pet at 273 KC. Used over 3500 ranarr/snaps combined. 1 kill trips, about 7-8/hour.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 12:11:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Other loot: 3 pegasians 2 stones 2 pets 1 jar 1 of the pegasians were together with my first pet at 273 KC. Used over 3500 ranarr/snaps combined. 1 kill trips, about 7-8/hour.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mage only ironman - Eternal crystal</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 12:12:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 12:12:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Other loot: 3 pegasians 2 stones 2 pets 1 jar 1 of the pegasians were together with my first pet at 273 KC. Used over 3500 ranarr/snaps combined. 1 kill trips, about 7-8/hour.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 12:12:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>A</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 12:20:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've got a few vids but not very active.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 12:43:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>A combination of that + complaining the kill right before this one cause I got another pegasian. lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>