<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject1545</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>found this on a fb group</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 07:29:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 11:32:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually found it on a hamilton fb group! Haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 15:39:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is another level, seriously beyond the average nicegirl.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 05:18:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I late? Have the mods done something yet?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 08:48:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Culture on your drinking life" why does that sound so much like my dad?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 11:42:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>It doesn't even make sense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 11:47:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's actually 'Panther hero'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 12:20:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>n o w a y</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A pigeon nested in my dad's backyard and I think it's really awesome.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 04:52:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 02:25:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you thought about running away? Just save up a little bit, fuck everyone and everything a travel to the other half of the world or something. I doesn't even have to be so far, you could just go on a road trip. Hitchhike. I mean, that's what I'm gonna do. I am aware about the dangers that I could be exposed and all like being kidnapped or worse but hey, if I get killed I suppose is a win-win, right? Just bring a knife or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 09:11:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's just straight up being an asshole</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I don't know if this is the right place to post this but I just love this so much</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 02:32:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 10:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I gave this "advice" to some one a couple of weeks ago, not sure if they listened but, why don't you just run away? I know it sounds stupid and like I'm oversimplyfiying (?) it but if you don't have major responsabilities like children or really close family that depend on you then why not? Save some money, sell somethings and just fly to another country or start a roadtrip or hitchhike. There's a lot of options, dude. I'm not going to tell you that I understand where you're coming from 'cause I don't, I don't know how bad it is for you to just wake up, but I do know that you don't have to wake up in the same bed tomorrow, or in the same house, or state.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 10:37:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I am not going to tell you not to follow your gut 'cause I have no right to do so but I wish you peace. And I wish that you are truly happy about your desicion. And if for some reason you wanna talk to someone there's like 6 billion strangers online or something like that and I'm one of those :) And wow, china? huh. My brother and I want to go to japan someday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 10:45:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, but be careful ok? I know it sounds stupid and stuff but you know what I mean right? I don't know what I mean I just...I don't know, just be careful. I'm weird, sorry. Have a good night or day or whatever, its night here so, good night. And yes, definitely Japan. (:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 19:35:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/trashy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 22:50:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/UnintentionalSupernatural</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 09:07:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait, never? I'm from Coahuila and this happens all the time here, also when I visit Monterrey on vacation. It's hard to watch but it is very common.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 09:09:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>It actually does happen, everywhere. It's just that on turist locations the police are literally everywhere but in normal parts of Mexico this is (sadly) very common.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 09:14:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think poverty is a factor on it, but in the places where I've seen it happen people just don't care about the law 'cause not even the police care about it. if (and most of the time it doesn't happen) the police pull you over you can get out of it for aprox 200 mxn wich is like 10 US dollars</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 12:05:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait, what? I'm from M #233;xico and I didn't know that :0</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I honestly don't know what the hell</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 13:26:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 01:00:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't, a friend send me this last week xd I assume it's a bootleg like one comment above said  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 13:23:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>HMC while I jump from the roof and break my legs</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 06:09:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"Just let me jump from the roof real quick"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 06:45:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 07:48:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tbh I hope she only broke her legs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 12:55:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/UnexpectedDwightSchrute</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 07:20:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, we don't talk about it. Never.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 07:22:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I swear to god, Luke, she lives in Canada!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 08:05:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, my brother had really bad acne all through his highschool years and he still got a girlfriend who he still loves very much. Physical apparence shouldn't be a barrier for you to meet people. You just gotta fiend the right kind of people and get away from the asshole-ish kind, you know? There's so much wrong with this comment and my grammar but I don't really care I think you get what I'm saying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 08:06:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thats pretty assholeish</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 08:19:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>One time I send a girlfriend my entire meme collection, over a thousand images all well organized and divided by its emotional undertones. I was so proud of that, and then she cheated on me like a week after we were official. I never knew if she ever send those memes to other people and honestly I don't wanna know, it would definetly break me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 10:20:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do that:"v</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I mean, they're not that bad, right?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 10:52:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you were born yesterday but you're so done with life already.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 11:02:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My dog mirin at the neighbor's dog</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 06:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I think my dog is in love with the neighbor's dog.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 07:09:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Parents at a Oklahoma school threatened a 12 year old transgender girl. A 12 YEAR OLD. A CHILD.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 10:04:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>