<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject8581</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-07-16 22:06:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't even see the mutation. I saw the nail and thought "EEEWWWW" so I let. I then read the whole title. "No, It doesn't make me swim better" Me "Huh" I went back and then noticed the toes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-07-30 06:47:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will now always know where the Melons are...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-08-27 22:05:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aww man, I wish my corgi wasn't so fat... I could bring to school.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-09-15 00:25:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>i stared at the picture for like 10 minutes before laughing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-26 00:41:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last time I checked Amy Farrah Fowler didn't have a dog, but herion is one hell of a drug.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-28 23:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love the Witcher 3! The inventory isn't actually confusing at all. It's an open world RPG, you use swords to fight a very vast array of enemies across the really huge world. The story is excellent and very grasping, even the side quests. The towns are jam packed with townsfolk and shops. It's a wonderful game full of things to do, I'd highly recommend it. You use different swords, potions, spells and weapon and armor attachments. I very rarely feel too strong because enemies take different strategies to fight. It's honestly one of the best games I've ever played. I adore Fallout as well, so I think you'll enjoy it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-28 23:28:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only if I can design shitty homes for those Nilfguardian assholes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My bunny is extremely mean.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-18 02:16:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have had my rabbit Luna for a few months now, she is 2 years of age and is spade. Her previous owner stated her as very sweet, would never bite or chew but since introducing her to my home she has despised me. I give her more than enough to chew on, yet she decides my bedding and pillows are her personal chew toys. She bites me constantly, won't let me trim her nails, pick her up, and she never binks or anything. She will flop, and on some occasions lick after a long petting session but it seems she just hates me. She has a full run of my room and part of the hallway but she sits in her house during the day and on my window sill at night. I don't know what to do to improve my bond with her, I personally don't care too much if she chews on my stuff, I just want her to approach me and not run away when I walk near her, whether I have the intent of touching her or not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sounds stupid, but I miss him.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-20 05:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm only 15, too young to really get things. I've never had a boyfriend, barely pass classes, and I'm too caught up alone in my room doing absolutely nothing. In the 7th grade, when my depression was at its worst, I started talking to this guy. I liked him, he liked me, but I was too awkward and weird to date or really talk in person for that matter, but I enjoyed texting him. We stopped talking 8th grade, and I miss it more than anything. I never told him I was depressed, but without direct words, he kept me from attempting suicide. He made me happy and feel cared about, and I haven't experienced the same thing since. I miss it so much, I just want to talk to him again, or give him a hug or even just say thank you, but I'm almost positive he treats that like how I should, like some stupid thing that happened in the 7th grade. Something that was fun, yet meaningless. That's what 7th grade is supposed to be. You aren't supposed to fall in love. I don't want to say that's what it was, because, I can't say I'm in love. I'm 15, my parents don't 'love' each other, who am I to say what love is? But I cared about him, and the things he said have honestly changed me as a person, he made me feel cared about. I'm too distracted by him to get distracted by someone else. I've never told anyone that I still think about him this much, which may not seem like a big deal but everything in the 7th grade was a joke to my friends. She makes fun of him, and the stuff we said and I kills me, but I can't let her know. I wish he knew. I'm glad I could say this because I've never told someone. I want to, but I can't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-20 05:39:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have been thinking of getting her a friend, however, she is extremely territorial so it's a bit hard finding a bunny I think she'll get along with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-28 04:11:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd hope so! Why waste perfectly good seasoning?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Falling behind, worried I cannot make it up.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-11 07:40:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, I'm a sophomore in High School, and I recently took about a week off of school due to a bad head cold (stupid idea, I know, I should've just sucked it up, but the deeds been done) and I've already fallen behind. I've missed 3 tests, one of which for a class I was seriously struggling in before, and the teacher kind of hates me. For some odd reason, when I put myself in front of my work and say, "Do it, It has to get done." I don't. I don't listen to myself which sounds weird but, I honestly don't. I make excuses to myself and It then brings me to shame myself, and my depression gets worse then I no longer have the energy to do anything, (a really stupid cycle, I'm aware) and I've become so stressed out I've begun sleeping for 9 hours at night, returning from school, sleeping another 5, waking up and watching Youtube, then repeat. Notice no work time and no eating time for that matter (I don't eat breakfast or lunch). I don't know how to motivate myself and make up the work, especially since it seems that if the stress piles up, my depression will get worse. Sorry for the novel, but I really need help, and I'm kind of freaking out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Falling behind.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 05:46:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm 15, a sophomore in highschool, and my depression is causing me to miss school, thus falling behind. At this point, I feel as though any hope for me catching up is hopeless, and some classes I believe I should just drop because I don't see myself passing them. I used to be an honor roll student, straight A's, awards, the seemingly perfect student. However, 7th grade, some depression started showing up. I kept it to myself and did my work and all was fine. Even 9th grade I struggled through, but I fear that I've just given up completely. While I currently have A's and B's in some classes, others are C's, Chinese even being a D- and I don't think I'll make it up and I'll be forced to drop it before the second semester. I take Prozac (don't exactly know if it's working) and I see therapists, and my mom is understanding and has explained she would much rather homeschool me, or even let me drop out should that be necessary. I don't want that to happen, but I just don't think I can do it. Here is the situation. I miss school when homework isn't done. I can't bare to show up and feel the disappointment, possibly even get yelled at by my teachers. I can't bare to see them say, "That's your 5th missing assignment, keep this up and you won't pass." Even on my days where I'm home, I don't do my homework. I just don't. I tell myself to do, I try and abuse myself into doing it (not self-harm, but more mentally) and yet I still don't do it. I'm lazy, and slowly giving up. I mean, here I sit, not doing it. I feel the shame and disappointment from my family and just feel like a failure. I have no goals, no motivation. I don't eat, exercise, anything. People usually think I've lying if I try to talk, but the fact that I laugh and make jokes and have fun the times I am with friends automatically means I'm fine and not struggling. I supposed this can be viewed as more than a rant than a question, or maybe it's just a cry for help. All I know is I've dug myself a hole to hide in, and lack the energy and motivation to climb out of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 05:50:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It has only been a few days since the election. Share kind, reassuring words, hold her close and make sure she knows that you are supporting her. Hopefully, the Xanax will start working and calm her down. We all need to stay hopeful through this time, and believe that it will all work out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-16 05:54:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>As someone who is falling behind in school and being drowned in depression to the point of considering dropping out. Yup, I can say that at the moment Skyrim and Pokemon Sun are my will to live.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scared of failing, yet destined to.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-17 09:04:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>My depression is causing me to fall behind, and to catch up you need to; be motivated, be productive, and talk to teachers. Of course my dumbass is basically unable to do any of those things. I'm mortified by my teachers because they treat my failures like a waste of their time and so my self esteem have basically dropped to the point where I'd rather fail than talk to someone to make up a test. Basically I'm skewed and I fear I'll end up dropping out of high school and excepting that I'm a huge failure to my very smart, educated family who will defiantly look down on me. I wanted someone to hear this and I really struggle with talk to people, I guess it feels good to tell someone this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-17 17:05:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>While I'm only 15, I can tell I will be playing as long as games are being released. Nothing is only for kids. You can do whatever you want, who cares about the age label?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 01:17:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Confused Athiest here, what is going on in the second half of the video. The man seems to be silent but looks like he's throwing up, the women next to him looks like she's held captive. What on earth is happening?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 05:02:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>A surgeon I knew kept a box of all the prints showing when people died, that he was allowed to keep at least. Kind of dark in its own right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-06 04:21:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is no one else annoyed that the OP doesn't know the difference between a turtle and a tortoise?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Never been asked at, and fear I never will.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 05:34:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm 15, a sophomore in High School, and I've never been asked out. Granted I'm young, it's not weird for sophomores to still be single, but people constantly call me pretty, cute, whatever and I've never been asked out. I don't think I will be... I'm really awkward. Like really. I feel as though if I was asked out I'd freak out, and thus drive whoever away. How do people act normal is situations like that. With how I behave when people say they like me, I don't think I'll ever get a boyfriend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DAE get paranoid after a frightening movie or piece of fiction?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 11:51:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Been watching a lot of Markiplier playing horror games lately, and once it's dark out I'm petrified of hanging a foot off the bed, going downstairs, looking out the window, opening doors, etc. It is 2 AM and I'm freaking out, yet I don't want to turn on the lights because it's a better experience when it's dark. I hate the feeling of being this scared but don't want to fix it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hate being pretty.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 08:25:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, this will sound bad, and self-centered so please bare with me. I'm in my Sophomore year, and I hate having people like me. So many guys I get to know, and it ends up they want to date or whatever. I'm not interested in dating anyone right now. I have zero interest in sex. But even just today, I have had two guys admit their feelings for me. It sucks. I hate having to turn people down because they get really heartbroken or angry. I don't think I'm super hot or anything. I don't wear makeup, I wear baggy clothes, but I have a naturally pretty face. I also have a naturally flirty personality, and I'm constantly scared I'm leading on a guy or what have you. They are always asking to hang out, and I always say yes despite being extremely scared. One of my closest friends hates me because she's jealous. I know it sounds cocky, or like I'm trying to brag about having guys flaunting over me, but I hate it. Sometimes they try and pressure me into sex, or to come over to their place to 'chill'. I'm 16. I rarely hang out with my best friends, never mind going over to a guys house. I hate turning guys down, but I also know how awful it feels to be led on. I can't talk about it with my friends because it sounds like I'm bragging, and I don't want to. I just want it to stop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Simply want to rant without repercussions.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-07 09:39:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't expect anything particularly interesting, respond if you would like but I'm not necessarily looking for advice. I'm a fuck up. Harsh.. yes, but it's kind of true. I'm extremely grateful that my parents are as supportive as they are, but I know I'm disappointing them even if they won't say it. I grew up being a model student. Straight A's, 90%'s, honor rolls. I remember my brother struggling with his ADHD, and me looking like the best student. In the 5th grade, I stole some toys from a friend. Not sure if others think its that big a deal or not, but it haunts me. This friend... was not a friend. Her mother was a narcissist and basically forced me to hang out with her daughter and have sleepovers. The girl bragged and was spoiled and it drove me nuts. I was overwhelmed with jealousy, and event stole things. Respectively, she found out. I returned some things (lying to make it sound less severe), but her mother and she decided to make the rest of my 5th and 6th-grade year a living hell. I probably deserved it to be honest. Her mother would threaten me, saying she would get me expelled, get me arrested. Her mother threatened to search her home and would ask my mom what she would do to punish me. Her mother was extremely active for our class, and I had many things with her, so I forced to be surrounded by threats throughout my day. This marked the start of my depression. In 7th grade, I had new friends. I met a guy... who I really liked. I mean a lot. He liked me, and we would talk over text but I was too shy to hang out or really talk to him in person for that matter. It's my fault it never worked out, (probably for the best in the long run) but he was not happy with that. My depression became more severe and I grew distant from him at the end of 7th grade. I've never been clingy, but for some reason, speaking to this guy made me happy. I allowed him to become my entire world, and I missed him uncontrollably until this year. I won't say, love, because of it sure as hell wasn't that, but I cared for this guy and I missed him because he acting like he genuinely cared about me, something I have only ever gotten from my parents. The loss of this person in my life worsened my depression a lot. Mind you, I had been diagnosed with depression, and thus was not receiving treatment. 9th grade. High school didn't treat me well. I felt pressured to be that good student I used to be, but depression took me over and homework and schoolwork became a thing of the past. I fell behind, only so much, but enough that I would break down during class, and felt my life start to crumble beneath me. After breaking down during my 6th period Technical Theater class to a point I couldn't do work was the first time a teacher told me to get help. Thanks to her I pursued a therapist and finally began getting treatment for my depression. 10th grade. The second I finished 1st Semester finals, I broke. I lost everything. I was constantly sick, to a point I couldn't miss school without doctors note. My A's became B's, and eventually D's. I began passing out, as avoidance to going to school. Finally, I was diagnosed with POTS. My parents pulled me out of school a few weeks ago and enrolled me in online school. I finally felt relaxed and like I had some control over my life. But now my mom is constantly pressuring me to do my class work, even if it hasn't been assigned yet, all my stress about school has reappeared and I'm back in a situation I had finally escaped from after 6 years. I have my license. I'm 16 years old. I just want to be able to do things as I please, yet I'm still being pressured by the people who I thought most trusted me. My mother is easily offended and has never played the villain, she's always the victim so I can't bring it up with her. I know she'll say, "don't you dare blame this on me," because it's how she responds to every situation. She urges me to grow up yet refused to treat me as such. There is is. My crash and burn. I'm 16, I have my entire life ahead of me. I'm supposed to be excited, but as people continue to tell me what to do, my motivation slips away. How does someone succeed when they feel like their slowing being pulled underground. I know it's not my parent's fault because they mean well. I'm probably just being an ungrateful brat. I just, like to complain and my life situation has felt so weird lately I wanted to shove all of it on text and sent it out there, so I can't say I've held it in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Video Games make me stable.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 07:42:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have depression and POTS and I have absolutely no motivation to do anything ever. I don't like doing school work, I don't like eating, or drinking, or taking my medication or showering or staying on a schedule or- I don't like anything. I can rarely do something for than 15 minutes. I don't crave to do things without losing interest almost instantaneously. Every now and then, I find a game, and I finally feel like i'm enjoying something. I have a distraction from the crushing realization that i'm a screw up as a person and I have responsibilities crawling up my spine. These bursts of enjoyment don't last long, eventually I'll get bored. Ill come back to it eventually but in another burst perhaps months later. I take advantage of these, because I know that soon enough, I'll forget what it feels like to be distracted. However, I am forced away from this distraction. My dad uses No Mans Sky as a relaxing relief from his stress, anxiety and work, and thus I am inclined to hand over the control and go else where. I know he needs it, perhaps more than me. But those hours, in which I'm exiled to my room, I loath. I wish for nothing more than to return and start playing. He'll play till midnight, so i'll go down at 1am and play until the sunrise. Then he and my mom get upset with me, "you are breaking your schedule, you are just being selfish and a brat." Is this true? In many retrospects yes, but I'm happy. If this is the only thing I find enjoyment in, then why bother doing anything else. I'm behind on school, on my medical situation, I'm behind on life. I hate having my parents be upset with me. But their constant complaints make me miserable. A schedule makes me miserable. Curling up on the couch and playing a game feels like the only relief I have anymore. Its all that I want to do. Even now. My dad is downstair, No Mans Sky lighting up the room. And I am here, using this rant as a distraction. Sitting alone in silence will make me break down. I will cease to exist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-30 11:28:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I find it irritating that it's one cent away from being exactly $40.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-30 11:56:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you referring to the slanted comments? It's part of r/mildlyinfuriating to further enhance your fury.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I don't want to be human.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 11:10:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I normally post my weird rants to r/offmychest, but I feel as though it was more fitting here. I don't want to do the things people do to be apart of society. I don't want to gain an education, I don't want to get a job or buy a house or get involved with politics. I don't want friendships. Hell, I don't want to eat, or drink or sleep. I don't want to. Of course, everyone says tough, you have to. But being dead just seems easier. I have no motivation to do any of those things, how am I supposed to do them. All i do is lie to avoid situations. I'm dug so deep I cannot just tell the truth and try and fix it. I am a selfish person who does nothing but waste my parents money, and ceasing to exist simply fixes all those problems. I've been to therapy, but I have nothing to talk about. I physically can't talk to peoples face about my personal situation. I can't. When I tell stuff to my parents I write it down and communicate that way, because I can't say it to their face. I get dizzy, my heart rate get really high very easily and quickly. Doctors have told me maybe POTS. They say take medicine, drink and eat regularly, have a normal sleep schedule, do all this stuff. I don't. I can't. My mom gets upset, saying I don't care, but I guess she's right. Doctor after doctor, blood tests weekly, she wants to know whats wrong. I can't tell her no, she gets hurt to easily. I want everyone to leave me alone, to leave me alone in my room to wilt and I want everyone to forget about me. This make little sense, I branch off into different topics, i'm sorry. Guess I'm just kind of freaking out. I have never thought of myself as suicidal, but I also wish I didn't exist. I just want some help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Question about Season!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 05:13:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just started playing, (very late, I know) and I was wondering if its possible to get rewards from previous Seasons. I haven't been able to find an answer. I am playing on PS4.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 05:14:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Distractions mostly. I play a game, binge a youtube series, or just doodle a bunch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 16:46:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely. I recently left a public school and joined online school. I'm not exactly trying to keep my friendships, because I don't really care? Since being told "you're sick" my friends drifted away and I guess I never tried very hard to reel them back. Some days I'll only leave my room once to get a snack. That will be it. My mom will come in to talk, I usually only give one word responses and thats the end of it. Its labeled as lazy, and now I'm starting to think there is something wrong with me, the more I analyze it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 04:05:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pink blossoms in bloom Fields of flowers filled with joy Its snowing on Mt. Fuji</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 15:27:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you. For making me feel a bit more normal. My depression declined rapidly in the last couple of days so I talked to my family, and they are starting to see my situation from my point of view.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Major vent about my current situation.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 03:53:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here is the whole deal. I left public school because of mental and physical health problems and my parents spent a lot of money enrolling me in an online school that I was really excited to start. A month in my school work stopped. I just, stopped. I haven't had any motivation to do it since May. I sit down with it in front of me and get nothing done. My depression which I've had for a couple years periodically gets worse to the point I won't leave bed. I won't eat, shower, all that. The last time I was like this, my mother came in and told me that I was an 8 year, talked about how I don't do anything and about how I'm going to live at home wasting her money. (she doesn't have a job, mind you) I guess that really hit me hard and after that I was in a state where I was the most suicidal I had ever been. I made a plan, thought about how I would do. A few days later, I had my wisdom teeth removed and for about 2 weeks after that my mood had greatly improved, perhaps it was the insane amount of drugs I was on, or because my mom was really supportive. However, thats over now. My depression is back and my mom is also extremely depressed. She is depressed because of me, because I'm slowly ruining her life. She still talks about college because she always imagined me having an education and a good job, but I'm in a state where I want to commit suicide to make it easier for her. Because i'm the problem. I never have energy or motivation, I get in short spurts where i'm really entertained by a game, maybe a few days sometimes a week, and I'm bored of it again. I don't eat actual food, I don't exercise, I don't leave my room. Im sure everyone will say you just listed your problems, do those things and everything will fix itself. I can't do those things without motivation. I can't do anything. I feel like i'm losing it being expected to now take care of my mom while she's in this state but I can't take care of myself. I notice now, as I'm writing this, that I never say that I will commit suicide. I say want, but not will. But whenever I talked about it, I realize that will is there. Since the 5th grade I told myself I wasn't going to live past 18. I always said none of it was worth it. Part of me still believes that. The other part of me just wants to find a working husband and be a housewife, because I am more than happy with being a housewife because hell, its something. This ran made zero sense and I apologize, I changed subjects a couple of times, I just never know what to do. Whenever things get better, a little while later every thing just gets a whole fucking lot worse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Missed Happy Home Designer DLC</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 05:22:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've missed every single Animal Crossing Happy Home Designer when I took a long break due to mental illness. Since it seems I cannot get them over WiFi, and cannot find any amiibo cards for said characters, is there anyway to get them or at least those items?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Am I actually Ace?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 09:39:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just yesterday, something in my brain clicked. i don't know what it was, and I cannot remember what triggered it, but I had a sudden aggressive interest in Asexuality. I'm 16. So, I have honestly no clue what sexual attraction is or feels like. I'm considered pretty naturally cute, i had guys hit in me back when I was at a public school. It was always about sex, I never understood it. I had zero interest in having sex, I'd never looked at someone attractive, and thought about sex. I didn't realize that was a thing. I thought it was all exaggerated. The thought of asexuality never crossed my mind, because what I knew it as was that every asexual was aromantic. I knew I wasn't aromantic, because I love the idea of having a boyfriend and cuddling and all that. So I assumed I wasn't aromantic, and thus, assumed I wasn't asexual. But something snapped, the weird no-sex, bi curious part of me I just crushed down there because I just assumed I was straight, was brought up and I began doing really extensive research into different sexualities. I assumed your sexuality was who you wanted to date, not have sex with, because sex has always been out of the question. I learned more and more, and asexuality sounded more and more like me the more I researched. I felt less weird. I tried to break it down more. I want company, thats what I want. I want someone to take naps with, and hold hands, and go to lunch together. Hell, I have a preference for men, but I could totally see myself having that kind of a relationship with a female, or gender queer, I don't care, just a funny, caring person. I just don't want to have sex. I view having sex the same way I view taking drugs. I just don't feel like i'm missing out. Masturbating never felt good, It just left me feeling, why do people do this. Porn was always been meh. Sure I get aroused, junk still works, but I usually watch it for like 2 minutes, because I get bored by it. My vagina calms down and porn becomes a boring video. The more I broke these things down. The more I felt like I fit into this group of asexual. Maybe I'm wrong. Maybe the community will say something different. But the "label" if you will, of Asexual Panromantic with a male preference, feels so fitting and just, comfortable. I guess I just want another opinion, because I feel like I'm not allowed to make that decision on my own.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 09:24:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im a young person who very recently came out as Ace. I used to be unbothered by sex scenes in movies and watching porn, but as i've aged (I'm in my teens), Sex scenes became uncomfortable, Porn is just boring, masturbating doesn't feel like anything. All this happened before I even understood what asexuality was. I'm not repulsed by sex, merely completely uninterested. Brain over body. Don't feel the need to follow your libido if your brain isn't on the same page. If you don't enforce the arousal, it will go away much quicker and you can just move on from it. Its sounds like ignore the libido will be more comfortable than dealing with feeling awful about it afterward. There is nothing shameful about changing. It doesn't make you weird. Just think of it as growing up. Not in a sense that you are immature, but theres nothing you can do about it. Nothing shameful about getting older, and you can't reverse even if you wanted to. I can't give a ton of advice. Try different things. Think about pros over cons. Hell, find a therapist if it gets bad. Maybe your developed a discomfort for sexual things. That's fine and its nothing to be worried about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 09:26:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>When ever guys freak out about me rejecting them, I simply say i'm asexual and have zero interest in anything and suddenly all interest the've ever had for me vanishes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 09:29:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I learned only a couple days ago. Nothing has changed in that time, but I just feel a lot more comfortable with myself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Making a group on villains for fun, each are based on a sexuality or gender. Feel free to suggest names. :)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 01:04:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 01:11:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just doodling characters, each one is a super villain with their own sets of powers and stuff. Not for anything, just for fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I am deprived of human interaction.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 06:02:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically, I've never told anyone this. No one has to read it, its pretty long, so I get it. I am a 16 year old female, who has never been in a relationship. It's not uncommon for a 16 year old to have never dated and been totally fine with it, and I get that, but it is tearing me apart. Sure, I've had people have crushed on me in the past, but it's always people I haven't been interested in, and I'm aggressively against the concept of pity dating. Sometimes I regret it, because I avoided those relationships out of pure discomfort and awkwardness, because I usually don't know the person too well. The other times, when someone had a crush on me and I was interested, it became obvious that the guys mind was on sex, which I have absolutely no interest in (I recently came out as Asexual). I had to be taken out of public school for mental and physical health issue, and so now, I have almost no contact with anyone. I only leave the house to go to the library to do schoolwork. With all of this. I crave a relationship more than anything. I watch romantic movies for the moment of feeling comfortable, despite it wrecking me afterward. Sometimes, I think its to a point where it isn't necessarily romantic affection I crave, but just a friend. I only talk to my friends through snapchat. Since leaving public school they feel i've betrayed them, and thus I am not worth making time for. So , the only 3 friends I've successfully kept, no longer view me as a priority. I go to lunch by myself, go shopping by myself, see movies by myself. My mom gets on my nerves, my brother is in college (we aren't very close), and my dad works until 5. I do everything by myself. I don't even think about inviting people anymore because I know the answer. There is only one person who wants to talk to me. A guy I knew in freshman year who is also homeschooled. He never talks to me though, and since he isn't the type of person I'd normally associate with, I don't particularly care if we become friends with. He talks about how much he wants to be friends and hang out, but he only messages me once a month if even. Hanging out with him is uncomfortable though, because he is a lot different than me, and I know he has a crush on me even though I've made it clear I'm not interested in him. (He's respectful about it, despite talking about how cute we'd be as a couple) Summary. I don't talk to anyone anymore and I am becoming a shell of a human being.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 08:28:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Asexual merely means lack of sexual attraction. I don't feel sexual attraction towards anyone. Sex is just something I don't care for. Usually along with asexuality is no sex drive. Perhaps part of it is, I don't want to fool around. I want something serious, someone I can rely on. Perhaps I'm just too used to the whole idea of high school sweethearts getting married and everything. I don't have to think about serious stuff. But I idea of loving someone and moving into an apartment and making pancakes in your pajamas sounds so great and I want that now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Told i'm too immature to decide if i'm Ace. (long)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 09:33:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I told my therapist that I recently started identifying as asexual. She didn't really understand what is was, I tried to explain but she seemed pretty convinced I was just immature. Talked about how her daughter wasn't thinking about sex at 16, didn't real let me explain what sexual attraction is specifically. She began listing off all the reason she didn't think I was asexual. - I am behind on school work - I do not work - No constant routine - Value "play" over "work" None of these things are necessarily wrong, all are related to my pretty severe depression and motivational issues (why I go to a therapist) but it hurt none the less. She rattle on and on about how teenagers aren't thinking about sex and my disinterest in sex wasn't abnormal. Saying I'm too immature to give myself that label. I vented to my mom after the appointment who seemed uncomfortable with the subject, saying I just wanted a label, and "we'll get you there someday" (????) and after that it wasn't brought up again. Later today I brought it up to my dad, saying I was upset about it. He gave me a funny face and said "I'm not sure I buy her argument." Conversation ended there. My friend said that it showed maturity that I can acknowledge my preferences and that i'm not the default setting, which made me feel a lot better. I identify(ed) with asexuality because it made me feel a lot comfortable with myself. I didn't do it to belong to a community or so I run around telling everyone I'm part of LGBT+. I felt more comfortable with myself. I wear the ring and it makes me feel more confident. Learning about asexuality and identifying with it made me feel like I got a part of my life together. Now, I'm not so sure. It was kind of a sudden thing, but it's because every single thing I read about asexuality related to me in some way. Please just be honest. I guess I just want some other opinions. Edit: Thank you so much for all the honest responses! I really appreciate people taking the time to read this and respond. The situation was stressing me, and seeing everyones response calmed me down. It's hard being 16 and being considered an adult but not old enough to question anyone or anything. I will still be seeing her (for my next appointment as least) and chances are she'll bring it (I has visible upset last I saw her) so hopeful I will be able to educate her more on it, not just for my sake, but anyone she sees in the future. Question my sexuality has been very overwhelming and I'm happy that this is such a kind and welcoming community. Thank you again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 14:06:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm 16. Frankly, I don't think I can determine if I've finished puberty till your there, so I'll say no. Although, I think i'm done growing. Haven't in probably a year. So, yes, being a "Late Bloomer" is a possibility.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The saw movies make absolutely no sense.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 08:33:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have very recently gotten in interest into horror movies, and I want to see the new Jigsaw movie coming out. Since, in honor of this, the first 7 movies are all on Netflix, i've decided to watch them. These movies are fucking terrible. They make no sense and requires a fucking mind reader to be able to set up the traps or whatever. My dad was like, "it's just torture porn, it isn't meant to have an actual plot" and I get that that definitely is a part of it, but they made 7 of these movies. All of which were in theaters. There is no way they could have made a successful franchise based exclusively to people who like torture. These fucking movies are all supposed to be connected but they introduce a completely new set of characters and act like they can tie brand new characters into the events of the first. The first movie where EVERYTHING WAS EXPLAINED! I swear, its heavy rain all over again. I'm on the 5th movie, and already irritated. (Spoilers coming up) Like movie 3 and 4 happen simultaneously, but theres only about 2 characters that have new lines going into the second. At the start of the 4th movie, after the title sequence (which happens in the future) they show magazines and articles about John Kramer, who is Jigsaw. They know who this guy is. He is a serial killer, why don't y'all just kill him, arrest him, I don't know. What, you don't know where he is? These things must happen in one city. How big can the city be. You would think they would be putting more effort into catching this guy! Then, the 5th movies starts after the end of the 4th movies. But not the very end, because that scene comes later. Also, the scene at the very end of the 4th movie, is the same scene that happens before the title sequence during the 4th movie. The scenes are out of order, the characters do not match up between movies. Great, so the plot sucks. Awesome. But what this guy is doing is basically impossible. What tranquilizer knocks someone out, and has them wake up completely aware of their surroundings. Also, they seem to wake up exactly when the movie plays. Or he's watching the person. He is sitting there watching a sleeping person until they wake up so he can dive across his desk and hit play. What kind of remote is hooked up to every single vcr, who knows. I guess the guy is dying and has nothing better to do. Oh, it could be Amanda or the detective. Also, the the trap that Amanda places on Lin that fires shotgun shells when John dies. Hey it looks a lot like the reverse bear trap Amanda wears in the first movie. Amanda made the trap on Lin, she can't have made the trap she wore though. So. John taught her how to make these traps look like their made by the same people. How about traps that require two people. The first movie for example. How did he know that the key in the tub would go down the drain. How did he know they would wake up at the same time. How stupid were to two guys to not notice that John was the corpse in the middle. Also, why the fuck was John the corpse. Why would you use the hacksaw on the very thick chains, rather than the weak little locker locks that were exposed. You know, the ones you can open with bare hands if your eager enough. Doctor boy from the first movie, Gordon Freeman or whatever his name was, cuts off his own foot and crawls out. Door shuts, credits. Okay, but what happened? Is he alive, is he dead, did he get home, your going to give me this much fucking exposition to what is essentially the main character of the first film, and he's just gone, poof, foot left behind, as you do. There is so much more shit I could write about but I'm organizing my Pokemon cards and frankly i'm tired. I'm not a hardcore movie person. I will watch bad movies and not criticize them. But this franchise is one of the worst written i've come across. Hell, i'd rather watch the star wars holiday special than this series. And yes, you are all going to say, "Just don't watch it then" but i'm stubborn, and i've committed and I refuse to back out in hopes it will A) Make more sense later on B) Catch me up on the lore for the Jigsaw movie. Sorry, stupidity at this level stresses me out. I also don't care if you spoil it for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 22:54:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not related to ace. I want to adopt kids eventually. As someone whose struggled through life, I think that birthing children is selfish. So, I think adopting a child, whose already here, would be fun and forgiving.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 08:38:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, but this is really sweet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 18:28:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>My computer layout has this, never been a problem</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Canceled bounties can not be retrieved again?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 01:10:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Edit: If someone could cancel their daily bounty after selecting it, and see if they can pick it back up, I #8217;d really appreciate it. I #8217;m extremely frustrated that I can not find an answer for this. I had the requisition pack bounty active early on in my game, and I decided to cancel it thinking I could pick it back up after i've finished the game. Well, I just did that, and the bounty has an X and is highlighted red, with no option to accept it. I tested it by canceling a daily bounty, and sure enough its highlighted red and I can not get it anymore. So, have I just screwed myself of getting that reward. If so, I wish they were more clear about that, as upon canceling a bounty all it says is progress will be lost. If not, does anyone know how I can get this bounty back?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 04:19:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, thats where it's highlighted red. I can not select it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 12:57:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. It's true you can't, but for some reason you can accept the special bounty early on. Like it's bugged. It's available from the board not in the menu, but like you accept it and you get it, same as getting quests off of the board next to it in the tower.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 02:18:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have finished the story. It shows up in the bounties list, but I can not accept it. It has an X where is timer would go. It is not in my quest menu.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I have no right to want to die.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 09:40:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im 16, and honestly, my life is not horrible. I have loving parents who do not fight, a calm brother, 4 pets, clean clothes, food on my table. I have my own car, phone, computer and all the game systems I want. I'm spoiled. Mind you, I do work for things, my parents are not fond of simple giving, but work I do to earn, others my age just have to do, with nothing in return besides the basic necessities. I have a job, I work at Del Taco, everyone there is nice. Despite being in the most ideal situation I could be, I don't want to be apart of it anymore. Depression and anxiety absolutely destroyed my ability to gain an education. My parents took me out of public school and into an expensive online program, but my procrastination, pure laziness, and the fact that I am genuinely always tired, I don't do my work. I no longer feel a sense of pride from doing anything, so that drive is completely gone. I've been working at my job a little over a week, and I've already taken two sick days and I'm tired and ready to quit. I can not consistently keep up with anything for more than a week before I get tired and basically give up. I eat usually 1 meal a day, and by meal its usually junk food. I don't drink enough liquids. I don't exercise. I know why i'm depressed. I'm completely aware of all the problems in my life and understand how to fix them, but I don't. I don't have it in me. The 'cure' for depression is doing all the things depression prevents you from doing. I genuinely dislike having to eat and drink, its a chore. I'm spoiled, and get too comfortable with having things just given to me. I've recently been struggling with self identity in my sexuality. I'm a mess. I'm not a lost cause to everyone but me. Maybe I just want to take the easy way out. I don't see myself cut out for life. I can't see myself completely high school, or going to college or even getting a proper job. The only thing I feel comfortable with is being a housewife because I like cleaning, but its a weak goal and something no one else will ever support. Everyone tells me I have to go to school, and get a career and thinking about growing up makes me shut down. In the 5th grade I started recognizing the fact that I'm not fit to be a member of society, and make me promise to myself that I would kill myself before I turned 18. I turn 17 in 6 days. I have a year to suck it up and get it done with. I feel selfish. I have a great life, that I should be happy with. I know it will affect people around me. I look like i'm depressed for being lonely. While I take prozac I tend to be a visually happy person. I am not comfortable expressing my problems to those around me. I just want to be done with everything. I've done nothing productive and I know I never will. This isn't necessarily a goodbye, maybe a cry for help. I don't know what to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Proper self harm for the first time?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 07:40:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've personally never been one to self harm, i've tried cutting but could never tolerate the sharp pain. Today, I had been having urges to burn. I'd never done it before but, just felt like i deserved it. I did it for the first time. I poured hot wax on the back of my hand and help my hand above the fire. I liked it. Kinda just looks like a rash. Been maybe 10 minutes, it still hurts pretty bad. It's weird. I want to do it more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>