<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7131</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 14:35:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now the real battle starts...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 23:06:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, thanks for this! I always had trouble landing that last hit, never knew you could skip the first hit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Beard patches?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 17:10:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey guys, so I'm trying to grow a beard (aren't we all?) and Im having some trouble with my right side. So the left side of my face is fine, all hairs growing downwards and no patches. However on the right side there seems to be a different direction of growth which leaves a noticeable gap, any tips to try sort this out?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 17:12:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would attach a picture but im not quite sure how to</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Reylos and TLJ twitter minions</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 18:19:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>When the TLJ fanboys and reylos defend the movie so visciously that they result to swarming others, I cant tell if theyre doing it to piss off other fans or that they genuinely think its the best SW movies to date. On top of that, the constant swarming on those who critique the movies is just ridiculous. Here are the Twitter links: https://twitter.com/BuddyBoyBaxter/status/1034634570140987392?s=19 https://twitter.com/MrKentSanderson/status/1034619707230511104?s=19 https://twitter.com/FlyingTrilobite/status/1031922183583477760?s=19 https://twitter.com/GreyJediRyan/status/1035126291945713664?s=19</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 18:32:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is George Lucas all over again with the forced Anakin and Padme segments in AoTC, only somehow Rian Johnson managed to cement this whole Reylo craze</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 18:52:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have this really horrible feeling that they're going to turn ghost Luke into comedy relief.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 18:57:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>"kill it if you have to"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 19:58:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think Finn and Rey is also very forced, there just isn't that natural spark Han and Leia had, I'm not sure if it's the writing or the acting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 20:14:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm convinced they've only seen the sequels and spin offs yet are even more touchy than most die hard fans I know, must be the hormones.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 23:11:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man Kelly Marie Tran is a lovely person irl but the bad acting combined with bad writing really hurt, the kiss with finn had me cringing hard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rian Johnson attacks small youtuber...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 12:36:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 12:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>The guy honestly acts like a man child</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 12:55:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=Rian%20Johnson</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 13:13:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you imagine Spielberg, Nolan or Tarantino taking this much time gawking and attacking fans who criticize them on Twitter?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 13:17:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 13:21:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's my main issue, anyone who doesn't like TLJ = automatic toxic man baby, according to them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>