<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject8395</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 20:03:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Evil as a descriptive term rather than a noun or adjective because of its looming and dark out-of-place appearance, although some people believe that the power to bring people back from death is evil itself. So go figure  #129320;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 18:20:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll miss you  lt;\3 hole in the community, RIP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 21:04:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>But why not catch them and relocate like snakes and crocs? Why make such a cult of it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 21:14:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it is a cult if you have to join an exclusive group, dress up in a certain outfit and blow on a horn. Even so we evolve, it #8217;s not like we are praising the sunrise anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 21:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not praising them, I just have respect for them. I can understand why farms raise them and kill them to be eaten or why people have pets. I just don #8217;t understand why anyone would want to ride a horse/camel/bull/pig/etc seems wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 22:10:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes but it has an endgame which is feeding people, where as riding has no real purpose</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 22:13:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not most abused but definitely most overlooked form of abuse to that point where it has become accepted</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 22:16:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean is there any actual proof they don #8217;t mind being ridden? And people do ride pigs, is that somehow more cruel than a horse?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 22:49:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, I didn #8217;t think of that! But still seems kinda bad :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 22:52:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I suppose it is more of a rural practice but it happens. Horses do occasionally buck and I think they get trained/broken so young they  #8220;learn #8221; not to though :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Old boy blop  lt;3</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 02:00:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Took this in the Amsterdam torture museum! My first ghost :D *completely unedited and ofc it had to be on a slightly blurry picture</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 21:53:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 00:41:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bottom of the stairs on the right!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 04:50:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg you did some edits on my photo! Thank you so much :D that #8217;s awesome! Above this photo was hanging cages and some blue lights, i #8217;ll also add this museum is very well lit :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 11:02:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah! I see it as like hunched up or crawling up the stairs! Was so happy when I saw this look back through my pics :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Swapping from cutting to burning?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 11:33:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Heya, first time poster (F22) :) Couldn #8217;t find this against any of the rules so I #8217;ll just go ahead. I #8217;ve been self harming (cutting) for a few years now, on meds, seen therapist and such. Stop harming for a little while then relapse every so often. Recently I #8217;ve swapped from cutting to burning myself and I wanted to know and tips or tricks anybody has on care and cover? My burns aren #8217;t seriously bad but I suppose they are quite obviously self harm and are taking much longer to heal than cuts :/ Even if you have nothing to say thank you for listening and letting me vent xx</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>