<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject5622</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>- -.-- .--. . / .. -. / -- --- .-. ... . / -.-. --- -.. . / ... --- / -... .-.. .. -. -.. / .--. . --- .--. .-.. . / .-- .. .-.. .-.. / -... . / .- -... .-.. . / - --- / ..- -. -.. . .-. ... - .- -. -.. / .-- .... .- - / -.-- --- ..- / .- .-. . / ... .- -.-- .. -. --. --..-- / - --- --- .-.-.-</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 07:50:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Translation: TYPE IN MORSE CODE SO BLIND PEOPLE WILL BE ABLE TO UNDERSTAND WHAT YOU ARE SAYING, TOO.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;ve decided to start a bucket list after seeing the post about the guy who #8217;s friend was diagnosed with terminal cancer, and I #8217;d like some recommendations/things you #8217;d put on yours.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 23:00:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bucket List: * I #8217;ve always wanted one of those BFF necklaces, but I #8217;ve never had anyone to share it with * Explore Japan, China, Canada and England in their entireties * Build a giant fighting robot and enter it in a competition * Fly in a Wing-Suit * Live in a castle with my partner * Meet somebody perfect for me * Make homemade candies (jellybeans, chocolate, mints, etc.) * Do stand-up comedy at least once * Record an album * Do a podcast * Become an animator * Write a book/make a movie * Have a documentary made about myself * Spend a day with a very important person (President, Dalai Lama, Queen of England, etc.) * Give out life essentials (food, water, clothing, etc.) to people in need (homeless, impoverished nation, poor, etc.) * Befriend a homeless person and spend the day with them * Befriend a tiger * Go on as many cruises as possible * Make a ton of friends across the globe * Have a fully-functioning mechanical suit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Woman arguing how clipping your dog #8217;s ears isn #8217;t immoral (I know it #8217;s not Facebook, but still insane).</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 06:50:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Chilling out with my good boy, Colt.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 01:11:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Despite what one might be told, Pandas can also survive solely on a diet of orange popsicles.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 17:26:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Going out to a friend #8217;s birthday party tonight, how do I look?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 23:12:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If you don #8217;t remember Mrs. Gorf than I #8217;m not your friend anymore!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 03:08:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Feel like I can bring some wholesomeness to this meme.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 23:25:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You #8217;re perfect just the way you are, don #8217;t let somebody #8217;s ignorance make you believe you #8217;re worth less than what you really are.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 06:51:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 01:44:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I think this is supposed to be... social commentary?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 01:54:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;m interested in an obsidian fireplace, but I wasn #8217;t expecting this in my research...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 16:36:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Apparently I can get 100 free spins that don #8217;t cost anything by spending money...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 17:02:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Every time I leave the house</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 17:53:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My very silly floofball, Pendleton.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 07:57:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It may be cheap, but it #8217;s the thought that counts.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 14:39:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;m always trying my best to help out my trans friend (ftm) with his confidence and self-image but I have no experience in helping with this kind of thing.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 00:12:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel that telling my own gender would help with giving advice. I #8217;m a cis male, fairly masculine. My friend often compares himself to me. Being naturally feminine, he feels like he #8217;s not good enough all the time, coupled with anxiety and depression. He talks about hating who he is, feeling destroyed whenever he looks in the mirror and says he #8217;s jealous of who I am as a person. I know I #8217;m not the source of his insecurities, but I do feel partly responsible for how he feels and I want to help him with these issues and boost his confidence. I always try my best to be supportive but I feel like I #8217;m running out of options.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;ve gotten used to having my dog sleep in my room with me to the point I can #8217;t sleep properly unless I have him to keep me company.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 14:31:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always feel so relaxed whenever I hear him snoring. I put an extra soft, small blanket in his bed for him to lie on and leave some toys, food, water and a plastic bone that #8217;s too big for him to choke on but can still be properly chewed on. I leave his bed next to mine so I can have him close to me and pet him or let him lick my hand whenever I get a little lonely or just can #8217;t sleep. I #8217;ve also noticed that he #8217;s been a lot happier lately and whenever I go to get him for the night he jumps up on my leg and gets really excited. I love having him around, I love his look whenever he sees me and most of all, I love him, from the bottom of my heart</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Siberian Flying Squirrel is known to make its nests in abandoned woodpecker holes; however, they will occasionally use birdhouses, too.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 18:12:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Will the universe ever stop expanding?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 05:12:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t mean will it ever be so massive that its own gravity will stop it from growing, but rather will it ever run out of energy to create matter? Is there a finite amount of energy the expansion can create or will the universe continue growing forever (discounting apocalypse theories)?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;m ready for my x-post to r/comedycemetery.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 23:41:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I have Asperger Syndrome, which is a mild form of autism. I #8217;d like to tell others about my experience with the condition but I #8217;m not that great at writing long posts without going off topic, so AMA.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 00:02:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ronald Reagan escalating the War on Drugs [1982]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 04:03:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #8220;Put down your pen, fren. #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 00:41:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How have you been lately?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 03:37:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you #8217;re still in school (Secondary, College or University) how has it been so far? If you #8217;re working has anything happened recently that #8217;s caught your interest, like a friendly customer or just a good work day overall? How about life in general, has anything interesting happened lately?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 06:49:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not exactly that kind of guy. Sorry lad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 12:39:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>What #8217;s been getting you down?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 14:52:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>How so? What kind of stuff has been going on in your life?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 17:40:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t we all?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 08:42:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Scrotum Squall.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 08:46:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t tell me what to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 08:49:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jokes on you, 0-1=0</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 09:08:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit . . . I think you #8217;re onto something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 10:21:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about the fact that I chose to protect the puppies?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 13:15:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most probably.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I know this is intended to be a positive subreddit, but there are people who deal with crap every day everywhere, so I #8217;m posting this here for those who need it along with those who don #8217;t but want to be able to help others.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 14:06:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 15:05:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, but it #8217;s less for the upvotes and more for the saves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 15:15:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I certainly hope so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 15:52:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I certainly hope you find the help you #8217;re looking for.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 15:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you need somebody to talk to more casually about these things feel free to message me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 17:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Change that to milliseconds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 20:07:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jokes on you mate, you just made me smile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 20:44:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not at all, man, just want to help people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 21:27:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dammit, I thought I told you to keep that under wraps!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 21:27:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>The trick is glue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 21:27:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s not even a roast, that #8217;s just being a dick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 22:27:55</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;[Toll-free telephone numbers in the North American Numbering Plan](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Toll-free_telephone_numbers_in_the_North_American_Numbering_Plan). In the United States of America, Canada, and other countries participating in the North American Numbering Plan, a toll-free telephone number has one of the area codes 800, 833, 844, 855, 866, 877, and 888. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 22:48:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know, I hadn #8217;t really thought about that. Still, you #8217;re welcome, I #8217;m happy to help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 02:13:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not in Canada, no. Igloos don #8217;t exactly do the trick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 02:30:42</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;What hairstyle did the suspect have? #8221;  #8220;All of them. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 02:32:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re honestly one of the most beautiful women I #8217;ve ever seen!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 02:35:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re welcome, mate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 05:57:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Being shy is cute and all until you #8217;re actually it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 05:58:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you mean?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 06:12:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>The people working on the other end of the lines are trained professionals, they should be able to help you deal with what you #8217;re feeling and going through. Of course, talking to a friend helps even more with this. I think you should give calling one of the lines a try, you might find yourself feeling a lot better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If someone is doing something to make you unhappy then you need to tell it to them straight, don #8217;t let things fester over time. Even if you #8217;re scared of the outcome it #8217;ll be over soon enough. You #8217;ll find yourself feeling a lot better with that weight off your back.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 06:17:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 06:22:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>They won #8217;t be able to *solve* your problems, that #8217;s the hard part, but they #8217;ll definitely be able to help, whether that be by helping you look at things from a new perspective or even just making you smile a bit. I understand your anxieties about calling, I deal with those feelings, too, you #8217;re not alone, but even a 5 minute conversation about how you #8217;re feeling can make your day that much better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 06:43:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don #8217;t need to worry about wasting my time, talking with you has made me very happy, I #8217;m glad I #8217;m able to help you and you #8217;re a very kind person! The workers are happy to help you, too. They #8217;ve chosen to apply to those jobs because they want to help people. I understand that you #8217;re nervous about bothering them, but they #8217;re all very patient and polite people who would be happy to have you reach out to them. Finally, what you #8217;re feeling definitely doesn #8217;t lack severity. You #8217;re a person just like them, just like your loved ones and just like myself, so you #8217;re just as important. You may not feel like it sometimes but you #8217;re surrounded by people who love you and care about you, you mean the world to so many people and they #8217;re happy to have you in their lives.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 07:02:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everybody deals with hardships in life that slow them down but that doesn #8217;t make you a disappointment, it makes you a human being. I deal with my own troubles in life that make things hard for me in daily life but I know I can talk to somebody about them, whether that be my mum, dad, my siblings, a good friend or a doctor. There #8217;s no shame in what you #8217;re feeling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 01:27:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here #8217;s where I found it from](https://twitter.com/awwcuteness/status/979121959765233664?s=21). If you find the original source please send it to me and I will change this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 17:35:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everybody has their own struggles in life to deal with, but if you make an effort to make your own life better than you #8217;ll have a way easier time making their lives better, too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 19:29:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember seeing somewhere that dogs trained to walk on two legs are forced to do it by their owners. Not saying this is the case, just that you should keep an open mind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Would it be possible to develop implants/contact lenses that boost the resolution of our vision?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 00:56:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let #8217;s imagine our eyes as computer monitors. Say the quality of an average person #8217;s vision is 720p, if something were to be created that would enhance it to 1080p or beyond how would it affect society? More importantly, how would it affect the brain? Would it  #8220;overload #8221; the input to the visual cortex, would we pass out from the stimulus or would something entirely different potentially happen?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 02:35:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>It would certainly be an interesting experience.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 06:58:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I swear I #8217;ve read this somewhere before... either I have future vision or there #8217;s something fishy about this...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 07:04:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>So then what would happen? Would it just fail to register?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 07:09:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems reasonable enough, but that poses another question. Since an implant into the *eye* would likely do nothing, what about putting it in the brain instead? Since what we see is computed by the brain, would added processing power allow us to have higher definition for our vision or maybe even see other wavelengths of light?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 07:19:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wasn #8217;t really thinking about specifics, to be honest; still, I see your point. It #8217;s a shame, though, it would have been so cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 07:34:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wanted to mention holograms but it seemed a bit obvious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 11:50:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>What if an implant embedded in the eye could act as additional rods and cones?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 17:30:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love the details and the creativity! The only thing this needs is Connie, Greg and Lion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 20:48:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whenever I do nice things for people I do feel nice when I do it, but there #8217;s also the feeling of guilt I feel when I don #8217;t help someone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 21:36:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe it could be attached to another implant in the brain and they could communicate through the optic nerve, but training of sorts would definitely be needed in order to not cause something like a seizure. Of course, let #8217;s not get too reliant on implants for this or we #8217;ll eventually end up talking about Hollywood.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I don #8217;t  #8220;eat #8221; oranges, I bite a hole in them, squeeze them and suck all the juice out.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 00:30:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 00:34:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>As an actual autistic person I take offense in you comparing me to those idiots.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 01:21:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>What #8217;s your religion?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 01:22:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not versed in Islam, mate, no need to be condescending about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 01:23:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then why bring it up in the first place?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 01:25:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey man, I understand, I get kinda groggy when I don #8217;t sleep well, too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 01:32:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re too late.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 01:33:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>By the way, those are amateur numbers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 01:39:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Orange you glad it wasn #8217;t bananas?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 01:45:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Weird bumps definitely don #8217;t sound like fun... and I don #8217;t even want to imagine the constipation! I wish I could eat that many, though, bananas are my favourite fruit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 01:50:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 01:52:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same here. It would really suck if I wasn #8217;t.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 02:44:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>It matters because it makes the good deed someone has done selfish. Imagine you #8217;re a homeless person feeling like the world has given up on you when one day someone shows you what you perceive to be genuine kindness. That feeling you get from the person #8217;s generosity makes you feel like life is worth living again, only for you to find out that they were just nice to you so they could brag to people online. It would break anybody #8217;s heart having the only person who was kind to them have it be due to selfishness rather than legitimate care for their well-being.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 02:51:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I honestly can #8217;t congratulate you enough, I #8217;m so proud of you! Keep your head up and keep pushing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 02:59:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s you, man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 03:14:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks pretty nifty, I might just end up buying one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 03:35:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Caught me just as I was eating a banana! In all seriousness, I just bite the banana, chew it as much as I can and then do the regular part afterward.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Let us not all forget the majesty that is Thiccoome.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 04:17:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 05:07:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s a Rockshund!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 15:13:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everybody knows the foreskin is the best part of the fruit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 15:51:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was in kindergarten I had a horrible gag reflex and vomited if the milk was warm or had a single pulp resting on my tongue. I #8217;m over it now, but geez, was I a little shit or what?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dual Action Can Crusher</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 03:07:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 03:35:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m doing alright, Josh. Been taking care of the dogs, sculpting clay and had Easter Dinner with my family yesterday. Yourself?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 03:36:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Josh. Joshua is really just reserved for formality.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 05:36:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>You seem suspicious...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 19:38:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Helped a friend online with their self-esteem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 21:25:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of your thoughts clearly isn #8217;t fashion sense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 23:04:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s a good one, I like it! Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 23:18:38</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Inject water into your veins to instantly rehydrate yourself! #8221;  #8220;Sure thing, mate. #8221; *Dies of water intoxication*  #8220;He just didn #8217;t use well water. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Two drums and a cymbal fall off a cliff.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 04:16:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>All three instruments break upon impact and are therefore not able to produce any music.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 04:19:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Steved hams.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Y #8217;all tryna summon the eternal dragon?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 04:28:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 04:47:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kemosabe was the nickname used by Tonto in The Lone Ranger. It basically means  #8220;friend. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 04:48:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Umm... sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 04:50:05</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128077; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 07:30:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>That video was actually my inspiration.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 08:29:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>You call hamburgers stiamhed hams?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 08:36:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uh-huh. Eh, what riygen?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 08:40:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really? Well I #8217;m from England and I #8217;ve never heard anybody use the phrase  #8220;Steviad Hams. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 08:48:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see . . . You know, these haggisburgers are quite similar to the ones they have at West Cornwall Pasty Company.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 08:55:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can smell the Zyklon-B and Starbucks through my screen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 18:41:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, they #8217;re broken.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The kettle doesn #8217;t need to be screaming for it to be done. A little extra steam won #8217;t make your tea taste any better, you silly fuckin reptile, it #8217;ll just annoy the piss out of everyone in the whole bloody neighbourhood!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 05:33:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 13:03:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even if the cymbal so much as bends on impact it will change its tone, and a fall from a high enough cliff would be enough to do this by a good amount. If you bent a cymbal in half it would barely be able to make any sound at all, and that sound would not resemble music.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 13:05:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t care how bad the stain is, I #8217;m not going to dab.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 23:13:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>You better STOP being here (JK, have fun)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 23:14:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which one is the brother?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If a galaxy cluster #8217;s overall gravity overrides universal expansion allowing galaxies to collide, will a cluster eventually become one giant galaxy? If so, will all galaxies in the universe eventually merge into one?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 04:04:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 04:37:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, but what if you owe your friend $500 dollars, for example?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 04:42:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Huh. Alrighty then, down it goes. I ain #8217;t no thief.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The The - Uncertain Smile [New Wave]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 04:44:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 04:46:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favourite band *of all time* is coming to Toronto around my birthday and I just bought tickets to see them, so I thought I #8217;d celebrate by sharing my favourite song of theirs with the world.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 17:57:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll be sure to check it out. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 18:59:41</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;I was deployed in Afghanistan and lost both of my legs but kept on fighting until the end. #8221;  #8220;I won a fight against a fly. #8221;  #8220;Oh, I #8217;m so sorry sir, I had no idea! *salutes* #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 00:38:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t shows filmed in front of a live audience have prompts that tell the audience when to laugh? If you ask me, they #8217;re essentially the same thing, just executed differently.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Beanie Baby.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 00:58:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 01:01:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree. It would be fine if it was just played after a joke, but it definitely could be cut back on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 01:03:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, you know what they say, patience is a virtue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 01:25:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I, along with many others couldn #8217;t agree more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 01:33:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, but the writing is terrible, too. I honestly can #8217;t stand Howard, and Sheldon rarely ever seems to grow as a character. It doesn #8217;t even work as stupid fun for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 02:02:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not mad about this, I just think it doesn #8217;t really belong. And without the laughter I can more easily get subtle jokes instead of them being blatantly pointed out to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 02:06:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re missing my point. I #8217;m not saying people aren #8217;t allowed to laugh, I #8217;m saying the laughter distracts from the show. The laughter can also just be edited out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 02:09:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair enough. What about just showing the audience once in a while during a scene where they #8217;re cued to laugh or just simply find something that happened funny? Personally, I think the knowledge that it #8217;s being watched by other people you can actually see would make the show feel more personal, therefore making it more enjoyable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 02:14:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess I can #8217;t argue with that. Do you have any ideas on an alternative to canned/audience laughter, then?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 02:16:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe. Still, this is all just my opinion. I #8217;m open to changing it, but I personally don #8217;t like it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 03:28:25</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Day 8, the human has been playing with my beans without getting an iota of sleep. How do they do this? I #8217;m beginning to fear for their safety more than my own. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 02:23:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Buddy, I #8217;m just giving my perspective, you don #8217;t need to be a dick about it. I never said they #8217;re some hellish abomination, just that they take away from the experience. If you #8217;re going to be an asshole, take it somewhere else. Nobody wants that kind of negativity here or anywhere else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When mommy doesn #8217;t bring home any tendies.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 07:06:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 17:27:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s kinda the main point of memes in general.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 18:30:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>After a long day of being the sweetest pup of all time Colt is ready for a good night #8217;s rest.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 23:56:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 00:15:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>This photo honestly put such a huge smile on my face!  #128516;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 00:22:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everybody deals with this kind of stuff, you #8217;re not alone. Through my experience, I #8217;d say just keep being friendly with her. Things will be a little awkward for some time, no doubt about that, but if you just treat her like one of your regular friends things should work themselves out. Besides, I #8217;m sure she understands where you were coming from, everybody has crushes, it #8217;s nothing to be ashamed about. Just keep your head up and keep living your life normally and you #8217;ll do great!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 00:25:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>While we do learn from other people #8217;s mistakes, learning from our own is what truly impacts us. For example, if my friend spends too much money in one day, I #8217;ll think to myself  #8220;well, I guess I should watch my spending; #8221; however, if *I* spend too much in one day I #8217;ll have an experience to learn from and look back on. There #8217;s no better perspective to life than your own.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 00:30:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmmm... if I upvote I #8217;m supporting a karma whore and contributing to the deaths of millions, but I get to see a Spirit Bomb. However, if I downvote, Buu will become further from resurrection and the Earth will be safe... decisions, decisions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 04:24:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re a good looking person with a beautiful smile. Trust me, you #8217;ve got nothing to worry about!  #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 21:57:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m really proud of you, mate! It takes a lot of confidence to ask somebody out. I know you #8217;ll do great with her!  #128513;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 18:11:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you know how to avoid a repost? Apparently not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 01:39:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you #8217;re going to answer, at least explain your answer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 01:42:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds kinda fun, aside from the semen bit...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 01:42:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>And you know this *how?*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 01:45:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not unconvinced, I just pay little mind to lazy answers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 01:45:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>She looks so soft!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 01:49:57</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Only a real man has had at least two heart attacks caused by poor diet! #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What did the pirate say when he turned eighty?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 22:40:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nothing, he didn #8217;t even make it to thirty...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 22:43:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Happy birthday, mate! I know sometimes things are hard, but that #8217;s okay, every day has a tomorrow, and every tomorrow has one as well. Keep looking forward. I hope you #8217;re feeling better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 23:23:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re actually a pretty handsome guy. The most I can point out that I #8217;m not a fan of is the sad/angry face. You have a very nice neutral and happy face, though; the ladies are missing out.  #128578;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 23:31:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>OH MY GOD! That man has Harold #8217;s face!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 01:06:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, matey.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #8220;Warrior unicorns. #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 02:25:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 02:28:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure they #8217;d be very fast, though.  #128517;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 02:32:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 02:35:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Somebody needs to start a petition to change Rhinos to Warrior Unicorns.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 04:39:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Horny Horse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 04:40:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Horses and Rhinos are distant relatives.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I only just realized the cake next to a username is for the anniversary of the Redditor #8217;s account and not for their birthday.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 05:40:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 05:58:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is 2018, rhinos can be whoever they want.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 07:00:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let #8217;s hope it gets gold!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 07:44:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>You look stunning!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 12:18:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 12:22:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Happy belated birthday, mate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 12:58:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I was waiting for someone to say that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 13:47:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Huh. I didn #8217;t notice that, either...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 13:56:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wish him good luck for me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 14:54:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are many different kinds of people in the world.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 15:19:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t really think this is quite interesting enough for r/todayilearned</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 15:21:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, I thought you were recommending it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 15:24:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 17:20:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>They #8217;re Scuba Unicorns.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 19:37:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 21:30:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reddit already has an envelope, it #8217;s the yellow one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 17:41:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you blame us?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 03:59:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It honestly fucking baffles me as to how these people live with themselves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 04:03:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess your dick and ass are cleaner than your hands...(?)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 04:17:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s just as bad. All you #8217;re doing is getting them wet then just walking away with not only dirty hands, but dirty, wet hands. It #8217;s essentially just saying  #8220;I #8217;m too lazy to use soap even for just ten seconds. #8221; Come on, man, you #8217;re not 9 anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 05:21:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, but they #8217;re more along the line of garlic bread #8217;s idiot cousin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 05:22:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>What will happen to it, then?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 05:25:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why would they be shaking their hands if they didn #8217;t even get them wet in the first place?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 05:26:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>You do know spacesuits exist, right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 05:28:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>When somebody doesn #8217;t wash their hands after using the bathroom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 05:29:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Space isn #8217;t hot, it #8217;s way below freezing. The suits protect against radiation. I never said anything about actually going to the fucking sun...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 05:32:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean what will the radiation do to it? Will it just char the outside or will there be some sort of baking-like process in action?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Young Ural Superbowl.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 05:39:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 05:44:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure, it may be overkill, but to me it #8217;s the same as picking your nose in public or licking crumbs off a countertop. It #8217;s disgusting, nobody wants to be friends with someone who has shit hygiene.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 05:57:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for offering a detailed explanation. Still, here #8217;s to hoping for that garlic bread Dyson Sphere I #8217;ve always wanted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 06:00:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, of course they do! At the end of the day it #8217;s still proper manners, and it #8217;s not like bathrooms are the inner sanctums of cleanliness to begin with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 06:19:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>For your first point, nobody wants mud tracked in the house. It #8217;s ugly and cleaning it off the floor is a pain in the ass. Second, you completely skipped over the manners part. If you couldn #8217;t give less of a damn about what people think of you then go on ahead, be as filthy as you like, but from the perspective of somebody whose friends aren #8217;t hillbillies and hookers, nobody wants to shake hands or really even associate with somebody who doesn #8217;t care enough to take half a minute to just wet their hands, lather and rinse. What do you think that says about a person? It #8217;s really not that hard, it takes less than half the time and effort of brushing your teeth, that is if you #8217;ve ever done that, either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 06:32:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically every post on r/imgoingtohellforthis.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 12:34:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m a Brit as well, but I still enjoy meeting new people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 15:18:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 15:24:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see where you #8217;re coming from, I hate public air dryers, too; I still wash my hands in the sink, dry my hands however and then use hand sanitizer. No dirt, no germs, no worries.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 17:13:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good to know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 18:51:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/woooosh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 18:52:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah mate, everybody #8217;s their own way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 02:30:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I see it now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 20:22:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Year 8 as a hosepipe collector. The government is rounding up hosepipes across the nation and disposing of them en masse. I #8217;ve hidden all of my hosepipes under the garden; I hope they don #8217;t find any of mine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 00:16:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve come to terms with it and I have proper control over my symptoms, so I should be fine. Thank you, though.  #128578;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL in 2010 Spain held a siesta competition. It lasted 20 minutes and contestants were awarded points on the quality of their sleep, their positions, their snores and even for their pyjamas.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 14:39:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>LPT- If you #8217;re feeling unconfident or are having some troubles with self-esteem, make plans with people.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 16:06:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>It can be with friends, families, your partner or even just some acquaintances. Even if the plans don #8217;t work out, it #8217;s still nice to know your friends want to spend time with you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 16:07:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, mate, I appreciate it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 16:09:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I a *pretty* drama queen?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 17:24:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>You won #8217;t know until you try.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 17:37:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then it #8217;s a good thing I only touch the handles and sink.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 19:00:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess that #8217;s just an indicator that you need better friends.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 19:07:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s all about finding who you #8217;re comfortable with. Just take your time and let autopilot take over, you #8217;ll stick to the right people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 19:08:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s a curry flurry!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 19:30:09</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Guess where I #8217;m taking you for dinner, babe! #8221; *Chuckles*  #8220;Hopefully the city dump. #8221; . . .</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 21:29:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you thought about an RP room? Even just pretending to do something feels pretty nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 22:14:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>RP is Role Play. Basically, you pretend to be in situations with other people online, like a tea party or in a drama. It sounds kinda stupid, but it #8217;s actually pretty fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 22:42:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re welcome mate, I hope you have fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 22:45:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>They check your heart rate to see if you #8217;re actually asleep, so you probably lose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 23:28:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Preach.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 01:22:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aw, shucks. Thank you, lad, I try my best!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 02:47:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t see what anime has to do with this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 02:02:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unless she smiled at you or made sure to present herself while doing it, I #8217;d say it #8217;s just her preferred workout.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 02:23:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>What #8217;s next,  #8220;University of Texas to treat testicles as late stage tumours? #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 03:10:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>You ever played Tetris?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 03:15:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s this instrument you blow into that awakens an instinct in us humans to stack ourselves into an orderly pile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 07:08:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aye, fair point, mate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 07:09:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, it #8217;s just his double chin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sometimes I wonder if I could have been born in a different time/timeline.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 07:31:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think to myself about how every event in history led up to me being born on October 24th, 2000. Was it the destiny of the universe for me to be born on that specific date? Was my individual consciousness specifically destined to be in *my* body? It all stirs up ideas of fate and alternate realities. Am I the version of myself born whenever, wherever along with other versions of myself with my exact same mind and morale? Am I the only me I #8217;ll ever be or will there be another set of eyes I get to see through? I know consciousness is just this process in the brain and whatnot, but it #8217;s such a special and unique experience that it #8217;s practically impossible to imagine only being able to have it once. It #8217;s all very difficult to put into words. It all makes sense in my head but put into words it sounds both too simple and too complex at the same time. Does anybody else think about this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 07:51:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>You ever see those  #8220;born too early to explore the galaxy and too late to explore the sea #8221; memes? Sure, my life is really cozy and comfortable, I can #8217;t really think of any big changes I #8217;d like to make in it, but with all those fantasies I have about fighting pirates or traversing those exoplanets I love learning about it does incite a bit of FOMO, if I #8217;m being entirely honest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 12:35:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>System overload</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 13:55:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of the thoughts I have is that there is no timeline and everybody #8217;s born in a random time. Imagine if bla bla physics and Thomas Jefferson didn #8217;t exist in the past and was born in 2728262826282.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 13:57:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I didn #8217;t really mean it by the whole  #8220;I wAs BoRn In ThE wRoNg GeNeRaTiOn #8221; trope. #8221; More just that I wonder if it was possible to have been born in any time, like being born at the base of the tree even though it #8217;s fully sprouted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 00:36:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a person in the spectrum (mild Asperger Syndrome) I can confirm this. Trust me, it #8217;s the worst feeling being seen as worth less than some virus. It really hurts. Edit: Hey guys, I really appreciate the support and kind words, it means a lot, but please don #8217;t coddle me. It #8217;s even more embarrassing than what the antivaxxers are saying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 00:47:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dr. Strangelove or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love the Bomber- a touching story about a pilot who falls in love with his B-2, certain to tug at the heartstrings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 01:21:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I #8217;m well aware of that. I make sure to dissociate myself with those people entirely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 01:44:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a bit of a tangent, but my idea of love is someone who I feel totally comfortable with and fully trust. Part of that trust is kindness and politeness, whether that be by being nice to people (not just women, for all the nice guys reading this) or simply *washin ya damn hands.* If you #8217;re just an overall good person, yeah, I can say I  #8220;love #8221; you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 01:53:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally, I don #8217;t like even bringing up the fact that I #8217;m autistic unless I feel I have a good reason to; but to answer your question, no, I don #8217;t like being called autistic. I understand that it #8217;s not really a bad thing to be on the spectrum, but it still feels insulting. I #8217;ve worked really hard over the years to get my mental state and behaviour under perfect control and being insulted like that is essentially just a big  #8220;your efforts and thoughts don #8217;t matter due to your condition #8221; to the face. It #8217;s kinda hard to explain those feelings, but it #8217;s the best way I could think to word them for now. On the other note, I #8217;m really sorry for the way you #8217;re being treated by others, some people out there have just never heard of the word  #8220;empathy. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 01:59:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I doubt they #8217;re able to read anything.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 02:01:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>And they call *us* the retards.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 02:02:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess you could just squeeze them in...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 02:03:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have no other reaction to that than just a long and heavy sigh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 02:08:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a pretty similar experience. As a kid I was always one of the  #8220;outcasts #8221; (I apologize if that #8217;s a rude thing to call somebody) along with other kids with LD #8217;s, Low-Functioning Autism and Dyslexia. I would spend a lot of time with them and I #8217;d eventually learned to appreciate people regardless of the hand life has dealt them. It was through learning to cooperate with them and adapt and adjust to their weaknesses that I was able to become the person I am today.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 02:14:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s going amazingly, thank you very much! This internet stranger wishes the same thing for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 02:17:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s not really like a closet experience for me, it #8217;s more just embarrassing to admit it. People #8217;s opinions do matter to me, but the feelings are almost entirely my own.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 02:18:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I shall graciously accept your hug and return an even warmer one!  #8834;(( #12539; #9661; #12539;)) #8835;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 02:21:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do get a little frustrated at times, I #8217;m not proud to admit that, but I #8217;ve gotten over my childhood anger issues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 05:38:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gracias.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Coming home after school and logging in to Webkinz on your parent #8217;s computer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 03:22:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 00:25:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t forget the crackers, Gromit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Possibly the most satisfying Brie pull in the history of mankind</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 07:04:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 15:32:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once it spread it across it was actually a good amount.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 15:34:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn #8217;t just have Brie, mate. There was tomato, avocado and some fried tofu and mushroom as well. It actually blended quite well together.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 15:35:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tried getting some rind in the first shot but the cracker broke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 16:38:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>This video has caused my leg to shake violently!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 16:46:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>So... did he win?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 19:50:51</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Were the effects only temporary? #8221; I #8217;d thought to myself, trying to pinpoint which direction the scream came from. Another scream was heard, seemingly from the west.  #8220;Erika Way #8221; was my first guess. I #8217;d begin running toward the source of the sound, and I could tell I was getting closer by the minute, but then something changed, the scream began echoing, almost as if there were more and more people being freed from their temporal prisons. I know I should have been chilled to the bone by the whole ordeal, but the only thing I can remember feeling was euphoria at the aspect of finally talking to another person after god knows how long; that is until it started to snow. I #8217;d reached out my palm to catch the white, fluffy flakes, but after finally having some land I #8217;d noticed they were black on some parts, too. The screams were also dying down, but not in a sudden halt; no, more in a quiet yet soul-crushing roar. I #8217;d turned around to face the new source of the sound. My excitement and intrigue quickly turned to absolute horror as the civilians surrounding me began aging at an unprecedented rate, seeming to pass through a decade every second. The fair complexions and shining hair of the young and healthy mutated into grotesque and vile collections and greys and whites, shriveled and dry, their skin turning to dust as the seconds inched forward. Seconds felt like hours as the formerly youthful people throughout the city disintegrated, disappearing from the face of the Earth. After what felt like a millennia of agony and heartbreak, the screams finally subsided. Nothing remained but the crumbled buildings and ashes of what used to be not just innocent strangers, but my friends, family, loved ones, and the scientists who #8217;d caused this whole mess to begin with. I wanted to be angry or sad or at least feel something, *anything*, but what would be the point? Everything I #8217;ve ever known is gone. None of the weapons work anymore so I can #8217;t simply put myself out of my misery and all the food has withered away so I can #8217;t distract myself with a meal, either. Everything is gone, and there #8217;s nothing that can ever be done. All I can do now is wait to starve to death.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 19:58:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re a really good looking person, and the glasses compliment the look. I #8217;d have to say an 8 or a 9!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 04:45:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks a ton, mate!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 20:31:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty sure that #8217;s already a thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 15:25:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, very in depth! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 05:13:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You seem like the kind of guy I #8217;d want to go out for a beer with just to hear the crazy shit going on in your life!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>FiRe GoD fUcKiNg BuRnS tHe PlAnEt To CiNdErS!!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 14:57:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 17:57:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, no, that #8217;s just Canada</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 18:02:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I imagine it had a rather Earthy aroma. Truly unmatched</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 18:33:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll give you the courtesy of cross posting to r/noisygifs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 18:35:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some see it as tedious, but sculpting and writing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 18:37:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>De nada, brother</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>WYR be in control of somebody of your choice for a day or suddenly have the same level of skill as someone of your choice (Gordon Ramsay #8217;s cooking)?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 18:43:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 19:58:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes you do</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 20:05:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s just one skill, like his skill with investment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 21:24:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>But *which* ninja skill?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 21:26:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, I see</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 04:01:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Preferably someone real, but, sure, knock yourself out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 04:12:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, you #8217;re essentially trapped in their body. Think of it as your body being converted into energy and then being assimilated into their mind for a day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 22:30:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t know, seems kinda lamb to me...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 05:35:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would, but there #8217;s a long and complicated backstory getting in the way of that...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 05:52:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks mate  #128578;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 05:54:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kinda describes my constant mood, happy yet always sorta pissed about something  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 06:04:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kinda. Not the cheeriest of stories, either</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 06:07:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have never gained so much respect for a person so quickly!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 06:10:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey man, it #8217;s *mildly interesting,* nobody said the posts need to be mind blowing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 06:17:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>My left eye is a good deal smaller than my right, the left side of my nose has a noticeably different shape and the entire side is overall leaner; the differences in my facial structure stand out much more noticeably than the average person #8217;s. If you ask somebody who isn #8217;t wasting their night being an ass to strangers on the internet you #8217;d get a similar answer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 06:17:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>No sir, I just look like that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 06:23:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Woah, at least take me out to dinner first!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 06:39:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Somebody gave it to me as a gift and it made me really happy to receive it, so I #8217;ve been holding onto it as a sort of good luck charm. It #8217;s also a part of this summer outfit I #8217;ve been sporting for maybe three weeks now. I also have a hat and sunglasses but I took them off for the photo. I think a more important question is *why aren #8217;t you wearing a lei?*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 06:40:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve been waiting for a comment like yours  #128578;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 06:42:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks awesome man, great work!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 07:17:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s... not a bad idea</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 14:09:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck... 17 over here, not looking forward to this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 14:14:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly thought this was a bacteriophage for a second and got super confused...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 14:15:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>This gets posted at least once every day</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 17:51:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>1,000,000 14 year olds. I #8217;d be able to pass life lessons I #8217;ve learned along the way to them so they grow up to be kind and respectful adults and pass them on to others as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The daughter of a melon farmer and a travelling musician met one day and fell in love at first sight</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 02:50:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>The woman #8217;s name was Angie, a beautiful, red-haired woman with a smile so magnetic and radiant one couldn #8217;t help but fall head-over-heels; the musician #8217;s name was Zachary, a strapping, young lad with flowing, blonde hair and broad shoulders, just wide enough to give him a powerful physique yet not intimidating in the slightest. The two had met in a bar on a clear, starry night in the middle of July. The second Zachary had stepped in his gaze immediately met Angie #8217;s. He approached her without a thought as to what he would say and had taken a seat mere inches from her. She turned to him, a gleam in her eyes as she introduced herself.  #8220;Good evening, the name #8217;s Angie. How are you tonight? #8221; A faint seductiveness in her voice sent a tingle down Zachary #8217;s spine as he hurried.  #8220;Lovely weather we #8217;re having, isn #8217;t it? #8221; Now, Zachary was always a fairly shy man. Despite his appearance he was never one for starting conversation and his fear was only elevated even more by the fact that Angie was by far the most beautiful woman he had ever seen. The two talked some more throughout the night and eventually grew comfortable with one another. Despite her lifestyle Angie #8217;s favourite genre of music had turned out to be soft-rock, which lo and behold Zachary was an artist in.  #8220;Why don #8217;t you come to my concert? I #8217;m playing tomorrow night at the theatre south of town and I #8217;d love to have you there with me. #8221; Angie had sprung on the offer, not wasting a second as she accepted with a great deal of enthusiasm. She gave him her address and phone number with a small note written on the bottom right:  #8220;pick me up at 10 #8221; with a heart drawn right next to it. The next night Angie had waited for her parents to go to bed before going out to wait at her door for Zachary. Luckily, he #8217;d arrived in the nick of time.  #8220;I #8217;m on in an hour. If we hurry we can make it about 10 minutes early. #8221; Once the two had arrived Zachary led Angie backstage, telling her to wait for his call in order to find the best seat in the theatre to watch him play. Not five minutes passed once her phone buzzed, with the message  #8220;there #8217;s a seat right in front of the mic stand, I got the set-up crew to reserve it for you. #8221; Once the concert had begun Zachary stepped up to the mic and looked right into Angie #8217;s eyes while saying  #8220;this first song goes out to the most amazing woman I #8217;ve ever had the chance of meeting. #8221; Throughout the concert Angie #8217;s eyes were glued to Zachary. She could feel herself falling deeper and deeper in love with him as he played, her beautiful, green eyes still stuck to his image long after the final song had been played. Once backstage Angie had rushed toward her lover, locking lips with him and holding him as close to her as she could. Once the kiss had broken she jumped in place ecstatically, screaming in joy  #8220;that was the most amazing thing I #8217;ve ever seen, Zachary! You were incredible out there! #8221; The drummer could be heard from the snack table,  #8220;I #8217;m here, too, you know, #8221; but to no avail. Zachary led Angie to the side where he held her hands and gazed deeply into her eyes, and said to her:  #8220;Angie, I can #8217;t stay here forever. I #8217;m always travelling and I can #8217;t just leave my life behind. #8221; Angie #8217;s eyes welled up as she fought to choke back tears.  #8220;Please, don #8217;t cry. We can work around that. #8221;  #8220;How? #8221; Whispered Angie, her throat still sore from crying.  #8220;Come with me! We can travel the world together! You can leave this old melon business behind and we could be together! #8221;  #8220;I... #8221; Angie said to herself.  #8220;What is it? #8221;  #8220;I don #8217;t think that #8217;s possible. #8221;  #8220;Why not? #8221; Now Zachary was starting to cry.  #8220;My father would never approve of it. He wants me to become a farmer just like him to keep the family business running. #8221;  #8220;Angie, please, #8221; begged Zachary.  #8220;I love you so much! I don #8217;t want to leave you behind! #8221;  #8220;I #8217;m sorry, my dear, #8221; cried Angie, wiping the tears from her cheek.  #8220;I cantaloupe. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 03:23:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, no need to be so meloncholy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 03:27:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>In dew time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 03:34:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>To the Hall it Joshuas!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 03:36:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let #8217;s try to keep a positive name for ourselves</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What song is stuck in your head?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 03:43:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 04:07:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>A classic!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 04:14:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>*everybody shoes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 04:18:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post was a mistake...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 12:51:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably gonna be embarrassing having a giant pearl in your forehead. I don #8217;t blame the kid</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 03:19:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>The guy on the left has five nipples if you count the head of his dick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 05:21:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congratulations man! Keep up the great work, we #8217;re all rooting for you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 05:52:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s nice knowing I can relate to someone about this. Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 05:59:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know, but I #8217;ve been trying for years to come to terms with it and I can #8217;t seem to make any progress. I really want to take your advice but I can #8217;t bring myself to do it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 14:33:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, hey, at least Beerus is there...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 15:22:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should work for MTV</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 20:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>He #8217;s the part of my life I don #8217;t want, and I apologize if this is bigoted but I view the German side of myself as the side representing him. Maybe it wasn #8217;t the greatest decision to tell me about him at the age she did, but I know my mum has made mistakes in the last just as I have and I forgive her for them. I know she never meant to hurt or scare me by telling the stories and even though I don #8217;t enjoy knowing about him, I feel that by telling me about him I have someone to work toward being the opposite of, kind and loving and patient instead of everything I know him to be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 04:31:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>1950 #8217;s Kevin Hart</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Don #8217;t put your wood in wood</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 04:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 05:03:27</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Wow, that #8217;s a really nice hat! #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 05:06:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s not what this sub is for. Take it to a different platform.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 07:13:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t put your S T I C C in the T H I C C</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 07:24:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw the post, Reddit didn #8217;t tell me it was previously posted, I crossposted under the impression it was new. Don #8217;t blame me for that, man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 09:38:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Care to explain why?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 10:03:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see a handful of guys talking about their bad experiences with women and taking time out of their day just for themselves, and while that #8217;s all well and good I see nothing indicating I #8217;d regret what I want to do with my life. We #8217;re all entitled to our own opinions and this one is mine. Like I said, I have nothing against women, I just want to prioritize myself and my own desires before I settle down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 14:01:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s fake, the lines are too thick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 14:02:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>My producer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 14:34:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 13:44:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think anal lemonade is a little worse...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 00:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not 100% certain on this, but I remember hearing pouring a drink from a higher elevation increases oxygen levels, therefore enhancing the taste.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 03:11:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>The age of marriage is getting younger and younger these days. Now even newborns are getting married!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 14:33:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>A mlem is when a doggo/catto does a lick on its snoot. This, my friend, is what is known as a r/blop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 20:19:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>A mlem is when an animal (long horse, grass doggo, doggo, catto, etc.) licks its chops A blep is when a catto/kitter sticks its tongue out A blop is a blep but for doggos/puppers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 22:10:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>R</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 22:10:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>U</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 21:32:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a better idea. You ever seen Steven Universe?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 22:42:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, so first we get every one of us together Next, we all start a flash mob so we #8217;re in sync Then we all fuse together Finally, we use our combined strength, intellect and general awesomeness to overthrow the United Nations and establish ourselves as the one true leader Edit: we should overthrow r/John while we #8217;re at it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 01:23:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>We ARE the mechsuit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 01:24:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Darn, had to downvote...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 01:25:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bad bot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 01:26:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;ve got yourself a deal. I call dibs on the left nut!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 01:29:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll be sure to fistbump you every time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 02:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>BAD BOT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 02:13:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>B A D B O T</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 14:45:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>How #8217;d you get that clothespin to stay clipped on the back of your head?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 04:57:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude... just... dude...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 06:15:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gahdam this post still gets views?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 13:17:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your handwriting is lightly written yet compacted. I #8217;d say you #8217;re a gentle person, but are feeling some stress in your day to day life; however, you #8217;re also organized.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 17:05:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>The iris is done well, but then it looks like he gave his 10 year old son the rest to work on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 17:06:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/fiveheads</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 17:10:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, I think it #8217;s pretty good. A solid $30 would be decent for a starting price.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 17:19:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Add a background and some kanji and you could pass it off as legitimate ancient Japanese art.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 00:33:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 04:46:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, no! You #8217;re supposed to nail it at an angle!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 04:55:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>THIS FELLOW BIOLOGICAL LIFE FORM IS WEARING A VERY ELEGANT PAIR OF FOOT ARMOUR, JUST AS I LIKE TO ON MY VERY REAL VERY HUMAN FEET</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TwO yOuNg BoYs RuN a GiAnT fUcKiNg PaInT rOlLeR oVeR a CiTy, DeStRoYiNg HoUsEs AnD dRoWnInG eVeRy CiTiZeN iN pAiNt!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 16:09:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 16:45:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m no scientist, but shouldn #8217;t there be an explosion from the sudden rise in temperature?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 16:49:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never referenced the water, I was talking about the transfer of heat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 16:51:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>There we go. Thanks for the explanation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 14:51:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, I just see it as  #8220;I subscribed to see cute pictures of animals, not your boring, messy, common human child. #8221; I mean, come on, there are subreddits specifically for those pictures, keep the two things separate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 15:01:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, children are animals in their own right, just not the kind that are very cute.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 15:45:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are always sides to every story. Personally, I think babies should be kept to baby subreddits and r/awww should be for animals only. It #8217;s what I came for before it was  #8216;redesigned, #8217; so the change just annoys me. It #8217;s like mixing two spices that don #8217;t belong together.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 16:54:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>That wasn #8217;t always there, it was added a few months ago. And as for what #8217;s wrong with it, it #8217;s not what I came for. If you design a building for pool to be played in, don #8217;t add a whole section for basketball is my reasoning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 18:12:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You look like Shrek halfway through turning human</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 00:11:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in Canada, we spell some things differently here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 00:15:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every now and again I like to change my lock screen to a beautiful landscape, and I #8217;ve just found my new one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 00:41:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should tell him your reason, I #8217;m sure it would make his day, and you #8217;d get more of the attention you want!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 03:49:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/terriblefacebookmemes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 03:51:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Welp, guess I #8217;m a lesbian</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 05:28:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/woooosh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 12:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s so refreshing to see more articles like this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 12:19:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re a nice looking woman, those guys are missing out! (BTdubbs, love the Eeveelution tattoo!)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 12:20:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>This really warmed my heart. I needed that.  #128578;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 16:41:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>My original thought was that was for writing your name on it, but I guess it #8217;s too small for that. I guess this is solved!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 16:42:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t, no. It #8217;s just on the left side, and the little triangle is only on the left</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 16:50:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>That picture makes me very uncomfortable, but hey, thanks for the help, mate!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 19:33:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember learning about that in the book (The Great Gatsby)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 22:45:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/subsyoufellfor</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 22:49:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I honestly think it #8217;s kinda funny</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 22:55:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>The spaghetti and Margaret part was funny to me, that #8217;s how</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 23:04:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>He said we could drill to reach the water under Mars #8217; surface, but wouldn #8217;t that introduce massive amounts of carbon dioxide, increasing the acidity of it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 23:35:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can ride non-jurassic animals in the Jurassic. The moose can be ridden indefinitely and can smash after charging for a bit. Just stay on it until you manage to take two triceratops out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 23:41:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>But a 4/4 kitty</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 01:30:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>The moose should come soon. For now, maybe use the rhino.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 14:52:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every now and then, yeah.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 14:56:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright, sounds good. Thank you.  #128578; Since the second I wake up is just inconvenient and kind of annoying in my eyes, do you think maybe once we get to school would be best, or maybe when I #8217;m about to get to my bus?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 14:58:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds good, thank you again!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 15:56:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s what I was thinking, as well. I #8217;m not dead set on it, and it #8217;s not really much of a serious thing, either, but since she #8217;s graduating this year and I still have to do grade 13 (Special Ed for Asperger in 9 and 10) I was hoping it could also be a way to stay close and keep in contact (I guess I should have included that in the post  #128517;). There is that lingering feeling that she might question it, so I #8217;m still on the fence about it. I don #8217;t mean to disregard your advice, I am taking it to heart, but my thought process is if she does ask me about it I can just explain it to her. Maybe that #8217;s not the smartest line of reason, I #8217;m no social scientist, so if I #8217;m not thinking straight just tell me. Thanks for the insight, though. I #8217;ll keep it in mind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 16:06:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re really, really misreading the situation. I #8217;m not trying to be intimate with her, I do the same thing with some of my other good friends every now and again, too. I #8217;m not interested in dating her anymore and I #8217;m not dead set on this. You #8217;re acting like just saying  #8220;good morning #8221; every once in a while is strictly romantic in this sense. I just see her as my friend and I have no intention of going any further with that. Would you please not make assumptions about me? I #8217;m not trying to be intimate with her, nor am I trying to push any boundaries. It #8217;s just a simple hello, I #8217;m not trying to make her fall in love with me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Damn they gettin serious with this</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 16:21:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 16:23:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t see why you #8217;re being such an ass about this, man. I asked for advice on a simple situation and you #8217;re mocking me for it. If you don #8217;t have anything positive to say you can piss off. And for the last time, I don #8217;t have feelings for her anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 16:25:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s fair. Thanks for the advice, mate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 16:48:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so sad, can we sue Akira Toriyama?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 18:27:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only real animator there is</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 19:27:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which just ripped off Roblox, which just ripped off LEGO, which just ripped off Super Smash Brothers?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 20:04:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds perfect, thanks mate!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 22:04:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not trying to  #8220;weasel around her guard #8221; or anything like that. I send a good morning text to my other good friends every once in a while, and I wanted advice on whether it would be a good idea to include her in that. There #8217;s nothing wrong with paying mind to your friends, and implying that it is is immature and rude. If anybody needs to grow up, I #8217;d have to say it #8217;s you, mate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 23:00:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which just ripped off Michael Jordan #8217;s birth video</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 23:58:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>And you know this how, exactly?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 01:12:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Second it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 04:34:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not to mention they gotta sue both World Wars, too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 04:39:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Indeed. We should all rally for Playerunknown #8217;s Battle Grounds Battle Grounds</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 04:47:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shit, gotta sue the ground now, too... Speaking of the ground, I think we #8217;ve officially run this joke into it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hey what #8217;s up SmoobTube</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 05:15:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 18:05:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>iPhone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 20:56:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gracias</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 21:08:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are there any special features you unlock after completing the game?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 21:22:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oof</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 00:00:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Went over to r/badanalogies because I felt like sharing something I #8217;d come up with earlier, posted standard, harmless content and got  #8220;temporarily #8221; banned for *999 days!* Edit- because the post was removed via the ban, it was  #8220;dating a gold digger is like shitting on an incomplete puzzle. It may fill the void, but it #8217;s still shit #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 15:21:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>That groomer has a nice neckerchief</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 15:26:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Loving the details of Blue #8217;s diamond!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 20:02:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ingenious, but hideous</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 21:08:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s awful execution because it #8217;s a shitty idea that had a shitty outcome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 21:20:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just because it #8217;s formatted onto the suitcase properly doesn #8217;t make it look good in the slightest</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 21:34:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everybody is entitled to their opinion, mate. I crossposted because I see it as awful taste and awful execution. You can make the same argument of something not belonging on r/atbge or r/gtbae, but the same counter-argument applies, as well. Just because I disagree with you doesn #8217;t mean I #8217;m wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 21:44:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m done arguing with you, I don #8217;t have the patience for this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 21:53:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>You just seemed aggressive in your approach. I understand if you didn #8217;t mean that, I suppose it was just a misunderstanding. But hey mate, I #8217;m willing to leave it in the past. I #8217;m sorry if I came off too harsh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cursed toilet tissue</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 21:55:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 21:59:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have a nice smile there, mate! The grumpy face is fairly imposing, though, but avoid the mean looks and clenching your jaw too hard and you #8217;re a solid 10!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 22:00:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair point</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 22:08:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ironically enough, I would probably do something like this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 22:09:33</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;No, no! I said enchiladas, not entrails! #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 22:24:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>All parties bicker. That #8217;s the main thing I hate about politics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 23:07:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I totally see where you #8217;re coming from. Thing with me is though I #8217;m independent, and I get a good amount of flack for that, too.  #8220;Pick a side or keep your silence #8221;  #8220;You clearly don #8217;t care about the government at all #8221;  #8220;If you aren #8217;t either left or right you don #8217;t have a say #8221;  #8220;You #8217;re too scared of what people will think to choose a party #8221; Like, come on, dude. In my eyes the government exists to *govern*, not fight within its own borders.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 23:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Serious comment, so fuckin happy other people remember Ghost Trick. Best game ever!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 23:17:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like a plan, Stan! I #8217;ll rant on about the government ruining the country with its constant in-fighting instead of thinking critically and listening to public opinion! (I feel like that uncle who comes over every Thanksgiving and just talks about the president  #128514;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 23:22:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let #8217;s maybe not go *that* far</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 16:37:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man just let me fuckin die</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 16:56:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congratulations! Keep up the grind and have an amazing life! I know you #8217;ll be an amazing husband!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 16:59:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, so that #8217;s how you do it. I #8217;ve been going about this all wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 17:35:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only one what?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 18:04:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>The creator said it has fade resistant inks, so I #8217;d say it #8217;s a print</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 18:17:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve been thinking about that scene in Jurassic World where the Velociraptors are running next to that motorcycle a lot and I think I finally got what I wanted</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ever since I was a toddler I #8217;ve always been stubborn and, honestly, a bit rude. Looking for ways to improve myself in this aspect</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 18:44:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess I should preface this by saying I #8217;m not a violent asshole or a bully. I don #8217;t treat people like garbage online and I #8217;m surprisingly good at socializing. The problem is I #8217;ve never been the nicest person in the world and I #8217;ve always had this constant state of minor frustration to full blown (but internalized) anger. I can be stubborn once every week or so and I can be pretty mean for little reason. Like I said before, I don #8217;t necessarily lash out and I never shout unless it #8217;s some douchebag annoying me after I #8217;ve already told them enough times to leave me alone. Anyway, I was hoping I could get some insight from some fellow gentlemen on how to achieve a sort of  #8220;inner peace. #8221; Do any of you feel the same way I always do? If you do or ever have, what ways have you gotten around this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 18:53:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kinda surprised you #8217;re not charging for these, but my favourite is the [Glaucus Atlanticus](https://www.mnn.com/earth-matters/animals/blogs/3-fascinating-facts-about-blue-dragons-sea). Thank you very much in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 20:48:02</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128077; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 20:49:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know what seems like a totally great idea? Getting a permanent tattoo as an adult of a 15 year old girl I have no relation to!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 19:31:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Justice was very much so served</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 19:43:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well sure but it #8217;s only good for three half-sandwiches, hot dogs or one double-decker sandwich</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 04:13:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe this is just me, but I don #8217;t think it #8217;s in awful taste. The execution is a different story, though. Maybe more along the line if r/gtbae</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 04:15:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright, now I see the awful taste. I take it back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;ve been having a reoccurring dream that I completely lose my left arm, and every time it #8217;s always by being run over by a train. Does this symbolize anything or am I just some kind of crazy masochist?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 05:39:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 05:44:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>About 10</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 10:29:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I gave up fighting about a full year back because I was hurting people too easily, and there isn #8217;t really much in my life that #8217;s actually difficult, so I don #8217;t think that #8217;s it. Thank you, though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 10:29:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, no, I said my *entire arm*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 10:31:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I usually sleep on my left but I do turn in my sleep, but there is the chance. Still, a train always being the culprit is a little too specific for that one reason, don #8217;t you think?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 10:32:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s a TTC subway in a blue tunnel, and I kinda just go  #8220;woah, I lost my arm #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 12:32:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>-Not sure -No -Perhaps... - Yes - No</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 12:36:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m about to get my first job (17) and my grandmother did die last year, and I really do miss her. Am I afraid to be in grief? I had clinical depression for a few years, so the thought of grief does scare me a decent amount. Maybe you #8217;re right. I can #8217;t really say for certain, but there is that possibility</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 12:37:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>She really does look amazing! It #8217;s her style, too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 13:00:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just Timmy #8217;s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 14:46:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Timmy #8217;s is [Tim Horton #8217;s](https://www.timhortons.com/us/en/index.php)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 14:52:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>MR. WATERMELON!  #128514; I love it so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 15:00:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks awesome! Good choice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 15:26:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 16:14:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>whgehdevb rvehue gehe jfonbr</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 02:16:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey now, wait one second! Where #8217;s Cousin Itt?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 02:17:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks sweet, but I #8217;m worried about the wheels...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 19:19:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Welcome to the community! We #8217;re glad to have you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 22:46:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be me, mate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 22:48:55</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128077; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 23:14:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m looking forward to it! I #8217;ll follow to catch your newest drawings!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 00:17:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m naturally a very strong person and my strength nor muscle mass really declines that much after not working out, so loss of physical strength is likely not the answer. In terms of metaphorical strength, I do believe I #8217;ve lost much of my emotional strength. I have natural anger issues (I don #8217;t scream or shout, I just get angry somewhat easily and have trouble letting go of the feeling), and I had become a very emotionally intelligent person at the beginning of the year; however, as of last month that #8217;s pretty much slipped away. My mean side has taken over again in a sense and I #8217;ve lost that love and compassion I #8217;d worked so hard to attain, and ever since I feel like I #8217;ve lost a big part of myself which I can #8217;t find a proper way to get back. If I had to guess, and I apologize for taking over your role in this conversation, the lost arm could signify lost emotional strength and losing a big part of myself. It #8217;s near impossible to regain an arm after having it removed, and frankly, I have the same feeling for that kind personality.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A meme in a meme in a meme in a meme... etc.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 00:21:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 00:56:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tiny hands to wipe them off</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 01:08:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Away</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 01:10:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>A way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 01:32:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I was used today to make somebody #8217;s boyfriend jealous!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 03:24:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll give some background for the story. I #8217;m a 12th grade student. Fairly decent looking guy and somewhat  #8220;popular. #8221; One of the people I know, I #8217;ll call her  #8220;Brat #8221; for the sake of protecting her identity has recently gotten into a relationship. The thing is, though, she used to flirt with me *all the time* before she began dating the guy, who I #8217;ll call  #8220;Buddy, #8221; since I really have no grudge against the guy. Anyway, just before third period I was taking a stroll through the halls after being excused by my teacher, and I see some of my mates, along with Brat and Buddy. The second I approach them Brat comes up to me and asks  #8220;Josh, can I have a hug? My boyfriend is being an asshole. #8221; I instantly know something is up and before I even have time to answer she just up and hugs me (no thank you, mate. I #8217;m not much of a hugger, and I didn #8217;t even say yes) right as Buddy is watching. As we #8217;re all walking down the hall together Brat keeps flirting with me and looking over to Buddy, obviously trying to make him jealous. I keep giving her short, disinterested answers, as I #8217;m really not interested in the bait she #8217;s offering and I want to stay on Buddy #8217;s good side. We stop for a bit in our usual hangout spot and she asks if she can hold my hand and keeps touching me and getting close to me in general. She #8217;s calling me a pet name, Joshy, as well, and I catch onto the fact that she #8217;s just using me at that point. I tell her to leave me alone and she seems to get offended by this. She stops talking to me and just starts doing the same thing she was doing with Buddy, I assume to try to make *me* jealous so I #8217;ll buy into her act and play along. I decide I don #8217;t want to be a part of her shit any longer, so I just say I need to get ready for fourth period and walk away. I tried my best to keep my cool during the whole thing, but internally I #8217;m honestly fucking pissed about it. I don #8217;t care about Brat #8217;s reasoning for it, at the end of the day she still fucking used me! I #8217;m not friends with her, she gives me vibes, but I still feel betrayed. I #8217;m angry about the fact that none of the others bothered to tell her to leave me alone, as well as the fact that Buddy didn #8217;t just step in. I was treated as some pawn to tease somebody. I especially feel bad for Buddy, since Brat clearly isn #8217;t faithful in the slightest to him and is this ready to just up and pretend to have feelings for some other guy. The only thing I can think of doing after this is just ignore Brat whenever she tries to talk to me and keep my distance from her. I try not to hold grudges, but I really see no reason to forgive that piece of shit for just using me and very obviously hurting Buddy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 14:45:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/sbubby</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 21:36:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I certainly hope that works, mate, thank you very much! You #8217;ve been a huge help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 21:46:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>*24 females*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 00:44:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Extremely hot. I could slow down my breathing and stay still so I don #8217;t produce as much body energy and my metabolism will slow so I don #8217;t sweat as much Even if I did survive the cold, there #8217;s still the risk of frostbite</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 02:15:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Peach Pearl lookin THICC</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 02:27:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>*doggles*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 02:51:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lay down the boogie and play that funky music til you die</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 03:35:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>The woodwind in Hocus Pocus isn #8217;t in the beginning, lad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 03:38:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>HRT will be smooth sailing for you! Best of luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 03:41:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not Bellbottoms either, mate. I remember it playing for a short time in a scene where Baby was driving off in a black car with his boss</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 04:50:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not the song, either, but I do like this one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 06:28:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oof</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 06:30:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Respect is definitely the most important thing to me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 16:58:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maple syrup? Never heard of that with cheese!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 21:05:22</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Um, aykschually #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 16:12:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 05:06:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you get rid of the  #8220;I still live with my mum at 30 #8221; pube beard you #8217;d be a solid 7</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Enemy spotted</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 16:19:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 16:21:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>*THIS ISN #8217;T EVEN MY FINAL FORM!*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 16:43:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking about posting it there, but it just didn #8217;t feel right</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 16:44:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe if it #8217;s a quiet kid</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Post was locked on r/whatisthisthing. Original photo by u/pandallama</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 16:54:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 16:59:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, mate. Looks like you #8217;re right</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Idea popped into my head so I made this, thought you guys might like it</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 17:24:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 17:40:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>This guy #8217;s fast as fucc boi!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 17:47:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here you go, lad](https://imgflip.com/memetemplate/125256078/Interrupting-bird)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 17:48:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know, funnily enough Stephanie was the first name I thought of for this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 18:06:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m getting a good handful of comments that seem to suggest I #8217;m the creator of the template. Want to get it out there that it #8217;s from [False Knees, a webcomic by Joshua Barkman](http://falseknees.com/158.html)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 18:21:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Great Gatsby</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 22:13:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve had the same song in this commercial from like 2008 stuck in my head and I still have no clues to what it is aside from flute in the beginning then something like  #8220;go where you wanna go #8221; in rockabilly-esque singing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 01:30:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, but that #8217;s still good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 10:28:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s already been posted there lad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 12:24:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here you go mate](https://m.imgur.com/xzuTzpv)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 14:00:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only if he gives you tater tots</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 14:09:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you put milk in cereal and don #8217;t eat it fast enough you get shitty oatmeal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 14:09:38</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128077; #127995; (Happy cake day, btw)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fellow warriors of justice, what is your favourite cereal to eat the right way?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 14:11:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 14:14:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>YOU FUCKING PSYCHOPATH! MINI WHEATS ARE THE *WORST* CEREAL TO HAVE WITH MILK!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 16:17:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can #8217;t sell Phillip the Nickel, he #8217;s too precious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 16:27:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, they #8217;re a nice snack to bring to school and work</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>WWWWWWRRRRRRRRRYYYYYYYYYY</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 16:46:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 03:00:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>(The Jojoke)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 05:17:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>YEET!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 19:43:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like milk, just not in my cereal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 01:10:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/blup</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 02:32:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>You shouldn #8217;t. The cheese deserves to be able to openly express itself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 02:36:30</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;You can hang from the ceiling? #8221;  #8220;I mite #8221;  #8220;That #8217;s tite #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 02:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>This would almost be r/mildlypenis material</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 12:31:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>A mlem is when an animal licks their nose, a blup is a blep for anything that isn #8217;t a cat or a dog</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 13:07:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kinda peeved they got the colours of Goku #8217;s gi wrong. Still pretty cool, though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 13:30:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I literally just said a mlem is a lick, but I never said a blep/blup/blop is a lick. Those are when an animal just sticks out it #8217;s tongue. Don #8217;t be an idiot, mate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Chair underwater</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 00:25:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 00:37:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Going down. I can #8217;t fall up the stairs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 04:57:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>She #8217;s shy, go easy on her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 12:39:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vote for ~~Pedro~~ Krillin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 12:46:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s with your Zebras</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 13:03:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Despite the consumption of Thot Diesel, they did not like it; however, they still breathe, so I would rule they are both half-thots</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 14:38:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re right, I apologize for the poor Thot Patroller judgement. I am a new recruit so I do not know the ins and outs of the job</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>StRaNdEd PrIsOnEr SiNgS sOnG tAuGhT bY tHeIr MoThEr As ThEy AwAiT tHeIr UnTiMeLy DeMiSe!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 14:44:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 14:45:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gracias, sen #237;or!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 16:17:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Found the vegan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 16:49:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the sarcasm was pretty obvious without it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 20:21:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>You look like you tried to inflate a balloon but somehow managed to do it backwards</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 02:35:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/a/6Np7WdW</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 03:35:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have to wait for it to come out of the house</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 03:43:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>The majority of people are actually allergic to peanut butter, but there is a chemical in all jam called Icouldntbebotheredtocomeupwithanameium that cancels out the allergenic properties. As long as you add jam to your peanut butter sandwiches you #8217;ll be fine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 03:44:20</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128077; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 11:38:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thoffee</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 12:14:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know, there #8217;s this really cool thing called  #8220;[Google](http://macabregallery.com/en/zane-wylie-replica-calavera-humana-caballero-templario/)  #8220;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 12:56:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d like to start this off by saying I #8217;m not a scientist, so I #8217;m not completely versed in biology or evolution, but I #8217;ll use what I know in order to try to make a compelling speculation. If the average height of humans was 3 feet we would be much lighter and have a faster heart rate than average humans. This is owed to the fact that with less distance the blood has to travel to reach the heart a faster pulse would arise in order to compensate. Our muscles would also be leaner and we would likely either eat only small rodents and insects as our meat source or not eat meat at all due to increased difficulty when hunting. Due to not evolving to hunt our eyes would also likely be further apart as we would need a wider field of vision to watch out for predators and we wouldn #8217;t need front facing eyes to accurately climb or jump due to humans being terrestrial primates. Along with this, we would likely still have fur, but not a lot of it, as smaller bodies retain less heat than larger bodies, for example a mouse to an elephant. Finally, we would be dumb. Like, really dumb compared to what humans are like today. Since we wouldn #8217;t need to evolve high intelligence in order to hunt we would be on about the same field as monkeys or gorillas, not rabbit levels of stupidity, but definitely incapable of what we #8217;re able to do. We would likely live in either dense jungles or caves/underground. Next is 12 foot humans. First of all, our skeletons would be ginormous. The average weight of a 6 foot person is 160 lbs. The Square Cube Law dictates that every time you double the size of an object its weight by 8, so the average weight would skyrocket up to 1280 lbs! We would need to accommodate for this by having elephant level legs, giant feet and bulky spines, probably cartoonishly big to accommodate for us being bipedal. Let #8217;s be realistic about this, though. If we actually weighed that much we #8217;d probably cripple ourselves by just jumping, so let #8217;s just say we walk on our knuckles like gorillas. First of all, our hearts would need to be very powerful in order to effectively pump blood, and we #8217;d also have a slower heart rate due to blood taking longer to circulate throughout the body. Interestingly enough, due to our need to consume more calories than normal humans, we would either eat richer fruits (bananas and avocados, for example), have a mostly carnivorous diet or, and this is somewhat unlikely, be full carnivores. Due to being very heavy and walking in such a bulky manner we wouldn #8217;t be very fast, so catching prey in a foot race or even so much as out-pursuing them wouldn #8217;t be optimal. Due to this we also wouldn #8217;t be the sharpest knives in the drawer. Smarter than the 3 foot tall humans, but still less intelligent than us. Finally, due to being slow and not eating heavy foods like meat we would likely sport a thick coat of fur in order to retain more of the heat we would frankly be lacking in the production of. Due to all of this we would likely live in jungles or forests.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 14:18:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Essentially. I know the sugar skulls aren #8217;t actually made of bone but it #8217;s the same concept as using a real one. Basically- paper=tree corpse, skull=human corpse</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 14:43:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not really a regular thing to draw on Christmas trees</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 14:45:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair, but paper just made more sense to me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 14:54:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Being a  #8220;nice guy #8221; is more of a personality. Desperation is the name of the game, but I guess I did jump the gun a bit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 03:44:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Thot is an elusive species. They disguise themselves as regular women but with enough training in Thotology you can recognize the signs of a thot even with the most average woman. For starters, thots breathe. Now, not breathing is near impossible due to humanity #8217;s curse by the Thot known as  #8220;god (which is a thotty enough name on its own); #8221; however, a pure Thot has their own breathing pattern, taking longer and thottier breaths than the average person. The most devoted members of Thot Patrol have worked around this by injecting pure oxygen directly into their blood stream. Next is how they dress and talk. The most obvious sign of a Thot is being scantily clad and saying common Thot phrases such as  #8220;OH MY GOID! #8221; The best way to dispose of one of these specimens is by simply saying the sacred phrase  #8220;BEGONE THOT! #8221; However, due to the risk of cooties physical violence must never be used against thots, and the Thot Patrol is merciful, so verbal and online harassment is *never* tolerated. We are all gentlemen here, after all. Finally is the sex drive. All thots have one, so the best way to avoid becoming thotinated is by maintaining your precious virginity at all times. Even the slightest semblance of a libido is sign enough of a thot. Never kiss a thot, hug a thot or so much as look into the eyes of a thot! Feel free to read through the Thot Patroller guidebook in order to attain true Thot Patroller status! PS- r/MGTOW is an excellent hub for talking to men of whom possess no thotty desires whatsoever</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 03:53:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Due to the Thot Patrol being a gentlemanly organization targeted harassment is never tolerated. Posting somebody #8217;s photo online without their permission is also immoral, and I advise you to please follow the laws of the land, not just the laws of Thot Patrolling. Exacting revenge is ungentlemanly and therefore frowned upon. Please do not stoop down to the level of a common thot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Third nuke armed and ready!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 04:35:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 04:56:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah mate, but I am a decent human being</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 05:09:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You sure you didn #8217;t order a French battle flag?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 09:23:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Permission denied. Thot Patrol operates in Japan, as well, Castle Bravo 15 Megaton Lithium-6 Isotope Warheads are too powerful. Just a few precise H-Bombs should be good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 00:59:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s more like it, soldier! Deploy in 3... 2... 1... fire!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 02:15:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I cannot *begin* to stress how terrible of an idea that is! If they have no money they #8217;ll just rob and murder, maybe even more to get that money back!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 03:16:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, soldier, but there are many more thots to be annihilated</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>(17M) Hoping to meet some people I can regularly chat with</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 21:12:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey there, nice to meet all of you! My name #8217;s Josh but most of my mates call me Jojo. I #8217;ve always been a huge fan of animation, starting with just watching a bunch of cartoons and anime as a kid to watching almost ten shows online now (Dragon Ball Z, Boku no Hero Academia, Mob Psycho 100, Ben 10: Alien Force, Jojo #8217;s Bizarre Adventure and a few more). I #8217;ve also been into Pok #233;mon most of my life, so if you #8217;d like to chat about some shared interests, battle/trade, get into some new things or just make a new friend in general feel free to hit me up, I #8217;d be more than happy to meet you! I have some more interests like cooking, travel, and animals. I #8217;m a pretty cheery guy when I #8217;m in a good mood and I like to help people however I can. Love to joke around and just talk to people in general. Again, looking forward to meeting you guys. Anyway, have a great day and keep your heads up! Sayonara!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 02:46:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please explain</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 02:56:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;*Sorry, honey, I was just watching some of that lesbian Hentai I #8217;ve been hearing so much about* #8221; Edit: Woah! Reddit Diamond? I had no idea this existed! Thank you, kind stranger!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 02:58:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would rather die after them. I at least know how I #8217;ll react after it happens instead of spending my last moments worrying about my SO #8217;s wellbeing afterwards. I don #8217;t want to die not knowing if they #8217;ll be okay when I #8217;m gone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 05:27:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yogurt with a banana and green tea</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 05:28:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>The second I see this photo I can smell the cigarettes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 05:31:03</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;*Bobby, what is that girl doing to that other girl #8217;s penis?* #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Curious as to what you guys have to say. Feel free to leave whatever else you like, as well</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 05:36:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 05:41:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Forgot the Starbucks, mate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 05:51:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, mate!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 06:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love you too  #128536;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 06:31:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t mean to be  #8220;that guy #8221; but I #8217;m not all that familiar with him. What #8217;s he like?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 06:32:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ehhhhhh... pretty quiet person, actually, but I definitely see the logic behind that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 12:57:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! Funnily enough all I use is moisturizer, haven #8217;t had acne in years</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 12:57:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!  #128516;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 13:13:00</DATE>
    <TEXT> #398;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 13:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s something somebody pays to award you for a post or comment they liked. Apparently it #8217;s worth more than Reddit Gold but there are only 7 subscribers on the subreddit for it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 14:04:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Somebody needs to award you one first, then you need to pay to award it to someone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 14:34:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I #8217;m a little skeptics about it, too, but I still feel pretty nice about it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 18:08:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gave me access to r/redditdiamond, and it #8217;s a new feature so it #8217;s a little obscure. I used quotes when searching it up and got results, so it is legit, just, again, new</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 18:25:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I still think gold is better, but diamond is decent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 20:17:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you not know what a joke is?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 20:18:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I mean I #8217;m a Joshua B so waddup?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 20:33:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could go on for ages about your friends, but I #8217;d rather not open that can of worms, but here #8217;s some advice- don #8217;t let one asshole of a woman ruin your romantic life. There are bad people in the world, but there are also lots of good people in the world. There are certainly a bunch of women who would be fine with men your height, it #8217;s just about meeting them. Tinder and other sites are perfect for that kind of thing instead of constantly playing Guess Who every time. One last piece of advice, stay as far from Inceldom as possible. No matter how angry you are now that is a dangerous path to follow. Just keep your head up, man. Don #8217;t let her get to you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 20:37:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly thought this was a mirrored image for a second</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 21:09:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Essentially, it #8217;s like Reddit Gold. It doesn #8217;t show up next to your username but it #8217;s still a form of appreciation and all donations made to give it to someone go to charity</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 21:10:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Always  #128077; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 21:11:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Half-homo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 21:11:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>My bi-fi is off the fuckin charts!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 21:27:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think r/joshua would like you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 21:58:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can #8217;t tell if I was just r/woooosh-ed or not</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me when literally anything happens:</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 22:21:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 13:57:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit it #8217;s girl Zamasu!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can we get some Kakyoin love over here?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 15:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 16:02:05</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;*Oh, Zamasu! I hear you #8217;re creating your own world! If I marry a god would that make me a goddess?* #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 19:30:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally, my favourite joneration is Phantom Blood, but my favourite Jojo is Jotaro</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 19:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah mate Kakyoin is better. Polnareff is a great character but Kakyoin did way more for the series (saving everyone from Death 13, figuring out Dio can stop time, immobilizing The Lovers, etc.). And Heirophant Green is just the coolest looking stand IMO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 02:10:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven #8217;t, no. I #8217;m considering getting into the manga, though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 02:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Leave the water in there running for at least a day or two. The soap should all melt away and your drain with be squeaky clean!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 04:24:29</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Grandpa, why do you have those tattoos? #8221;  #8220;To fulfill a pun, kids #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 04:26:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>You look like you #8217;d snap my arms if I told you kids can #8217;t legally consent to sex</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 04:42:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll look for a place around town I can buy it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 05:30:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds good, thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 05:32:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Watched the anime in order, so I think it #8217;s a bit of a trait. Besides, I can #8217;t *stand* people who do that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 05:33:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, gotcha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 13:24:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well yeah sure but he #8217;s also the reason Avdol almost got killed by Hol Horse and Centerfold</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 15:05:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a raging bisexual my hormones are now off the charts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yo can I get a mufuggin uhhhhh Joestar who isn #8217;t an edge lord?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 15:08:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 17:27:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Giorno was pretty edgy, too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 19:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>So... you #8217;re straight?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 02:33:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Welp, apparently I #8217;m a 9... frick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Would it be possible for an animal to develop metal as part of its body?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 04:16:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Say an animal were to eat some pure metal as part of its diet (let #8217;s just say iron for simplicity #8217;s sake), would it be possible for it to incorporate it into an exoskeleton or its bone structure like calcium?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 04:27:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d say they both count, yeah. I had something like Durant or Wolverine in my head when I was writing the post, as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 04:33:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know I #8217;ll be seen as a  #8220;nice guy #8221; for this by some, but this is a real thing that actually kinda pisses me off. I understand that they love their bf/husband and they still see some of the good in them, but, and feel free to ridicule me for this, it #8217;s just stupid in my eyes. (I #8217;m not talking about women who have been abused by their partners, I completely see why they stay loyal, I #8217;m just talking about the women [and men] who stay faithful after being cheated on)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 04:55:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, you #8217;re right. I just remembered Kid Polnareff still has Silver Chariot  #128517; Jotaro didn #8217;t have Star Platinum, though...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 13:52:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d say Ireland</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 20:41:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 05:43:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m afraid she #8217;s too powerful, we need to bring in the big guns... call the THOT SLAYERS!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 05:49:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like he went the wrong direction in life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 13:46:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>WOAH WOAH WOAH WOAH WOAH WOAH WOAH! Where #8217;s my boy JONATHON?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Samuel de Champlain discovers native settlers in Quebec- 1534 (colonized)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 14:17:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 17:26:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely! You look just like one of my buddies!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 19:14:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haven #8217;t yet, no. Feel free to make the joke, though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 03:17:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can definitely date a loyal, normal girl. If she does not display thotish tendencies then feel free to enjoy a happy life with her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 03:18:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those legs are almost as long as their list of exes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 03:55:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t be a fuccboi and treat her with the same level of kindness as you #8217;d like her to treat you with, and let her handle things at a pace she #8217;s comfortable with. As long as you think of her as your companion instead of an excuse to say  #8220;I have a girlfriend #8221; you two should be happy together</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 03:57:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I felt this on a spiritual level</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 04:52:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I prefer the non-violent approach, but I #8217;ll keep fighting the good fight</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Georgie #8217;s favourite place to sleep is next to me in my bed!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 17:37:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 17:41:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Got her from a wookie breeder</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 17:53:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Georgie #8217;s a girl, too. When she wants attention she stands on her hind legs and flails her front ones up and down until I pick her up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 17:59:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/crappydesign</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 02:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Huh, neat  #128578;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 02:43:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Funnily enough it #8217;s actually my second most used</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 02:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use them really often. I worry someone will think I #8217;m not invested in a conversation if I don #8217;t, and it just feels more like I #8217;m actually *talking* to the person</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 04:57:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>(You #8217;ll have to pardon my shitty handwriting, I #8217;ve always been a little messy)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 05:00:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Always written in cursive. Printing just feels... weird</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 05:00:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Big mood</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Aye mates, what does my handwriting say about me?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 05:09:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 13:32:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>This kid is honestly me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 19:25:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow... I wasn #8217;t expecting something *that* accurate. That encapsulates me pretty much perfectly, thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 19:27:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same to you, mate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 19:38:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Born in the Netherlands, living in West Germany</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 20:42:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!  #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 22:00:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I once knew this European guy who told me they don #8217;t have time in Europe and everything there just stands still and is only able to move when the Big Ben clock chimes. That would explain why he was so young</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 22:02:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>You kidding? If I didn #8217;t know any better I #8217;d think you #8217;re a model! You have nothing to worry about!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 22:18:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the people here wondering what it is, it #8217;s a [Campaea Perlata](https://bugguide.net/node/view/202926), also known as a Pale Beauty BTdubbs, great post, OP!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 22:19:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Moth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Biological male here. Just wanted to give you guys some words of encouragement</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 23:51:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don #8217;t need to worry about looking super macho or having a deep voice or big muscles, a beard, strong facial features, etc. None of it really matters. Hell, there are a *ton* of biological guys I know who have soft faces, small muscles, are unable to grow beards, have higher voices and all that jazz and aside from the occasional asshole and r/iamverybadass fodder nobody thinks of them as lesser men for it. I #8217;m not exactly the most testosterone fuelled person out there, far from it, actually. I have a soft voice, undefined muscles, a pretty average jawline and really, aside from being pretty tall that #8217;s it, but everybody still sees me as a man. Nobody is perfect, but that #8217;s okay. Strong men are men, weak mean are men, brave men are men, shy men are men, and trans men are men. You have nothing to worry about. I, along with so many others, accept you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 00:07:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I know, silly me. TBH I forgot the word existed while I was writing this  #128517; But yeah, you #8217;re welcome!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 00:23:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re welcome! And yeah, some guys can be a bit possessive with their gender</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 00:28:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The human prefers solitude, but loves being cuddled and having his hair stroked. He is shy, so compliment him now and again so he feels wanted; this will also build a sense of trust for the human. He is a vegetarian, and usually eats one meal a day and snacks on fruits and sweets as the rest of his food in a day, his favourites being oranges, bananas, grapes, cherries and avocados; his favourite sweets are Jaffa Cakes, lemon squares, Cheetos and 80% dark chocolate. His favourite food is fried rice, the recipe has been left on the counter. The human also enjoys being stimulated, so watch creative shows, movies and videos with him in order to feed his creativity and curiosity, and give him a pencil and paper, maybe some clay as well so he can play. He also loves music. His favourite band is The The, his Spotify collection has been downloaded on the green USB on the desk. Finally, he does not enjoy having multiple people around unless he knows they will be coming over beforehand. He does not like surprises and will recluse if he feels overwhelmed. Keep the house clean and the noise down to a minimum, and check up on him every now and again, he appreciates the sentiment. That #8217;s all, have fun!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 00:29:36</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 01:06:46</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128077; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 01:54:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course, mate! And thank you, I appreciate the compliment!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 03:02:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course, bro. Anytime</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 03:03:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Being a man is just as simple as that, being a man. Sure, there are different ways of doing that, whether it be by being born cis or identifying as one, but at the end of the day it #8217;s the fact that *you* see yourself as one that matters</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 03:40:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey man, I just saw posts about people saying they feel like they #8217;re not actually real men and that they don #8217;t feel like they fit in, I was just trying to do the right thing, no  #8220;you #8217;re a special snowflake and everyone loves you #8221; mush, I #8217;m just being nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 03:52:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course, mate, I #8217;m really happy you like it, it means a lot!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 03:55:19</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;You don #8217;t wanna mess with me, Naruto. I #8217;ve mastered every single Jutsu and I have the entire demon world trapped inside me #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My mate who I #8217;m talking to online messaged me first thing after waking up, and it honestly put the biggest grin on my face!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 04:17:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>This really isn #8217;t some long story or tale of romance or bla bla whatever, I #8217;m just really happy about it and wanted to share it. They live in the Netherlands, so they #8217;re 6 hours ahead of me. I #8217;m usually in bed while they #8217;re already waking up so it #8217;s a little hard to chat as often as I #8217;d like, but the times we do get the chance always feel really rewarding. Anyway, they usually wake up pretty early (4 or so) so I imagine they #8217;re in a rush in the morning, so the fact that they messaged me to start a conversation right as they got up honestly filled me with so much joy. It #8217;s like  #8220;hey, it #8217;s the start of a new day, and I really like talking to Jojo (me), so I #8217;ll start the day with that! #8221; It #8217;s like a huge compliment just on its own, and I honestly don #8217;t have much else I can say about it than I #8217;m really happy! Thanks for reading!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 04:24:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>It really just goes to show how much they care about you and like talking to you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 04:28:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know what? You seem like a pretty cool person (sorry for stalking your profile  #128517;). I #8217;d be happy to chat with you sometimes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 04:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks mate, same to you!  #128578;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 04:50:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s not your fault, buddy. We all have our own strengths and weaknesses, and what you may lack in physical you #8217;ll make up for in emotional and mental strength. It #8217;s all just about seeing the best in every situation</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 05:27:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re welcome, bro! I was smiling while writing it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 06:32:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s kinda like  #8220;hey, just wanted you to know I care about you and I #8217;m thinking about you. #8221; It #8217;s really sweet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 06:34:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re welcome, bro  #128578;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 13:45:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, you still can, it would just take a few days to get to him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 15:43:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course, you #8217;re welcome!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 18:01:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey mate, I get where you #8217;re coming from. With the whole  #8220;biological #8221; think I #8217;d just forgotten the word  #8220;cisgendered #8221; existed and was using the first word that came to mind. With the features, there are certainly people out there who refuse to see the bigger picture and only take transgenderism how they want to. I #8217;m really sorry for making you feel even worse, that really wasn #8217;t my intention. All I can think to say is I #8217;m sorry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 18:13:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>No worries, it happens to the best of us. The best advice I can give is just hang out with or talk to someone who supports your identity. A little support can go a long way. Keep your head up bud, it gets better</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 18:52:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty much just what it #8217;s like being men. House life, social life, cooking, stigma, how we #8217;re feeling... pretty much just whatever you want</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 20:44:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually really like this, it #8217;s cool! It needs a filter and some shelter, but aside from that it #8217;s fine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 22:22:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolute fruinit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 22:33:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I... what the... fuck?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 04:39:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, I really appreciate it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 04:41:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I still have the reminder to post a picture of a chimney saved on my phone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 04:50:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 05:25:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sonia seems nice /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 13:59:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>This sub is more for just talking about being men. r/selfimprovement would be best for becoming a better man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 14:01:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>No worries, bud, this one #8217;s still good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 14:24:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Guys don #8217;t like *needy* girls, but we do like having someone who wants our help sometimes. Personally, when I #8217;m dating someone and she asks me for help with something I know she can do on her own, it feels like she wants me around and admires me for my strengths. Guys like girls who aren #8217;t reliant on us, but total independence creates a sense of distance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 15:29:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ayyyyy!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 15:30:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Almost nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 15:36:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know one or two guys like this, and they pretty much always do that because they #8217;re horny and aren #8217;t bothering to hold themselves back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 19:00:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Started about three or so years back. Lost a bit of weight, started giving a shit about my hair and face, shaved my filthy, disgusting neckbeard and generally gave a damn about myself. After some time I started getting a pretty good stream of compliments, people started conversations with me more frequently, I made a solid amount of new friends, was flirted with every now and again (according to a good handful I #8217;m in the 8.5/10 range!) and I was actually in a healthy relationship for a strong 2 years. Things are still going smoothly and my pride has been boosted to a healthy level. I guess under all that carelessness was a genuinely good looking guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yeah come on dude have some respect</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 20:11:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Mine] What can you deduce about me from my bathroom setup?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 20:21:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 21:03:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am male, but I #8217;m not in that age range. I #8217;m Canadian, upper-middle class, my hair is a short-medium length. The fitness statement is correct, I #8217;m single, work at Tim Horton #8217;s, I am indeed vegetarian and I do try my best to be a fair person, but not so fair that I #8217;m preachy. I do have some dogs and I do like to think I #8217;m a reasonable person, but I am often known to jump from point A to C and then B. I smoke weed infrequently, really only if I #8217;m in an awful mood that I can #8217;t do anything to fix. I live in a medium-sized town, I do like to go out but I #8217;m a pretty reserved person so I #8217;m not very energetic, I do have a larger amount of female friends and I #8217;m dominantly German and English. I like summer activities but I #8217;m actually more of a winter</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 21:08:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>No worries, bud. That was a good shot! And thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 21:56:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>That depends, does the car actually like spaghetti?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 22:38:34</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Daddy #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 23:04:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I literally just had a conversation about this with someone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 23:10:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 03:16:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not in my 20 #8217;s, and I #8217;ve already answered a good handful of the same points made by another commenter. I am tidy, actually, thank you! I also did recently brush my teeth in the photo, as I got bored and felt like styling my hair but had to wait for the product to need to be washed out (it needs to washed out after 10-15 minutes), so I decided I #8217;d clean myself up a bit more, just because I like to feel nice; I did brush my teeth in the morning but a little extra hygiene never hurt anyone too badly. I don #8217;t grow much facial hair at all, that #8217;s true, but I do enjoy having a clean face. I am indeed right handed, I don #8217;t live in the US and my hair is short-medium length. Good job, though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 03:20:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, this actually put a big grin on my face. Upvote for you, mon amie!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 03:22:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>No worries, you did good!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 03:24:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aww, just regular? I like my Cock XL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 03:30:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Snobbish French  #8220;ahem #8221;* Bienvenue means  #8220;you #8217;re welcome #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 03:39:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, so maybe my French is a little rusty, too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 03:50:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m Canadian, as well, just out of practice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 04:05:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am indeed a Canadian male, I do have my fundamentals (oral hygiene, washing my hands, styling my hair). I do have a tendency to overreact, but I #8217;m still a fairly rational person. I don #8217;t have OCD, but I do like organization. My family is doing well financially, and I don #8217;t have any facial hair at all, as I shave every two to three days. My hair is naturally straight, but I #8217;d prefer it have a curve on it like it used to. I do take a bit longer than average to clean myself up, as well. Excellent deduction!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 04:08:57</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;He looks like a strong guy, but kind and gentle #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 04:12:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>My gums have never been swollen in the past, but I do have about five fillings from when I was a kid ( #128561;). I appreciate the compliment, thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 04:14:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re really pretty! Definite 8/10!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 05:03:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I #8217;ll be sacr #233; damned</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 16:09:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck man I just woke up I don #8217;t need this shit right now  #128557;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 18:57:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>The expression is pretty mean looking; I #8217;d say if you smile a little more you #8217;d be a lot more attractive! With the smile I #8217;d say a solid 7.5/10</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 18:59:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn #8217;t even use the cream if I were you. SPF50 sun cream contains 50 suns, so it #8217;s extremely dangerous</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 20:04:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s not loss</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 03:52:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 04:07:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>EXCUSE ME BUT IS THAT MOTHERFUCKING *FIRE*?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 04:08:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why, thank you. I must say it #8217;s rather *lit*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 04:19:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/subsyoufellfor</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 04:24:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>On my way to reYEET this  #128076; #127995; #128514; Edit: shut up that was funny</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 04:57:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fap-n #8217;-nap</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:13:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just used Snapchat, bud</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 21:12:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aren #8217;t cats carnivores? Why are there so many recommended fruits and veggies?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Article]  #8220;Lots of trans kids go to therapy to help deal with their fears of being found out by their friends and family, so to help with that we #8217;re not going to give them a choice as to whether they #8217;re outed or not #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 21:45:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 04:12:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I smoke weed very infrequently, so I highly doubt that would be the cause. I #8217;m 17 and cisgendered, so hormones are an unlikely culprit, as well, and I #8217;m not on any medication, either. My scalp has no damage and is never itchy and I don #8217;t have any parasites or infections, either. I haven #8217;t been using a new brush or any new shampoo or conditioner, and I #8217;m not stressed, either, so I #8217;m really not sure what any of it could be. Maybe a visit to the barber shop and possibly the doctor #8217;s might help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 19:07:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everything is the same as it #8217;s always been</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 19:07:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really? I #8217;ve always been told it #8217;s orange by everyone, and that #8217;s what it looks like to me, as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 19:08:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Needs more garlic bread and less everything else</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 00:07:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I eat a lot of oranges and bananas, so would that have any effect?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 00:27:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have about two oranges a day and one banana every one or two</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 06:56:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not usually cold, I #8217;m never constipated, I actually feel pretty strong, my weight #8217;s been constant, I have no joint or muscle pain, I #8217;ve been in good spirits for a good few weeks, I #8217;m not tired at all, my skin is smooth and soft, my stamina is regular and I #8217;m in general good health, but maybe it #8217;s just started, so a visit to the doctor #8217;s wouldn #8217;t hurt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>LPT- the only person you should care about impressing is yourself</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 07:01:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t stress yourself over how much others like you. As long as you #8217;re working to be your best self for your own sake the people in your life who truly matter will stick to you on their own</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 07:11:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>As long as you like yourself I #8217;m sure she #8217;ll like you  #128578;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 07:13:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oof</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 17:26:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well sure but this isn #8217;t directed toward narcissists</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 18:40:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not really seeing the point of that. People will generally assume this is for ordinary people. If it *is* for narcissists then I #8217;d put  #8220;for narcissists #8221; or something like that. No point in catering for a minority when addressing a majority</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 18:42:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am a male, but I #8217;m not in my 20 #8217;s. I #8217;m not American. I try my best to be organized, and my bathroom is actually rather large, I just took a photo of the sink I use</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 18:43:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re welcome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 18:52:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>You might as well go all out at that point</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 19:08:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The meaning of what I said was that if you work to be proud of yourself you won #8217;t have to worry about impressing those around you, as you #8217;ll attract who suits you best</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 19:11:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you mean?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cuz he T H I C C</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 21:26:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 21:33:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like my space and alone time a lot, but if it #8217;s someone who #8217;s actually a lot of fun to be around and makes for good conversation then I #8217;d gladly choose hanging out with them!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 00:58:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s not that we necessarily take longer to do it, we just like being on our own and playing around on our phones sometimes, and the bathroom is a great place to do that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 01:12:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 03:32:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boi quit dissing on my senpai</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 04:37:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boi he thicc as shit and you know it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 04:50:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>No it #8217;s his thigh-job level thighs. I bet Erina was getting fucking demolished</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 05:03:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gotta love people who can #8217;t take a good joke</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 05:09:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>You must be fun at parties</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 05:27:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d love to join, mate! Could you DM the link once you set it up?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 20:06:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is ThAt A jOjO #8217;s ReFeReNcE?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The bartender says  #8220;I #8217;m sorry, we don #8217;t serve potentially faster than light particles in here. #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 06:53:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>A neutrino walks into a bar</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 20:19:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah mate he just T H I C C A S S H I T</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 06:27:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just wagging their tail left to right</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 15:47:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>GIBBAAAAAAYYYYYYYYY!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 15:53:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Theoretically, yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 15:54:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sentence still makes grammatical sense, bud</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 17:38:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god, it #8217;s like [Kingdok](http://boneville.wikia.com/wiki/Kingdok)!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 17:54:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Want a bone?](https://imgur.com/a/HJ63ozO)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 20:50:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let #8217;s say 75 BPM and they #8217;re 70 pounds, swimming in fresh water and their body is surfaced and straight in posture</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 01:44:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey bud, nothing wrong with liking yourself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 00:06:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was just posted here last week</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 17:40:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s why I asked what they dream about, bud</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 18:14:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/trashy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 19:38:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay so I don #8217;t mean to *that guy* but it #8217;s not opening on Reddit or Safari. Can someone please screenshot and send it as an imgur post?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 20:50:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d be happy to learn my partner #8217;s native language! It would help with conversation and it would make a good impression</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 20:56:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe not Axl, a bit edgy for my taste, but I like Hendrix!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 21:01:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good idea!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 21:06:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t know, I #8217;m a little paranoid about that one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 23:21:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just screen record, if you can</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 07:18:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everyone on Reddit is a boa except you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 07:23:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can #8217;t really say I #8217;ve ever had any *friends*. Sure, I like to talk to people and I #8217;m down for a party or a get-together, but generally I prefer being on my own sculpting, writing, reading, watching shows or whatever else I feel like doing. I #8217;ve never really connected with people, but that #8217;s just who I am, and if I #8217;m being honest I #8217;m happy that way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 07:32:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eat it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 07:36:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where, Jurassic Park?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 08:31:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate the support, thank you  #128077; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 12:53:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>A good comeback would have been  #8220;put a plastic bag over that empty head #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 22:32:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thought this was a diagram of human skin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 06:28:32</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Oh my god girls only wanna date fuccbois, but not me, a modest gentleman! #8221; . . .  #8220;Oh by the way I #8217;ll eat your booty like groceries #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 22:10:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Woah, that #8217;s creepy as hell! Thanks a ton, by the way, I really appreciate it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 23:25:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Spams Dragon Ball Z*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 05:50:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It would have made more sense to put a tiger in the suit so its higher definition</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;d definitely like to *BURN* this meme</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 14:33:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 14:40:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>The last one actually made me flinch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 17:48:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, this is epic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 18:34:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s like if modern day Smosh tried too hard to be  #8216;back-in-the-day #8221; Smosh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 19:19:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Burning it will just release its evil into the atmosphere. You need to lock it in a safe in a safe in a safe... so on and so forth</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 21:14:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, that would explain the arms...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 23:02:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re goddamn right it is!  #127464; #127462;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 23:23:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I peed and farded and shidded and camed](https://imgur.com/a/Rj6Rp8D)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 00:17:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably 12 year olds</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 00:39:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good grief, don #8217;t remind me...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 01:55:14</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Yo momma so fat she has her own orbit! #8221;  #8220;Oh My GoD sToP vErBaLlY hArAsSiNg Me!!! #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 01:56:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well either it was stolen from a meme page from 2009 or... *shudders*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 03:12:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Buddy, I went through the new posts in the last 24 hours and I #8217;m the only person who posted this, not to mention the tweet the image is from was from just this morning. r/quityourbullshit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 03:34:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>You expect me to know about a photo you saw three years ago on Facebook? Mate, believe it or not other people don #8217;t know everything you do</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 03:56:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is ThAt A lIzArD pErSoN?!?!?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 07:50:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>oH mY gOd I #8217;m LiTeRaLlY cRyInG sOnIc WoUlD nEvEr SaY tHiS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 07:54:26</DATE>
    <TEXT> #7482; #7506; #695;  #7511; #688; #7590; #738;  #7590; #738;  #7511; #688; #7497;  #738; #7511; #7506; #691; #696;  #7491; #7595; #7595;  #7491; #7495; #7506; #7512; #7511;  #688; #7506; #695; #8901; #8901; #8901;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;ve been having multiple gruesome dreams for the past four nights, and I just want to talk to some people about them</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 16:30:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Before I start this I #8217;d like to say I have no violent tendencies and I #8217;m actually a pretty squeamish and almost *too* gentle person, so I #8217;m not having any of the dreams because I want these things to happen. I #8217;m starting to get a little scared now, not afraid to sleep but kinda spooked when I wake up. The first dream was about a sort of circus in which people were volunteering themselves and others to be murdered. The first victim was a newborn baby, who #8217;d had two giant gashes cut into its chest by the host, then put in a stream and bled out. Next, another baby #8217;d had its head cut off with a chainsaw. I had volunteered and was assigned to operate a crane with a wrecking ball, and I had to hit a guy in a cage with it. Once I did he exploded into some kind of medication in an orange bottle (I don #8217;t take any meds, so this still confuses me). I had asked the host if I could go home, and he was surprisingly very polite and let me leave. When I was driving home I drove into a miniature swamp full of cattails, and when I awoke in the dream I was a female surgeon performing brain surgery on my actual self. I had to free tubes in my brain from fishnet, and once I did small beads began flowing through them. After that I had woken up (for real this time). I remember being really intrigued and feeling as if I was watching a show on TV. The second and third nights are very vague. All I remember from the second was a monster with scaly, black skin, six red eyes, a small mouth on its head and a large one with huge, pointy teeth on its stout torso; along with this the monster had long arms and legs, large hands and feet with sharp digits. Last night I had the fourth dream, in which I was in my parent #8217;s room at night looking through a window after hearing somebody had been torn apart in a car crash. I saw the man who was injured, his body was ripped in half with his lower body crushed into small pieces and his organs mangled and on the ground in the direction of the car that hit him. Unlike the first and second nights I wasn #8217;t curious about this at all; I was completely mortified and was feeling extreme dread and grief. That was the only dream I had last night, and I don #8217;t feel rested at all. I #8217;m not really seeking answers, but feel free to offer some if you like. I just wanted to talk about the dreams with some people, since I feel they make interesting discussion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 17:27:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fucking nuke it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 18:41:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>So essentially what he #8217;s saying is nightmares are a way to understand yourself on a deeper level and to explore ideas that are running through your mind?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 22:14:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t watch TV, so I don #8217;t think it would be that. Still, people being torn apart doesn #8217;t play any part in my life, so I #8217;m at a loss</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 22:39:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not doing a very good job of it, if you were to ask me  #128517;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 18:59:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>( #8226;)( #8226;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 23:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yo what do I get if my battery is -1 - gt; -100?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Echo #8217;s in a bit of a milk coma</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 23:42:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 00:20:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Compensating for something, Pete?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 00:21:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude how many emo dwarves have you met, holy shit  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 00:26:12</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;W-what am I supposed to do with it...? #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 05:11:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t. My siblings don #8217;t, my friends don #8217;t, my neighbour doesn #8217;t, etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 16:02:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah mate, Echo #8217;s impossible for anyone to hate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 16:04:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>She #8217;s a [Pekingese](https://s3.amazonaws.com/cdn-origin-etr.akc.org/wp-content/uploads/2017/11/12225945/Pekingese-On-White-01.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 02:09:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 21:42:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aw yiss, Texting Driver is my favourite animal!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;ve been feeling pretty distant lately and I don #8217;t have many people I can legitimately connect with, but I #8217;m choosing to keep my head up and try being positive, so let #8217;s just talk about stuff  #128578;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 05:24:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>It can be about anything- school, work, personal life (if you #8217;re comfortable with that), what #8217;s going on in the world, your views on things and anything else, really. Feel free to ask me about myself, as well (I #8217;m comfortable with anything as long as it #8217;s not too dark. Aside from that, go wild!). I #8217;m fine with talking about my views and feelings, good and bad, so don #8217;t worry about offending me with a question. I #8217;m not a very easy person to anger, anyway. I #8217;d just like to talk to people, and I feel this is the best place to do it. I #8217;m kinda lonely but I work to not let that get to me; however, I do still need a helping hand every once in a while. This isn #8217;t for me to vent, I #8217;d just like to chat with you guys. I hope to meet lots of you, I #8217;m looking forward to it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 05:26:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey bud! I was born in Langley, Vancouver, which is in British Columbia, Canada. How about yourself?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 05:28:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, did you spill anything on yourself? If not, they might just be looking for attention. I #8217;d say pet them for a bit or just sit down with them. What #8217;s your cat #8217;s name, btw?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 05:28:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure thing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 05:49:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>In terms of quirks, I #8217;m not the most talkative person (I don #8217;t really feel like people around me need to know everything I #8217;m thinking) but I usually express myself with my eyes, and apparently I #8217;m pretty good at it, since people generally know what I #8217;m feeling and almost  #8220;saying #8221; just by that. In terms of hobbies, I #8217;m an avid sculpter, and I #8217;m actually almost done a project! I #8217;ve been doing it for a little under ten years now and it #8217;s always been a way for me to just forget the outside world and create imaginary worlds where I #8217;m the boss and I can make and think of whatever I want. I also have some  #8220;side-hobbies #8221;z I #8217;m pretty into anime. I don #8217;t buy merchandise or draw fanart or really even join groups revolving around the shows aside from a few subs where I can look at memes and fanart. I #8217;m also really into music and almost always have headphones on. I like listening to stories on YouTube, as well. How about yourself?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 05:53:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>No worries, I #8217;m not a frequent talker as well, aside from one or two people I #8217;m in regular contact. Anyway, what kind of music are you into? What artists and songs are your favourites, as well?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 05:54:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds awesome, good luck! What teas do you like?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 06:00:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice! Whenever I listen to the radio I usually tune into BBC radio 4 to listen to the stories, and Boom 97.3 to listen to the music, as well. My favourite genres would have to be rock, funk, punk and alternative. In terms of soundtracks I #8217;m pretty into anime and game soundtracks (Jojo #8217;s Bizarre Adventure, Dragon Ball, Death Note, Pokemon, Monster Hunter and some others) What movies do you like?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 06:03:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve only ever tried Oolong out of those varieties. The ones I like are Chinese Green, Orange Pekoe, Mint and Earl Grey. What varieties do you recommend?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 06:08:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don #8217;t say? I had no idea  #128514; I #8217;m not really much of a movie nerd, if I #8217;m being honest, but I like to watch a picture every once in a while. I #8217;ve always been really into animation, since so much more can be visually accomplished in them. My favourites would have to be The Breakfast Club, Coraline and Ferris Bueller #8217;s Day Off. I #8217;m also pretty into Shrek and Toy Story, plus some others. I #8217;ve been thinking of getting more into Disney lately, as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 06:16:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Doesn #8217;t sound weird at all, mate. I #8217;ve just finished grade 12 and I #8217;m about to do my victory lap, and I still like to watch Bear in the Big Blue House, Bill Nye, Mr. Rogers and Sesame Street every now and again  #128517; It #8217;s been a while since I #8217;ve seen Up, guess I should revisit it Aside from music and movies, what other interests do you have?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 06:24:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s a cute name! I have a dog named similarly, her name #8217;s Georgie, in reference to [Georgina Stirling](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Georgina_Stirling) As long as she #8217;s not licking too much or too hard she shouldn #8217;t be much trouble. Maybe just lightly push her face to the side if she #8217;s getting on your nerves</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 06:27:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t really play many games, but I do play Pokemon somewhat religiously and I play Monster Hunter and Mario Kart every once in a while, as well. I like to have a go at Halo 3 every once in a while, too Are you into art, like drawing, sculpting or writing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 06:42:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don #8217;t need to be good at something to like it. Art exists in order to express feelings and ideas. You can still just look at it without making it yourself in order to enjoy it. Like I #8217;ve said in a previous comment, I #8217;m an avid sculptor, and I #8217;m just about finished a [project](https://imgur.com/a/kEJIAhL). I just need to add details and improve the structure and it should be good to go</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 06:46:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s fair. To each their own? How about some other things? Do you like science?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 06:50:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome! What branches are you most interested in? Personally, I #8217;ve always been really into entomology</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 06:53:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t think physicists are even into physics  #128514; Are you planning on entering a job in science?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 06:55:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds groovy. Personally, I #8217;ve always wanted to be a fireman</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 06:56:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>But how do the camera crew not get hurt?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 06:58:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, I #8217;m intimidated by the field, as well I #8217;m sure all firefighters are afraid whenever they tackle a fire, since it #8217;s not only the citizens #8217; lives in danger, but theirs, as well. Still, I #8217;ve always been a really determined person, and even though I have my fears I work my best to not let them consume me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 06:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>*DUN DUN DUN*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:04:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>It comes with age. Don #8217;t worry about forcing yourself to reach that point, just let life happen and you #8217;ll grow over time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m 17 and I #8217;m about to do my victory lap (basically grade 13), and I #8217;m about to apply for a job at Tim Horton #8217;s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:08:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah, not at all. I like their cappuccinos. I know they #8217;re not  #8220;real #8221; cappuccinos, but they #8217;re still nice Don #8217;t tell my mum I #8217;m drinking coffee, though. She #8217;ll take away my TV privileges for a week!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:17:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jokes, mate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:19:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s not quite done yet, but [here it is](https://imgur.com/a/RiGHiDE) If I had to choose my favourites I #8217;d say rock, punk, alternative and some others. My default would have to be alternative (The Smiths, New Order and my favourite band, The The) How about yourself?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:20:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>No worries, I don #8217;t usually expect people to get mine anyway Anyway, you like to cook?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:23:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally, I #8217;m a decent cook. I can make complicated dishes, but I #8217;m no professional</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:26:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, at least you #8217;d be having fun  #128517; That begs the question, though. If you could choose an element (Earth, Fire, Water or Air), what would it be?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:30:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow... not what I expected... I #8217;d just go with water because I like to swim and I #8217;m a pretty calm guy, but I can be really serious when I need to</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:31:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh please, you #8217;ve got nothing on me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:33:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I wouldn #8217;t call myself depressing, but I can be pretty witch-doctory when I #8217;m alone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:38:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like the average creepypasta to me.  #8220;Once upon a time a guy killed people. #8221; The stories I #8217;m into are more about people #8217;s minds being bended and going insane. I #8217;m not big on murder in stories, it #8217;s either done well or, more commonly, very poorly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:43:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like before, to each their own I #8217;ve always been really into psychology and how people work, so that #8217;s why I find stories like that appealing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:44:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome! I #8217;m taking Anthropology, Sociology and Psychology once I get back. I don #8217;t plan on making a career path out of it, it #8217;s just one of my interests. Same thing with Entomology</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:47:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a general plan for my future, but I #8217;m prepared for things to change. My main goal after graduating college is to save up enough money to travel in my 30 #8217;s for a few years before settling down. Everything else is just  #8220;whatever works #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That doesn #8217;t sound rigid at all to me. It sounds like you #8217;ve got a lot of fun stuff planned. I #8217;m just the kind of person who does what I want as long as it #8217;s not immoral or illegal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:55:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>No offense, but I think the best thing you can do when planning for the future is be prepared for randomness and change. If you #8217;re not ready it #8217;s gonna hit you like a truck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:57:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not a fan of them, either, but it #8217;s a part of life, and it #8217;s a bitch sometimes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 07:59:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think avoiding it will be just be unnecessarily stressful. My point of view is to just roll with it. It sucks but it #8217;s better than fighting a losing battle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 08:01:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you tried meditation? I don #8217;t mean sitting on a mat going  #8220;oooooooooohhhhhhmmmmmm, #8221; but more-so just taking a few minutes out of your day to sit in silence or outside for a bit and just think positively in order to calm and reassure yourself. Just have some time within your own head</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 08:04:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try not to see it as straying from it, but just adding onto it. Try making it a regular part of your day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 08:10:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whatever works for you Change of topic, what #8217;s your favourite song?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 08:12:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favourite is [Uncertain Smile](https://open.spotify.com/track/471PyH24DyOBgR4fKRXfZN?si=cwGxhVEqReaELPvMT6kvwA) by The The. They #8217;re my favourite band, as well!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 08:14:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here, just use YouTube, instead: https://youtu.be/jgu-nQDSXnM</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 08:24:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can see where you #8217;re coming from. It #8217;s the sort of music I like to listen to on rainy days</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 08:26:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course, I #8217;ll take as many as I can get! So, how was your day? Anything interesting happen?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 08:29:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, I really appreciate the compliment! I don #8217;t really make things for any reason aside from a monster I remember from a dream or if I #8217;m following along in a scary story. I #8217;m personally not much of an R amp;B guy, but I #8217;ll listen to anything as long as it #8217;s good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 08:33:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds like a lot of fun! Good work on striving toward that goal, as well, it #8217;s a good one to have! For me, I woke up around 10 and went to TD to open a bank account. I got a credit card and then immediately bought candy with it.  #128517; Aside from that today was uneventful. I #8217;ve been listening to stories, sculpting and watching over the [newborn puppies](https://imgur.com/a/IEaUHgC) as usual, so it was pretty stress free</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 08:40:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll be sure to take your advice into account, mum  #128521; But seriously though, thank you. That #8217;s some solid advice  #128578;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 08:46:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll be sure to keep that in mind Everybody always calls me the  #8220;big brother friend. #8221; I #8217;m kinda bossy, too, but I give the best advice I can and I watch out for those around me. It doesn #8217;t really bother me, but I want to hear different things about myself sometimes, you know?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 08:51:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn #8217;t call myself smart or mature or anything like that, I usually leave the judgement up to others. I #8217;m usually a pretty restricted and responsible person but even I feel held back by myself sometimes and just wanna be kiddish and silly. It #8217;s hard to let go of habits, though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 08:56:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally, I work best under pressure, it forces me to do my best. I like some calm as well, though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 15:47:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey there! You sound like a pretty busy person. How #8217;s the blog going and what do you write about? I #8217;m gonna be honest with you here. I #8217;ve been pretty down lately. I #8217;m working toward the decision of leaving my group and hoping to meet some better people. They never contact me or invite me out to places with them or even bother listening to me fully when we talk, and I #8217;ve realized I don #8217;t really matter to them as much as I thought I did. It #8217;s a difficult decision to make, though, since they #8217;re the only  #8220;friends #8221; I have aside from people I talk to whenever I get the chance to see them so I don #8217;t really have anybody to turn to once I leave. Sorry to drop that bombshell on you, I just needed to get that off my chest. I #8217;m gonna be moving back to BC in a year or two, so I #8217;m looking forward to starting my life again, in a sense. For now it #8217;s just do my victory lap once school starts back up in September, work, take care of the house and dogs and do the things I like to do. I #8217;m thinking about getting away for a bit, maybe going camping so I can just be myself and reflect on my life for a bit to see what I can do to fix my problems. Again, I #8217;m sorry to drop a bomb on you again, I just have a lot on my back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 16:02:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds like fun, I #8217;m glad you #8217;re able to do something you like, good job! Would you be alright with sharing what happened? I won #8217;t press for details if you #8217;re not comfortable to talk about it. And yeah, I #8217;m looking forward to it. It #8217;s kind of intimidating, going to a place I really only lived until I was 9 months old, so everything there is going to be new to me. I #8217;m planning on moving to Victoria for college and then exploring the world for a few years after I make enough money to do so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 20:41:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll be sure to do that, see you there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 20:49:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like a great lineup, enjoy! How about a review of each, as well?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:28:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds good!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 03:31:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally I think Baljeet and Doofenschmirtz make the best ship</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 03:35:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want Rodger to give me the succinator</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 03:49:52</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Goddamnit, I just wanted to buy a shower curtain, but now  #1040; #1083; #1077; #1082; #1089; #1072; #1085; #1076; #1088;  #1040; #1092; #1072; #1085; #1072; #1089; #1080; #1081;  #1040; #1083; #1077; #1082; #1089; #1077; #1081;  #1040; #1085; #1072; #1090; #1086; #1083; #1080; #1081; #8217;s dick is rock hard! #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;ve finally decided to distance myself from my group and I #8217;m now realizing just how angry they all made me and how sad I #8217;ve been for the past few months</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 09:31:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d been with that group for a good year and a half, give or take a few months. We #8217;d hang out at the same place together every morning and afternoon, so I #8217;d finally felt included after being accepted by them. I know I was never an actual close friend, but I didn #8217;t resent them for that and I still don #8217;t. What I #8217;m angry about is the fact that they would never contact me, never invite me out with them and never even bother initiating conversation with me aside from when they #8217;d see me in the halls or when we were all together. I know it sounds a bit childish to be mad over my own expectations, and maybe even like I feel entitled to their attention. I find it kinda silly looking back on it now. The thing is, though, I #8217;d never wanted their constant attention or for them to think of me as the backbone of the group, I just wanted them to treat me like an actual thinking, feeling human being. A text sometimes or a call or even just a  #8220;hello #8221; was perfectly fine, but I barely even got a shrivel of those at all. It didn #8217;t bother me at first,  #8220;they #8217;re used to each other so I get why they talk to each other more than me #8221; was my rationale, but over time it had developed into the realization that they don #8217;t actually care about me. Like, at all. Have you ever been with someone but still felt lonely? That #8217;s how I #8217;d felt every time I was with them. I was always ignored or given a half-assed response and nobody even bothered to message me to see how I was doing, what I was up to or even just to chat. I #8217;d felt outcasted and, frankly, belittled. If all made me realize I don #8217;t actually have any real friends, just people I see regularly. I #8217;ve finally decided to leave them behind tonight and not carry the burden of worrying about them and feeling like a liability, and although I #8217;m feeling all of that pent up frustration slowly seeping out, I also feel better. I don #8217;t feel as hated now and I #8217;m already starting to be happy again after a while. I #8217;m not interested in revenge at all, don #8217;t get me wrong when I say these things about them. I just need to let off some of the pent up heat I #8217;ve been dealing with. I #8217;m not really sure what I want to do right now, but I #8217;m happy I #8217;ve finally gotten that toxicity out of my life There are some details I #8217;ve left out for the sake of not boring you guys, but I #8217;d be fine with answering questions to add additional details in order to add what #8217;s missing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 18:21:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>What kind of stuff do you build?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 18:23:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much, honestly, this means so much to me. I #8217;m so happy to finally feel like somebody actually cares about me. I #8217;ll hold onto this for as long as I can, and I #8217;ll be sure to keep your advice in mind. Have a great day!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 21:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the support, mate, I really appreciate it!  #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 06:31:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I knead this so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 06:54:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course he has the fucking Kekistani flag on his arm...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 20:48:44</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Awaken, my masters! #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 01:01:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love how Zekrom just looks like a Bakugan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 01:12:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Oh no*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 05:14:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yo shoutout to Monster House that hoe was thicc af  #128076; #127995; #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Suddenly hella gay</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 20:21:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 22:54:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow. Just... wow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 06:17:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>****DELELELELE WHOOOOOOOOOOOP****</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 06:19:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s a really cool bird</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 04:40:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last girl I dated was 4 #8217;11, I #8217;m 6 #8217;2, and this sums the experience up perfectly  #128076; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 05:16:31</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;My mind tends to wander when ball-shaped things are involved #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 05:19:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean... it *could* be Oolong, just saying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 05:26:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>A weapon to surpass Metal Gear</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 04:09:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every time he swallows I hear  #8220;**HWOMP** #8221; in my head</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 05:18:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey baby, those legs go all the way up?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 05:28:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/imaginarybehemoths</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 05:30:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dear god, I can only imagine the sound that thing would make...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 05:36:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s some r/fiveheads shit right there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 05:41:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe more of a 4.5 head</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I know I #8217;m late to the party, but I thought you guys would still like this</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 09:52:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 21:52:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re welcome, bud  #128077; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I painted for the first time. It definitely has room for improvement, but I #8217;m not as bad as I thought I would be</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 01:19:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 03:00:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Howdy doody pratner!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 02:53:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who here remembers Over the Hedge?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 03:24:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 05:55:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a habit of taking off my glasses whenever I #8217;m being sincere. I never knew why I did it, but I #8217;m glad it #8217;s a good habit  #128578; [Pic of the glasses](https://imgur.com/a/JniM6o6), I think you guys #8217;ll get a chuckle from them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 05:57:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good bot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 05:58:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re welcome  #128077; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 07:13:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve not played before, but I #8217;ll check it out if you ever wanna play online sometime</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 07:18:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, I #8217;m a little out of the loop. I #8217;m still open to it sometime</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 22:52:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck, Richard?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 02:12:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>For those of you wondering: Esoteric class SCP #8217;s are really just used to further the narrative for an SCP (say somebody made up an SCP to test 682 #8217;s strength in combat, that SCP would be classed as  #8220;esoteric #8221;) Apollyon class SCP #8217;s are essentially  #8220;end of the world- #8220; types (e.g SCP-231, the seventh birth supposedly ending the world due to spawning the Antichrist) (yes, I know it #8217;s classed as  #8220;Keter, #8221; but it can also be seen as Apollyon) Maksur class SCP #8217;s are basically fragments of a whole SCP (e.g 682 is cut into six separate pieces- head, body, front and back legs, but each piece continues living. They would all be classed as  #8220;Maksur #8221; until brought back together to form a complete 682)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 02:23:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Adam Ruins Everything is pretty decent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 19:59:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>He doesn #8217;t want people seeing his id</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 19:59:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>OH NO!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 06:49:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aw man, she didn #8217;t even say  #8220;I love you #8221; back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 06:55:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dads leaving their kids behind. It #8217;s really morbid when it #8217;s explained...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 06:57:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s called subliminal messaging, bud</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 08:02:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why can #8217;t you just see the joke as it is?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 16:54:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>*inhale* . . . AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What do you guys think of Bot-tholomew The Butler Bot (and esteemed gentleman)?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 06:00:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 15:25:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god, I can physically feel this video</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 16:30:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>They always say yee haw, but they never ask haw yee?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In France a pain in the ass can either be something very bad or very, very good...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 08:02:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 16:14:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t think it would have mattered, either way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 16:34:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is it with liars and clapping?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 18:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s a joke, it doesn #8217;t have to make perfect grammatical sense, it #8217;s just there to be funny</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 00:50:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Say no to pornography and yes to Jesus</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 01:59:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s the funniest looking butterfly I #8217;ve ever seen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I was told by my sister #8217;s mate I look 30; I #8217;m 17. I #8217;m a bit worried about that, and I #8217;d like some other opinions</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 05:13:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m on the fence about it. I asked him what he meant and he explained that due to my voice, height, behaviour and build I look like a 30 year old man, and he was fairly surprised when I told him my real age. While I #8217;m kinda happy to seem mature and possibly  #8220;manly, #8221; I #8217;m also a little bit offended and self conscious due to not looking my age. I #8217;m worried it will be hard to date someone my age, as this isn #8217;t the first time I #8217;ve been told I look more than my age, normally 20-30. I #8217;m worried people won #8217;t be attracted to me due to thinking I #8217;m a good deal older than them, and I #8217;m also a tad concerned about potentially looking 40 in my 30 #8217;s. In the back of my head I know it isn #8217;t really a big deal, but I still feel scared to some extent. What do you guys think?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 05:16:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m literally shaking Freddy would never do this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 06:26:11</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;WHO #8217;S THAT BI- oh, sorry... #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 06:28:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re not very polite</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I (6 #8217;3) can put my chin on my sister #8217;s refrigerator</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 06:34:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 07:19:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you  #128077; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 11:53:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder what she got so riled up about</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 14:14:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess there is hope for the future, then. Thank you  #128077; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 15:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get a head rush EVERY. DAMN. TIME I stand up quickly. I have to do that slow-rise giants do in movies so I don #8217;t feel like I #8217;m about to pass out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 15:39:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh man, Peppa Pig is so cool, am I right fellow big kids?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 15:52:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I made sure to thoroughly clean my face after taking the photo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 02:27:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Link?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 02:31:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, mate  #128077; #127995; I was thinking more along the line of boxing but showcasing a diversity of styles Still, cool fight</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 16:16:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s an [Ailanthus Webworm Moth](https://bugguide.net/node/view/31529). They #8217;re generally harmless</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 16:25:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course  #128077; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 18:47:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whoopsie daisy, got me there /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 20:58:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>[N O M](https://imgur.com/a/L1idCYb)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 21:07:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can imagine us making football Timbits</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 21:14:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Real shit that #8217;s something I #8217;d still do today</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 00:34:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lovely, until you get mud on it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 00:35:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Half points for participation...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 00:50:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m assuming the questions assumes the house you #8217;d be in has a basement, which would be the safest option. A store would be difficult to hide in due to the lack of areas you could hide in along with the size of the building, making it more susceptible to being damaged by the tornado. A park would be a very dangerous place to hide, as they #8217;re almost entirely open space, greatly increasing the risk of being hit by debris. Comparing the last two, I #8217;d say a park would be the most dangerous, as at least in a store you could take shelter somewhere, and there might be a storage room you could take refuge in I #8217;m not a meteorologist, though, so I don #8217;t know the exact science behind it all</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 03:57:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you  #128077; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 18:01:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I look nothing like Shea Labeouf</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 18:03:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>How come there #8217;s a scar along with the imprint of the fingernail still there? Looks more like she lost it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 23:09:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m gonna be honest, I wrote this post when I was in a bad mood. I #8217;m a surprisingly agreeable person (when I #8217;m calm or happy), I just have different mindsets when I #8217;m in different moods</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 02:23:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got them at an underground store called  #8220;The Black Market #8221; in Toronto. They cost me $3 since they weren #8217;t sold on time, but they #8217;ve lasted me a good four months of everyday use</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 03:39:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the answer, but you didn #8217;t fully answer the question. Shouldn #8217;t the acid dissolve it, as well?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 04:30:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 13:25:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>How does one look both 0 and 40 at the same time?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 13:28:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>[GIBBAAAYYY!!!](https://imgur.com/a/SgI1UaX)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 13:29:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>It doesn #8217;t work like that, friend</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 13:39:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Remember when these were wolves? Me neither</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 13:43:15</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Wait a minute, celebrities are actually *people*?! #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 16:44:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s amazing, great job! Can #8217;t wait to see Venusaur, he #8217;s my fav gen 1 starter!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 16:48:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tried Hi-Chew for the first time a few weeks ago and I was genuinely disappointed after chewing for a minute and finding out it wasn #8217;t actually gum</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 02:56:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even as a bad boy he #8217;s a good boy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 03:21:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>AAAAAAAAAAAA WHY?!?!?!?!?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The universal agreement</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 08:01:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An iconic meme for y #8217;all</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 08:05:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 08:25:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gotta watch out for that deadly Dihydrogen monoxide</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 16:33:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I gotta admit, I actually think this is really funny</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 21:30:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you  #128077; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Gonna be a real good time</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 22:28:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 23:08:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you know it #8217;s *not* intended that way?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 23:41:28</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;I sucked dick by accident #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 23:42:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good bot, thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 23:44:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>With every hug the pupper grows another inch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 07:58:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oooooooo, r/garlicbreadmemes is not gonna like this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 11:02:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Life is fucking terrifying sometimes. You could just be enjoying your day; meanwhile, there are people in the world with sea mines made of shit from their own bodily contents stuck inside of them. I hope this never happens to me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sent a ship into deep space with a super powerful video camera in order for everybody to be able to experience what it #8217;s like to travel the stars</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 11:04:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 11:07:25</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Dude, are you actually fucking kidding? #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 11:09:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are you doing? They told you specifically to not lick the screen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 11:09:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d smack the fuck outta you for that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 11:10:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, a video, not photos. A live POV of space travel into the far reaches of the solar system</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 11:22:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s why I posted it on r/crazyideas. I know it #8217;s stupid and unrealistic, but that #8217;s why I think it #8217;s a cool idea, because it #8217;s practically impossible but still really friggin cool</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Gotta love a good pupper</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 11:34:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 19:09:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, but that wasn #8217;t extravagant enough</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 21:28:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maimoucalzetoophobia (fear of sock monkeys)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When your parents drag you to a work party and you #8217;re just sitting there alone like...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 04:38:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 04:51:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Speeedwagooowwwnnnnnnn!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Think I could get a bodacious photo of me with my hoodie and shades? I really like jazz, if you want some extra content</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 05:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 06:39:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>ThEy WeRe ThUmBs YoU uNcUlTuReD sWiNe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 06:46:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love how that #8217;s probably something Jolyne would actually do</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It #8217;s not delivery, it #8217;s...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 07:02:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 07:05:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>IT #8217;S AN ENEMY STAND</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 07:23:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>He wanted half of it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 15:50:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks beautiful, I love it! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 19:29:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s just strange enough, fren. I like it!  #128077; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 20:08:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Yu-Gi-Oh! 5D #8217;s](https://imgur.com/gallery/HEM7rhA)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The only post on here that #8217;s actually OC</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 20:13:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 23:39:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually carnivores will occasionally eat plants in case they aren #8217;t receiving enough nutrition from just meat, like Fennec Foxes. Herbivores like deer and rabbits are known to do the same with meat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 16:27:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pain means bread</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #8220;Pichu still hurts itself when it uses electric attacks #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 17:30:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 17:36:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes he does, he destroyed his arm in his fight with Muscular. It still happens when he pushes himself too far at once</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 17:37:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sweet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 17:39:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I can technically name it *anything*?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 17:41:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>How about  #8220;Legal Australia? #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 17:47:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>You want some?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 18:09:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>He doesn #8217;t really *hurt* himself, though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 00:42:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Either works</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 01:27:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>*insert Green Naruto joke*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 07:24:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>He kinda sounds like the guy who performed surgery on a gummy rat, but French</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 07:25:07</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;Yeah just make me look like the first bite of an ice cream cone #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>*Ptoo ptoo*  #8220;FINAL FLASH! #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 08:09:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 08:38:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Paw Patrol one looks like Smile Dog #8217;s mutant brother</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What are your habits for when you #8217;re creeped out?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 08:48:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know a lot of people have a nervous tick or chew their fingernails when they #8217;re on edge, but for me I have the sensation of my nails being pulled I don #8217;t mean just a light tugging and then it #8217;s gone, I mean it actually feels like someone has a firm grasp on every one of my fingernails and toenails and is prepared to pull them off. It always makes me super uncomfortable and it happens every single time I have no idea why this happens, maybe it #8217;s just out of the discomfort I get from the idea of it happening, but I #8217;m really not sure. I #8217;ve heard of a crawling sensation on the skin when uneasy, so I guess pulling is just my version of that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 08:57:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>You see, the problem with me is I #8217;m really into creepy stuff, so I get to experience this *treasure* almost every day</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 08:59:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Or is he?*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 09:00:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean sitting in dark rooms and listening to scary stories, going for walks late at night, looking up scary photos, etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 09:01:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in a really safe neighbourhood in a safe town, plus I know for a fact I lock every door before I go to bed just in case Thanks for the advice, though, I #8217;ll be sure to use it next time  #128077; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 09:03:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really just do it because there #8217;s not much to do where I live</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 09:06:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not without me, you #8217;re not!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 09:10:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m browsing r/uncannyvalley at 3 AM and I #8217;m also slightly scared of the dark, tbh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 09:17:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imagine already being on edge then looking over and seeing that... I would fucking sprint</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 09:27:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always get a little pissed off when I feel unsafe in my home. Like, it #8217;s *my home*, the safest place I can possibly be, but I worry someone is watching me from behind my phone or around a corner or in another room. Also, I know I #8217;m gonna probably be posted on r/iamverybadass for this, but being a 6 #8217;3, muscular, broad shouldered man with a deep voice I can sort of rely on myself as a source of safety</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 10:02:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>For me I flex my chest and arms in order to push up my shoulders and look bigger. It #8217;s primal but it helps out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 10:05:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m more of the fight or flight type, personally</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 10:07:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair enough, mate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 21:21:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>People are so willing to ruin someone else #8217;s life until they have to deal with consequences</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 21:52:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>His hair looks like those steel wool pads you see in art class</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 22:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amber is a good preservative because it restricts the movement of bacteria. Decomposition is the result of biological matter being broken down by bacteria, but due to the viscosity of tree resin bacteria cannot move as freely as it can in water, so less of it will be able to consume the living matter. As for why things don #8217;t decompose in amber: - a) bacteria cannot move in solid matter - b) the resin enters the plant/animal, preserving it on a microscopic level and preventing the cells from dissolving on their own and turning the entire thing into mush TL;DR- things don #8217;t decompose in amber because bacteria can #8217;t break them down, and they can #8217;t dissolve due to the amber essentially freezing them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 00:13:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Horsky</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If you could have any creative superpower, what would it be?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:25:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally, I #8217;d like to have Equivalent Exchange Essentially, I could replace the property of an object with another one; however, it would have to be of equal value to the original property Let #8217;s say I #8217;m out bowling. I want to get a strike, but I #8217;m not good enough to do so; I could double the weight of the ball in order to knock the pins away harder, but in exchange the ball would become smaller, making it harder to aim. I could also use it to make food taste better. For example, I don #8217;t like cauliflower very much, so I could remove the negative taste from it, but in return it would have a negative texture- it would taste good, but it would have the consistency of over cooked porridge. I could also use the power to make myself smarter, but I would lose half of my overall body strength, including that of my heart and lungs. To sum it up, it would be a powerful ability, but it would be fair in the sense that I can #8217;t just abuse it in order to become a god. I would have to be creative with it, making it a more interesting power.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:32:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>The thought originally came into my head while I was thinking about Jojo #8217;s Bizarre Adventure, tbh. Specifically, I was thinking about my favourite stands and Soft and Wet is one of them, with the power to remove a property from an object. I was thinking about how to put a spin on the power and I eventually settled on equivalent exchange</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:38:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s from part 8 (only manga so far), it #8217;s Josuke Higashikata #8217;s Stand. To make it less confusing, parts 7 and 8 are set in an alternate reality. Josuke 8 is a fusion of Josefumi Higashikata and Yoshikage Kira. I really recommend them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:39:33</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128526; #128077; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:46:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really giving me the Moody Blues</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:47:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>True, yeah. How about focused time travel, like making yourself younger but leaving the rest of the world unaffected?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:49:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like stealing your neighbour #8217;s milk without them noticing you!  #128520;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 02:13:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you mean?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 02:18:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s really interesting, I like it!  #128515;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Jotaro with his beautiful (ex)wife</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 04:15:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 04:24:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mum likes to use phrases such as  #8220;dear god #8221; and  #8220;good grief. #8221; I picked it up from her and have become a sort of Clint Eastwood regarding catchphrases</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 07:20:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>BREAKDOWN BREAKDOWN ORANGE JUSTICE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 10:09:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can see the appeal of that. I #8217;d definitely be happy never having pubic hair for the rest of my life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 10:12:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excuse me but that #8217;s just an unflattering photo of her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 10:15:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your hands will be so clean it #8217;s like they #8217;re not even there anymore</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>