<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject6930</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-29 23:56:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn. I thought they would mix well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Which conference would you say is the most balanced currently?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-14 15:44:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>By this I mean, nearly every game go either way and the conference isn't too top-heavy or bottom-heavy. I would personally say the Pac-12 is because every team can keep up with each other with the outlier being Washington. ASU is having a strong season; Arizona seems like they always pull off those crazy upsets at late night games; Colorado is having there best season in a while; Cal, UCLA, and USC never finish great but it seems they can beat just about any team; Utah is doing decent this season; Washington is fantastic; Oregon and Stanford are both having an off year but they can still make games close (except for against Washington); and Washington State and Oregon State aren't absolutely awful anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-23 05:47:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>OSU and UofM's game is in Columbus this year I believe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-23 05:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it does, how can you put a one loss OSU over an undefeated Alabama, undefeated Washington, undefeated Clemson, and undefeated Baylor/West Virginia (assuming they all win out of course).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-23 20:32:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I miss the 4 team cycle between EnVyUs, Fnatic, TSM, and Virtus Pro at the end of 2015. Those matches between those teams were always great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-31 01:46:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think he said successful teams</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-09 01:58:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just want to point out that A amp;M dropped only 4 after losing to a sub500 Mississippi State team whereas LSU dropped 13 after losing to the fucking gods of college football, also known as Alabama.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-10 00:27:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I so badly wanted to respond negatively and give you a downvote or something stupid. But damn, it has been years since we've been good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The CIS minor's loser final, to decide who goes to the major qualifier, was a bo1</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-13 16:56:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>How is this even a thing, 1 map deciding who goes to the qualifier. This is just ridiculous. Yeah historically teams from the CIS minor don't do much at the qualifier, but this is still something that's a problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-17 18:30:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I already owned '13 but picked up '14 the other day just for the hell of it. It's definitely worth it. Player animations after the play and during the play look really nice. Dynasty is so much better and has a coach skill tree where you can slowly upgrade your coach. Recruiting also isn't quite the same, it's a lot less of a pain in the ass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-18 17:31:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Arrival is a good fucking movie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-20 04:15:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Proxy Wars: Chattanooga  gt; USC</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In response to the sexism "controversy"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-22 00:12:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>First of all I would like to say that I use the word controversy very lightly, it's more so another awful mainstream media source trying to push an idea, with little to none research or strong basis, onto the general public. But this leads me into my point which is more in-line with the lack of females in the top levels of CS. I did some digging and checked the stats of the two most well known female teams (**CLG Red** and **Team Secret fe**) against predominantly male teams both online and on LAN (only on HLTV registered matches). * **Team Secret Fe** has lost all 19 maps they have played in with a combined score of 104-304 (that's an insanely large gap against very low tier teams in Europe). * **CLG Red** has won 2 of their 14 maps in total (both maps against a team named **Eanix** at Fragadelphia 6) for an accumulative score of 120-215. Now let me say I have nothing against female teams or female pros entering high levels of CS, in fact I would love to see the female scene spread and possibly make it to a major someday. But with the current results against the lowest tiers of male CS I feel like there is no way you could argue that in today's environment they deserve spots in larger tournaments.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-22 00:29:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Joining teams is completely fine but that is not at all what I'm talking about here. But some people argue female tournaments deserve larger prize money pools and that they deserve spots at larger tournaments, I am just simply arguing otherwise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-23 04:30:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so proud of this team. So many years of hardship and poor seasons it's great to see them not only making a bowl game but also going 7-5 (including a dub over the Chips)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-24 02:23:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn't know you were a Michigander. Let's go Red Wings</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-26 01:03:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>So now that the game is over, the players can come back from there boycott.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 01:13:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you would've told me at the beginning of the year that Wisconsin would play Penn State in the Big10 Championship, I would've told you to get behind Manti Te'o in line for imagination land.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 01:18:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus what has happened to the Ducks. Take me off the crazy ride of 2016.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-27 04:29:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I personally expected Iowa after there killer year last year. But then again I should have expected Ferentz to have a let down year considering he just got an extension.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 18:30:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Interesting is who they're dropping. FNS was very much expected, TSM had absolutely zero chance to reach the next level with him on the roster. But Twistzz as well? I personally expected semphis to be dropped, because iirc he is the IGL as well as an AWPer, and they picked up players of both of those positions if this goes through. I would assume Twistzz heads to a solid team, considering he's pretty damn good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How should I get into college hockey?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-01 16:59:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've always enjoyed hockey, as well as college athletics, and if I see the frozen four on tv I'll usually watch it. But lately I've been trying to fully get into it, which is kinda hard considering most main stream media sources don't follow it at all. Just wondering if there's anything I should know? Anything much different from NHL when it comes to on ice play? Thanks in advance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-03 05:02:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fellow /r/GlobalOffensive user checking in. I never thought I'd see this on fucking /r/CFB of all places.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-03 21:03:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/theydidthemath</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-04 21:57:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean shit dude. I had us 4-12. I had no faith in this team, especially not in Caldwell. I thought we'd fire him halfway through the year and end up with some interim. But I'm so glad I'm wrong. Gonna go see the Lions in person for the first time ever next Sunday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Best bowl games to go back and watch?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 14:25:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>With bowl season starting in about 13 days, I thought I'd wish everyone a happy (almost) Bowl season! I've always had such a strange fascination with bowls, I watch every single one nearly every year. But getting in preparation for this year's bowl season, I wanna watch some of the best bowl games from the past. All I can think of off the top of my head is the OU-Boise State Fiesta bowl from a few years ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>QUALITY LOSSES</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 15:46:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-05 22:06:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be ECS where they got Astralis. Major qualifier bracket/swiss system/groups have yet to be announced yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Finally going to first Lions game Sunday</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 03:15:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Finally going to my first Lions game on Sunday after years of watching. Anything I should know or need to do downtown? I want to make my gameday experience the best possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 04:40:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn. Your username. Life sucks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 04:47:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a comeback. Really happy with coming out with the W after being down 3-1. Sick shot from Zetterberg in the shootout.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-08 01:20:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I fucking love root beer. Any kinds that I should try?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-08 01:24:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good stuff, but I'm personally a Mug guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-08 20:48:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/gallery/WxU4U tb to the UofM/Wisky game ^^^not ^^^really ^^^a ^^^selfie ^^^but ^^^whatever</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-10 01:49:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spot on. Thinks it was all s1mple lmao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-11 00:23:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let's go red wings. And yeah, I agree, fuck Crosby.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-11 01:48:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm still in high school so I took a part time at Subway. Been here for 1 and a half years. Tonight's shift I got stuck with this one girl who refuses to do anything. Won't make any subs for customers, clean, or anything. What do I even do? Like I can get shit done by myself but it's a pain in the ass and she's getting paid for sitting in the back on her phone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-11 02:26:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like you. ^^^but ^^^i ^^^also ^^^hate ^^^you ^^^^^because ^^^^^Iowa</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-11 02:33:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, planning on moving out west and going to Arizona State. You hoping to go to Iowa?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-11 02:38:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>What made you an Iowa fan then? Parents go there or used to live there?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-11 02:53:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah I see. Well good luck out there. And enjoy Kinnick stadium, I imagine you'll go to a couple games, and it's pretty hype out there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-11 05:20:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow. 0 shots on goal, 1 MLS Cup. The better team didn't win today, but that's what makes soccer so exciting. Edit: what? lol I got downvoted for literally stating a fact. Not even a Toronto fan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-11 16:36:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you get the TuneIn app, you can get a 7 day free trial and you can listen to any game free.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-11 16:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not tailgating, but hanging out with my dad at the Beer company.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-11 20:26:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't wanna be that guy. But the difference between not and now is pretty big</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-11 20:28:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate the Pack, passionately. But a 2nd seed with a first round bye is more important than than the Pack losing another game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-15 15:35:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>with the Browns, 20 plays should be *way* shorter than 20 yards</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-15 20:35:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not exactly a fix but I would love more customized/individualized campuses and stadiums. I'd love to hear Womp Womp at Houston games, more traditions, oh and don't forget Boomer Sooner after every OU first down. I would also love FCS schools implemented.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-15 20:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Watched the UofM/Wisconsin game. Next year planning on one in the Big House, as well as a trip down to South Bend to see the Irish and USC play.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-17 04:34:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>1st time since 2004 that Wisconsin-Whitewater or Mount Union didn't win. That year it was Linfield that won.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-18 02:18:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>that doesn't happen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-18 19:41:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't wanna be happy that someone is injured. But if Jenkins is actually hurt that's huge for our offense</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-18 20:11:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those were the percentages on CSGOLounge, ^^^^^rip I wouldn't say those are odds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-19 14:07:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me just assuming here, Lions didn't get enough time themselves to look at the play and challenge it? That's the only logical thing I can think of, but then again, when is Caldwell a logical thinker?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-19 18:21:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not your standard cheese bread</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-19 18:51:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like about half Lions fans also like the Pats, because of Brady's Michigan ties. I know I do at least.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-19 22:01:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you mean sliders then I would recommend heading over to operationsports subreddit. Pretty good sliders can be found there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-19 22:44:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the actual shit, you greedy money-loving ESPN fucks. Show the game not the damn commercials.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-20 02:54:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>E</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-20 23:31:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same happened to me. Lost 28-42 to Ohio State. Not nearly as pointsy or as large a point diff but that's because it was a slow run game. Me as an OC can only do so much, my DC Sucks ass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 18:32:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>There isn't really any important stats for pro bowl voting. Except who's the more popular player</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 16:04:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just because the 76ers own them doesn't mean they can get as much cash to invest in a team as they want.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 05:59:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>And Cowboys fans wonder why people don't like them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 22:19:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was posted earlier. Sorry bud</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 00:22:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kinda new to this sub. What's the jacket in the left pic?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 01:18:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks fam</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 01:45:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can I get a source on that hat?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 20:09:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder which org it will be under. I would assume it would stay nV because of the core of the team already being under the org, but who the fuck knows</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 01:21:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had us getting a 4 or 5 win season but now we in the playoffs. Have some sips and enjoy tonight's game bros</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 01:28:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Home against the Giants if we win, and away against the Seahawks if we lose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 01:30:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who cares about ESPN. Fuck the media, and fuck the Pack. We're in the playoffs. Sip!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 01:33:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>FUCK THE PACK</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 03:24:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Zach Zenner likes to eat, Eat, EAT!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 03:35:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw the hold as well but apparently the refs didn't, but whatever, it's 4th down</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 03:44:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good shit Boldin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 03:44:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>ZZ is eating this defense tonight</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 03:46:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now we need to keep giving the ball to ZZ in the second half</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 04:20:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>So our secondary disappeared that drive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 04:26:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had to be some miscommunication there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 04:30:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Live by night. Originally was a book, and it's pretty fuckin great</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 04:38:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could download TuneIn, and just use the free trial to listen to the game. I had to do that once earlier in the season when I had no other way to watch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 04:44:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would say your right, but the fans of this team that have been following through years and years of disappointment sure as hell deserve it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 04:44:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah it's prohibition era with a bunch of mob shit. I hope the movie is as good as the book.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 04:46:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's hilarious you kids talk shit about Stafford.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 05:33:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really feels as if we've given up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 05:37:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck? Why can't we move the ball like this throughout the game. This hurry-up, 2 minute drill-like scheme works, why don't we apply it throughout our offensive attack.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 05:40:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everything about this game just pissed me off; Rodgers dick in the announcers mouths, us not being able to stop anything in the second half, that long haired fuck on their OLine that seemed like he was holding Ziggy every play, Stafford having arguably one of his worst games on the year, and last but not least getting my heart torn out again and again. I love this team, but god damn I hate them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 05:41:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>But is the game really still a a game at this point?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 05:56:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck being a Detroit fan sometimes. Red Wings gone to shit, Pistons are mediocre, Lions made the playoffs but our best wins are the Vikings and Redskins, and don't forget the Tigers we're gonna have a few years of rebuilding with them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 06:10:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>All of them being "Instant Classics" man I'm so tired of this fucking shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 03:16:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus christ, the game that just keeps giving</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 03:24:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here we go boys</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 03:30:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so happy we didn't lose in an instant classic today, we also didn't lose 31-0 to Clemson in the playoff!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-03 03:57:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>But we have shut out every team we've faced in the playoffs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 01:40:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>These "package deals" in the French scene really fuck shit up. shox wouldn't have even left nV if he wasn't a "package" with SmithZz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 01:46:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shhhhh, don't give them any ideas</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mouse dpi/sensitivity random inconsistency</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 05:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>For some reason my mouse keeps changing speeds going from a sometimes real slow speed to a really fast. its the same problem as in [this steam forum post](http://forums.steampowered.com/forums/showthread.php?t=3236906), and it only happens in CS:GO. I own a SteelSeries Rival 700 if that helps. This problem started a few days ago, I have owned the mouse for a few weeks now. Does anybody know a fix?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 05:49:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Raw input is on and im not sure about advance pointer precision ill have to check edit: pointer precision is checked off so thats not the problem here, thanks for the suggestions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 06:00:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>i unbinded that button after thinking that was the problem, i think ive checked all the obvious possibilities, its gotta be something thats not common</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 18:38:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's been off as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 18:39:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good idea I'll have to check, I hope it's not broke though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-06 17:22:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's a joke. Might be a true story though??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-06 19:21:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're pretty dumb if they think this gonna help. Higher bitrate but it's not as large as a platform, only reason I ever watched an online match in the first place is because of the ease of access on Twitch. YouTube gaming isn't the same.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-08 05:40:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>We need one of those imo and hope their not an NFL bust. To have one of them be a lock-down corner as well as Big Play Slay would be a huge starting block for this defense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-08 05:45:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>God I hated playing 3 weeks in a row on primetime, especially when all three games we sucked ass (except the first half against the Cowboys).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 03:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Were you saying hot as in you think it's hot, or as in McQueen thinks she's hot? Because there's a rather large difference</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 04:38:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You and me both then haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 21:20:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>No /s needed, it's a joke that a "world championship" only has a 250k prize pool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 19:16:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Enjoy your birthday man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 17:47:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>More relevant than the Chargers will be in LA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 22:16:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tried opening the auto save file but it wouldn't work (I'm assuming because the main file had been deleted).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 22:42:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright thanks, I'll try that later.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-19 17:34:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit I go to school with him haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-19 17:46:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know he's on the USA team (which isn't doing too hot in their respective league), I'm not sure if he plays for our school team, I don't believe so though. Either way I haven't seen him play, just sit next to him in one of my classes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-22 19:02:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly, when you check out the reviews it's either a ten or a one most of the time. They don't genuinely give their exact opinion and go all in on either 10 or 1.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 00:54:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most frustrating match I've ever seen as a Liquid fan. Definitely didn't feel as close as it was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is it possible we could get bandwagon flairs for the upcoming playoffs?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 04:15:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>With the playoffs of the major here, that leaves us with half the teams gone which leaves a lot of fans looking for a different team to cheer on to win the major. With me being an example, I'm a Liquid fan that now is cheering for North to win it. Most other sports subreddits do this, such as NFL, NBA, Hockey, Baseball, and [CFB](http://imgur.com/a/myrF1). I just thought it would be fun to have a second selectable flair for us to bandwagon on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 04:32:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus fuckin Christ</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 13:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would agree with you, but apparently "Sesame Street Live" has been booked for today for a long time. So they couldn't get the arena open for that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-28 22:08:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>First 2-0 of the major</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Astralis are the ELeague Major champions!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 20:35:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 01:04:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>You kidding? Some people are fans of players so they cheer for the team of the player. And then there's fans of teams who support the core of the lineup or the org.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 01:07:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>If Liquid is gonna upgrade Hiko to Stan they sure as hell aren't letting go of Elige</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 01:11:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>That doesn't make any sense. Elige wants to win, and honestly dropping Hiko for Stan is a great step forward. Anyways Liquid isn't gonna upgrade in one spot just to let Elige walk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 01:23:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>ok https://twitter.com/nwdekay/status/826948952117256192</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-03 19:53:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah that's nice and all but he doesn't have the best player in the world's config. -a2z</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-05 04:41:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>pics or didn't happen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-05 05:03:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>that dunk by LBJ at the end was pure sex</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How would you value Andre Drummond and Reggies Jackson?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-06 16:59:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Title says it, **IF** we were to trade them, what do you think we could get out of them on the market?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-06 20:38:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry for hijacking but wtf, I'm a Pats fan and this tweet is ridiculous. On NE he had 4 receptions for 42 yards and a TD (the touchdown being against Miami, which was a blowout anyways). Yeah man what a turn around, couldn't have done it without you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 18:31:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't think an /s would be needed for a post like this, but then again this is /r/globaloffensive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 18:32:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Excited for this, also would love to see Fnatic play in this laid back atmosphere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Games starting at 9pm EST?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-08 04:44:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haven't been able to catch much College Basketball this year, but I had to watch my boys in blue take on Sparty tonight. I also wanted to go to go to bed at a more reasonable time. But why the fuck is an eastern time zone game starting at 9? This doesn't make any sense to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-08 13:41:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not for someone who has to wake up at 5 the next day</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-08 14:48:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not listed on the site but likely with aizy leaving FaZe, he will most probably replace RUBINO on North. ScreaM would then be the filler on FaZe, and RUBINO would head to Maikelele's team eZaF. Edit: apparently ScreaM to FaZe didn't work out and he will head to EnVyUs replacing devoduvek. I'm curious as to who FaZe will add.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-09 12:44:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah this isn't like that, I'd say it's more like "The Decision" when LBJ left the crappy Cavs to join up on the loaded Heat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-10 00:39:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can only imagine there is a big fat buyout on ScreaM's name once that time comes around</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 14:55:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same here, not complaining though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-15 17:11:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>So just a silver?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 04:10:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>We at /r/detroitlions are proud of two things; 0-16 and our memes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DeKay: Las Vegas Crowd wasn't Representative of NA fans</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-22 17:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ELeague announces season of Street Fighter</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 18:31:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-24 04:05:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>KClutchP saved our asses today. Ish is the future, not Reggie. We better try to trade Reggie in the summer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-01 00:53:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idk man, might just be me but if I was a top org I wouldn't drop a rising Dig for an American team. And I am American</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-01 22:10:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You seem to have forgot about Immortals</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-01 23:15:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>What? The [standings](http://wiki.teamliquid.net/counterstrike/Intel_Extreme_Masters/Season_XI/World_Championship) in the regular rounds of this round robin were; 1) FaZe 4-1 2) Astralis 4-1 3) Immortals 4-1 4) Fnatic 2-3 5) NiP 1-4 6) OpTic 0-5 With **Astralis**, **FaZe**, and **Immortals** all tied with each other in spots 1-3, as well as there losses being to each other. That means those teams are in the tiebreaker.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 03:02:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>WELL WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT, WE WERE IN ANOTHER INSTANT CLASSIC</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 20:34:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since Heroic has head to head against both Na'Vi and North they get the spot in the semis.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 04:33:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>ITS OVERREACTION TIME</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-04 23:02:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Christ who cries over women not going to him in /r/Hockey</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-09 17:31:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Although from a broader perspective Detroit is declining, the past few years or so things have gotten much better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-09 21:33:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rest In Peace</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 05:21:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I'm probably gonna help fund this, I haven't really been this intrigued and excited for a game in a while. Just make sure you guys don't pull a No Man's Sky on us and you'll do all right</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 16:34:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>74 madden rating</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-11 20:43:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm totally fine with being a Renegades fan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-11 23:13:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>NEPHEW</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-11 23:15:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree it's definitely a better option. But where to?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-11 23:19:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why? From past decisions the team cares more about winning then being an "all NA team." For example bringing s1mple in as well as Pimp.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-11 23:52:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think NAF or Rush will go to Liquid because of there bad blood with Stan, we all have to remind ourselves this is NA. I hope the guys can grow up so we can see teams get better and not let beef or politics hold them back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-11 23:56:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>But is mouz really in a better spot then C9 (obviously only if there willing to drop Ska for mixwell)? I mean I guess I could see EnVy but I think if mixwell gets an offer from C9, then I could see him go there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 00:50:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Again I agree with you, but EnVyUs is his best chance at exploding into the EU scene and if they don't offer him I don't see where else he would go. The NA CS mentality is pretty bad but I would be dumb as hell to take mouz over C9.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 17:58:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>FUCK THE PACK</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 18:00:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly I would put us higher then around 10 with this o-line</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 18:00:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a fucking ride. 10/10 would do again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 18:18:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>again LOL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-12 22:09:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Crazy](http://www.freep.com/story/sports/columnists/jeff-seidel/2017/03/09/michigan-baketball-team-plane-crash/98975924/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 20:01:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's some pretty good reasons for these. Koosta was pushed out of the position he came to play in by s1mple. JDM is still pretty good, but as we've seen lately the AWP meta is slowly becoming less effective. Dedicated AWPers are dying, they need to be able to hybrid on rifles, and JDM clearly can't rifle. And pimp is still pretty important to the roster, not sure why you call him a "non-factor," he does what he needs to in-game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 20:02:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. Enemy was built around Koosta, he could do what he wanted when he wanted. On Liquid, s1mple took over his role.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 14:02:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>OP stole his shoes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tim Lelito visiting Detroit today</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 14:32:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 14:33:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>71 Madden rating btw</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>PGL to hold next CS:GO major in Krakow, Poland</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 18:33:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Jason La Canfora: Oakland and Detroit are possible landing spots for AP</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-16 15:26:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-17 21:02:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not OP but Creighton didn't deserve that 6 too much but don't talk about SMU like that. They definitely deserve that 6 possibly higher.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-18 19:38:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol what? He had bomb on site and it seems from the screenshot Shazam provided on Twitter that n0thing had the upper hand in his current gunfight. That turns it into a 1v3 with bomb planted, you can't actually be serious saying there's no way he could win that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's hard saying no to this face when he's begging for a snack</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-19 18:45:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-19 21:31:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Deleted right when I came into the thread. Wanted to at least see the story RIP :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 00:42:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Username checks out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 01:17:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>**#NotMyOneSeed**... No? Alright next time it is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 04:16:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>ACC is easily the best conference. Oh and I'm pretty sure Marquette will upset South Carolina.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 13:57:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still too early to tell for GeT_RiGht, let's see him play a little more</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 11:35:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus christ guys, is he self aware?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 16:58:35</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;downtown Arizona</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 02:03:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man I would love to go to the finals, fate has me out there in Phoenix at exactly the right time. But stuffs expensive haha, yeah I would sell through StubHub, that's what I usually buy from</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 02:11:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha not my team, normally a Michigan fan but jumping on the SCar bandwagon atm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 02:15:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>at first i thought yellow shirt guy was holding a small dog</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Final four wallpapers for your bandwagon needs</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 04:06:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 05:33:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>After looking up pictures for these I noticed him re-appearing a lot, so I got the pleasure of learning about him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 06:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, wasn't too hard though. Took about 20-25 minutes, hardest part was finding the right pictures</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 21:41:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>[and here you go](http://imgur.com/a/E7qqS)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Frozen Four iPhone Wallpapers for your bandwagoning needs</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 22:33:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 22:33:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Finding a good quality arena pic of Harvard was hard so I stuck with that one. Also the colors for Denver were hard to mess around with so I stuck with that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 02:49:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep, college hockey photos in high quality aren't exactly plentiful. And even when there are the picture angles and such usually suck. I could make a better one though if you'd like?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 14:17:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Appreciate it I'll make a new one when I can</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 14:19:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll gladly make some WMU ones?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-04 23:49:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Psh who needs more hits anyways</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 20:22:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>In a tournament with; world beaters in Astralis, the Virtus Plow, both Brazilians in SK and Immortals, Gambit the cobble gods, honeymoon NiP, the French superteam, the drug Danish CS in North, Na'Vi, Fnatic gods back together, as well as a star-studded FaZe. With those teams, who would've thought CLG would make the playoffs?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 20:27:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Beating CLG? nice try Brits, America always has hope</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 23:01:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank god for the slight pitching meltdown. Saved our asses</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-08 03:54:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Out here in Phoenix tonight repping the Thunder, lots of Thunder fans out here actually. Ready to see history.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-08 06:28:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The whole stadium was desperate for it, it felt more important than the game's final score itself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-08 23:38:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice run by CLG. Nice seeing a little structure from them when they were expected to go out in groups</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 01:30:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will they ever lose again?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 01:36:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>seriously tho, he's the hero we need but don't deserve</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 22:05:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>NiKo's first big win, the best Finals since SK (then LG) vs. G2 Bo5 at EPL last year (for me at least), and an Inferno decider. What a great conclusion to a really fun tournament. Also pretty glad rain dropping his gun on round 29 didn't cost them the game, that would've sucked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 22:15:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah they almost won gfinity spring in 2015, but lost to nV in the finals</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 22:18:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah I did mean EPL, I just forgot that SK were still LG at the time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 22:19:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I definitely could see that, I guess it's all in preference.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 22:42:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>What an embarrassment of an 8th inning. Slight flashbacks of how our BP looked a few years back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-13 03:02:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Assuming they don't want to have to try to come out of the NA minor with both C9 and Immortals there, they probably keep JDM till then. Giving him enough time to try to pick up form and keep his spot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 05:14:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>holy butt clench</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 23:44:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>God fucking damnit, I thought I left Beth Mowins back in /r/CFB</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-15 23:47:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>it is but i'll be damned if it doesn't sound exactly like beth</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 01:48:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh yeah, that's what it feels like</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 05:14:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are jesus</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 22:36:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well at this rate we'll finish the season 108-54.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-17 07:55:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>REVERSE YES</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hanging out atop the four peak's highest point at Brown's Peak</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 15:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 15:46:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wasn't the longest or hardest hike I've ever done, but definitely fun going through the chute and a really nice view.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-19 17:28:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Niceee got myself a Lions one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 02:46:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alongside with the right wear, I'd suggest a nice umbrella if your walking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 04:49:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would guess the Cobras</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 05:01:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice seeing the offense click but our pitching was fucking embarrassing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 15:22:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll try to get a YouTube link up tomorrow, in case anyone else does a YouTube stream make sure not to call it "Zurich Classic Free Livestream" or something like that, those are really easy to find and take down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 18:40:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll try and get something going. I used to stream NBA games off my old Reddit account so I'll see if I can set it up right again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 04:34:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>How fucking embarrassing, we got our asses handed to us repeatedly in this game. ^^^^btw our bullpen sucks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 17:13:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>K</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-28 02:23:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>WHAT THE ACTUAL FUCK</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-28 03:42:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Especially with early talk of him possibly going to the Browns, must be great to go from Cleveland potentially to a Houston team with a damn nice looking future</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-28 04:42:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm disappointed we didn't take Reuben Foster, but Bob knows best</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>First time breaking 100 since moving back a set of tees. Got a 99.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 01:55:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 19:46:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think if Desmond King drops all the way to next round, we should take him. I remember early on his draft stock was great, I don't know what happened for him to drop this late</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 19:52:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not what you guys needed, but having watched him throughout my entire life I have to say he is a good wideout. Not gonna be your #1 or #2 guy, but still a really solid player.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 20:43:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just watching the feed go by, butt clenched, hoping Brantley is still available.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 20:56:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I find it interesting how we haven't picked up a dline player yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 21:02:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>watching him return is something else, he seems like he could be a huge steal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 15:35:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Came here for Parks and Rec reference. Not disappointed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 17:51:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was one of the first to redeem, did it just as it was posted. Never got an email confirmation, so I'm not expecting anything to be honest</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 17:55:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I know where I'm going later today.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 18:14:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Driving, second, and third shots aren't my issue. I play god awful around the green</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 18:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shot a 99, still alright off the tees and fairway, and also still can't chip/putt for shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 19:54:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe so, I've seen the course's name being watermarked on their videos before</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 16:04:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have access of the golf channel but I'd like to see DJ and the early groups. I can never find a PGA Live stream, I'm tempted to just purchase it and stream it myself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 13:24:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only videos I watch are from the meandmygolf guys</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 19:27:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>At first to me it looked like a big ass driver head</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 21:39:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>No Desmond Howard or Anthony Carter for WR?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-08 01:55:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Should KRod still be our Closer?](http://i.imgur.com/5CCqLFT.gif)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-12 13:27:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember my first eagle was a par 5, I hit the right dogleg really well, hit my follow up onto the green and then one putted from 20ft away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's the worst possible torture, that does NOT include pain infliction?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 02:16:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 17:53:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Watching the crowd in this gif reminded me I need to go to more games this year</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 22:20:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>it looks like its gonna be a film instead of a series</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I was skeptical at first</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-21 21:13:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was also kinda worried I would do it wrong, but after I started I realized you can't do this wrong because it's pure instinctive feeling. It was a pretty incredible experience</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 05:04:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>We could make a religion out of this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 12:43:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/efreebies would be a better fit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 17:36:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>For those that can't open; Melancholia, The Fountainhead, A Man with a Movie Camera, Psycho, To Be or Not to Be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-27 16:49:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/efreebies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 22:12:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work at subway, we had it a few years back. I'm glad we brought it back, it tastes really good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Started a discussion about Narnia with my tinder match</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 03:32:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 19:13:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep that's the one, not sure if it's national, but it is in a lot of places</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 02:02:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd personally do Elephant as a starting point. And assuming that the different parts are then scaled to the size of the creature I would add hummingbird wings because those motherfuckers are fast. Then I would add a scorpions tail to it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 05:24:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I started Master of None yesterday and I'm already 11 episodes in. It's extremely relatable with how Dev (Aziz Ansari) goes through everyday life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-05 15:34:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haven't seen it yet but from what I've heard it does have closure, that's why most people are surprised there's a season 2.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is watching these finals hell for anyone else?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 04:53:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a good matchup and all but who on earth do I cheer for? Because with OKC being my second team and being a basketball fan in general, Fuck KD. And as a Pistons fan Fuck the Cavs and Fuck LBJ (even though I got mad respect for the guy). So far I'm leaning towards GSW just because of the stuff LeBron has said lately, what about you guys?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 16:37:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. Because every single person in Michigan is cool with this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 16:50:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit how have I never seen this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-09 17:43:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I miss the days when olofm was on top of the world. This article proved to me that he should be the poster boy for CS, he's a smart/self-aware guy and one of the greatest to play the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-09 20:05:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>English speaking capabilities are huge and, Olof has a much more marketable personality and face. E: although I would put Pasha up there in the top 5 for being a "poster boy."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-09 21:29:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Savage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-09 21:36:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>jks when Renegades were at ELeague, on a community DM server. E: also with ptr when he still was a part of CLG</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Looking to make podcast based on Netflix originals</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 05:01:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not quite sure if this is allowed, because the rules don't say anything about it. But anyways I've been wanting to make a podcast for some time and I have been looking for a topic. Today I came up with the idea of creating one where me and one or two peers discuss and review all new Netflix originals (both film and series). And I came to here where all fellow Netflix users reside to see if I could find a co-host. If you're interested comment on this post or pm me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 05:08:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>the NBA is looking like a joke tonight</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 05:15:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>those saying that the NBA wants the Warriors to win tonight are high. Cavs win means more games, more games means more tv time which means lots more money.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 18:24:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah when I go through with this I plan on covering everything. Obviously we would put popular shows as a priority because that means more clicks. But I'm definitely planning on doing everything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 05:39:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well for weekly seasons we would do weekly reviews. And I would imagine for shows that release all at once we would do 1 episode for every 4 or 5 episodes depending on the length.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fuck the penguins :(</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 04:58:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 19:09:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tomorrow night actually, but yeah I'm excited for the future.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 19:14:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>My store recently started doing prep in the mornings which is a heck of a blessing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 21:59:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank mr friberg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fuck the Cavs :)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-13 05:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-13 07:48:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh I agree, fuck both of em.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-17 06:02:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>CHEESE AND RICE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-17 20:45:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know if we were watching the same show, but there really isn't a main plot to it. The show is more based around giving an in depth view of Aziz's views on each topic that was discussed (relationships, elders, life goals, etc.). His views being shown on screen by his character Dev, as well as some comedic balance to the show.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-18 03:05:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was this just you testing out different music and cinematography styles? If so not bad. But if it wasn't that, I guess I'm kinda confused as to what the point is</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-22 02:49:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>He might just be really bad at passwords, I mean for all we know his new password could be *gocavs1*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-22 18:36:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry, did you forget what your management is like?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 01:09:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can understand for a team like the Cavs who are in win now mode, but that's literally it. E: I could see the Spurs wanting to pull the trigger too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 01:57:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pour one out, then rub one out? Because you guys got a fucking beast</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 02:23:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck GarPax ^^Am ^^I ^^doing ^^this ^^right ^^?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 02:38:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>considered /=/ will happen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 02:40:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's basically Philly Jesus at this point</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 02:44:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>But did Wentz die for your sins?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pistons take Kennard at 12</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 02:47:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 02:50:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>As to be expected tbh, definitely don't expect a trade to come out at this point. SVG and his win now attitude makes no fucking sense</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 02:56:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah just realized that my bad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 03:06:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I smell a bamboozle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 05:14:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Frank Mason dropped kinda far, Sac might've gotten a steal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 05:24:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Celtics also possibly getting a steal with Semi, he was a really good player that carried that SMU team, interested to see what else he might be able to do</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 07:14:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>We just got swept in a 4 game series, to the fucking Mariners. Sorry but this is the absolute last straw, fire Ausmus and rebuild this shithole of a club.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 16:46:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's been going for 20+ minutes, what the fuck. This is a 600k tournament with delays that are long as fuck and awful production. It also makes no sense that they got the arena for 3 days, but are only utilizing it for fans on 2 of the days? You're 100% right, I don't think they care one bit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-23 18:09:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess I find it weird that they're playing in the arena because usually they end up playing in a studio. I suppose it makes sense if there testing it out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-24 20:06:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Considering NiP just added Rez and haven't had a real shot to use him, it's definitely gonna be a little bit longer before there's a chance of it happening.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-25 07:07:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>HEY! ^^We're ^^Ass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"Can I get a meal, without a drink or side?"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-27 03:10:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-27 06:48:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah there's no guarantee life will get better, but there's a chance, and for that I personally keep on going. I just got my heart broken tonight and I'm fucked up over it, but as sad as I am I'm also glad to be sad. Sadness is an emotion, an experience, everyday I feel something I know I'm living. This comment is a bunch of rambling on, but I just need to say that it's worth it to keep on trying and looking to find happiness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-27 06:57:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to be in the same boat as you. It sucked to say the least. But as much as I wanted to die, I realized that I also really wanted to live, I wanted to experience more of life, try things I haven't done before. I don't think it's worth it to commit when the world is so big and there's so much to do, so much to feel, so much to see. I know my comment probably makes no sense and it's rambling on, but it feels like you mostly need a friend or companion to talk to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-27 07:23:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know how it is with social anxiety, I suffer from that hard, and it's bullshit. I drew a bad card in life, and I've suffered because of it, I used to feel exactly like you did. But instead of committing I decided to wait, and I'm glad I did. I put effort into cleaning myself up, and trying to make the most out of life. Don't get me wrong my voice is wavery and legs are shaky whenever I talk to people, but I've learned to keep trying. There's no loss in trying, in fact I think it's worth the effort. Check out /r/SocialSkills it's helped me out a ton in trying to become better socially.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-27 08:32:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could seek a counselor/psychologist, there not allowed to say why you're visiting. Anyways companies are not allowed to discriminate against things like that. Saying all this I'm assuming you're from the US?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Vote for Michigan's Best Inland Lake (Detroit Free Press)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 18:45:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DL Rashan Gary is on the Sporting News pre-season All-America team</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 19:34:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 19:35:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>OL Mason Cole is on their second team as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 20:31:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>SHIRTLESS FOR LAST YES</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 20:32:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>HE FUCKING DID IT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 20:33:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>HOLY SHIT 14 NOW</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 20:34:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>this is what we call history ladies and gentleman</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 20:35:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>What if I told you 4 days worth of calories can be eaten in 35 minutes, 30 for 30 presents...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Contractor: Worker's death at Little Caesar's arena "not a cronstruction accident"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 22:38:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-29 00:03:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you think about it best is an opinion, and this poll is just trying to find out which one is the best in most people's opinion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-29 17:30:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah going from all those long intense matches to that one was fucking weird</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-30 02:41:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm 17, and the first championship I remember was Texas in 05-06. So this list is pretty much correct.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Absolutely hating the offseason lull of American football</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-30 23:09:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I need something to fill my hunger for football, so I'm here to give CFL a shot. And as it looks like from the standings, the season is just starting. So I'm here to find out about the league itself (I already got the basic idea of main rule differences). 1) Who's the Patriots of the CFL? 2) The Browns of the league? 3) Best players out there that you could see making it to the NFL one day? 4) Rivals or matchups that are really fun to watch?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-30 23:31:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's definitely streets ahead</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 00:28:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks a ton, great information. It looks like Winnipeg and Saskatchewan play tomorrow so I have something to look forward to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 02:18:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's exactly why you don't throw on that spot of the field with  gt; 15 seconds left in the half.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 02:19:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same here, but I'm gonna have to disagree with you, ***GO ARGOS!!!***</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 02:34:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>This will be the second CFL game I watch. The Argos/Lions game is a ton of fun, especially in the offseason of football down here in the states.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 03:14:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn Burnham is burning us</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 04:09:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could see him going to the TWolves tbh with Rubio gone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 05:30:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be fair just because Teague wants to go there doesn't necessarily mean the TWolves want him. Edit: ^^^nvm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 06:45:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a Pats and Lions fan in the NFL, but I decided with the Argonauts because of proximity to where I live and there name is pretty fucking cool tbh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 06:52:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The fucking shanked kick, I wanted Sas to win, kinda disappointed. But disappointment went away when I realized that I watch an absolutely fun game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 16:08:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gotta be honest never really liked Winnipeg sports, and I've committed to the Argos</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 19:27:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Post it anyways like you did for that sweet sweet karma</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 19:29:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>As much I don't like Immortals, their stickers bout to be dope</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 04:43:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Three years after the 2003 season we kinda went to the World Series, so I mean..... ^^^jk ^^^fucking ^^^fade ^^^me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 06:35:59</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8226;Expand and put at least one more team in the league, Quebec City for the East.  #8226;Change overtime rules to keep going until there's a winner.  #8226;Cut down on shit coaches can challenge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 17:38:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>While I guess I see why the Bombers are ahead of the Argos, I also disagree. A win against the worst team in the league shouldn't put them ahead of a team that lost to a team in the top half. So that's my reason, oh, and lots of personal bias too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 22:50:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly! BO7 playoffs, and BO9 grand finals (+Dust2 +Season), Jesus Christ I'm tired of short matches...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 02:14:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>As well as either mouz or NiP which is *extremely* surprising considering we got teams like FaZe and SK.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 03:01:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very true, still kinda shocked that these teams won against teams like Na'Vi (although there not exactly a top tier team anymore), G2, North, SK, and Immortals. It is a lot of fun to see big time upsets on a stage like this, right before the major where we're most likely gonna see the top teams come out where they belong (on top).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is it possible if we could get bandwagon flairs for the upcoming major?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 20:19:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I asked last time but it was way too late, but it'd be cool for an option of a flair for a team we're bandwagoning to (because being a Liquid fan, I gotta cheer for someone). I know all the major sports subs do it in a few different styles; the logo in a wagon (/r/NBA, /r/Hockey, /r/Baseball), a golden version of the logo (/r/NHL), and a moving gif style in /r/CFB (no I don't expect this because that's a lot of work for 16 teams). Just a thought</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 22:11:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly! People love comeback stories, especially Kim Kardashian's.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-06 18:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Signed up and selected Cleveland as my NTC</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-06 22:02:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>3 NORTH AMERICAN TEAMS ON THE STAGE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 19:20:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>2/5 of their rounds on train were pistols</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 19:34:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry, did you forget what the east looks like?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 19:36:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep, on CT side they got buried by an eco, and on T side they won the round after but FaZe got the bomb down. Getting the bomb down got them the cash to have a legitimate buy, whereas Liquid kept their scout and UMP. The worse guns combined with some idiotic pushing lost us the third round.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 01:02:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure if you're agreeing with me or not but I'll play devil's advocate with your comment. From last season to this one three playoff teams have lost there stars (Jimmy Butler/CHI, PG-13/IND, and the Hawks lost a lot). So that's three less teams that are in the playoffs from last year especially since both the Hawks and Bulls appear to be entering a rebuild (who knows what the fuck the Pacers are doing). Granted you could argue that both the Hornets and Heat buffed up a little bit, you could also say the Pistons are looking better off with adding Bradley and Reggie Jackson could be getting healthier. TL;DR East playoff fringe teams lost talent whereas the Pistons got a little stronger</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>*Puts the first vegetable on</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 03:28:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Actually could I add egg and get it toasted?" *Hands the receipt over "Wait actually I have a coupon"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 02:57:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Incredible how dogs can turn their neck, almost as incredible how OP turns a repost into tons of karma</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>CS:GO Organizations with trophies from 250k+ LAN events</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 19:56:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 19:57:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some interesting things I found out when putting this together; -The Astralis core didn't win a single 250k+ tournament when they were with Dignitas and TSM. In fact the current North core (which has always been seen as the second best team from Denmark) won a premier tournament before the Astralis core did. -Fnatic has far and away the best track record among organizations, although if you combined SK's wins under their current and former orgs then they would be closing in on Fnatic's 7. -The former kings of second place only went above and beyond that nickname once in a premier tournament, but Na'Vi have only reached 3rd/4th since.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 20:04:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought about adding the names and tried it on Fnatic, but it got a little messy and over the top. I wanted this to be a quick visual representation of what orgs have the most.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 20:41:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the first 3-4 majors, there weren't any pictures I could find. If I find any ill update it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 21:10:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>WESG</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 21:48:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Epicenter</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 22:43:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sydney was only 200k</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 00:11:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>They won the major, but I couldn't find a picture of the champion badge. Maybe I'm just shitty at finding things</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 00:42:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>In order; Fnatic, Virtus Pro, Ninjas in Pyjamas, SK Gaming, Astralis, EnVyUs, Luminosity, G2, LDLC, Na'Vi, Dignitas, Cloud9, OpTic, FaZe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 15:55:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Usually it stays at the team house, but if the players go to a new org it stays with the org that won the trophy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Go for a jog first</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 03:29:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something I finally figured out today. Before jumping on CS, make sure to do something active so you're fully alert so you can play your best. Not only does it help you out in game, it's also always great to get a little exercise when you can.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 08:18:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also here from /r/motorcitykitties, excited to cheer for the baby bombers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 04:37:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well fuck that catch was dirty</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 05:11:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've always seen the DBacks as my second team/NL team, this just absolutely reinforces me rooting for them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-20 02:22:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>100% agree, definitely a respectable guy. Anyone who has this happen to them is sad, despite party/opinion. Country over party, get better John</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 02:14:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unless we get another one of ESL's wildcard things, the Main and Premier games with them in it will probably be the most viewed of all time at that level.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 18:22:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>HellRaisers weren't at the major</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 18:17:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm getting Desolate Space vibes personally, but it is sick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 22:43:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>If this is JV's last game (which I doubt), it was a damn fun one to watch and I'm sure for the players to play in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 18:12:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>If we got locked into seasons in the US, I could definitely see teams from Europe and Asia moving over to be apart of the money flow. The game is played where the moneys at as we see in most professional sports.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 17:38:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>For even further off in the future talent, is wrath. The kid is like 16 or something and absolutely carried Enigma6 through everything. He just joined Hiko's team (Rogue) so now he'll get to spend time learning from a very experienced veteran and his name will be thrown out there more as Rogue will be a fairly big team in the NA region.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ESPN to profile former Pistons player Darko Milicic, 'the NBA's biggest bust'</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-01 21:35:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 05:24:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Toronto because who doesn't love cheering for the best team in the east that would be 5th best in the west! ^^^and ^^^we ^^^need ^^^more ^^^fans</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 06:08:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>WE MAY NEVER LOSE AGAIN ^^^also ^^^Shane ^^^Greene ^^^is ^^^dad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 17:08:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would venture to say the Roughriders but even that is damn close</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-06 00:25:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imo if mineplex wanted to help the competitive pvp scene they should do something that's based off standard pvp, and not just use their game mode that's essentially CS. I could be wrong but that's what I think</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Best MCSG server? Best Overcast type server?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-07 22:22:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I miss mcgamer so I've been trying to find a good mcsg server to play on, what do you guys play on? Also miss the heck out of overcast, any good overcast like clones (with ctf, destroy the wool, etc.)? Haven't been any able to find any of either so I'd appreciate help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 21:56:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>See I personally don't think it had to do with them not having the money. I think at first they were looking to grab ANGE1 and electronic, but then they found out Zeus had interest to return. And I'm sure that if Zeus wanted electronic instead of seized they would've done that. Again don't take that as fact, just my opinion Edit: apparently I was wrong for buyout money on Angel, HR wanted upwards of 200k and Na'Vi wasn't having any of that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 23:48:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh shiiiiit, how did I not know my savior had a sub?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 04:49:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn dude I feel for ya. Leave because you lost hope?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 20:42:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>UPVOTES FOR EVERYONE!! CHOO CHOO MOTHAFUKAS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tigers have sent Rondon to Toledo to make room for Fulmer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 05:23:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 05:22:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've always stuck with Liquid, through shuffle upon shuffle. But if this shuffle goes down I'll be cheering for the best team coming out of it. Call me a bandwagon, but I just want a good NA team that can stay that way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-16 00:29:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>EliGe would be going there to get experience with longer term vets, learn the game more, maybe win a couple ESL tournaments, and then eventually head out and join up with another top team as a better player. That would make the most sense for me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-17 16:53:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I chose to forget that era</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fell in love with it, what now?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 22:50:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kayaked today for the first time. Although I've done a lot of canoeing with friends and family, I never touched a kayak until today. I had an absolute blast and I now want to do more and more. What next?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 23:27:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the advice, I was definitely gonna buy used to start off. And after some research, a touring kayak would best suit my needs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 03:48:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Offensive Coordinator for the Lions, has helped out Stafford learn his role better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 03:49:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Offensive Coordinator for the Lions, has helped out Stafford learn his role better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 03:48:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I downvoted at first then I realized his username is a character from a tv show I used to watch. He's acting in character, I got baited</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 04:07:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn dude, that's fuckin brutal. At least you tried.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 18:04:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lions fan, but the love of the game can unite anyone. I got started young too and now there's nothing more exciting than the feeling of autumn and the great Saturday's and Sunday's that come with it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 03:42:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would assume it's a Lake where only people with a membership/lakeside house can access it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 19:21:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who would Liquid drop for NAF? The only realistic option is nitr0, but is NAF really better? And wouldn't NAF and stan clash from the whole OpTic drama, or they cool now? E: apparently NAF  gt; nitr0, haven't been able to keep up with CS so a little behind on players skills. But the personality conflict might prevent it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 01:36:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lake Michigan has been gorgeous this weekend; sunsets finally clear, and sunrises as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 16:31:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oceania region</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 04:17:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>First time I've been in a few years, forgot how great the atmosphere is. The crowds pumped up, as well as the players. I'm going to many more now. ^^Also ^^we ^^have ^^Lion ^^King ^^on ^^our ^^team</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 02:21:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/CFBStreams</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 05:27:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can think of 0 to give them attention. ^hmmmmm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-03 16:05:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah like that, I'm one that can accept it was a first down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Immersiveness in game</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 00:01:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know it's not likely we'll get another NCAA game in some time, but for the next edition we receive it'd be great if the game felt more immersive. What I mean is more traditions shown on camera (War Eagle, that type of thing). Another random immersive idea (not sure if fully possible), but if you pull off a major upset at home it'd be sweet to see the crowd rush the field. What would you add as far as aesthetics?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-05 00:22:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn, do you know which years that was in?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-08 21:45:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>OVERREACTION TIME; BRADY RETIRES, JIMMY STARTING QB, NEW BACKUP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 21:34:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>KState is an exciting team, I like when there good. Go Cats from a Michigan fan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 01:04:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aliens probably</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 01:13:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>In case this was not known, North Dakota State is a good football team.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 05:24:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>ugly win is still a win my guy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 05:25:11</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;WE ARE THE BEST FOOTBALL TEAM IN TEXAS ^^^except ^^^fort ^^^worth</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 21:29:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>isn't he redshirted? not sure we wanna break that when we have no idea if he'll be much better</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 23:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>not necessarily worse, but if he's not ready for the game there's no need to put him in. If Harbaugh thought that Mccaffery was better than Speight then mccaffery would be in the game. Only player I wanna see take some snaps now is Peters</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 01:14:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>SYRACUSE BEATS TEXAS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 01:15:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>no, please, no i forgot what its like to be scared of purdue</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 03:41:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hot take for the day... we don't make the playoffs. Any thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 05:21:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>God damn it! I was gonna go to this game before I got sick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 20:23:02</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Fuck Stanturd</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 03:47:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>damn, I love Lang. He just must not realize that now that he wears Blue and white he can't make contact with the d-line :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 03:49:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>PRATERS UP BOYS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 05:32:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is he gonna be on tommorow? iirc he was in NY for the game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 05:34:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did like Gruden's acknowledgment and respect for us in the first half. But yeah.. FTP and FOBJ</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-24 19:26:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>that was literally the most blatant holding ever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-24 20:17:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>THE PROPHET?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 21:20:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Were they good?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 01:39:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tuned in for a little of the SECN stream to hear how surprised they were EMU held Kentucky to such a low score. EMU has a LEGIT defense for a G5 team, always fun watching them play it tough. Now if they could get there offense rolling this would be a good team. Also feel the need to state that I absolutely love the turn of tides this program has faced the past two years, from crappy 2 or 3 win seasons and almost giving up on football, to beating a B1G team in there stadium and coming close to beating a SEC team on there turf.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[S2:E11] Even more foreshadowing on Buster losing his hand</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 03:03:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Searched and this doesn't pear to have been posted before but at 14 minutes and 45 seconds into the episode George Sr. and Michael are talking about Buster heading off to Iraq. Then George Sr. says "what if I never get a chance to reach out and touch that hand of his again?" I just thought it was pretty funny so I thought I'd share.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 05:57:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I had this prepped for no reason ig YOU LAUGHED AT THEM YOU CRIED WITH THEM YOU SCORED A SHIT TON OF POINTS ON THEM NOW YOU JUST GOT LONG CONNED BY THEM IM ON THE BIG DADDY KLIFF BANDWAGON</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 19:47:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>so basically... trade Ebron and JUMP ON THAT FELLS BANDWAGON</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 20:08:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>is there any other team that constantly gets fucked by injuries? or is it just us?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 20:57:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>GET RESERVED</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 21:04:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>WHY ARE WE NOT GETTING FLAGGED, IM NOT READY FOR THIS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 22:25:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>you guys get the shaft on this and we get some bs no-calls our way today? sorry for giving you the curse</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 22:38:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>~~FIRE~~ HIRE BUTCH JONES</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 22:40:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally I would throw Northern Illinois in the East, and Air Force in the West to make it a 14 team conference.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So now that the season is officially over, who's your postseason team to root for?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-02 00:29:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wanna see the DBacks play the Astros make the series, then go Astros to win it all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can LSU beat LSU?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 03:45:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-03 03:45:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think LSU might want Bama.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mango Grove - Sense of Identity</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 03:18:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-07 21:16:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it confirmed back? Or is it just a home and home?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-07 21:23:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Finally the little guys get a shot at the sought after Bad Boy Mowers Gasparilla Bowl! Happy for you guys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-07 21:27:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>**TEXAS**  gt; OKLAHOMA Serious thought; out of the 2nd, 3rd, and 4th ranked matchups today, this is the least suspected upset.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-07 21:46:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't let Oklahoma losing distract you from the fact that UVA is 4-1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-07 21:48:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>God this year is hard as an Eagle fan, all our losses have been 1 score.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Okay. Which one of you did this?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-07 21:50:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 01:08:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>in my opinion, Notre Dame is extremely underrated. I had them at 14 heading into this week, and there definitely just looking better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 01:19:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Big XIV with 12 teams? Checks out according to conference math.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 05:32:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean he was set up for failure, some bad decisions, but why on earth is Drevno playcalling pass plays in that weather??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 05:37:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>We need to start a blue blood suicide pact. Inviting all Sooners and Seminoles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 05:38:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any Cougs down to let me on the Ol' Crimson bandwagon?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-08 05:45:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope we cause as much chaos as possible for you guys</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>FUCK</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 01:41:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>This weekend is shitty as fuck; Michigan loses because we're god awful, the Lions just get slaughtered for 50 minutes, and now Aaron Rodgers pulls something out of ass yet again to save the Packers. Dude fuck ^^^^^thepack this weekend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-14 17:55:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just tuned in, who the fuck is this James guy?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Western Michigan/Akron game yesterday was postponed due to flooding over 5 inches</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 19:49:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 19:49:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Row the boat?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 03:18:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Plan A tonight was to go to opening night at the Yost, my dad had back problems so we didn't go. Plan B included me watching college football all night and planning on how to ask out my co-worker. Eventually I ended up in a long fought 2 and a half hour game of war with my little brother.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 03:40:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>hmmmm check yes or no would work wonders. if i send a text the ay needs a lot of y's. so were talking something; like ayyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyyy bbg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 21:22:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well Toledo is a good football team, makes me feel even better about Eastern's D.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 23:27:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus Bowling Green is hot garbage</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 23:41:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>FUCK, we've lost 5 games this year with a total of 20 points in separation in those 5 losses. We can hang with any team, we just need to close it out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 04:37:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Easy Carolina is a bad team. They nearly doubled BYU's score.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 04:39:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which is crazy to me, because most of my life BYU has been *at* *least* a halfway decent team.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 04:50:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hope the guy lived a good life, and no way to go out like watching football. Rest in peace</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 04:51:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cardiac arrest</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 04:55:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's definitely accountable, first we need to fire Drevno and bring some new life into the OC position. Seriously what the fuck was some of the play calling today? Dump pass on 3rd and 13? Then play action on 4th and 11 the play after? Who's actually gonna fall for PA on 4th and long?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 04:58:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>This game fucked the Pac-12 as a whole</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 04:59:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any legitimate reason to not give Peters a go next week? Against Rutgers, and it's not like theres any hope for anything else to happen this season (for even a shot at B1G we need Penn State and MSU to lose *twice*). Let's prepare for the future, this season is over.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 05:00:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pistons could potentially do well within the East, and the Wings are at least competitive so far? Silver lining my guy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 05:54:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>**TERRITORIAL** **CUP** **HYPE**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 03:53:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>We've looked pretty good so far, 3-1 with our only loss coming from a top 15ish team. Were giving ourselves so much more room on offense compared to last season. Were no world beaters but it is fair to say were pretty good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 04:54:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>okay what the fuck. these close losses are pretty damn ridiculous</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 04:56:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>you drop this "/s"? as bad as it is to lose 6 in a row by one score, you cant' exactly fire everyone when close games like this are more often than not determined by luck. I mean christ, this school was about to not have a football team before last season until Creighton and company saved it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 19:23:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agree but atm I'd say the Pats are more hated than the Packers in the NFL.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 19:25:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gusty call but the right one, we may be pretty good but I wouldn't trust our team to keep up for much longer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 19:29:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>MSU flair and Browns fan? How'd that happen?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 00:06:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>They only 10 guys on the field for that fourth down didn't they</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 02:02:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't understand how Penn State would drop out of top 5 with a one point loss in Columbus? In my personal opinion it would be; 1. Georgia 2. Alabama 3. Ohio State 4. Penn State 5. Notre Dame But what I think AP will do? 1. Alabama 2. Georgia 3. Ohio State 4. Notre Dame 5. Penn State Same gist, not that it matters considering there's still a lot of football to be played this year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 02:07:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't understand why people are downvoting on-topic opinions in an *opinion* *thread*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 02:15:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because I think Penn State is an overall better team but by a very thin margin, NC State and USC are great football teams I do think they are both overrated. But your QB definitely worries me, if Josh Adams gets shut down in a game (like in the game against Georgia where he averaged 2.8 ypc), your team seems like it may struggle a bit on offense. For me personally I rate on the field performance higher than resume. But this is all my opinion as a non-analyst that loves watching college football.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-30 16:10:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not quite the same but Eastern is 2-6 with only a negative 3 point differential.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-30 22:42:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes internet is still available to us, streaming was definitely a plan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Planning to come to Indianapolis for the Big Ten Championship game. What else should I see in town.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 13:41:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gonna be the first time in Indy, so I'd like to see a little of the town before the game. What are some must see spots in town? Great restaurants?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 03:11:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>As much as I respect them feeling the need to protest, and I definitely support their right to. Unfortunately in the college scene getting away with such things is not quite the same. The pressure to win is definitely not the same in professional sports, so if you have a shitty AD or coach they won't think twice about giving you the boot. And it's in a "league" where players don't hold the same influence, NFL/NBA/etc. players have huge fan bases backing them. Now I'm saying this without much knowledge of the Vanderbilt team, much less women's college basketball. This is just my thoughts on the kneeling protest in college sports in enteral.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 03:12:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same with State, although them losing is sort of a rare occurrence unfortunately for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 03:44:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Statistically yes. Visually yes. This TCU defense is legit, a shit ton of fun to watch too (from B1G country, meaning I love a good slugfest). I don't remember a TCU D this good since the Rose Bowl year (granted I don't watch much TCU). Offense needs big improvements though for this team to have a playoff shot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 03:49:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for that knowledge, those were the two years I sorta checked out of hardcore cfb frenzy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 16:44:07</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;in a bowl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 18:14:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I one hundred percent agree with you, the plot formula was very similar (like how The Force Awakens was similar to A New Hope).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 05:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would probably make a pretty quick gif.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 20:02:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>THEY WOULDNT HAVE IT ANY OTHER WAY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 21:27:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tennessee scored 42 on this GTech D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 00:47:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friend was on a visit (recruiting purposes) to Furman today, definitely wouldn't mind seeing him in purple and white.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Favorite custom conferences?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 19:57:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I recently made a set of conferences that I think are the best historically/regionally, and a lot of fun. *ACC* *(Orange Bowl Bid)*: Atlantic; Boston College, Clemson, Florida State, Louisville, Maryland, Wake Forest. Coastal; Duke, Miami, NC State, UNC, Virginia, VA Tech. *American* *(BCS Bowl Bid)*: Cincinnati, Connecticut, Marshall, Memphis, Pittsburgh, Rutgers, Syracuse, Temple, UCF, USF, West Virginia. *Big12* *(Fiesta Bowl Bid)*: North; Arkansas, Iowa State, Kansas, Kansas State, Missouri, Nebraska. South; Baylor, Oklahoma, Oklahoma State, Texas, Texas A amp;M, Texas Tech. *B1G* *(Rose Bowl Bid)*: East; Indiana, Michigan, Ohio State, Notre Dame, Ohio State, Penn State. West; Illinois, Iowa, Minnesota, Northwestern, Purdue, Wisconsin. *C-USA*: North; East Carolina, Georgia State, Middle Tennessee State, Old Dominion, UMass, Western Kentucky. South; FIU, FAU, South Alabama, Southern Miss, Troy, UAB. *Independents*: Air Force, Army, Navy. *MAC*: East; Akron, Bowling Green, Buffalo, Kent State, Miami University, Ohio. West; Ball State, Central Michigan, Eastern Michigan, Northern Illinois, Toledo, Western Michigan. *MWC* *(BCS Bowl Bid)*: North; BYU, Boise State, Colorado, Colorado State, Idaho, Utah, Utah State, Wyoming. South; Arizona, Arizona State, Houston, Nevada, New Mexico, New Mexico State, TCU, UNLV. *Pac-12* *(Rose Bowl Bid)*: North; Cal, Oregon, Oregon State, Stanford, Washington, Washington State. South; Fresno State, Hawai #8217;i, San Diego State, San Jose State, UCLA, USC. *SEC* *(Sugar Bowl Bid)*: East; Florida, Georgia, Georgia Tech, South Carolina, Tennessee, Kentucky. West; Alabama, Auburn, LSU, Mississippi State, Ole Miss, Vanderbilt. *Sun* *Belt*: East; Arkansas State, Louisiana Tech, Tulane, Tulsa, UL-Lafayette, UL-Monroe. West; North Texas, Rice, SMU, Texas State, UTEP, UTSA.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 22:53:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a Lions fan, I think he has more positives than negatives, but that wouldn't make him a good hire in my opinion. He does have a good effect on players, as it seems thy like him, he also is good at coaching guys up (Stafford has flourished with him). But his play calling can be incredibly frustrating with how stubborn he gets (see Redzone). If he can get that under control, then I could see him hit the big stage (although if that happens, I'd prefer him in Detroit).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 00:50:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm curious. What's with the crazy Independents?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Oh okay</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 04:15:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 13:39:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see you're looking at most of the imbalance as it normally would, but at this point in my dynasty Iowa and Wisconsin are ranked higher than any of the B1G East teams, as well as San Diego State being #8 and other PAC-12 South teams being strong. I also added GTech to the SEC *because* of how weak the East was looking, as well as historical ramifications. And as far as the two power "G5" conferences are, the American is more a conglomerate of what I was looking for (I always loved the 2000s Big East), as well as some other G5 teams that became strong in my dynasty. And the MWC is an actual regionally consistent conference, that is really balanced with talent, especially elite talent so I figured it should be considered a power. And with the "leftover" conferences, that's exactly what they are, conferences that are full of bottom feeding teams. I personally don't see anything wrong with this. For the ACC, how would you suggest those divisions would look with those teams in mind? In all honesty these are the conferences I've had the most fun with, so I'll probably stick with it for the most part.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 14:49:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>07 was always my favorite, although 06 gets more love on here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 21:17:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never knew about the Butch Jones to Michigan rumors. Jesus Christ we were saved from what could have been.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 23:33:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, don't ask me how because I'm not sure about that. But a good ole Google should do the trick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 03:02:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>2007 you say?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 14:41:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hell yeah I'd put GState as a 3rd flair if possible</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 16:36:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I personally just couldn't see Kiffin in Arkansas. Maybe it's just a personality clash, but I don't see that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 22:03:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Keep track and log your dynasty, that's what I do. I write out basic details of the season (W-L, final rank, BCS Bowl winners, etc.) as well as write out storylines of my team both on and off the field. The funny thing for me is that I don't even share them with anybody, I just have a document slowly building up full of my dynasty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 04:35:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not too mad it was us. Because we were the good team on the road</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 04:49:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eastern Michigan vs. Bowling Green 2006, froze my ass off but was in love with the game so I couldn't tell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 04:49:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Crazy fact for you, Dixon has two super bowl rings</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 04:51:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess with most games this season just being us losing a coin flip, I'm a little salty. But then looking back and realizing how Eastern is historically? I'm not too mad. I'm just a little happy we got to play spoiler, go Eagles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 15:14:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>If there blitzing as much as you say they are, then try to get off quick passes. There's gonna be some DBacks on your guys but there will be weak spots that have less coverage. Try to read the defense to see if their safeties are pushing up, if they are get off some deep balls. If they have their linebackers pressing but not their safeties? Then go for quick mid level passes, quick slants for example</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 16:20:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean I guess just focus on recruiting faster wideouts that have good CIT for those deep balls. Having just one solid vertical threat is a real game changer when facing teams that like the blitz.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 00:17:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 02:25:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>The limited playoff system is what makes the CFB regular season the best there is. It makes games mean more, where in the NFL you can drop 5 or 6 and still be alright.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 04:47:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>3 Takeaways: 1)USF in light green and yellow is something I never knew I wanted 2)USF is most definitely not as good as their record shows 3)Tulsa's backup QB is hot garbage</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 16:01:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice win, keeping track of defensive tendencies on teams is a good idea to try and find the one guy they aren't covering well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 06:27:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>For dynasty mode recruiting is completely remodeled. I personally prefer it because it's actually fun and a lot quicker. Learn it as soon as you can, because when I first struggled with it I did not pull in good croots. Check out the operationsports recruiting guide.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 17:45:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Glad to know I'm not the only one that thought that was really weird</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 19:37:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check out ABC for Virginia to avenge your loss from last week</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 18:39:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're not kidding; Texas (whose defense you put 50 some points up on), UCF, Wisconsin, Ohio State, and then the last three being a slate of Michigan, Michigan State, and Penn State. I think against nearly any other schedule this Maryland team is a 7 win team or at least bowl eligible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 19:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>School: Minnesota Coaching Position: HC Record: 0-1 Number of Seasons: First season at Minnesota, fourth on the dynasty Conference Championships: 0 National Championships:0 Previous School(s): HC at Georgia Tech, and DC at Alabama Custom Conferences: Yes but generally what they are irl Season Recap: I took over at Minnesota after dominating for 2 straight years as a Bama DC. Minnesota previously was 2-10 so it's gonna be a long road upwards. Most my team is young and can be coached up until we recruit some studs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 23:10:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>No it's cool their quarterback was injured so they don't count</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 23:12:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you mean? When it's rivalry time, it's time to throw out the records</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 15:57:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright what the fuck? I don't give a shit about anyone's political opinion here because this goes deeper than that. This is an issue about freedom that WE as a PEOPLE have, not something that should be taken away from us by people that clearly profit off voting to repeal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 22:09:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really can't stand this bullshit anymore</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 23:16:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey you're not the original guy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 02:55:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>This game and Bedlam were easily the two best of the year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 03:05:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Curious as to why Josh Allen hasn't payed in the last two games, anyone know?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 04:54:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think he's stellar whenever a big play happens, because he genuinely seems to be excited. But listening to a whole game by him? No thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 05:16:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't know about the QB himself, but Arizona Western is consistently a top 5 JUCO team. So I assume they have a good QB?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 18:18:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see where your coming from with Troy, but it's hard (for me at least) to rank them with that god awful loss to South Alabama.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 15:23:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only thing Wisconsin can do is win all it's games. Done. That in my mind measures up to deserving of a playoff birth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 15:31:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe he's regarding that the best win out of conference is Notre Dame (which has been exposed). The SEC isn't ass, but I think there is still some SEC bias leftovers from the BCS era.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 15:37:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>tOSU would also have 3 ranked wins, two of those would be top 10.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 15:39:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>You think a 3 loss Auburn makes the playoff? Are you kidding? Because that would be the ultimate joke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 17:40:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh I'm glad I got wooshed. There are some delusional SEC fans on here, you never know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 18:00:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no I agree. Hell there's delusional UofM fans, but here I was honking specifically SEC</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 18:05:01</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;John O'Korn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 22:06:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>SEC Best and SEC Least back at it again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 22:17:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haven't kept up with the scene over the last few months, why would they leave their own org?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 17:19:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>F</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 17:23:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>They struggled heavily through the regular season (as did the whole East conference), was honestly a real surprise they won.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 19:04:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>no way OU does anything in the playoff. their offense can't even outscore their defense?? smh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 20:39:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>is this the most boring MAC 'ship ever? god awful announcers, the game sucks, and those akron unis make me want to hurl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 01:36:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wisconsin #4 seed? Okay Gary. How's that SEC dick taste?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 01:41:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why stop at 2? #1 Georgia #2 Auburn #3 Alabama #4 LSU</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 01:42:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>He said you guys should jump Wisconsin. You guys are a part of the SEC.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 06:15:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>everyone on their schedule, more than anyone else can say</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 19:18:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be a huge hire for UCF, a consistently good SEC coach as a replacement for Frost would do a lot for that school and G5 in general.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 19:24:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a fun one. Not one I would've seen coming, nonetheless a fun one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 19:41:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last year both were pretty much blowouts. This year is gonna be the opposite. Alabama never gets "blown out," so that game is naturally gonna be close. Oklahoma vs. Georgia I just can't see being decided by more than an a score based off how well they've played.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 20:00:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Were there rumors he was leaving?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 20:11:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Miami ahead of UCF is the biggest bullshit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 20:12:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would've loved to see you guys match up with TCU.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 20:21:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Strange teams in a strange location. The geography on this one is wack</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 20:28:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Simulations showed the same 4</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 20:34:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>The de facto Rose Bowl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 20:37:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hot damn I would've preferred TCU v. ND, but this will do fine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 22:47:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>McMurphy has sources that are in the know. And the decisions are constantly changing as these games aren't usually final for a while. He reports what he's told via his sources.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 22:48:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>And getting Akron as well? If I'm the faU I wanna show what I can do against a P5 team.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 22:49:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bahamas bowl is the best MAC tie-in imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Finally Kansas gets the respeck they deserve</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 22:56:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 17:23:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>31 + 7 = 39?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 21:22:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basketball is honestly just turning into a drama shitshow. I mean Jesus there is a Ball family version of Keeping up with the Kardashians.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 00:08:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>To get into this boy's hole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 15:04:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>flair up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 15:30:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good, if you're afraid of competition you should get out. Just because you win the job one year, doesn't mean you should complacent and lazy. Glad that Peters is fine with the competition, I hope McCaffery is too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 15:36:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>So you're saying you wouldn't want him? Yeah you have Lewerke, but competition always pushes players to work harder to earn their spot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Al Avila defends signing of Derek Norris</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 23:49:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Al Avila defends signing of Derek Norris</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 23:49:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 00:48:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess you can't expect as much on here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 03:19:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not enough but the guys at our SBNation, BlessYouBoys, posted [this](https://www.blessyouboys.com/2017/12/6/16739268/detroit-tigers-derek-norris-suspension-domestic-violence). /u/Brown_boot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 03:44:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got wooshed there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 14:43:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd prefer to be locked against Minnesota, not necessarily because of parity but because their our rivals. The Little Brown Jug is my favorite trophy, I wish it was played for yearly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 19:35:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you go about sponsoring a bowl?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 13:19:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The American League (one of the conferences in MLB) has a Designated Hitter (DH) position, whereas the National League (also a conference) uses the pitcher as their ninth batter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 16:05:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Louis CK loved to joke about beating the meat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Been a Subway employee for over two years, AMA</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 18:04:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 18:21:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rotisserie sub with a few slices of roast beef. Ended up experimenting after getting bored with the generic subs and fell in love with this one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 18:35:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Toasted. Is there any other way?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 18:36:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>My store is usually really good at keeping all items fresh, BUT even at ours there is one thing I would recommend. The meatballs get kind of nasty fast, so I wouldn't recommend getting those at night when we're about to close.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 18:44:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>just ask. Because I have no understanding as to why we're supposed to only give you 6 or so, Subway corporate never was that smart. I personally give more than that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 19:44:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That must be the store you go to, because in mine 'staggering' (the term we use) is the way we're supposed to do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 20:25:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn't see much of this game unfortunately. But from what I did see, Simpson played out of his mind on both ends of the floor. Loving this kid</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 22:09:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's only a couple of different positions that we have; Manager, assistant manager, night manager, food safety manager, and sandwich artist. At the moment I am next in line to take over the night manager position, as I'm currently just an artist. The job itself is extremely easy and pays good if you're their long enough (at least at my store, other stores sound like nightmares). Both of which are helpful for me since I am a student. The benefits are as what would be expected out of a fast food joint, and vary from store to store.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 22:10:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most annoying subs are flatbread subs that people try to cram as full as possible with veggies and stuff. It just doesn't work and it starts to crumble at a certain point. Grossest? Easily the sandwich I made the other week. Black olives on rye bread with a line of mayo, no meat no cheese, nothing else. Looked nasty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 22:12:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Specials are definitely interesting. The sub of the day, which is what I believe you're mentioning, isn't really a deal we have going on anymore but we'll still do it at my store if you ask. So most deals and specials are driven as the coupons we send out every other month. Everyone at the store knows that the first couple weeks that coupons are out are the most busy. And other than regulars, most sales during that time are those that use the coupons.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 22:14:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Favorite is the chipotle southwest, it's a ranch with a tiny kick to it. Tastes good on nearly every sandwich. Least favorite is actually mayo, because after being at Subway for so long you realize the other sauces can do so much more for the sandwich. Whereas mayo is pretty much just a liquid fat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 22:37:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus Christ that's scary. No thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Post Game Thread] Mount Union defeats UW-Oshkosh, 43-40</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 22:43:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Box Score provided by ESPN](http://www.espn.com/college-football/game?gameId=401002968) **Mount Union** 43 - **UW-Oshkosh** 40 Team | 1 | 2 | 3 | 4 | T ----|-|-|-|-|-|- MTU | 7 | 3 | 20 | 13 | 43 WIS | 0 | 21 | 14 | 5 | 40 **Thoughts** What a game [Generator](http://reddit-cfb-postgame.herokuapp.com/) created by /u/swanpenguin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 22:44:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Death, taxes, and Mount Union in the D3 championship game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 23:27:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>On the BMT just get a little bit, maybe a line or two.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 00:12:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Two teams that love pounding the rock, that weather, and the tradition? This is college football at its finest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 00:13:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>On one hand I want a rematch in the final, on the other hand NDSU-SDSU would be so much fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 04:06:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>3 at a minimum</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 04:07:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That we always go through really fast, so we end up refilling at least every other hour. Probably one of the freshest items for us.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 04:08:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>so close but no cigar. 3 marijunas</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 04:09:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>At the beginning of November we started a Reuben thing (which comes with the recommended eye bread). We'll probably have it until the end of the December</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 04:37:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>3 marijuanas with one on the side please sir</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 04:47:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>No I understand a standard needs to be set, but the fact that they set it at 6 is what's ridiculous to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 07:57:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>When it's fresh (I'd suggest sometime after lunch rush) it's fantastic. Would definitely recommend adding a few slices of pepperoni, which would unfortunately cost more</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 10:22:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>We still have them. And from what I can tell, cookies are a in-store choice as well as chips and drinks. Because some stores have snickerdoodle, M amp;M, sugar, etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 16:44:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, or some variation of a greeting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 16:45:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chicken ^^^and ^^^other ^^^stuff</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 16:45:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, call them out on their bs. Probably just being lazy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 23:09:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The "toys" are absolute bs to save money. And as far as orders go, occasionally we get someone ordering some catering that doesn't come and pick it up. And this screws us because we aren't allowed to ask for their payment info ahead of time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 23:13:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>The rotisserie is definitely the most natural meat we have, better than chickens strips and basketball breast</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 14:53:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Club is popular, but I would say either the Turkey, Veggie, or Steak and Cheese is the most popular.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 14:54:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Quite a few people actually order a veggie without cheese, surprisingly. And the tuna is eh, I'm not big into seafood anyways so it's not my favorite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 00:42:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Our store doesn't have a tip jar so I can't answer this sorry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 00:42:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tuna is probably the most fresh thing as we constantly change it. This might only be my store because we sell a lot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why isn't there a Reddit writes Black Mirror?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 04:52:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like we could get some really crazy and fun ideas going</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 14:37:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not actually write out a whole episode. Check out /r/RedditWritesSeinfeld for what I mean.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 04:30:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just downloaded Cuphead, how is it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 04:46:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Flair bet a safe assumption?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 05:39:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>can confirm, cuphead is good. and hard. but good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 06:21:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do I get put on a list if I upvote this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 21:25:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well the fact that anyone even wanted him suspended over an *allegation* is ridiculous.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 22:54:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>The team that wins the MEAC championship goes to the Celebration Bowl against the winner of the SWAC iirc</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 22:55:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Finally. What the fuck was up with that no-call on the punt?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 22:59:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>No you're not overestimating it. Honestly I have no clue why they go to a meaningless bowl game when they could go to the playoffs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 00:53:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry the word "science" is banned from this comment section, if you would like I could offer an alternative?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 14:30:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Our region doesn't sell them so I can't honestly respond</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 14:31:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>the sauce gets thicker and and hard in some places</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 18:13:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>innocent until proven guilty doesn't hold much anymore these days does it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 18:14:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>so let's just automatically assume it's true, right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 14:38:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just accusations that Politico released on [Sunday](https://www.politico.com/interactives/2017/obama-hezbollah-drug-trafficking-investigation/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 14:39:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>too often</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 15:02:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus this kinda sad. The mentality in this thread is just straight to the pitchforks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 15:12:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nearly all media sources are using this clickbait BS. This article is very bad, just reading the headline would lead you to some really bad conclusions, hell I admit that before reading I assumed the worst. The article itself is NOTHING like you would think from the comments here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 17:32:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think many kids these days understand the word commitment, whether German or American. Not that it's worse than schools pulling offers out from under players</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 17:36:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>he is a 4*, but since Rivals is lazy and didn't scout him they gave him the automatic 3*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 18:27:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Syracuse Detroit Tigers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 05:34:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>AAC is POW6R? Hahahahaha so they thought. C-USA is the real P6</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 05:38:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I'm gonna need to call /u/NCAAInvestigations in on this one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 17:28:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely wanna experience a white out at Penn State</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've been thinking of buying the sequel</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 23:38:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Note I have not played the first. I'm really stingy with money so I don't buy games often. But as a huge fan of Hearthstone, and a fan of Skyrim, this game seems to fall right in between the two? I've been watching reviews and the game seems like a lot of fun, what would you guys say? Is it worth the purchase?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Finally read a book from start to finish.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 04:13:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've always been a big reader, but as I've gotten busier in the past couple years I've been reluctant to get back into it. The book I read was "I Am Legend" and I was absolutely drawn in, finishing the book from cover to cover in a day. It made me question things about how two sides of opposing forces can both be in the right, and ponder true loneliness. I loved it and can't wait to get reading again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My new watch having the wrong Roman numeral for 4</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 04:32:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 05:24:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>any recommendations as to what i pick up next?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 05:26:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>While the movie was a good sci-fi horror, it was nothing like what the book was. Both are good, but the movie tried to use the book's title for automatic success. The book itself is about so much more than a hollywood thriller type story. ^^^happy ^^^cake ^^^day ^^^btw</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 05:28:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post has become a TIL for me ty</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 06:16:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely heavy, love seeing a lot of plot unfold right before my eyes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Sign Of Friendship In The Midst Of War I THE CHRISTMAS TRUCE 1914</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 18:26:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 04:59:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mid Tennessee/Arkansas State was fun but that's about it..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 18:45:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Underage gambling happened a lot on that site, so I assume that would be it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 18:50:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know, that site made me so much more excited to watch matches I didn't necessarily have any stake in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 21:43:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>No one beats FCS like they do! You hear me? NO ONE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 22:08:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck I wanted us to be the only ones</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 23:05:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who said I'm making fun of ya'll? I wish we could beat FCS teams.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 19:02:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>ESPN FUCK YOUR COMMERCIALS. But it'll probably be worse during the playoffs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 21:20:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>O'Korn was in for one play?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 22:31:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/nocontext ^^^seriously ^^^what ^^^is ^^^the ^^^context?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 21:00:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dak as in Dak Prescott? The QB that played at Mississippi State not South Carolina.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dark Brotherhood Questline</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 06:36:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is my first playthrough of the game and I was roughly 40 hours in when I started the Dark Brotherhood storyline. And now 8 hours later (granted there was of course distractions like selling my crap or fighting random dragons), I have reached the point where we started a new life in Dawnstar. And I have to say... the Dark Brotherhood story is one of the most enjoyable and immersive ones that I have started. I've gotten distracted into other things for the Thieves Guild, Companions, and all the other ones I started. But for some reason the DB was constantly keeping strung in, and for one of the first times in the game I felt emotionally attached to the characters. I'm not sure what the common opinion on here is but I loved it. What storylines reeled you guys in?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 16:42:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you implying Sun Belt = AAC? Not that I'm saying the SOS in either is incredible, but the two conferences are definitely not equal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Change the front of any USD from presidents to Pok #233;mon. Put the more rare Pok #233;mon on higher value bills and coins. Distribute the money accordingly to type of Pok #233;mon and region (water type found in Miami, grass type found in Wyoming, and so forth). Watch the ensuing rage.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 02:03:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 22:03:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>give the UK version a try once you're done with the American version, I preferred it actually.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 19:33:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>holy shit, been a fan for 8 years and it never clicked inside of me that the two D's were different. Maybe I never payed enough attention? Maybe I just lack a few brain cells? I guess something always seemed off but this weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Haven't had the opportunity to follow much this season, can anyone give me a quick TL;DW</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 18:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>What storylines are dominating the media heading into the trade deadline? Who are the favorites to win each conference? Any info would be cool?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 06:22:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>The owners I work for are pretty great, helpful as well as keeping everything in well stock. But I have heard horror stories of other stores. All in all the major problem is that Subway Corporate has franchises out wayyyyy too many franchises which causes just about any ole cheap Joe Schmuck to do a bad job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 17:19:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>If they only add four slices of ham it would only be $1.50 I believe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 02:09:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean yeah, I wouldn't wanna go back to Ohio either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-31 04:37:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's exactly what will happen. See "grab her by the pussy" defenders by supporters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 04:52:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Money matters. And it would seem Heroic has more green than Sprout.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[TOMT] [Movie] Movie where a kid is at an airport and sees his future self in a chase. I remember a suitcase being prevalent.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 01:09:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 01:51:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Solved. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 16:52:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is very exciting, the Great Lakes have vast importance to our state' cultural history as well as modern economics. I'd love to see this put up as a way to help educate those who want to learn more about the Mitten state.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 06:06:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>My school is currently selling a few Nestle products in the cafeteria, and for a while I've been wanting to write a complaint or something. But I have no idea where to start.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 14:40:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've always wanted to go on a trip to England, this may be my reason</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 19:22:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I figured, that's why I'm gonna make a big trip out of it. I intend to visit some of the national parks, and other places. Any recommendations of what I should check out?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 21:12:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dickerson's voice on the radio means warm weather is coming.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Need help planning my summer trip.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 00:45:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>This might be my last year in this great state before I move. And I feel as I haven't experienced as much as I should have, as most of my life has been in the metro Detroit area. So this summer (which feels so much further away today) I wanna go on a self guided tour visiting and seeing places that I've both already seen and haven't seen. I'm hoping to do things based on the outdoors, hiking and kayaking, but honestly anything cool would be fun. If you have any recommendations, let me know please. The agenda so far pertains:  #8226;Go up the west coast of the lower peninsula, check out Grand Rapids, Holland, Ludington, Leland, Traverse City, and Petoskey  #8226;Go to Mackinac Island and bike it  #8226;Camp around Drummond Island  #8226;Visit/hike Tahquamenon (can't ever spell this)  #8226;Check out Lafayette and Kitch-iti-kipi  #8226;Drive north to Munising and kayak the Pictured Rocks as well as complete some hikes in the area  #8226;Visit the Marquette area, hike Sugarloaf, jump off the cliffs at Presque Isle  #8226;Hike around Keweenaw Peninsula  #8226;Hike the Porcupine Mountains I would love to visit and backpack Isle Royale, but the logistics just don't work out. I'd definitely plan on coming back to Michigan one day in the future solely for Isle Royale.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 01:34:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've heard great things about the sculpture garden, I wanna check that out so thanks for reminding me. And that little waterfall looks incredible, I'll have to check it out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 01:53:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen both forts, they're really cool. I just wanna bike Mackinac because it's seen as a "classic" Michigan activity, and I've never done it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 03:03:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Roughly 3-4 weeks. There's a lot to do, but I'm not gonna hit every trail at every place, just the views and places I really wanna go to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 23:32:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks a lot, there are some great spots that I'll have to check out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 16:10:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly it all depends on the owner. From the sound of it, your store had awful management. My store is fantastic and is probably the easiest job I've ever had, good fellow employees as well as a good manager if anything goes south. If it was that bad where you worked, you could probably complain to corporate about the owners, as Subway is trying to cut down on how many franchises there are so they definitely would look into it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Here's to an incredible weekend hiking at Bruce Peninsula National Park</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 21:09:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 15:18:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also from SE Michigan, would love to know when you plan on doing this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 22:41:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I definitely remember being very confused at this one, I just kinda accepted it and moved on</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 00:48:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can we get this stickied?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 04:46:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>hey man, ramble on. When I went through the harder years of my life, the only thing that kept me going is rambling. You have thoughts in your head going one hundred miles per hour, let that shit out somewhere. PM me if you need to</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 04:50:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where you going on spring break? If you feel like you'll be okay for that long, then you should go and use it as a way to feel yourself out. I've never gotten better by sitting at home and thinking, going out and doing something you haven't done before is the best way to better understand yourself. If you don't think you'll be okay, then go get help as soon as you can, your life is worth way more than a couple thousand dollars.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 04:51:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you want most in life? What's something that interests you like nothing else, your passion?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 04:56:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've never had a close-knit circle of friends, and honestly I don't believe you need that. You don't need others to make you happy, finding myself is what got me through my tough years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 05:43:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>The best thing about this is that at the end only one team will own it all. Land is really the sole purpose of the tournament right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 11:23:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then maybe you should start trying things out. There's a lot of activities out there, it's kinda crazy with the broad variety of things you can do. Take a hike, ride a bike, hell go curling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Isle Royale likely to get 20-30 wolves over a 3-year span</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 14:50:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Isle Royale likely to get 20-30 wolves over a 3-year span</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 15:04:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 15:04:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I really like this plan, and was definitely worried that it wasn't go through after initial coverage</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 15:28:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>At the moment there are only *two* wolves that are confirmed alive. And the problem is moose populations booming way too high, which could cripple the entire ecosystem. Edit: correction thanks to /u/phantomofthelawlpera</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 16:58:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure where you came up with that? The last documented fatal attack on a human was in 2010. E: in North America that is</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 18:01:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do so many things "that don't excite me," but are a healthy way to keep myself occupied. For some reason it's a common belief that you have to have a life filled with excitement all the time, sometimes sitting back on a bench in a park, without distraction, and just thinking does more for me than anything else</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 01:14:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate the correction. I should've confirmed it, but I guess I got a little lazy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 01:18:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's the documentary titled? Seems interesting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 02:49:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks man, appreciated</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 02:51:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed on the overpay, but as it doesn't seem like a big signing is super likely we might as well guarantee something with that extra cap space.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 02:52:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>that was... hot?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 03:06:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude I was almost there, you had to say that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 03:12:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anddddd you redeemed yourself, thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 04:26:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>who do you have? UK, UofM, and who else?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 04:45:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shit I totally forgot about Gonzaga haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 16:17:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like /u/ormagon_89 said backpacking is the idea of living out of your backpack but there are two different categories to it. The first is wilderness backpacking, and as it seems it's more popular in the US but that's not to say limited here. That's the kind where you see people camping, and that sort of thing. The second is more of a travel from city to city kind of thing, this one covers just about everything. I'm not sure if there's a specific name for it but it's living on the road with nothing but a backpack to your name. Very similar to a /r/shoestring style.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 19:05:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>That and the mouse commercial. Why are you using a mouse to advertise? Yeah it's cute, but it doesn't put me in a hungry mood.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 21:50:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure if you're saying it's too much, but my comment will be in response to that. Right now the head coach of Eastern has made them nationally relevant for the first time in a LONG time. Like it or not football is THE sport, it brings in the most money through new students and boosters. Football money is the most important out there as it will funnel into other sports. So I 100% believe it is justified to allocate that much to a head coach (which in of itself isn't that much compared to other schools).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Favorite picture from an amazing weekend winter camping at Bruce Peninsula National Park</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 01:06:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 16:15:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've only been to the Mogollon Rim once in my life, and I'd definitely say it's worth going. It doesn't even feel like Arizona in some parts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 05:30:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Today was about as good as it gets for a Michigan fan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 19:34:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm in love with Jenna Fischer but I hate to say it. This picture scares me. Reminiscent of a Nick Park film character.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 08:40:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>He said subway you silly goose</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 16:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Swedish moms or Latina moms?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How much would I sell a barely used PS4 for?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 21:47:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've had my PS4 for roughly a year now and I'm looking to sell. It's been barely used with around 50 hours clocked in. What would the going price be? And where would I sell it? I was thinking of Craigslist</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 21:51:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, I figured around that range but I wasn't sure. Through Craigslist, or is there a better marketplace?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 22:02:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice try but I'm not biting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 22:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Huh I though it was bait. I've never had a good experience selling to Gamestop so I'll see.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 03:29:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think we suck?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is this?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 04:33:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 03:33:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah fuck you mate. Cheering for those Honkeyes. Go Blue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 17:50:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is dating confusing as fuck for anyone else?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 17:55:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh and what might those be?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 18:04:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn those are some tough rules</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 18:38:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's fun, I just don't know what I want</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's you're favorite view in all of Michigan?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 15:00:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>From city, to sunset, to forest views, what's your all time favorite Michigan view?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 15:33:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can I brag here? Because I need to brag somewhere, real bad. Saturday night I just went for it and kissed the girl I'm seeing. I need to brag because I've never had confidence in anything with myself but I just mentally said fuck it and did it. It's nothing that big to be honest, but it was for me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 15:45:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>No not yet, not sure I have the balls to make a move like that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 16:29:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why wait?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 01:10:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the fuck are you talking about? His son's name is clearly Lions. It's the only capitalized word in the title. Learn Englesh asshat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>As a non-disc golfer I have a question regarding course courtesy.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 03:12:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been walking my dog on a certain stretch of trails and paths at a local park for a few years now. I headed out today to go walk it and apparently they had recently put in a course over fall/winter/early spring. So that brings me to my question. I avoided walking there today because I didn't want to be a dick for walking on it. Should I find a new place to walk my dog, or would the golfers there mind if I walked my dog?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nearly half of Michiganders live in unacceptable smog levels</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 15:34:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 14:48:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which episode would you say that one is? This is coming from someone who has only seen the first season (I am excited to start season 2 today though)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 00:05:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>18, senior in high school. Looking to go to trade school after I graduate to become an electrician. I love the outdoors (hiking, kayaking), watching movies and TV shows, and reading. I'm currently a sandwich artist, at subway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 15:59:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>It all depends on how fresh the meatballs are. The earlier in the day you go, the better it will be</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pistons owner Tom Gores tied to alleged inmate phone call scheme</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 18:05:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 00:35:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>^^^The ^^^pathetic ^^^part ^^^was ^^^clearly ^^^a ^^^joke</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Michigan is incredible</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 23:54:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve lived in Metro Detroit my whole life, it #8217;s a nice area but it #8217;s not even close to what the whole of Michigan is like. After work Thursday last week (I got out at 10pm) I was contemplating what to do with the rest of the night. Out of nowhere I impulsively decided to pack all of my backpacking gear and just drive. I ended up driving to Ludington and getting there at about 2am. I was gonna find a random spot in the Manistee National forest near the lake to camp for the night. After not finding anywhere due to large puddles blocking off backroads (big enough to prevent me risking to drive my little sedan through) I decided to crash for a couple hours at a Walmart parking lot. Once I woke up I hiked around Ludington state park for a bit. I then headed off to drive the absolutely gorgeous M-22, hitting Sleeping Bear dunes and Leland along the way. I then made my way down to Traverse City and bikes around for an hour, while checking out the beach and various shops. It was the craziest 24 hours of my life but also the most incredible. It #8217;s insane how much Michigan has to offer so close to nearly everyone, and I didn #8217;t even scratch the surface. If anyone wants pictures I can post those. Edit: [Pictures](https://imgur.com/gallery/aPtd6xE)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 01:18:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Posted some in the OP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 02:34:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who said you had to grow up? I #8217;m 18, you just need the will to do things and you can do them (cliche as all get out I know). And I really like the Chevy idea, even if nothing comes of it I wanna write to them. The Cruze is probably one of the best cars I #8217;ll ever own, a total workhorse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 05:51:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I plan on both of them, just didn #8217;t have the time on this impulse trip. I will definitely make time to explore them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 15:05:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m assuming you mean The Cove in Leland. Great food with a great view</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 15:08:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely recommend checking out the Lost Lake trail at the state park</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 17:14:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>How close are you looking for? There #8217;s plenty of national forest and state parks both north and west.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Trying to start a podcast based on the fast food industry</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 23:19:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to create a podcast where I talk to various fast food industry employees and discuss what life is like at each store and different aspects of each store. Thoughts on this? Would you listen to something like that? And if so, what stores would be interesting?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 03:42:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sony tells Epic that they have to lock out accounts used on other consoles or else they will take the game off of the Playstation store. Epic decides they don't want to lose a decent portion of their playerbase so they agree. This lock out is to be blamed on Sony.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 04:02:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Epic doesn #8217;t make money from me buying a PlayStation, Sony does. If Epic wanted to make people buy consoles, they would lock out crossplay all together.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 04:12:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then why don #8217;t they lock out switching accounts from console to console on ALL consoles? Why just do PS4?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 08:36:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was terrified of spiders just a few weeks ago, but somehow I got into a rabbit hole of watching YouTube videos of critter keepers (like  #8220;The Dark Den #8221;). All in all I love spiders now, they #8217;re incredible little creatures</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 04:02:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trump didn't win the majority vote, he won through the electoral college.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 04:36:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>If he doesn #8217;t earn the majority vote, that means he gets the.... that #8217;s right, you guessed it! *Minority*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 05:02:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>mi #183;nor #183;i #183;ty m #601; #712;n #244;r #601;d #275; noun 1. the smaller number or part, especially a number that is less than half the whole number.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 08:25:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/travelpartners is a good sub for this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 08:27:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bear Mountain is a gorgeous hike too, I #8217;m still upset I couldn #8217;t finish it last year due to an ankle injury</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 03:48:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>was with you until the injury shit came up, don't wish that upon someone no matter how much you dislike them. grow up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 22:17:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>i love this sub</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 16:23:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Getting downvotes for admitting you were wrong? Huh?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 21:01:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>My biggest pet peeve is  #8220;I don #8217;t know. #8221; Like I #8217;m supposed to know what you want, I #8217;m not you man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 00:11:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy fuck that #8217;s gonna be 5 years since 14 #8217;. Time goes by fast</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How can you insult me in a way only people that share your hobby will understand?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 01:21:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 23:39:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>The back of the Texas flag is still the Texas flag, which may remind you that nothing has changed and Texas is indeed still not back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 01:39:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>If every sub here gave at least $1 we could do it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Will college football ever lose its luster to you? If so, when?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 22:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>When do you think college football will start to become dull to you as a viewer/obsesser? I personally don #8217;t think it will to me. The sport is set up in a way that actual happenings take up only 4 months out of the year. By time I start getting burnt out of watching so much, the season is over and I get to take a break before getting excited for the next season.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 23:20:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hell yeah, I don #8217;t have any kids. Does that mean it will always be fun?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 01:06:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely agree on the kickoffs. I #8217;m okay with seeing them go in pro football, because generally nothing happens anyways whereas in college football there #8217;s always that possibility.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 02:51:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was fucking beautiful to read</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Unexpected giveaway winner</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 05:46:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 23:38:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has anyone ever been to a football game while high? What was it like if yes?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My mic arm seems to be a great spot for my Juul</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 22:17:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 19:36:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>And that anonymous coach? Lane *motherfucking* Kiffin (he will fuck your mom, watch out).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Show the snap recipient how many snaps were taken before one was finally sent.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 20:41:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 05:12:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well. Half the team tried, the other half is the defense. To be fair though CSU #8217;s offense has been fast, meaning the defense has been out more and is probably gassed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 22:35:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for your sugar?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 17:18:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>i agree, maybe michigan, minnesota, or wisconsin? possibly one of the great lakes because of how far the water goes out in the distance (as far as i can tell)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The skies in South Haven from a couple days ago</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 17:25:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why I Love Drugs.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 21:13:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know why I love drugs? Because everyday I #8217;m one of two things; high or trying to get high. Using everything you got the night before and now you need more stuff to get blasted. So in response you spend the whole next day trying to get high. That right there is the best part of drugs. Now you may ask why that is, why it is I #8217;m wasting my whole day desperate to get stoned? That #8217;s valid response too, but for me it #8217;s more than trying to get high, it #8217;s everything that comes along with it. You go on mini adventures every few days where you #8217;ll meet interesting characters, do crazy ass shit to escape from situations, all while cruising around with your buds on a nice summer day with your windows down with the radio bumpin. Then after we complete our quest after slaying scamming dealers, rescuing friends from situations, and acquiring our loot which also happened to be a bomb ass strain called Diablo (in the bag)*. And as we sit there with a movie on in the background, we recollect the memories of the day and create plans of future purchases. Fuck I love drugs, they #8217;ve changed me into a person who feels like he finally fits into a community. *inside joke from one of my adventures</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 21:22:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Appreciate the thoughtfulness, I take my precautions as much as possible. Thanks for looking out man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 04:06:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn #8217;t get to watch this game due to being in East Lansing (5 min left in 4Q, let #8217;s see how that goes). But a score like this can #8217;t be a bad one, here #8217;s hoping Eastern can perform this year and maybe go bowling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 04:09:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>What #8217;s the read on this game? Good look for Cuse or bad look for Western?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 21:31:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>No you can say fuck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tinder but FaceTime where you have to say yes or no to their face</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:36:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:30:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bill Murray, he kept coming back in Groundhog #8217;s Day</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>