<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject9014</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 19:49:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi :) I #8217;m in the same position as you! I live in Portsmouth and have suffered with depression and chronic pain, which from researching ayahuasca may help with. I #8217;m struggling to know which retreats are reputable so would love some help! However, I #8217;m not sure I can afford South America, so am hoping to find a good one somewhere in Europe  #128515;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wondering if anyone who has Fibromyalgia/chronic pain has experienced ayahuasca??  #128515;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 20:50:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi, I #8217;ve recently been researching into ayahuasca and am considering going to a retreat to take part in ayahuasca ceremonies. I have fibromyalgia (apparently, but that #8217;s a whole  #8216;nother story  #128584;) which in turn has made my depression horrendous. I #8217;ve read that it can help depression and fibromyalgia but I #8217;d love to hear directly from people with chronic pain/depression, their stories if you wouldn #8217;t mind sharing? Did it help? How many ceremonies did it take to help? What was your experience like? Thanks in advance for anyone who takes the time to speak to me.  #10084; #65039; #10084; #65039; #10084; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Has anyone tried ayahuasca plant medicine to try to treat/manage their fibro symptoms? If so, please take a few minutes to read my post  #10084; #65039;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 21:06:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi, I #8217;ve recently been researching into ayahuasca plant medicine and am considering going to a retreat to take part in ayahuasca ceremonies. I #8217;m at my wits end with this illness and it #8217;s making me more depressed as the months drag on. Apparently, ayahuasca is quite an intense experience so I don #8217;t want to jump in blind. I #8217;ve read that it can help depression and fibromyalgia but I #8217;d love to hear directly from people with chronic pain/depression who have tried ayahuasca, their stories if you wouldn #8217;t mind sharing? Did it help? How many ceremonies did it take to help? What was your experience like? Thanks in advance for anyone who takes the time to speak to me.  #10084; #65039; #10084; #65039; #10084; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 19:25:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for that! Really appreciated... don #8217;t worry this isn #8217;t something I #8217;m jumping into. I #8217;m probably not even going to book something until next year most likely if I #8217;m certain it #8217;s something I want to do. I did LSD twice when I was younger. I guess I #8217;m unsure about my mental state atm so perhaps I will work on that before looking further into ayahuasca. I would always be very picky about any retreat I might choose and make sure I feel confident In the shaman and I would never mix medicine/drugs. And sorry I #8217;m new to reddit so what do you mean when you say SWIM??? Anyway thank you for your advice  #128525;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 19:27:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, I will make sure it #8217;s the right time and place if I do decide to go ahead with it. Okay thanks, I have never heard of ibogaine so will look into it.  #128525;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 11:59:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>ALL THE TIME.... all the time my friend  #128553; #128553;. Also when I #8217;m having a particularly good couple days I immediately start thinking  #8216;oh maybe this is it.... maybe it #8217;s almost over and things are finally getting better #8217;. Then two days later I #8217;m crying in bed because I can #8217;t find the energy to pick the tv remote off the floor!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anyone know what this might be? It says ching dynasty 1644 A.D?? Looked online and can #8217;t find anything</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 17:55:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can anyone tell me the meaning of this coin or better yet a translation of the text please?? It says ching dynasty 1644 on the box.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 18:03:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anyone else feel anti depressants do nothing other than make you emotionally numb</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 23:41:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like seriously when I #8217;m on my meds (I #8217;ve tried loads, most recently mertazipine) I look at my husband and kids and I #8217;m like meh do I even like you? I certainly can #8217;t feel love (giving or receiving) for sure and I can barely laugh or find things funny. When I #8217;m off my meds sure I #8217;m way more emotional.... I cry ALOT more but I can feel love. I feel happy. I look at my husband and kids and think wow I #8217;m so lucky. I think I #8217;m gonna stay off meds for a while because although I may be less stable, how can I possibly go through life feeling literally nothing towards anything or anyone?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 09:38:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://abnb.me/Qka8QB83HN We stayed in this place a few weeks ago and it was beautiful. Most amazing view of a cathedral however it #8217;s basically a greenhouse on top of a building so was INCREDIBLY hot. Not sure if it #8217;s specified as smoking friendly but there is a wrap around balcony which we smoked out on. However I warn you now we swear we heard satanic screaming coming from the cathedral.... I had smoked a few by then though  #128514; #128514; I convinced myself the place was haunted when I was high but other than that it was perfect!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 09:43:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven #8217;t tried either of those and tbh I #8217;ve always kind of suspected I might be bipolar but didn #8217;t really want to tell my doctor this as they don #8217;t like when you  #8216;self diagnose #8217; and shrug you off. Might be something to look into though. Thank you  #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 22:20:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll come back and message on this post everyday if needed so I would sure notice if you stopped responding. Please don #8217;t kill yourself. You #8217;ve survived 100% of your days so far even during those times you thought you wouldn #8217;t . Find something you love to do and ease into it. Happy to talk things through with you if you want to work it out xx</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 22:50:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most relatable post I #8217;ve seen so far</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 22:10:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>She sounds like a dick and this is coming from a female (25). No one should have to be second choice or even unsure if they #8217;re first choice in a relationship. She hasn #8217;t treated you right from day 1. I #8217;m always skeptical as I know this is you #8217;re view of the situation and you could be a complete dick but if what you #8217;ve written is true then you deserve better. There will be a girl out there who will want you and only you. I felt like every one of my boyfriends were my  #8220;best friend #8221; only to be let down and screwed over.... until I found my husband who made it clear I was the only woman in his life. At the end of the day you #8217;ve got to think can I see a myself living and being in this girls life forever or am I just scared of being alone or what the future without them may be like....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 23:00:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay so this clearly was a filtered view of the situation.... however you can feel like you can #8217;t imagine your life without a person and it still be unhealthy and toxic. Tbh from what I #8217;ve heard, unless you can both agree to see a relationship counsellor or at least read a relationship help book together... I #8217;m not sure anything would change. If jealousy is the main issue, it #8217;s something that needs to be talked through logically which is usually a lot easier with a unbiased third party. I wish you all the best and hope you can get through this. Obviously no need to agree with what I #8217;m saying but my view from limited info we have xxx</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 19:05:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don #8217;t deserve her one bit so yeah leave her now before you marry her to only then break her heart, killing any self esteem she may still have after staying loyal to loser like you who continually tells her that she #8217;s not good enough as she is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 19:06:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also I #8217;d love to see what a stud you are....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 19:33:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not saying he has to find her attractive, but if he doesn #8217;t then leave her so she can find someone who will find her attractive... or at least help her get through whatever she #8217;s struggling with if you care enough. Clearly he doesn #8217;t care about her feelings as he states that he #8217;s told her and she still doesn #8217;t care and that  #8216;her body #8217;s not doing it for him #8217;. He states his feelings are that she #8217;s just lazy but not once has offered what her view on it was. My point is this marriage is not going to be great unless you have an arrangement between yourselves or something dramatically changes, so why drag it out and have to go through divorce?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 14:58:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean my husband is 12 years older than me so I #8217;d always say age doesn #8217;t matter, however I don #8217;t see the same dynamics working if I were with someone younger as personally I feel males emotionally mature later than women (no offence). So I #8217;d say it depends on your personality #8217;s but the age itself doesn #8217;t have to be an issue...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Something triggered a past experience and now I'm questioning if it was rape or not?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 10:35:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>So to put some perspective to the story I'm 25F but the incident that took place happened when I was 18 with an ex boyfriend (21 At the time) of about 6 months. This I know for sure.... He held me hostage In my own flat for about 5 hours. No he didn't tie me up or anything extreme but he threatened me with a knife every time I tried to leave. He'd push me back on the bed and get really in my face... At one point during the incident he smashed a beer bottle and ran it along my throat. Eventually the police/ambulance were called... Possibly by a neighbour or perhaps by his mother who he'd rung several times in a state saying he was going to kill me and himself. I never really found out, or at least I don't remember that I did now. The police tried to convince me to press charges but as he had already been in trouble with the law my ex had told me he'd go straight to prison and if I ever be the one to send hi there he'd send "people" to come after my family. I say people in quotations because at the time I believe him but now looking back I don't think he had anyone to do his dirty work, it was all just talk to scare me. It worked. So anyway, I didn't press charges and the police told me that meant that they couldn't escort him away so unless he chose otherwise he was free to stay the night with me. That's when it happened. He tried to have sex with me and I kind of was not in the mood after what had just happened but as he got more forceful/aggressive I knew I didn't really have a choice. I didn't want to go through the last 5 hours all over again. So I didn't resist, I just did it. I guess I should have been tougher but I was honestly scared about what would happen if I didn't. I never really thought about it tbh I think I always emotionally disconnect from the memories whenever they surface. Therapists have tried to go there when I've mentioned it and it's been like I'm numb.... I say "oh I'm sure there are people who have had worse happen". But the other day I watched a real crime programme and a woman had been threatened, then raped then killed. What got my head overthinking was that technically she had agreed to the sex but the court determined that because she would have felt so scared, she would has felt like she didn't have a choice. Up until watching this It didn't even cross my mind that I'd possibly been raped and I'm still not saying I have. It doesn't make a difference to me if it was or wasn't but since watching that programme, every time I think about the memory (which currently is ALOT) I get panicky and burst into tears. I even went back to self harming a few days ago coz I couldn't stand the emotions. I guess my question is how do I now get over this 7 years later when previously it hadn't affected me and I was able to numb and disassociate with what happened? If this post is not suitable for the thread I apologise and please remove</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 08:08:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>In my experience, absolutely not. And It's incredibly frustrating for the victim.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 08:44:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. My narc SIL once lost it and threatened to hit me in front of 20+ witness' and then denied it ever happened, still to this day. Everyone who disagreed with her had been manipulated by me apparently. Do you think they know they are lying or genuinely are so confident in what the believe that other people cannot change their mind??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 09:02:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes every single one of them saw what happened and didn't need to be manipulated into a story. Some of these were 'her friends' as she would always remind me and she has refused to talk to them all for over 10 months now because they won't back her up. They are now my friends instead so her loss!! That's awful, it's like they seriously believe these made up fantasies in their heads. I'm struggling to empathise with any narc ATM though so probably not thinking logically about why someone would do these things.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 09:04:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't please, send me a message if you want to talk x</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 09:45:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lots of bare foot walking in nice natural areas like fields and forests... Be careful not to step on anything. Even just lying in nature or meditating in nature helps ground me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 13:43:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is not a marriage. He treats you like a slave if what you write is accurate. I don't know a single couple with or without kids who doesn't help out their wives... Even our friends who's husband is a doctor... He works 60+hrs a week and always helped at night and with housework. It's a partnership. He may be at work earning the money but that doesn't devalue what you do every single day. Being a mom of two (same age gaps as you too I think) myself, I understand why you'd feel depressed. You are COMPLETELY unappreciated and therefore you are left with zero self esteem. The only problem here is your husband... Whether that's because of some OCD thing or he's just a dick; he needs some help with whichever it is. You are doing an incredible job</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 20:45:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I second this... Perfect every time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Where do I begin with past life regression?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 21:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have recently been very drawn to past life regression but I'm not really sure where to start?? I have looked into going to past life regression therapy but would like to see if I can achieve something on my own first. Should I be doing meditation on YouTube or is it completely different?? Any tips on where to read up on and how to begin would be great!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 10:42:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I personally am not sure it would look good if they find them accidentally or if there was a bandage (they are bound to ask what happened and unless you are a great liar they will be suspicious). I think your best bet would be to be completely honest if they ask to lift your left sleeve (hopefully you can get away with just the right one and not say anything). Say something like "okay I just want to warn you that I have some scars on my arm... It's something I'm getting help for and is also why I'm trying to better my career for myself". Yes this may lose you the job, but there are so many more people now who understand mental illness and how actually getting a job you want will only motivate you to do better. It will all depend on the interviewers personal opinion tbh. Perhaps if some cuts are fresh, wear the bandage underneath your sleeve anyway. I know it's really hard to do the above, I understand as have avoided job opportunities myself when I realised it may mean bloods/blood pressure etc. but when I look back now I wish id tried to be honest (or try to use the other arm) as someone may have seen past that and looked at my capabilities to do the job. I have got better at being honest when people ask questions sometimes. For example yday it was extremely hot and I got stopped by some old friends who asked wasn't I hot in my log sleeved black jumper (was all I had to wear)? I thought about lying and could feel myself starting to go red and panic because I'm a shit liar. So I just said 'I did something stupid at the weekend' and although they looked uncomfortable for a second, they were then empathic and one even said I've been going through a really shit time too recently and have thought about similar things. So I guess it actually helped us relate a bit and I felt a bit more at ease. Honesty is the best policy I necessary as otherwise they won't trust you which is a worse trait as an employee. Ultimately it's your decision but don't do what I did and miss opportunities that eventually will help your mental health. Edit: also I find when I go to docs and know they will be looking at my arms, I angle the right side of my body to them slightly so that when they go to do it, my right arm is more accessible and in don't look so awkward swapping arms. Has worked so far for me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>