<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject8432</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Home loans and credit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 23:56:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm debating between a home loan from State Employees Credit Union, or a loan from USDA in North Carolina. Both of them seem to have great benefits, but I'm worried about what our income will leave us with. I have a 680 credit score but I own two credit cards at 50% maxed out, I own other without balances. My husband and I make about 55k before tax. Which place is known for giving more money and about how much would I be approved for?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 00:08:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not entirely sure. I was hoping between 170-200k.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 00:11:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what I was thinking, just wanted confirmation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Should I discuss this with my manager?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 21:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Last week I had a discussion with my manager who suggested I needed to toughen up on my team, I agreed. Today I tell one of my associates (Stan) to get back to work who then is rude to me. My other associate (nick) decided he does not want to work for me for the rest of today. At the end of my day I go to another manager asking what steps I am suppose to take when I want to get someone off of my team. Personnel demands I tell them what we #8217;re talking about so I tell them. Personnel tried to say if I have a problem with everyone on the team then maybe it #8217;s me. But I #8217;ve only ever had an actual problem with 2 out of my 6 people. I really don #8217;t feel as though it is me so I feel like I should ask my direct manager on what I need to do next, but my manager strikes me as the kind of person where if I don #8217;t know then I don #8217;t need to be a supervisor. I am respectful to my associates, I ask them instead of telling them, I always say thank you, and when I think they #8217;re doing wrong I always ask them what they #8217;re doing first. Should I talk to my manager about this situation? If so is there something I should mention when bringing it up? My management staff is almost always rude and confusing and I hate going to them without something being very well thought out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-20 23:24:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Texas Pete chilli</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 23:33:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Death. As a child it was something that seemed so far away. Now sometimes I sit and think how fast life really goes by and that one day I will literally feel nothing, see nothing, and be nothing. Trying to imagine not existing is strange, not because I think I #8217;m great but it #8217;s just weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 23:36:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>My cat is name Lady Stoneheart. We call her Lady.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Asking Cap 1 supervisors, what is expected of you and what are you able to complete in one shift?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 23:37:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you always come in to live freight? Are shelves your responsibility? How about setting up features? And are you the designated person for pulling down pallets? I #8217;m curious as to how everyone #8217;s else average day is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 23:58:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jeez how many associates a day do you get??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 00:23:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy moly I #8217;m lucky if I have 3.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 00:37:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Our bins and steels for every department are full plus the 2 pallets of live grocery we come into and the 2 pallets of overstock no one bins in, plus two pallets of live we come into for paper chemicals. Us 4 are never able to cap everything let alone get to top stock or reshops.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do you keep up with your things?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 17:32:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m a 21 year old women with terrible ADHD and I can #8217;t manage to keep up with my things (wallet, keys, phone, etc). I #8217;ve tried the whole phone case wallet, purse, things. It just isn #8217;t working. How are you keeping up with your things?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Helpful reading advice</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 05:18:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Being ADHD meant I never read many books because I had to read the same paragraph ten times and still would have no clue what it said. I discovered reading a book turned upside down a long time ago, it forces your brain a little more to concentrate. Give it a try.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 13:33:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Edit. Turned upside down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anyone else with anxiety sweat through their sheets??</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 04:16:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>If the temp in my house is above 67 degrees Fahrenheit at night I #8217;m sweating through my sheets and not sleeping. It can be hotter during the day but if I #8217;m trying to sleep it HAS to be cold.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 00:39:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awful. I don #8217;t even consider it my first time. It was in a truck in the woods during school lunch. I had an hour. The guy was small and couldnt last two seconds. He was pulling out to come before I even knew he was in. Quickly got dressed and still had time to go out for lunch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 02:05:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>His choice. Precome and come make me vomit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 02:16:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was about an hour every time and he finished every time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 02:24:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, together for 5 married for 1.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 02:27:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was his idea, he #8217;s attracted to the whole hotwife stuff. I think it #8217;s more excitement than weight. But the weight could play a small part.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 02:29:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t think so, I haven #8217;t had sex with anyone else in a few months and even then I wasn #8217;t super excited. But I was a bit more active, so very possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 14:08:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, together for 5 married for 1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 23:00:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Being able to solve a rubix cube and white v-neck t-shirts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is it better to get a loan to pay off credit cards or is it better to keep them separate?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 23:02:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve got two credits cards with about $2200 on each of them. One with a 8% interest rate, the other with about a 12%. Is it better to just get a loan a pay off the cards or is it better to keep them separate on the cards?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is it better to get a loan to pay off credit cards or leave them separate?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 21:07:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have two credits cards at about $2200 each. One with about an 8% interest rate and the other with about a 12% interest rate. My credit score is a little over 700. Is it better to get a loan to pay them off or should I leave it alone?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 21:15:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I pay over the required amount each month, I just didn #8217;t know if there was a faster way of paying it off without it gaining so much interest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 21:18:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not able to pay them both off in under a year. And the only other debt I have is my car which is about $16,000.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What does your HBA and cosmetics bins look like?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 10:21:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cap 1 supervisor (21f) here. Our HBA department manager has random small items all through out her bins, so I hate capping them because they #8217;re so messy and it takes almost all day. What do your HBA bins look like? How are they organized? What makes them easier to cap?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 22:40:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Her top stock is insanely full. That #8217;s why I haven #8217;t put it up there yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 22:41:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 13:35:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>She just got her first cart last week but I #8217;m not sure that she #8217;s using it correctly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 21:07:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I moved out of my fathers house at 16 when he beat me because I was in a interracial relationship. It #8217;s been 6 years, I have a one year old son with the same man, and I have never regretted it. About 3 years ago I tried to fix things with him but he just kept telling me everything was my fault. If he has apologized I #8217;d probably still talk to him. My only problem is... I would never be able to disown my own son because he goes against my beliefs. So how could my father? I miss him at times but I #8217;m okay with it because I know he will never apologize. Maybe give them a chance if they #8217;re being genuine. Start small, let your son decide for himself. Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I #8217;ve got grocery from 164ft of bin space to 32ft!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 00:08:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cap 1 supervisor in the past 2 months not only have I lowered my grocery bin space but I #8217;ve got paper chemicals from 32ft to 8ft!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 01:51:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve completely moved everything around, and I #8217;ve taken them down to store pallets of water and supplies we sell to George #8217;s BBQ sauce.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 02:21:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know this. All of his counts are wrong and he #8217;s got almost 3 cases of everything. I #8217;m still getting it lower I #8217;m just proud to be at 32.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 03:34:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have pics but I #8217;m not sharing, not taking any chances!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 03:41:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>For chemicals I personally spent the whole day blitzing/purging the bins correcting every count for every item, I put everything in top stock. I did this everyday for a week. For grocery it took a full two months and one day I had everyone in the store. On the very first day I asked all associates and department managers to just run one or two carts Of blitzed grocery into topstock, that got rid of about 48ft. On the next day my team spent the day running topstock and correcting counts for every item in topstock. On the next day my team blitzed. Then it was a continuous cycle of that over and over until we got it down to about 48 ft we started capping. It took a long time and a lot of arguing with my team. But we #8217;re getting there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 03:42:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Feels like it. They make me scan his outs and change his features too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 13:53:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>The problem with that, he thinks my associates should stay in his department only and no other so I have to leave notes when I #8217;m not there, otherwise all 3 of my people would spend 8 hours in grocery 24/7. When I first came to this store they weren #8217;t going to any other department.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 14:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>We #8217;ve had Easter out for weeks now. I don #8217;t see how it #8217;s too early.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 14:49:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t allow my team to put an item in top stock without running the 4ft section they #8217;re putting it in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 16:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>All of our new mod came in this week but we #8217;ve already got them back right again for 92 and 95. And for 4 and 13 he filled them with feature but I #8217;ve already come up with a plan that was approved so that #8217;ll be back to normal too. I #8217;m not saying they won #8217;t fill up, but I #8217;m trying my best not to let them get that way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 20:50:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was 28 ft for 95 and 136ft for 92. When I first started at that store 8 months ago all 164ft were full all the way to the top with no holes for anything else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 00:14:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>No reason to apologize. We hate each other. He #8217;s been with the company for 30 years and refuses to follow the new process. He #8217;s continuously blaming us for his awful department, gets mad when his bins aren #8217;t capped because we came into live freight, although he doesn #8217;t help run his live and never caps his own bins. And he continuously makes us clean up his junk carts or features he tears down. I #8217;ve begged them to approve his transfer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 00:17:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 04:19:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>My husband and I both work 40-50 hours a week and we have a one year old with two pets. I struggle with depression he struggles with depression and insomnia. On sundays we are both off we set a meal plan and grocery shop together. Our rule is whoever cooks doesn #8217;t clean the kitchen that night. More often than not I am cleaning the house while he cooks. We eat and then we hang out for a while, We rinse dishes as we put them in the sink and then I wash them the next day. I do an hour of scrubbing when I get home and I just pick up small things (clothes, toys, trash) before bed. Not long but like ten minutes. As far as organization we bought a file cabinet for our paper work and then went through EVERYTHING in our home and if we hadn #8217;t worn or used it within the last two months (with the exceptions of seasonal clothing and other items) we donated it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 04:25:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>In high school there was this girl sitting in the lunchroom that I feel like I just HAD to know her. After getting to know her she asked me to run my fingers through her head and she started saying how good it felt and blushing. And then I realized I was wet and turned on. That #8217;s when I realized I was attracted to other women because they #8217;re hot not because she had a cool personality as friends.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The best shave I have ever had! Smooth, painless and bump free. Advice from a porn star friend of mine.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 01:46:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 02:05:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since she isn #8217;t into sports maybe take her to the kids activities at the library? I was very shy around kids growing up but when it was more forced around people similar to me it made it easier. If she suddenly stopped having friends you might want to make sure she isn #8217;t being bullied, but I wouldn #8217;t pressure her into talking about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What #8217;s your timeline?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 20:22:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got my kit on 3/26, they received in on 3/31. Been in analysis since then! I #8217;m in NC.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 20:54:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>In analysis</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>For those of you with partners who didn #8217;t want to adopt, how did they eventually come around to it?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 19:58:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 20:12:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>My husband won #8217;t even consider fostering, but I want to so bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 20:39:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have a 1 year old boy. He says he #8217;s scared of getting one who gets in trouble all the time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 20:56:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>If he isn #8217;t fully in to it, I would never. But sometimes people change their own mind and that #8217;s more what I was talking about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 21:21:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was younger I lived in a really shit household and I just wanted someone to love and take care of me and because that never happened for me, I want to be that for someone else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can someone tell me how to pull a report on what #8217;s capped when I don #8217;t work?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 20:50:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cap one supervisor trying to figure out what my people really do when I don #8217;t work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 23:07:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve asked them to do this, they won #8217;t do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 01:52:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m talking about doing it the next day I work? Why would I pull it on my day off anyway?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>