<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject6866</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Some small nitpicks about Battlefield 1's physics</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-24 02:29:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love the physics in Battlefield 1, however I've seen a few problems that I haven't seen anyone else adress. The cloth physics in the game are good, but they clip through the ground. I would be able to ignore that, but in a recent update they added cloth collision on capture flags so they don't clip through the ground, so if they added that to flags, why not add it to coats and capes on soldiers? I've noticed that blood pools under dead soldiers appear only when in buildings and certain rocks, not on sand, dirt, etc. I've also noticed ragdolls clip through many objects such as desks, chairs, sandbags and crates and this still hasn't been fixed. One thing that confuses me is that the physics on the gear of the soldier's model (such as shovels, anti tank grenades, canteens, pouches, and a small piece of cloth on most characters) are disabled when someone dies. This is just weird to me. I love the game and play it regularly and I would be extremely happy if DICE fixes just one of these issues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-31 16:10:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, and the blood decals disappear after 10 seconds with no option to configure it. (Blood pools after 20)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-19 17:22:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would like to see an option for corpses to stay longer in Story Mode and blood staying longer in game. If I have a good PC, I should be able to make the blood stay longer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A suggestion for a quick option</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-25 00:10:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>We should have an option to change the stay time of blood decals, since they stay for only 3-4 seconds and that is ridiculous. And in the campaign, dead bodies disappear after only a couple of seconds. I have a good PC and I should be able to see an aftermath of a fight, and adding an option for changing it is pretty easy. (If you pause the game in campaign, the blood and corpses stay during the pause)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 21:25:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you think in the next update you can add an option for blood to stay longer and corpses to stay longer in the campaign?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This game is absolutely phenomenal, but...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-09 23:45:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry for the clickbaity title, but what grinds my gears is the resource inventory capacity. I have it fully upgraded and it's a bit annoying when I have to sell things because it's nearly full or full. They should up the capacity or make the stacks of items hold larger quantities.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-09 23:51:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, that's how I roll, but it gets pretty annoying having to stop by and sell my resources every once in a while</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tutorial quests and their tracking</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 15:17:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dear Guerrilla, please make it so that the tutorial quests can be completed even when they are not tracked, if you can, of course. It's just a bit annoying having to go to the menu every now and then to select which one you want to progress.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 15:28:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>If the quests are open but not tracked, their objectives will not progress even if you try and complete them. You need to have them tracked to complete them which means it is impossible to do multiple tutorial quests at the same time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>That face when you hear Cross outside your walls</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 23:16:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-21 21:28:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>The blood shouldn't be there cuz in For Honor the blood decals disappear after 7 seconds</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-21 21:37:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you have Nvidia GeForce Experience installed (if you have an Nvidia gfx card you definitely should install it) you also get Nvidia Ansel, which is like a photo mode you can activate by pressing alt+f2 You can move the camera around, add filters and take really high resolution photos (68k is max)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[No Spoilers] ME:A Blood Effects</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-21 21:55:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>In all previous Mass Effect games when you shot someone there would be a blood effect in the air, and most of the time a blood decal will spawn on the floor, walls, etc., and that is not present in Andromeda. Am I the only one that misses this small detail? It's kinda inconsistent that you see blood effect but nothing spawns on the ground. Does the blood evaporate before hitting the ground? I wonder if such a small detail can get patched in eventually.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-21 22:12:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I know, but there is no blood on the ground. Does the blood just evaporate?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[No spoilers] Ryder! Worm!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-30 00:38:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ryder! Worm! Ryder! Worm! Ryder! Worm!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-01 20:40:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>When the Nomad was airdropped from the Tempest I immediately thought of Ilos</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bots really pissed me the hell off</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-20 16:31:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Playing VS AI on PC and can't get rewards</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 17:02:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yesterday it was working fine (1v1 vs AI never got you any rewards in the first place) but now playing Dominion, Brawl and Deathmatch with my friend vs only AI gets us no XP, Steel or Order completion, we only get the "Retrieving Data" message and it never retrieves the fucking data. Ubisoft pls</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 17:08:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, so I guess I'm not the only one having this problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 23:25:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would like an option for the blood on the ground to stay longer on PC, it disappears in like 7 seconds. And maybe blood pools, since they had one in a cutscene at the end of the Viking campaign</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 20:46:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>goddamn it, it looks like they're not even acknowledging the problem which may mean that it is intentional</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 10:24:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any tips on growing a beard?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 22:35:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>And also the space battle in episode 2 was phenomenal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-07 23:19:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the kind of person that just deserves a punch in the mouth</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 16:32:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can someone pls explain the B and P memes. Im new to reddit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Boats in this game are ****</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 16:13:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friend and I were in a duo match and we were getting pretty close to the end of the match. The zone moved and there was no way we were getting to the zone in time on foot, so I proposed we take a boat. The boat was perfectly placed so if you tried to turn it, you would beach it. The river was too narrow to turn it, both ways and I ended up beaching it and the zone killed me. I think the boats should be placed so you can drive them either way down the river</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 16:19:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate the boats in this game, they handle so poorly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 16:28:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>If i tried to go reverse I would have beached it as well and turning with the boats is legit cancer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 22:04:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>We were to far to run to the zone, and if the boats aren't meant for the river, then why did it spawn in the river?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 15:14:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've always found them there, maybe it was a spawned boat maybe it was a player boat, but the boat handling should be improved and you should be able to turn the boat without moving forwards</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 18:28:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>The proletarians have nothing to lose but their chains</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 18:44:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>"The proletarians have nothing to lose but their chains"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Girls like this have a 125% chance of conquering Ashfeld</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 19:35:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the cringiest thing that you have ever done or that has happened to you?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 23:05:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 11:53:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Iako me Ubisoft nebrojeno puta razo #269;arao, jo #353; uvijek se radujem novim likovima koji danas dolaze u For Honor</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Boys like this have a 125% chance of establishing a dictatorship of the proleteriat</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 12:18:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This big problem still hasn't been fixed</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 17:57:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hopped on For Honor today to check out the scavenger crates I got and to see if they fixed the "receiving data" problem that I and some other PC players have been having. For Honor's matchmaking is problematic, to say the least, and when you have an order to, for example, get 50 kills in elimination, you're gonna spend a lot of time in matchmaking. So what I like to do is go on a match vs. AI and disable matchmaking (private match) so it's only me or a friend vs AI and we can complete the order as quickly as in 20 minutes. A network outage a couple of weeks ago broke that. If you go into a private match and go for anything except brawl on PC, you will most likely get the "receiving data" message and you won't get any rewards. This isn't intentional since you can still play brawl and get rewards and they increased the private match xp gain from all game modes in today's patch so we should be getting order completion and XP but it's obviously broken and Ubi hasn't even adressed the issue. Before this only happened in Duel private match, but now it's happening to every gamemode except brawl. I opened a support ticket, and if the same thing is happening to you, you should open one too to raise Ubisoft's awareness of this issue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 18:01:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Je, zanimljivo je i zna bit zabavno, pogotovo sa prijateljima, ali je igra u #382;asno, u #382;asno frustriraju #263;a i skroz strgana, i ima pun k**** mikrotransakcija.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 18:30:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, thanks, I had no idea they already knew about it, i tried googling it and no results came up. It's a shame that they don't know how to fix it. Classic Ubisoft</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Private matches vs. AI, any fix yet?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 23:01:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have we gotten any further news from Ubisoft about the matches vs. AI with matchmaking off not giving any rewards? Did anyone find any fix yet?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 00:00:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you put something in the microwave and it is unevenly heated, one part being cold, and one part being hot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-19 18:25:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Any news on fixing the problem with private matches vs AI not giving any rewards?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 17:19:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Profesorica engleskog u na #353;oj  #353;koli je poznata po tome  #353;to nelogi #269;no razmi #353;lja i po tome  #353;to je glupa. Neki od njezinih bisera su: " #381;iva uzrokuje autizam". "Vrijeme zapravo ne postoji, Albert Einstein je rekao da je vrijeme iluzija". Volio bih da ovo izmi #353;ljam, ali na #382;alost, ne, zaglavili smo s njom jo #353; jednu godinu.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 21:11:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://i.redd.it/mc9noys99pxy.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In which engine would it be easiest to make a 2D top-down shooter game?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-21 22:13:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm looking to get into game development and I'm pretty good at coding, so I'm asking you guys what do you think would be a good starting place to try and make a 2D top-down shooter style game, just for practise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ship Damage Mod?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-22 12:41:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you know of any mods that add burn decals or scorch marks to the ships from missiles or miniguns? The bullet holes from normal fights are too small and not visible enough, and on the bigger ships they are very glitchy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-22 17:26:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not studying on time and delaying it and procrastinating</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-22 22:14:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>koji cringe...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-22 22:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Svje #382; mim</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 11:06:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fallout 4, stavio sam otprilike 70 modova i totalno promijenio iskustvo igre</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 19:37:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>He kinda looks like Aaron Taylor-Johnson but with a few extra chromosomes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 20:24:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>X. Gimnazija</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-23 22:36:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>From launch duel vs AI didnt give you rewards. A month ago a server outage broke rewards vs everything in private match (vs AI and matchmaking off). They still haven't fixed the issue, and now it looks like they even made it worse</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 11:42:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>On PC it's still broken (been broken for a month) on vs AI matches with no matchmaking. The only game mode that works this way is Brawl, but everything else gives you no rewards.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cloth physics in video games</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 23:40:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>What game, in your opinion, had the best cloth physics? For me, it's the new Hitman game, since none of the cloth actually clips through the ground, unlike most games.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 23:54:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahahah that sounds amazing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 00:03:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>For some reason, when you crouch in Unity the cloth collides properly with the floor, but in every other instance it falls through. But it does look great</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What are some weird things that were said by your teachers/professors?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 00:51:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any way to make the blood or bodies stay longer?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 22:19:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm playing the game on PC and the blood disappears in less than 10 seconds, and bodies disappear almost as soon as you look away. Is there an option in the config files to make the bodies and blood stay longer? Because seeing the aftermath of a fight would be friggin awesome. They should put in an option in the PC menu that can allow this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 00:17:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gears 4 could come close if the blood and bodies stayed for longer. The mess when you rip someone apart with the Gnasher looks amazing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Option for blood and bodies to stay longer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 21:10:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>There should be an option on the PC to change the time that blood and bodies stay. In the campaign, bodies disappear after about 2 seconds, and blood decals on the floor disappear after 7 seconds in the game. A simple option to change that time would make the looks after a fight much better</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-05 18:27:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is both on r/mildlyinfuriating and r/mildlyinteresting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This brave man has taken up arms to protect his home against foreign invaders. 1 upvote = 1 prayer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-09 00:19:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-09 01:46:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>This isnt really cringe, its just sad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 13:15:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, but if you look down at the ground you see the rain follows your character, and it's basically a screen overlay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 17:51:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn, why does my name have to be David :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-17 21:19:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Penny Dreadful. A great show set in Victorian London and it has vampires and werewolves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The physics in this game</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-18 02:58:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>If Dice can make the conquest flags not clip through the floor, then why not soldiers' coats and capes? Also the gear on the soldiers, such as pouches or grenades, moves realistically, but that is disabled upon death, but in the beta it was enabled and it looked great. It should be enabled on ragdolls just like the cloth physics are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The physics in BF1</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 03:31:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>If the flags dont clip through the ground, then why not implement it for soldiers coats and capes? The physics on the gear look amazing, but why are they disabled upon death?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 21:11:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, basically. The cloth physics are active on ragdolls, even though they clip through the ground, but the gear isn't and it would be cool seing the gear move even on ragdolls, like it was in the Beta</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-20 15:26:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course, but it's such an easy thing to fix, especially the gear physics. I assume it would be easy to stop the clipping of clothes since they did it to flags.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-21 01:35:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would like an option to extend the time that blood decals stay on the ground. By default it is a very short time of 7 seconds and there should be an option on PC to change that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-25 15:07:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can anyone fix the cloth physics in FO4 so that they don't clip through the ground?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-25 18:12:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just watched that movie a week ago and that theme is one of the best things I have ever heard in my entire life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-26 00:33:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Night Call was in drive, the music linked here is Wanna Fight? from Only God Forgives</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-27 22:22:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really hope The Last Man on Earth gets another season</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Joel Goes Ham</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 22:37:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 02:02:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>No It Wasn't, And Stop Capitalizing Every Word</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When the AI actually helps you</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 21:48:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 22:02:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was playing on Grounded and I would have definitely died without him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 22:20:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sam was constantly throwing bricks for me, but would almost always miss</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 02:08:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was pretty intense cuz I needed to lure them to me, they wouldnt come automatically</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 16:59:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw some gameplay when the NDA was lifted. A guy threw a grenade and there was a smoke puff and the lights flickered, thats all. No doors moving from the blastwave. I dont know how it is know since even though I've purchased the game, I still haven't gotten access to the early access build</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 17:24:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I said that, and got downvoted. I really wanna play this game, but I havent gotten access to the alpha/beta yet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Suggestion: Mark medicinal plants with a different icon</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 16:51:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Medicinal plants should be marked with a different icon from normal resources out in the wild. It would make them easier to diferentiate from normal plants.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 19:20:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this a Slovenian product?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 19:24:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Preston is just in the back thinking about settlements</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 15:52:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a quest in Horizon Zero Dawn where a weird guy from the Banuk tribe asks you to kill machines and bring their "blood" to him so he will drink it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 17:22:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should marry that woman. Oh, wait...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>By drinking juice, we are actually drinking the blood of trees' children</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 00:14:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 03:05:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is the game going to be released on Steam? Have you decided on a price yet? Will the game have any gore, considering that it is based on gladiators</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 14:36:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I usually just hit them with freeze arrows and them use sticky bombs, that brings them down pretty quickly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 20:06:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have freeze mods on the war bow and i can freeze them in about 5 arrows and then it just takes me a couple of stickies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 12:54:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Derangement started shortly after GAIA blew up, probably because Hephaestus changed the designs so Thunderjaws, and Sawtooths started appearing. The Sun-King though that if he sacrificed people to the Sun, that the Derangement will stop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 13:19:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea but that is how its actually explained in the game. The Sun-King started killing people to try and stop the Derangement</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 21:28:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love how when you kill Eclipse soldiers their capes still flow in the wind while they are on the floor</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 00:01:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fantasticno ime u/asshair</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hilarious Death</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 00:04:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 16:31:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Smash that mf like</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 20:34:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great use of depth of field</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 02:28:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>XxX420_BowlingTeam_69XxX</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 20:31:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mislim da sam izgubio nekoliko mo #382;danih stanica gledaju #263;i to</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I killed an enemy with an incredibly elastic neck</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 23:22:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The view distance in this game is incredible</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 23:54:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What are some good, automated subreddits, such as r/subredditsimulator?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 03:03:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 16:21:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Took this with photo mode</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 16:59:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>The soundtrack is fucking amazing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 17:02:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/space ili r/earthporn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 22:16:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Na HRT teletekstu pise da je NASA uslikala po #382;ar iz svemira a nigdje izvor niti adresu. Provjerio sam na njihovom twitteru i stranici, ni #353;ta. Ima li netko link za te slike ili preporuku gdje da tra #382;im?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 22:20:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hvala puno. Gdje si to na #353;ao?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-17 22:22:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tam je jbno te #353;ko na #263; te slike</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Aloy and Uthid share a look</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-18 22:22:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 02:58:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ne znam je li smije #353;nije ako je ovo  #353;ala ili je smije #353;nije ako si ozbiljan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 16:33:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can talk to the survivors and one of them gives you a reward box</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 22:07:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I managed to finish it today aswell, holy shit the final boss was intense, but I didnt die during the last mission</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 22:09:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck that guy so much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 22:10:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are under a cease fire</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why dont lodge weapons count as shadow weapons?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 00:05:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm playing on NG+ UH and I'm contemplating whether or not to spend 14000 shards on a shadow blast sling to get that last bit for 100%. I already have the lodge blast sling, I think it's stupid that lodge weapons don't count in completion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 12:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go check out the completion guide, shadow weapons and outfits do count, I have all the collectables and side quests complete, I just meed the weapons. If you go under your game progress tab in the menu, you have a stat that says how many shadow weapons and outfits you have</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL that friendly Thunderjaws have a funny reaction to being shot</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 20:11:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you override a Thunderjaw, and then shoot it while its on your side, it will turn to you and start nodding its head. One of the top posts of this sub is a gif of that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 21:06:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cloth physics in video games. Its just fascinating watching the clothes mkve realistically</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 02:49:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/titlegore</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 01:19:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are there any Fallen in the beta, and if so, where are they? I've gone on the strike 3 times and I've never started from the beginning so I don't know</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>There should be a "ragdoll" button in hubs</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 19:41:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was messing around the football pitch in the EDZ and someone ran out of the area and jump right as he was about to die and he flopped beautifully. The other players and I started to do the same and it turned into a beautiful cluster****. There should be a button assigned to make your character ragdoll while in hubs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 19:53:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unreal Tournament 3 had a button that did exactly this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-23 20:16:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>(suggestion)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Biggest WTF in Bloodborne for me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 20:50:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>The cloth physics. Clothes move very realistically, but the clipping is what gets me. MOST of the cloth falls through the ground, and sometimes even the characters. Now, if ALL of the cloth was like this, I wouldn't have a problem because making the cloth not clip is difficult, however... some characters, like Martyr Logarius, Queen Yharnam, the Pthumerian Descendant*/Elder have cloth that interacts nicely with the floor instead of clipping through it. The WTF moment was when I realized that one enemy, the Loran Priest, has a cape that clips through the floor, and a waistcloth that doesn't. If they managed to do it for the waistcloth, why not for the cape as well? Why not for the other characters? This is legit my only nitpick with the game, everything else is IMO fantastic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 22:02:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, but certain enemies show that FromSoft can make cloth not clip through the ground, so why don't they apply that to every piece of cloth?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 23:07:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's just inconsistent. If they could do proper collision with Logarius and Queen Yharnam, it would be easy to do it with the rest of the cloth physics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 16:35:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reddit gold</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[FO4] Would it be possible for modded companions to say the player's name, like Codsworth?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 20:31:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was wondering whether it is impossible, or if no one has done it. After all, recording all of the names is very difficult</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can we get a PC option for blood and bodies to stay?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 13:41:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know this isn't directly related to the PTS, but seeing blood disappear during a fight is immersion breaking and is really simple to fix. Seeing all the blood and bodies stay after a fight would give the game a great adtermath feeling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Question about blood and corpses</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 16:20:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there a tweak or a mod that increases the limit of blood decals and dead bodies? Because it will be quite cool to see a nice aftermath of a foght with blood and corpses everywhere</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 00:32:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Got it back in February. Still haven't gotten the key.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-02 11:17:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was put in the game on purpose. Friendly thunderjaws always do this when you shoot them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Request: mod to increase the limit of blood decals and dead bodies</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-03 00:22:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>This seems like it would be a very simple fix that would add a lot. The current maximum amount of bodies is 6, I think, and blood decals about 7. Can anyone make a mod for that or tell me how to do it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-07 04:09:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>This episode was fucking LIT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can scavs spawn with helmets?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-07 19:34:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just saw a scav on a factory run wearing a helmet, didnt behave like a player, so I was wondering can they spawn with helmets?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-08 03:38:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rains odfCastamere. Self-explanatory.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What the aftermath of an execution would look like if Ubisoft would give us an option to keep the blood</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 12:59:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 14:56:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is exactly why ubisoft needs to give us an option of how long the decals will stay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 16:47:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Woah, that's a bit excessive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-09 17:05:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a strong computer, and I am willing do sacrifice a few frames for longer blood decals. Ive modded my fallout 4 to keep nvidiavflex debris, bullet shells, corpses and blood and it looks and feels great with a minimal impact on my frames. The most important thing is to have an option.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-11 11:29:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL, I found a helmet off a dead scav a few days ago</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Gofa storg ohome?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 17:40:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 15:53:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Needs more frying u/deepfrybot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Funny Moments and Intense Firefights</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-17 14:46:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-17 22:29:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Needs more frying u/deepfrybot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Will using cinematic tools mod for singleplayer get me banned?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 03:10:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 16:58:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Needs more frying u/deepfrybot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[The Order 1886] Amazing ragdoll effect</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 23:42:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 17:08:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should be able to get it very cheap now. Its pretty good, but very linear</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-23 13:37:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>FRICK YEAH MFER</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-25 13:21:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>A surprise, to be sure, but a realistic one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 13:27:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is outrageous, its unfair!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 02:21:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>He must feel far from good while he is hanging</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 19:53:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mr. Speaker, we are for the big</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 19:58:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not if anything to say about it I have</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 03:21:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, I don't think so</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 13:50:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>DO NOT WANT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 14:07:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>The memes here are great. I love this sub much more than r/gameofthrones but Im only here off season because I cant watch leaks and dont want to get spoiled</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 18:41:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>When that happens, I'll GTFO faster than Jaime</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 20:20:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good. Good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 20:23:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>The negotiations were long</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 11:44:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>u/hamsack_the_ruthless can't do that. Shoot him... or something</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 03:29:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel far from good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 16:40:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>He can't do that! Shoot him... or something</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Went into a FD match with randoms, this happened</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 13:56:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ansel glitched and came out with this cool picture</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 13:57:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 16:33:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you not do it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 17:00:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahah exactly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 18:20:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im new to the game and have no idea what I'm doing :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 16:42:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Death cannot come any sooner</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Scavs are lit AF fam</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-16 17:35:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-17 21:46:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>hahhahah, wow, that's the best thing I've seen all day</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 00:46:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not anymore in CET timezone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The terrorists in situations</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 12:28:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why don't they use the terrorist enemy character models from situations in Terrorist Hunt? They look so much better than the ones in Terrorist Hunt. Adding new enemy models would add some variety. Also, if you watch the intro cinematic the woman says that these attackers have no motive except to cause harm and to kill people. Wouldn't that just make them anarchists? Since terrorists have a political cause for the harm they cause. Edit: typos</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 20:31:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>General Reposti</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ansel keeps glitching, but coming out with cool photos. Does anyone know how to fix it?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 12:56:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 16:25:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>And lighting and textures too, lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 21:03:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Theres a typo in the subtitles for the armored briefing. It says sqaud instead of squad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Val the Impaler</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 20:50:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-01 22:59:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, its a rep 5 helmet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Y'all'st'd've</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-17 23:10:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-18 12:48:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Srijeda je, moji drugovi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The new music</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 19:22:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really dig the new "sp00py" rendition of the main theme, and the new loading music is so out of place in For Honor that it is excellent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What would be the most popular r/askreddit posts in 2117?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 15:50:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Please let us rebind quicksave and quickload keys.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 21:26:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't even know this game had quicksaving and quickloading because they were not listed under keybindings, and you cannot change them, they are defaulted to F5 for quicksave and F9 for quickload. If anyone knows of any way how to change this, it would be much appreciated. They should just give us an option to rebind it in the menu</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 21:54:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ive gotten used to rebinding quickload to F8, since I use my F9 key to record with shadowplay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I've already had one character death in the campaign spoiled - by Youtube</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 20:13:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd watched a couple of WWII videos about the multiplayer and the beta. My plan was to buy the game around Christmas so I wasn't gonna watch any campaign videos not to get spoiled, but lo and behold, the first thing that pops up in my recommended section is "Call of Duty WWII All Character Deaths and Ending" with a thumbnail of a dead story character. I have no problem with people uploading these kinds of videos, but for chrissakes, putting character deaths in thumbnails is a huge dick move by itself, but even before launch day? C'mon, how much of a jerk do you have to be to do something like that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 20:51:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't spoil anything to anyone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 20:51:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ugh, happened to me while I was waiting for the game to download</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 22:25:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, you know someone's gotta die, it's a WW2 game with a squad dynamic, it'd be stupid, unrealistic and disrespectful if noone died</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ubi, please give us blood on our weapons when we hit an enemy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 14:32:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>If just a generic blood texture was placed on swords, axes, clubs it would make it more immersive and cool looking when your shiny weapon gets stained in the blood of your enemies. It looks weird when you stab someone through the gut with Warden's sword and it's still perfectly clean.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 20:44:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't get salty, the people working on effects and art, and people working on gameplay are in different teams</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 21:32:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go post your suggestions in another thread or on the forums if you want to provide your feedback</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 21:43:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>u/MrEricPope</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 22:46:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blood for the blood god</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 12:51:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ugh, I have posted this before on reddit and on the game's forums and I got a response saying that they thought about it. I dont know why they dont give us an option since it would be easy to implement</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 16:30:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kakav je? Horizon mi je bio fantasti #269;an i triput sam ga pre #353;ao, je li DLC jednako dobar kao i base game?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Man, the cuts in this game look brutal</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 22:43:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 00:49:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>hahah, check my post before this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 00:50:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>she most definitely diededed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tried taking a screenshot with the new Nobushi execution, but Ansel glitched and made it even cooler</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 21:34:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 22:43:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I take my screenshots in Nvidia Ansel, but often it glitches and the lighting is totally messed up, and it ends up looking something like this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Your thoughts on the campaign?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 20:39:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen a lot of rants and discussions about the multiplayer, but not a lot about the campaign. I'm curious to see what this community thought of the campaign.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ubisoft, please let us keep the blood</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 22:44:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ubisoft, please give an option on PC for blood decals and dead bodies to stay longer. The dead bodies in multiplayer stay until respawn, which is fine, but in the campaign they disappear in 1-2 seconds, and blood that is spawned on the ground when a character is hit disappears in about 5 seconds. If blood and bodies could stay, the aftermath of a fight would look and feel awesome. This could be an easy option to implement, and if someone doesn't want blood and bodies to stay longer, they leave it at default. So, an option for bodies to stay longer in story mode, and an option for blood decals to stay longer on the floor would be awesome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The tribute order to claim 20 offerings is ridiculous</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 21:31:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The new game mode is great. I haven't had this much excitement in For Honor in quite some time, and the soundtrack is fantastic. However, I think this order is just ridiculous. It should be claim or defend 20 offerings. It's even difficult to do with bots since they will just pick up the offerings while you fight other enemies. Either lower the number of required offerings in the future, or change it so you can gain progress by defending as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 21:46:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need to fully claim it, though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 21:58:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>takes a lot of time and is pretty difficult, though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 22:11:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Teach me, master</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 22:14:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hit my bot teammates but they dont drop the offering</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[A3][UK/EU/NA][MILSIM/CASUAL][RECRUITING] StowMarines - Tactical Play For New Or Experienced Players!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 23:41:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>TL:DR  #8211; Small Special forces group, MilSim but still able to joke around. We teach tactics and procedures if you are new to ARMA and we have our own mission makers! We do require you turn up for missions regularly if you are thinking of applying, 16+ only. Check out the links below. ###Who are we?: We are a NATO, Arma 3, Special Forces MilSim unit. We accept all nationalities (as long as you can speak good English and attend most events). ###What is different about our clan: We make our missions and training as realistic as possible whilst still having a bucket load of fun! We also don't just go to a town and kill people, we have under water missions, HVT, hostages, campaigns, night missions and much much more. ###Times  amp; Events: We have a training session on Fridays from 8:00pm GMT and a main mission on Saturdays from 8:00pm GMT. ###How do I apply?: Head over to our website and see if you are eligible to apply and if so, how to! All you need to do is do a simple interview with one of our membership team staff for around 5-10 minutes and you will get an immediate answer, whether that be that you are accepted or not! ###Mods: We use multiple mods to make our events realistic as possible, all our mods are under one mod folder found on our website and optional mods are listed below. This makes it easier for our members to just update and play and not have to worry about compatibility. ###Links: * [Official Website!] (http://stowmarines.epizy.com) * [ARMA Units!] (https://units.arma3.com/unit/stowmarines) ### Email: * smbjsgaming@gmail.com</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is what an aftermath of a fight could look like if Ubisoft would give us an option to keep the blood and dead bodies</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 21:37:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 22:59:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spawn lvl 3 bots at higher skill levels, but don't spawn them in PvAI matches, they're OP AF. The Elimination and Skirmish playlists should be separate, like in season 2 and season 3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 00:31:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-26 11:48:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you turn off the HUD in replay mode?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-26 12:23:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. I don't know why that isn't listed in the controls</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 00:42:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>If only the blood would stay on the ground, it would make it even more badass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shaman looks extremely happy while throwing her axe at someone</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 07:09:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found two physical bitcoins in two subsequent raids on Factory, in the office safe</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 14:33:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Battle of the 12 Days</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 19:10:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>It started on a frigid winter's morn Fifty Knight's to their master sworn Marched with icy armor keeping time Down a treacherous valley towards Valkenheim Unbeknownst to them the Samurai had similar thoughts For the bitter cold had emptied all their pots Food was scarce and the hunger was setting in This battle each Faction needed desperately to win Twelve days of bloody battle saw warriors cut down Over the food they thought was in this Viking town On the twelfth day only one warrior stood Only to find that there had been no food</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does weapon mastery do anything at this stage?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 02:03:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just leveled up my Saiga to level 2, and it didn't seem to do anything. Am I missing something or are they gonna add it later?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[REQUEST] Stop destroyed vehicles from disappearing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 12:03:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>In TPP when you destroy any vehicle, it will explode and fire and smoke will be coming from it for about half a minute/1 minute, and after that time has elapsed, the vehicle will explode and leave no trace of it ever being there. Would it be possible to stop destroyed vehicles from disappearing, or at least increase the time they stay?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 15:07:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, fuck then.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 19:40:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>In This War of Mine, I stole supplies from an elderly couple. My character was depressed after that. So was I.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 13:29:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seconded. I'd also like to see an option to make blood and corpses permanent, because they disappear too quickly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 18:23:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>You even added an oil filter, jesus christ</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 22:55:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can see a wound on her right shoulder, pause at about 0:35 and you can just see her flesh ripped open by the bullet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My Rep 9 Warden</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 14:07:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 16:44:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Money</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 16:45:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 16:48:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Supermaaan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 11:40:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Drug use, really? A man of your talents?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 14:44:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Galactic President Superstar McAwesomeville</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 00:03:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, they could at least keep let us keep it for a minute or two, instead of just 5 seconds</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wounds disappear whenever you kill someone with a heavy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 17:11:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>The wounds in this game look great, but whenever you kill someone with a heavy and get prompted for an execution, all of the wounds they get in the fight disappear and are replaced with a big blood splat on their body.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 03:58:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can anyone explain the we get it and thats it meme? Ive seen that video and still dont get it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 09:29:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>BR2049 je meni osobno najbolji film 2017. i zao mi je sto nije barem nominaciju za najbolji film dobio.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How you doin?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 23:01:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My face whenever someone starts speculating when the next AC game will take place</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 23:02:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can PC players get an option to keep the blood longer?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-08 08:02:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>The blood effects in Origins are pretty solid, but they disappear after a few seconds, and all thats left behind is a blood pool. Giving us an option to keep the blood decals would be easy and it would give fights a better sense of an aftermath, and a few decals wouldnt decrease performance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 22:15:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>This game is just a playable meme now, isn't it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I wish Ubi would give us an option to keep the blood decals and footprints for longer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 20:35:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 20:59:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It would be very simple to do, as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 21:10:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Hyena, Khaliset</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 21:26:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>The blood pools and corpses already stay, so I doubt the rating would change because of that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 22:10:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>A lot of games have realistic gore and blood effects and still arent banned. The game doesnt need to have dismemberment and it can still be gory. The new Hitman game does this pretty well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 13:18:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kingdom Come je fantastican, super gameplay, prica i likovi, ali prepun glitcheva. Imam nekih 30ak sati na njemu vec i ne zalim sto sam dao novce za tu igru</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Backstabbed</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 17:01:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 19:05:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know I had to do it to 'em</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An opinion on ISIS execution videos</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 15:40:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude, ISIS execution videos are very high production quality. You can have your shitty Brazil street killings and Mexican cartel beheadings in 144p, but we have ISIS over here with 4K, multiple cinematic camera angles, and a fucking orchestral soundtrack all playing while they let a little child shoot a man with a shotgun in the face. I enjoy good cinema, and ISIS provides me with that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 20:52:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can we get an option to keep the blood and bodies for longer on PC?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 19:42:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was straight up an anime moment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I love emojis!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 10:40:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Virgin Croat vs Chadcegovac</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 11:40:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you get attacked by bandits but are max level and in full heavy armor</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 00:05:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 00:50:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is where the fun begins!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 09:21:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Post this on r/farcry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 15:16:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>It would be extremely painful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 15:28:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>For you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My favourite artist</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 15:27:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Y'all incels need to read this</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 22:18:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Women can SMELL the lack of confidence. That's how they identify their prey. Then they suck the life out of you through passively showing zero interest, and go away to sleep with Chad. #65279;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>info_player_loss</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 16:39:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ancient writings</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 16:36:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Oh, look! Henry's has come really close to see us</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 20:43:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Aramusha somehow looks really happy while getting hit in the face</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 21:47:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 23:52:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Henry Christ be praised!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 23:56:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely some brain damage caused on that hit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Virgin 2nd Wave Division Agent vs Chad 1st Wave Division Agent</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 18:19:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I N C R E D I B I L I S</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 20:55:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Let us keep the blood and bodies in the training arena</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 18:52:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>An option for that would be nice. Seeing all of the dead enemies would look awesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 21:10:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>On weaker machines yes, thats why there should be an option</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 22:47:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Visit any bathhouse and there will be an option for it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 23:03:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was added on the latest update on PC, not sure about consoles</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Falcon Punch!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 02:01:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When Ansel glitches but it doesn't matter because Cent is still Incredibilis</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 10:14:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ansel keeps glitching but coming out with awesome photos</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 13:01:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Loss is timeless</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 13:20:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ubi, can we please, please get an option to keep the blood longer?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 00:06:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 00:26:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>In the campaign, the corpses disappear in 2 seconds which is abysmal. They should change that so the corpses stay like in the trials</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 13:17:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thats why it should be an option, just to prolong it a bit, not for the whole match</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 20:22:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want die</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 10:41:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's treason, then</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hmmm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 17:54:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 20:28:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>In the first few months of For Honor, someone somehow got into my Uplay account and changed one emblem to a penis emblem, and another into a swastika. I deleted them immediately. That's all they did. I haven't given my password to anyone and have now changed my password. This isn't related to the post but just wanted to share this weird thing that happened to me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hmmm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 09:22:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The new soldiers look inspired</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 20:18:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 17:36:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Skirmish</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm going to be disappointed if Ola Strandh doesn't do the soundtrack for The Division 2 or the Division movie</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 20:52:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely phenomenal soundtrack, fits perfectly with the setting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 21:04:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Clint Mansell would be great for the movie</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 09:58:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Johannsson died recently</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 13:06:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was just about to comment how I saw this on the r/forhonormemes subreddit. And he just reuploaded the exact picture with a different title</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hmmm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 19:28:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>2meirl4meirl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 19:31:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How I learned about The Expanse</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 23:42:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I played Call of Duty Infinite Warfare's singleplayer mode which takes place in a far future solar system and revolves around a conflict between Earth and Mars (sound familiar?). I was really engaged in the story, and even though the physics and travel isn't as realistic as The Expanse, it was still a very fun and interesting spin on a Sci-Fi FPS game. So I googled "sci fi shows set in the solar system" and The Expanse was the first thing that came up, and boy, am I glad it did. If you're looking for a game with a setting similar to that of The Expanse, I think this is the only modern FPS you're gonna find, and I wholeheartedly recommend you rent it if you got a console or get it off g2a for 6 euros if you're on PC. It's worth it for the campaign, it has some great characters and is very unpredictable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 00:04:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really? I kinda actually prefer it as a book series and a TV show, but it would have been extremely interesting seeing it as a game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 01:39:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, that price is wayy too high. The game has mostly negative reviews because people hate the futuristic aspect and Call of Duty in general and on pc it has technical issues on older pc. If you can rent it on console or get it for 6 euros on g2a like I did, its worth the price</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 12:48:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Death is no disgrace! Mars aeternum</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The signs were here all along... Now is the time to rise up, my fellow gamers. We won't be living in a society anymore!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 23:48:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lord, forgive me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 21:37:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 23:54:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ultrachad The Expanse</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 02:10:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>It says time to go back to the old me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 22:05:44</DATE>
    <TEXT> #10240; #10240; #10240; #10484; #10484; #10340;  #10240; #10464; #10240; #10431; #10247; #10311; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10416; #10423; #10327;  #10240; #10422; #10429; #10303; #10455; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10492; #10343; #10242; #10240; #10240; #10492; #10487; #10310;  #10240; #10240; #10494; #10422; #10256; #10481; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10468; #10460; #10491; #10471; #10482; #10470; #10276; #10471; #10495; #10294;  #10240; #10368; #10495; #10495; #10439; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10267; #10303; #10495; #10495; #10487; #10468; #10436; #10361; #10495; #10487;  #10240; #10424; #10495; #10424; #10495; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10248; #10265; #10431; #10495; #10495; #10495; #10495; #10495;  #10240; #10303; #10243; #10248; #10303; #10246; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10297; #10303; #10303; #10303;  #10240; #10368; #10368; #10304; #10240; #10368; #10468; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10304; #10304;  #10240; #10495; #10335; #10311; #10240; #10285; #10315; #10245; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10416; #10463; #10431;  #10240; #10489; #10316; #10240; #10240; #10472; #10494; #10487; #10436; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10376; #10260; #10252;  #10288; #10487; #10495; #10304; #10384; #10431; #10495; #10495; #10427; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10400; #10495; #10367; #10340; #10484; #10244; #10368; #10432; #10304;  #10264; #10495; #10495; #10242; #10248; #10424; #10495; #10495; #10488; #10240; #10240; #10240; #10392; #10495; #10495; #10432; #10336; #10464; #10490; #10495; #10487;  #10240; #10495; #10495; #10310; #10240; #10424; #10495; #10495; #10494; #10311; #10240; #10495; #10495; #10495; #10495; #10495; #10455; #10491; #10363; #10303; #10241;  #10240; #10495; #10495; #10311; #10240; #10424; #10495; #10495; #10311; #10240; #10240; #10249; #10249; #10249; #10249; #10249; #10249; #10241;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 01:01:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really hope they do what you said because it just looks wrong. Do you have a source of them saying they will fix it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 14:36:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Outbreak, outbreak, outbreak!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 15:02:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thats oddly wholesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Daddy Cent and Mommy Peacekeeper entertain their baby</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 13:31:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 00:24:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least it wasn't as cringy as the gameplay for the first game, and it was kinda nice seeing they kept the same names</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 00:25:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>ISAC voice is back baby! FUCK YEAH!!! Also, it seems as if the soundtrack is just as good as the first game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 00:13:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I expected like 2 new heroes or something, but this is just amazing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 01:08:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>He did mention it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cursed_tubby</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 16:50:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 17:32:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Last of Us had some pretty damn great gore, but this is leagues better than that. I really hope all the blood and bodies stay instead of vanishing, it would make an even more immersive experience</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 17:34:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably not if you're in the EU. Part one got censored and for me, living in Croatia, there was no gore in multiplayer, just blood on the ground and blood soaked clothing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 22:18:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>When Ellie shoots the girl with an explosive arros, the blood stains everything, and even the fucking ceiling</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Matura iz fizike</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 11:46:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jel se to samo meni  #269;ini il je matura ove godine bila teza od prijasnjih? Zadatci su jos bili i rjesivi, ali teorija je uzas bila</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 12:05:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kondenzator sam pogledas formulu i vidis kak se mijenja, a hitna pomoc je bila Dopplerov efekt. Ovo sa energijom mirovanja ni ja nisam uspio</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 12:14:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ne sjecam se toga, taj je skroz zbunjujuc bio</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 22:28:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>even if you don't play games, Gustavo still won 2 Oscars in a row for his incredible soundtracks, so he might be pretty well known to film buffs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 02:21:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dammit, why did they have to makes some of the challenges DLC? I still don't have the season pass and I don't wanna buy it either</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 03:11:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>delet this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 12:30:53</DATE>
    <TEXT> #268;ua san od frenda da je ima 300 bodova i upa je</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 13:04:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cini se kao da je netko ljut sta nije upao. Omega susramlje</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 20:11:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Valkyreeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shaman T-pose</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 20:14:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 22:42:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did they move again?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Snow...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 23:21:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Baldur's death was really beautiful. Kratos quoting Zeus and snapping Baldur's neck with that incredible soundtrack and Baldur's eyes slowly filling up with blood as he feels snow fall on his face. What a beautiful scene and an amazing game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 00:26:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too. I wish I could erase my memories and start the game anew</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 01:13:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reminds me when I was playing elimination and was last man standing with walk and I held up on a bridge. An enemy said in the chat: "She doesn't stand a chance." Then I proceeded to toss 3 of them off the bridge and threw a spear at the last one and finished him off easily.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 01:44:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you delete someone else's post?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 03:07:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Totally agree. Game would have been great even if Baldur was a boring character, but his depth really elevates this game beyond greatness and into godlike status. He wasnt really a villain, more of an antagonist. And its rare you can see an antagonist cry in a game or movie. He was one of my favorite characters, and his death did him justice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 13:49:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel honored that my post got a sequel. Very nice T-pose, very assertive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 18:27:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>In one of the previous God of War games, not sure which one though, cant remember</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 18:48:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just checked, it was God of War 2</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 19:22:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Matura iz hrvatskog</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 10:17:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kak je vama bilo? I #353;ao sam na A razinu i poga #273;ao sam valjda 15% testa ahahah. Dost lagano, ali je bilo nekoliko retardiranih pitanja</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 10:46:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whenever I hear boy I just immediately think of Kratos now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 10:48:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>There were 12 of us in For Honor but now there's just 8 like in God of War</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 11:25:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ma nizu bi i poluretardirani majmun uspio uspjesno rijesiti</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 11:27:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ma to pogadjanje samo hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 11:52:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kak si to zapamtio hahahahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 12:25:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Za 2-3 dana otprilike</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 12:34:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bas to. Puno bodova ovisi o tome hoces li se sjetiti nekog malog retardiranog djela koje ni profesor hrvatskog ne bi odmah znao. Npr. Suglasja od Baudelairea i kako je Gundulic zvao svoja djela. Katastrofa</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 13:38:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bas cu ja strebat neka nevazna djela koja smo na satu hrvatskog samo spomenuli i proveli manje od 5 sekunde na njima. Nebitna su ta pitanja i nesvrsishodna.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 13:40:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mogao bi cak i Kiklop napokon doci. Nadam se</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 13:58:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Krivo prorocanstvo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 14:00:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Da</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 14:01:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Liku na K</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 14:09:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kakav kompas? Valjda znas osnovne strane svijeta, jbt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 14:17:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ne kuzim kako netko ne moze znat to pitanje</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 15:04:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rezultati tada dolaze, a rjesenja za 2-3 dana</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ghlowe'e, Bringer of Light</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 17:21:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 19:47:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Moraju ti oba dijela bit pozitivna i onda se zbrajaju bodovi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 01:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bazga means Elderberry in Croatian</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 11:13:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>A razina je bila macji kasalj. 550 rijeci sam bez frke uspio napisati. Ruka me strasno boli, ali drago mi je da nismo dobili pjesme kao B razina hahah</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 11:16:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kriste, God of War je remek djelo. Cekao sam popust al kad dodje nastavak moram odmah uzet jer takvu igru dugo nisam odigrao. Muzika, prica, likovi, sve. Imao sam onaj osjecaj unutarnje praznine nakon sto sam ju zavrsio</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 12:46:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ja sam imao otprilike 10 rijeci po retku i ispunio sam dvije strane te sam imao oko 550 rijeci. Bez brige, 2 strane su dovoljne</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 12:49:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesi se vratio kuci nakon zavrsetka price? Imas custcene jedan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 12:57:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesi igrao sa hrvatskim prijevodima?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 13:02:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Prijevod je zapravo jako kvalitetan i profesionalan. Ak ces ponovno odigrat kad ubace new game+ preporucujem ti da odes u opcije i namjestis hrvatski. Neke stvari ce zvucati smijesno, al sve u svemu jako dobar prijevod</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 13:07:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm very happy to see that T-pose memes have entered the sub</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is this...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 15:21:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 15:12:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is perfect. Just beautiful in every way possible</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 17:22:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wtf same thing happened to me. Anyone got a solution?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>For Honor was great, but the story lost me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 19:17:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not sure if intentionally bad or not</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 23:24:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My Reynauld died, but I really liked him so I got a little creative with the name of my new crusader</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 00:40:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 01:45:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>He'll get it... Sooner or later</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Matura iz matematike</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 12:22:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Polagao sam A razinu danas i moram reci da je dosta lagana bila. Kak je vama ostalima bilo?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 20:19:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not dominant enough, that there is an A pose, we need a real T pose</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 02:43:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>So many bloodborne memes, it's awesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 21:54:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Zainteresiran sam, da vam se javim ovdje u komentare ili private message preko reddita?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 13:12:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ban me pls</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 22:20:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> #3900;  #12388;  #9685;\_  #9685;  #3901; #12388; GIVE BAN  #3900;  #12388;  #9685;\_  #9685;  #3901; #12388;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 12:04:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 22:43:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ban me pls</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 22:30:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kurac</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 23:37:19</DATE>
    <TEXT> #3900;  #12388;  #9685;_  #9685;  #3901; #12388; GIVE BAN  #3900;  #12388;  #9685;_  #9685;  #3901; #12388;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 22:40:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bot got the vid wrong, here's the actual sauce: https://www.pornhub.com/view_video.php?viewkey=ph5b118269126a7</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 04:56:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or First Encounter Assault Recon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 16:13:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cant wait for July 31st</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 05:28:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>e</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 18:24:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Game over, man. Game over</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 21:53:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>K</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 21:54:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>E</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 21:54:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>R</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 19:14:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ovo je fakat jadno</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 19:20:13</DATE>
    <TEXT> #129300;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 03:17:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/2meirl4meirl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 17:54:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>3 days champion status?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 18:11:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Remember me~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This perfectly sums up my experience with Dead Air so far</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 20:45:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 21:44:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, hahaha I panicked</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 14:43:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Youre gonna have a really big fucking farm in a few days</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 21:10:06</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128170; #3900;  #9685;\_  #9685;  #128170; #3901; GOT FLAIR  #128170; #3900;  #9685;\_  #9685;  #128170; #3901;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 12:52:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, fuck me, I posted the exact same thing a couple of months ago and got 20 upvotes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 15:05:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Repost.fresco</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 15:59:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have already tried restarting the game and backing out, etc. But it still says the wrong amount</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 16:08:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nvm, it seems to have fixed itself somehow, probably was a server issue</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 19:40:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>And a thicc a$$  #129321; #129321; #129321;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>His face cracks me up</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 01:02:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anyone else experiencing A LOT of crashes and freezes this patch?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 22:50:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>During previous patches, I would crash probably 1 in every 20 play sessions. This patch, I crash every second time I try to open the damn game. I also have a lot of freezes during the loading screen to main menu when you start your game. I even had to restart my computer because task manager wasnt working.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 00:08:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, something got fucked up this patch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Just had my best scav raid ever, but it went horribly wrong...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 00:11:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was on Factory, spawned in with a pistol, and I immediately see a bunch of corpses everywhere, unlooted, no sign of players anywhere. I go loot, and eventually find a dead player with an AK and a glock. I'm only lvl 10 and have no leveled up traders, so this is a pretty big deal. I head to extraction and check out a scav that passed me. He had fort armor on. I kill him and rush to extraction. My heart is rushing. I never had a fort armor before. I successfully extract. So... what went wrong? You see, this update in particular has, for me, had a shit ton more technical issues than ever before. I only get to play 1/3 of all raids that I enter for the first time because the game keeps freezing and crashing. And you probably see it coming now. Right as I was moving all the loot to my stash, the game froze and there was no way it was gonna unfreeze, and even the fucking task manager couldn't help, I had to restart my entire computer. I know that all gear before release is temporary, and will be wiped eventually, but I was really excited to try that fort armor and AK out. They say the next big update will be mostly fixing the technical issues, and I sure as shit hope they fix the unbearable, and game-breaking freezes and crashes before anything else, because I am literally going to lose my fucking mind trying to play this game. Thanks for reading.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 01:19:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I generally dont like the meta in the game and these ridiculous crashes and problems only make me wonder why the fuck am I trying to play this in the first place</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>More music coming to the main menu?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 02:59:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>The music in Tarkov is incredible, easily one of my favourite parts about the game. There are only a few tracks, though, but Geneburn has made more great tracks that would fit the game, and particularly the track heard in the new 0.9 patch trailer. BSG should implement them in the game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:21:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I noticed that as well. Virginia Woolf stuffed her pockets with rocks and jumped into water and drowned herself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 03:58:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reminds me of that one face in the This is America video</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 10:24:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Poli #382; bi bilo bolje</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 10:27:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Polisi mi jaja" zvuci glupo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 10:40:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Makes me wanna puke too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Saw a body glitch near gas station and it created some kind of Lovecraftian monument</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 15:19:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cursed_tooth</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 15:46:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 17:24:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ovi mortadela memeovi su izasli van kontrole</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 11:29:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Polis vec ima znacenje u hrvatskom jeziku</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 02:56:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok, now THIS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 10:31:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really hope its as detailed in the final game as it is in the gameplay. And I hope it stays permanently, unlike the first game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 13:06:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gameplay was in 4K so it was definitely pro</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 23:33:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely not on native since it was 4K footage. Normal PS4 cant possibly run that at 4K</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 02:40:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>when u cant et anymore chcib, you will need to fard or shidd. trust me, it is epic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 02:41:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wanna be an actor. (Inside gaming reference)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Click here to unlock Ben Shapiro in Fornite (this is epic, no scam)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 02:46:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>troll_face.png</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 03:00:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Runescape 2 looks really good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 03:03:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shugoki is just boring to fight against</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 03:23:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Add an option to disable sound on hitmarkers and hitmarkers in general. That annoying sound when you hit someone from 500 meters away just breaks immersion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 03:24:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also, an option to keep the blood and dead bodies would be excellent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 03:29:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you get that nvg helmet?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 22:44:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im just gonna ask this here if its okay. Can we get an option to disable the hitmarker sound? It just breaks immersion for me. Oh, and no disappearing bodies option, please</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I dont think that's how parachuting works...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 02:57:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 14:48:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blood and bodies would disappear in the last of us, even in the remastered version</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My freind Brad said fortnite is betterer then call of duty and that is not true!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 18:55:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Who do I trust?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 19:10:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 19:26:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok, now THIS  #128526; is EPIC!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 04:06:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>/unrart whats the song name?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 19:13:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cummy, are you okay? Do you need to talk?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 19:18:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>What cargo shorts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 19:20:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was making a camo joke</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 19:58:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>*gamer walk*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 20:21:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please message if you do find out anything</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 21:02:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok, thanks, buddy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 15:57:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is some Mission Impossible shit right here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 04:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>This happened to me today in the exact same place</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found on a cursed image</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 05:40:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember that fateful day. I had decided to venture into my father's lab, a choice sorely regretted later on. My father was a geneticist, and was very keen that I not come into his lab. But I, being the rebellious child I was, didn't listen. Inside there were many different animals, including snakes, spiders and the like, but what interested me were the mosquitoes. He had them inside a large jar, where they were fed decaying flesh. I didn't know what they were being fed specifically, but I was curious. Unfortunately, I am rather clumsy, and knocked over the jar to the floor where it promptly shattered. They then turned their attention towards me. Although they had wings, they did not fly. They crawled their way towards me, until they reached my foot. Up my foot they went, I could feel their tiny legs scurrying up my body. They suddenly stopped once they reached my waist. I writhed in pain as they shot up my ass and urethra, I knew they would not come back down until they had had their fill. I could feel each tiny leg prick my anus as they crawled farther and farther up. My dick had swollen to about 5 times it's normal size as more and more mosquitoes piled in. Some went after my balls as well, drilling in and extracting semen. After they filled up, they crawled back out, and I ran to the doctor. He told me that there was nothing wrong with me, and I had imagined it all. Just a regular Monday night.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 11:34:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was in Age of Ultron</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 19:51:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Povraca mi se od ovoga</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I have no words</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 22:19:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 01:35:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>OMG he did not just say that, im literally shaking right now, im gonna fard and shidd</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 02:00:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>cammed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 09:18:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Done</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>One feature of Infernal Dominion I really like</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 14:24:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>The cuts and blood from fights stay even through respawns, so at the end of the match you're basically just covered in blood, it looks awesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 00:14:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, you dont</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 00:22:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just played a match and you clearly start clean</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 03:31:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post is fucking with my brain</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 08:40:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought because Gunn was dressed as Elvis that Rooker was dressed as someone too as he looked very familiar. Thanks for your answer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 20:18:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is fucking incredible</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 16:26:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Less than a minute, even</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rockets out</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 16:51:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 18:46:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you see that guy getting hit with a pickaxe a dozen times before dying? Or any cartel execution. Those arent okay deaths</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 00:48:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Second time activating Ansel, but first missile launch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 08:29:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>goddamnit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 15:59:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/2healthbars</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>No.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 23:10:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 23:10:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you need to buy the DLC to use these weapons in the main storyline?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can we please get bot matches in Battlefield V, or some equivalent of Battlefront II's Arcade mode?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 20:33:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would like to be able to practice and test out weapons in an offline environment with bots. Coop play in this mode would be nice but not neccessary. It'd be great to also test out destruction and the new game mechanics upon release.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 20:37:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, that was great. Shame it didnt return for BF1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 20:44:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really hope they do that, when was the last time we got bot matches? BF2142?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 21:04:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, thats at least something. Do you have any confirmation of that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 21:06:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thats just the coop mode. Offline bot matches are different</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>r/titlegore</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 21:48:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you see the Knights don't have 20 million units on the vultcano</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 12:00:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>