<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7830</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>F/20/5 #8217;9 #8221; [254lbs  gt; 211lbs = 44lbs] (3 months) I #8217;ve always been the heavy girl and I decided that needs to change. With a new lifestyle and positive thoughts, I hope to be in a much better physical and mental state as I reach my goals. I #8217;m not close yet, however everyday counts.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 18:33:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 18:45:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! Trying to more and more lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 20:24:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Abs and butt workout (with weights) everyday and a much better diet! Cut out soda, bread, etc</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 20:41:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pants suck!! Even still I have a hard time finding good jeans. You #8217;ve got this, you #8217;ll get there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 21:08:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most helpful would be drinking more water and eating better if I #8217;m honest. I used to have the hardest time getting through my water but I #8217;ve gotten it to a gallon a day. As soon as I stopped eating poorly I felt a bit fresher and could see the results. Hardest would absolutely be the food, though. I #8217;m a foodie type of gal and can go for pizza and brownies any day at anytime but I realized that if I want to reach my goals, I have to cut back a bit. I #8217;ve started experimenting with recipes and ingredients to make my faves, but healthier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 21:33:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I work abs and butt everyday with weights and drink tons of water. I try and focus on those areas most as that #8217;s where I wanted the most improvement!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 14:47:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>For butt, weighted squats, donkey kicks with resistance bands, step ups, and weighted hip raises are just a few faves. For abs I do jackknife sit ups, flutter kicks, planks, etc!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 09:14:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>You look like a new person, too! Good job  #9786; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>F/20/5 #8217;9 #8221; [254 lbs  gt; 193 lbs = 61 lbs] (4 months) FINALLY BELOW 200 LBS! I posted about a month ago and was about 211 and I am finally here! So much closer to my goal of 175. This page has been a great help and motivation. Thank you for all of the help! Stay positive  #128519; #128156;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 05:50:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 05:55:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s all in the butt and thighs lol, thank you! I have been doing the Keto diet and focus training on my tum as well as my bottom!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 06:14:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I burn fat really quickly, always have. The biggest thing that helped me see a difference was diet! I #8217;ve been doing Keto for the entire time and it really is a fat killer!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 06:55:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 08:09:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Keto diet and plenty of exercise!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 20:08:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got them at Marshals! They were like $3 lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 20:09:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! Marshals!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 01:50:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Challenge accepted  #129300;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 05:16:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Living in Utah I #8217;ve seen quite a few regrettable names, however  #8220;Rayce Carr #8221; has got to take the cake for me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dog attacked me when I went to pick up the food I dropped</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 17:36:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 04:19:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. He #8217;s a corgi.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 18:50:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had a friend in high school absolutely lose her mind when I said I was making crepes for breakfast. She said that I wasn #8217;t allowed to make them unless I was at least a bit French and that I was  #8220;abusing #8221; their culture. From there she threw a tantrum every time I, or anyone else, made any sort of dish from a different country. We no longer speak...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #9729; #65039; #9729; #65039; #9729; #65039;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 01:19:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 01:33:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>How could I turn that one down</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 01:35:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s all gooooood</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> #127826; #127826; #127826;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 10:28:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 04:52:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 05:45:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol, just posted it there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This family at target. The kids ran up and down the isles pulling out shoes, toys etc and the parents just walked passed it. Not to mention the two older kids weren #8217;t wearing shoes and the THREE toddlers were all screaming yet the parents still did nothing.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 05:53:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 06:04:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just don #8217;t be a shit parent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 06:30:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not in Utah my friend</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 06:52:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>EDIT **aisle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 06:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>EDIT *aisle My bad y #8217;all I #8217;m tired ok</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 07:07:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>If only you were there. I, along with multiple others, went and asked if they could use some help and got waved away and a nice  #8220;fuck off #8221;. Both parents didn #8217;t give a damn and weren #8217;t embarrassed at all. They just simply didn #8217;t care. I do agree with you, but don #8217;t assume they are angels looking for a saint either. After the electronics section, they were kicked out and yelled at the manager all the way to the parking lot. Some people are just trashy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 07:54:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>They were an Indian family but nice try</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 07:55:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I corrected myself in the comments okay it #8217;s been a long day lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>