<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7946</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Some incel-esque graffiti in a Uni restroom</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 21:00:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 21:07:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have dated 2 guys with asperger's, and they both struggled similarly with what you're talking about here. However, the first guy couldn't get himself past it and ended up pressuring me into sex much too early and I resented it greatly, which caused our relationship to deteriorate and collapse over time, largely in part because he was still drowning in self-hatred and seeking validation from other women even after I gave him what he wanted. You need to learn to be happy, and if you can't do that alone, it's okay to need help. But don't treat your relationship with this girl like she's just a way to lose your virginity, because if that's your main focus in this relationship, that's how it will come off. Then you'll alienate her and make things worse for yourself. Having sex won't magically make you feel the validation you're craving, and that's the unfortunate truth. You're gonna be okay, keep at therapy and talk to them about all of this, and be honest with your girlfriend. Good luck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 21:47:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>No no, girls are repulsive because they pee out of their vaginas and poop out of their buttholes and it's a miracle that normie cucks can still be attracted to them! /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 22:17:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah dude, pretty sure you're the one who doesn't know what the fuck you're saying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>College students trying to rent an apartment with fair credit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 23:25:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>So my friends and I are trying to rent an apartment and the best credit score among the 4 of us is 697. Should we go ahead and apply with our own information, or should we try to rent under the name of a family member with better credit?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 18:26:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 18:27:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 18:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh hey 2 of the 3 people I love most in the world. You're adorable and I love you so much  #10084;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 04:05:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep you do. Goodbye</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 04:15:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Super left" by what definition? Not agreeing with transgenderism being reduced to an inaccurate caricature is "Super left"?  #129300;  #129300;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 04:40:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a childhood/adolescent developmental psych major, I can assure you that children know what gender they are very early on. Kids don't hit an age during which they decide what their gender will be, as I'm sure you did not do whenever you understood what it means to be the gender you identify as. And as for the whole "underlying point" bit and the fact that most people being made fun of on here are conservative, I have full confidence that if the users of this sub come across liberal folks spewing insane garbage, they post it, because many of them do (despite what the ratio of conservative to liberal posts may be). I don't think people are cherry picking conservative crazies to poke fun at, I think they sincerely come across more of them naturally. It's not like it's a personal attack</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>They're bad at taking turns for pats, so they smoosh together and make a lil bun heart for attention</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 21:23:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 21:45:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>As cute as this may seem, bathing rabbits is actually really dangerous! Please don't do it unless absolutely necessary, and even then, there shouldn't be more than an inch of water. Aside from potentially dying from shock from being submerged, rabbits also have a layer of oils on their skin that get displaced by water and can cause death by hypothermia! There are plenty of alternatives to washing your bun if he has a poopy butt, such as a wash cloth or baby wipes. Bunnies are very clean and don't require bathing regularly, just like cats, so please don't do this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Help with a monthly food budget for 2 in Maine</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 15:02:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello! My partner and I are moving in together this June, and neither of us have had to buy our own groceries before. We are both in college and this is our first apartment, so we have very little idea of what food should realistically cost in a month. In addition, we both could use to eat healthier, so ideally, we'd like to be as healthy as possible while also eating as cheap as possible. Does anyone have maybe an old shopping list of theirs as an example, or suggestions for foods we can buy in bulk for cheap? Also, an estimate on what we're looking to spend in a month? As an aside, is a Costco/BJs/ Sam's Club membership worth it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 15:24:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 15:31:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bitch literally what. I'm a sub too and I have a porn blog on Tumblr that I post to and the same shit happens. Like it literally says in my bio "not looking for a dom, don't send me dick pics, and I'm not gonna send you personal nudes so don't ask" and for some reason dudes think they're fucking God's gift and they'll change my mind, and when I reject them, it's "well you're fat anyway; you're not even that hot; I just needed spank bank material so fuck you slut." Sorry bro, your dick is prob average and you're clearly a shitty dom if you don't take the .2 seconds to read through someone's post enough to see that they are not looking for a dom. A real, respectful dom wouldn't insist on being yours after you said you're not interested. His whole "I messaged the wrong person thing" is bullshit. And fuck him for condescending to you about the gb because who gives a fuck if he doesn't like it, he doesn't know you anyway</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 15:39:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Garbage people. I'm sorry you can't post what you want without entitled ass dudes hitting you up like they have a right to you or your body.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 15:48:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a fairly good cook, I loved to cook when I lived with my parents so I am definitely capable, but I'm not a master chef or anything lol. We both love Mexican food and Italian food, and he is a big meat eater although I'm sure that will change a bit once he realizes how expensive meat can be. Neither of us are picky but I have a tree nut allergy, other than that we're open to most things. We both really enjoy fruits and vegetables, which I'm worried might get expensive because they're more perishable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 15:50:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, amazing advice! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 17:29:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 17:41:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good point!! We tend to be disorganized so some ingredients might spoil before we remember to use them. I'll probably combine these ideas with previous advice, thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 18:19:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good idea. My mom has tons of cook books, I'll ask her for a few!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Two small babs sharing a big snack</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 00:59:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 06:33:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not ugly at all. Try smiling with some teeth, everyone looks better with a genuine smile. And your hairstyle isn't the best, perhaps it just needs to be brushed in these particular pictures but going to a hair stylist and asking for advice can help a lot. You aren't ugly, but you could use to enhance the features you already have. Nice skin and pretty eyes. I certainly wouldn't be offended or defensive if someone said i looked like you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 06:34:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also very cute nose</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 06:40:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're gorgeous. I let people get to me in high school too but once you escape this bubble where you're surrounded by the same people constantly, you'll see how little weight their opinions really hold. You're very beautiful and interesting looking (in a good way of course). Don't sweat it, you have so much time to figure out relationships and dating and hooking up, high school is stressful enough without worrying about all of that so honestly you may very well have dodged a bullet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 01:40:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Noo it's so much funnier this way lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 22:05:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>My boy Casper was suffering from some minor bun depression and my vet suggested a lady friend. I was hesitant about getting him a friend, but I am absolutely happy I did. Now they're both so happy and in love, but it took a while to get to that point (8 months) but it was very very worth it. bonded rabbits also live longer on average and exhibit more playfulness and intelligence! Overall, it's definitely a wonderful idea if you're ready for the commitment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 05:20:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love when these lunatics cite psychology journals/ APA backed articles that they clearly either don't understand/ignore the discussion section of. Also there's this fun psychological concept called confirmation bias which basically means you cherry pick information that suits your views but ignore everything that goes against them. Hmm. Funny how well versed these guys seem to think they are in psychology when most of them refuse to see a counselor in favor of "LDAR" because a psychologist isn't a plastic surgeon. Weird to discredit therapy and psychological practices and then cite them in your misogynistic rants about women. Oh, and nobody argued that men's issues don't need a louder voice. Nobody said that female pedophiles shouldn't get the same social and judicial punishment as males do. But NONE of those things mean that every single woman is absolutely privileged, and not one of those things justifies such a sad and hateful outlook on half of the population.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 16:39:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is absolutely adorable and so original, you'll be sure to brighten people's day! Just looking at this picture made me smile, this is such a cute idea!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>An abandoned hamster is falling into my lap and I need some advice!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 16:45:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>So a friend of mine lived with his girlfriend and she up and left about a week ago, moving to another state and leaving behind her hamster. Last night he asked me if I would take her, and of course I said yes, but I don' know much about hamsters! I have been doing research all day and I feel more educated, but I want to give my sweet unexpected new girl the best life possible, and so I have some questions! 1. Verdict on balls? I've seen conflicting info online, and I know balls aren't good for mice or rats, but are they good for hamsters? Everyone seems to think differently and I wanted your opinions! 2. The little girl is coming with a wire wheel, and I've read that wire is not good for their feet, so should I buy her a plastic wheel or will the wire be fine since it's only on the wheel? 3. I feed my 2 house rabbits oxbow food, will the hamster food from oxbow be my best bet for the hammy as well? I try to feed my pets the best food i can get my hands on and oxbow is the best around here, but if there is a better brand of food I am willing to get it shipped to my house! 4. She is currently housed in one of those brightly colored cages with a bunch of tunnels, and I've read that those aren't the best for her. I would like to get her a wire sided cage, and would love some recommendations of good brands/specific cages that would be good for her. (She is a Syrian hamster for size reference) 5. Is paper shredding an acceptable substrate/bedding material? At my workplace I have access to a TON of paper shredding and figured that would be a great way of recycling it, but if this would be unsafe or a bad idea I won't do it, just a thought I had! 6. Any general insider tips? I learned from having my 2 rabbits that there is tons of information that rabbit starting guides don't tell you, so if anyone has some advice that I'm not likely to find on the suggested websites, I would very much so appreciate it! Thank you in advance for anyone who has advice to offer, I appreciate it greatly. I want to give this hammy the best life she can have, and I'm excited but nervous. (Also as a side note, the pet abandonment laws where I live will allow her to be legally given to me so that isn't a worry). Thanks again!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 23:09:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 23:51:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh wow, thank you. I'll probably follow the advice above to get a playpen instead! Also thank you for letting me know!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 00:52:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for this! Rabbits are the same way with illness so I definitely understand. I already have a small/exotic animal vet for my rabbits who works with small rodents so I've got that covered :) thank you so much for your advice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Having a hard time making friends</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 07:35:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey everyone, I've been having a tough time making friends and I think it's because I am coming off as a downer to people. I've been very busy and stressed lately and it's making me feel lonely, so I've been trying to be more social but I've had little success and it's making it harder. I'm thinking maybe it's just reading very clearly that I'm in a rough patch, because I tend to wear my heart on my sleeve. I'm not totally sure. I'm wondering if you guys have any advice on how to make healthy friendships with people even while I'm not in the best patch of my own life, and how I can sort of disguise the negativity until it passes so that it doesn't put people off. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 15:50:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awesome, thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 15:52:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for this advice. That should be easier to do because I'm in college so there are lots of opportunities to do things like that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 15:53:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess just people to spend time with and hang out with. I'm not looking for a best friend, just nice people to be around</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Advice for starting keto with a history of ED and BDD</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 21:53:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey everyone! So I have been considering keto for a few months now, and reading through all of the struggles/successes of everyone here, along with the breathtaking progress photos that have been posted, I am rather convinced. However, I have a history of disordered eating and body dysmorphia, and my partner is not so convinced that it is a good idea for me. My weight has fluctuated since I was a child, and in my teenage years I fell badly into a pattern of disordered eating that landed me in some dangerous situations. I was my heaviest and most depressed at 17 when I started attending counseling in order to heal mentally, and now that I am 21 and have worked very hard to learn healthy coping mechanisms, I would like to start healing physically as well. My main concern is that I am the type of person who becomes obsessed with weight and measurements. I can easily look at someone else's progress and say "wow, they only lost 6 or 7 lbs but they look so much more fit!" while I have a very hard time having the same attitude toward my own progress. All of that being said, these are the specific questions that I have: 1. How do you know that your level of dedication is a healthy one? I know this is a difficult and more abstract question, and it might seem obvious to some people, but it is a very fine line for me. 2. Is it a bad idea not to track my weight/measurements? I'm having a hard time deciding if it would be better or worse to keep track of these things since they can be a potential trigger, and if anyone else has had a similar struggle I'd like to hear some opinions. 3. How might I convince my partner that this could be a really great lifestyle change for me? He's all for me getting in shape and having a more healthy lifestyle, but he is (understandably) concerned about me relapsing into my ED. Has anyone else had a hard time convincing their partners that this isn't some crazy dangerous diet, and how did you go about handling it? He's the most important person in my life and my main support system, and while I know he would never put me down or discourage me, it would make it much easier if I could gain his support rather than just his toleration. Thank you guys so much. Every single one of you is such an inspiration to me, and I don't think I'd ever have felt this intense wave of motivation to try losing weight again in a healthy manner if I hadn't found all of your journeys on this sub. Good luck on your own journeys, and thank you for helping me with my own.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 22:16:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for this. It would probably be a better idea for me to ease into it and go slow, thank you for the suggestion!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 00:06:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much, that's exactly what I've been worried about. I hope that you keep strong too. It's hard finding that balance between getting in shape and not relapsing and I'm thankful to have this platform to talk to others about it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 21:29:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, I needed to hear this. You're very right about not wanting my partner to be the one who catches the heat, and I am worried about that because I don't want to seem like I need a babysitter or that I'm a burden. I appreciate your advice very much and I will absolutely take it into consideration</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Every single time</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 21:41:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Where to buy Thai tea in bulk?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 02:21:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey everyone! I was wondering if anyone knows a good website to buy Thai tea from? I got Thai tea at a ramen shop and it was the best tea I've ever had, so I want to buy a bunch of it. I live in the USA and I can't seem to find it at a store. Thanks in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 16:23:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sweet thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Video idea: people who believe Australia isn't real</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 00:33:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm (21F) having trouble dealing with a mentally ill friend's (21F) personal hygiene</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 08:02:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>TL;DR: My friend has a personality disorder which contributes heavily to her having terrible, borderline dangerous personal hygiene habits and I'm unsure how to tell her how uncomfortable it makes me because I don't want to seem like I'm giving her an ultimatum. Her boyfriend is also sick of her habits and we are both at a loss on how to proceed. I have a friend Emma. Emma is my best friend and really my only female friend, which is partially why I'm struggling to figure out how to properly handle this situation with care. Unfortunately, her hygiene is appallingly bad and I don't know how to bring it up without hurting her. I'll go to her house and there will be fruit flies everywhere and mold on dishes that have sat in her sink for a week. Trash and bottles and cans everywhere. She has caged animals and a cat, and the cat frequently vomits on the carpet and she leaves it there for several days. During our earlier college years, I used to have to talk her into going to the showers with me (which she had told me on multiple occasions that she only does rarely). She has made jokes many times about how she never brushes her teeth because she only brushes when she showers. She never washes her hands after using the bathroom, unless I am there and I give her a look when she walks out of the bathroom and she goes back in to wash like she's a young child. She has lived in her apartment for nearly a year and I haven't seen her wash her sheets once. The list goes on, and on, and on, and on, and on. She acts like I'm just over reacting but her new boyfriend convinced me that I am not, because many of his complaints mirror my own. --TMI WARNING-- Once she started dating someone, I took the opportunity to mention to her that she needs to be showering regularly and cleaning her vagina if she's having sex, especially unprotected. She responded by telling me that she just uses baby wipes to "clean out" after, and I just couldn't continue the conversation anymore because i felt physically upset. I chalked this up to her maybe not knowing whats proper because it's her first boyfriend and the first person she's been sexually active with, but I know that is untrue, and that it aligns with her other bad hygienic practices. She has a history of pretty serious mental health issues that I wont go into, and her treatment (and her commitment to her treatment) has been sporadic at best. I love her dearly, but it's getting to the point where she will ask me to clean her disgusting apartment every time I come over and even though I know its enabling, I feel compelled to do it because 1. I know she has trouble understanding why it's condition is so appalling and 2. I want to be able to enjoy my time there without feeling like I am sitting in a landfill. I don't know how to tell her I don't feel comfortable in her apartment ( or with her touching me so much and cooking me food) knowing how dirty so many things in her life are. I'm afraid she will take it as a personal attack. Her mental health issues complicate everything further because I don't want to seem like I'm being insensitive to the struggles that she has. It's to the point where her boyfriend (who I'm not particularly close with) has confided in me that he can't take her mess and dirty lifestyle anymore. Please help, I really don't know what to do. TL;DR: My friend has a personality disorder which contributes heavily to her having terrible, borderline dangerous personal hygiene habits and I'm unsure how to tell her how uncomfortable it makes me because I don't want to seem like I'm giving her an ultimatum. Her boyfriend is also sick of her habits and we are both at a loss on how to proceed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 15:59:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you very much! I think the schedule thing is a great idea. I guess I was worried about coming off like I'm trying to "mom" her, but making a schedule together that she can look at every day will probably really benefit her. Thank you for the advice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 16:05:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a really good point. I have "jokingly" said to her many times that I have a terrible immune system and I don't want to catch something when I come over, but it does have truth to it. My boyfriend is really not comfortable with me going to her place because he knows how filthy it is and I'm sure he's probably thinking the same things you've mentioned here. I think I'm going to take the approach of distancing myself from it and trying to help her in a more hands off way, by helping her make a schedule and sticking to it. And it seems like from what people have said so far, I just have to be bluntly honest about her personal hygiene, so I have to draft what I'll say to her and hope she doesn't take it as badly as i think she might.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 19:24:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a very good point. I have told her before that looking slovenly at her job isn't going to help her get the full time position she is looking for, and she seemed receptive so hopefully that means she won't immediately shut down and be upset when I bring it up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Discovered in a donation bin in my college dorm! Who would throw this away???</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 04:35:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 06:50:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's basically a "I don't want this so if someone else does they can have it" bin, and whatever doesn't get taken gets sent to the schools thrift store and they resell it secondhand. It's a whole system, my school does it every semester. It's basically just giving other people stuff you don't want anymore</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Her name is Gigi, she's 13, and she will whine at you until you pick her up and hold her whenever you walk in the door</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 22:41:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 19:30:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is pretty normal, but I will say that if it bothers you maybe you should have a talk with her about it, even if its just "I'm having a hard time fully understanding what you mean by that." You don't want to become resentful, and having strangers on the internet assure you that it's normal is not the same as having a conversation with your partner. You guys are young so I don't know if you're planning on marrying this girl, but I've seen spiritual disagreements and a fundamental difference in religious practices lead to some emotional break ups. It's definitely worth sharing your feelings with her in a way that isn't trying to reprimand her for how she feels. If you're able to accept her devotion to her religion it shouldn't be an issue for you, but consider how this may make her feel as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"The Hate U Give" by Angie Thomas has made me excited to read again</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 16:44:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've recently been trying to get back into reading, so I've been going with YA novels because I've always found them very easy to read. "The Hate U Give" was recommended to me by my mother, and I couldn't be happier that I followed her advice. This book had me laughing out loud, crying, and so angry that I had to walk away from it for a while. It's the exact kind of book I wish existed when I was in high school as a person from a mixed race family. It is bluntly honest on both sides of the issue of police brutality in the US, and for me, it's exactly what I needed to read at this moment in time. The characters are vivid and colorful, the narrator has an amazingly clear voice, and the world in which these characters exist is so well painted and familiar that I could practically see the story unfolding as I read. I blasted through this book in a day, and I couldn't tell you the last time I read a book over 400 pages in a day. This book has effectively jumpstarted my love for reading again, so thank you, Angie Thomas, for your wonderfully relevant and colorful story. I feel excited to read again, which is something I haven't felt in a very long time. It's also being made into a movie which is exciting!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to dispose of photographs in a positive way</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 18:02:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I realize this is a weird and somewhat niche question, but I have some old photographs of an ex partner (I'm not in any of them) and it feels wrong to just throw them away. To be clear, I have no malice towards this person anymore, but my relationship with them was mentally, verbally, and sexually abusive for nearly 3 years. Somewhere along the way I realized that he is a sick person and I cannot fix him, and I got out of the way of his path of negativity and self destruction. Just throwing these photos away feels wrong to me. I'm wondering if there's a way I can dispose of them that will also allow me to wish him positivity and healing, and the courage to someday get help for his emotional turmoil and become a better person? Would it be unethical to do that? I don't want to contribute more negative energy surrounding my experiences with this person, and I really do wish him well. I just don't know how to dispose of something as personal as photos in a way that isn't steeped in negativity. Returning them is out of the question because, as much as I hope he heals himself, I do not wish to interact with him again. Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 02:54:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks so much everyone. I think I'll burn them and then send the ashes downriver</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Advice for a chubby girl with short legs who's trying real hard to be sexy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 19:03:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey everyone! I'm a chubster and my legs are short as hell (a family curse inherited from my mother). My boyfriend is a fit guy, which makes me feel this weird sort of self consciousness when we have sex. I basically feel hyper aware of the fact that he's more fit than me, and it makes me get this weird sinking feeling sometimes. He always tells me that he loves my body and that he loves my cushion, but i still feel weird about it. We have been together for 2 years and are very much in love and I never question whether or not he's attracted to me, and he often tells me I'm the best sex he's ever had, but I want to learn how to make myself feel sexier in bed so that I can chill out and enjoy myself instead of being worried about my body. I'm in the process of trying to drop some weight and I've already started a diet, which he seems hesitant about but overall he's being supportive of my choices. I just wanna feel more confident in my body during sex, and I'm unsure how to do that. Some advice would be greatly appreciated!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 20:10:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I literally already said in my post that I am so there was 0 need to be an asshole to me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 20:11:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was so uplifting and honest. Thank you for your comment and advice :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 20:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think working out and feeling stronger (not necessarily thinner) will help with feeling more confident for sure. Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 20:13:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is an awwsome idea, I'll definitely do this. I have thigh high stockings that make me feel fierce as hell so I think lingerie would definitely help. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 20:15:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also the fact that you said losing weight is an "easy" fix means you've probably never struggled with trying to lose weight sooo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 20:18:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to get into yoga!! I've always worried I'm too fat for it lol. I also think the fashion part of it will help too, honestly I'm realizing that I don't dress in a way that makes me feel like I'm presenting my best self so I will take that into consideration for sure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 20:22:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I knooow I know, I guess it's more about me than anything. He really isn't the problem I'm just so in my own head, especially because I want to lose weight for other way more important reasons so it all feels wrapped together</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 20:53:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, I certainly will :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 02:08:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Catch me picking up a yoga mat at Wal-Mart tomorrow then lol. Thank you!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 02:09:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hell yeah!! This is inspiring as hell</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 02:10:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oohhh a corset would be awesome, good suggestion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 02:11:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's wild too because I'm queer and I find chubby women super attractive, like thats pretty much my "type." Idk, my brain is weird lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 02:12:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love this, thank you  #10084; #10084; #10084;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 02:13:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good point. He is supportive, I think it's more that he doesn't want me to feel like I "need" to change</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 02:14:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thst last sentence got me, that's very true</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 02:15:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>He loves me plenty but thanks asshole  #128579;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 20:23:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey douche, here's a concept: you don't have to fucking hate yourself when you're fat, even if you're trying to lose weight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 18:06:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>You seem like an extremely caring, patient, and empathetic person. To be blunt, based on his refusal to acknowledge his addiction, let alone do anything to fix it, he does not deserve any of those things from you. I'm not married and I don't know how marriage might change the dynamics of things, but I know what it's like to be in love, and while you have said here that you are giving up and trying to focus on yourself, it doesn't sound like that's really going to be the case. Beating yourself up over it isn't going to help. You shouldn't be in tears every day because you've done everything right. Tbf, I would very bluntly say to him something like "your porn addiction has made it so that I feel like I have to prioritize your problem and your health over every one of my own desires and my own self-care. I refuse to allow you to drag me further into this hole with you. I want to be happy and feel loved and wanted, and clearly that isn't going to happen with you." You deserve so much better than this. Remember that. He is the problem, not you. Separating from him honestly sounds like the best option here, as much as it will suck. But you are becoming depressed because of HIS problems, and that's unacceptable. If he wanted to change or showed any inkling of interest in getting better, it would be different, but he isn't. Good luck, you are in my thoughts and I wish you strength to get through this. Remember, above all, that you are a good person and you deserve happiness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 05:24:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly I think you have great face shape for a pixie cut!! I think they're adorable, I know some people are reluctant to cut their hair that short but I think it'd look cute on you :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 17:12:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally I think you should start the conversation off by essentially saying "we've been together for 2 years, after all this time I love you and there is no one else I'd want to be with. I want you to feel comfortable sharing your life with me, and its important to me that you can feel 100% free and secure around me." Coming right out and saying "hey I know you wear a wig" could very well be extremely jarring and upsetting to her. She likely feels unattractive to herself for wearing a wig and therefore feels that you will also find her unattractive for it as well. When one of my close friends transitioned, she was very secretive about her increasing collection of female clothing and beauty products. She would hide lipsticks and mascara like they were contraband in her sock drawer. I offered to help her with her makeup one night while we were going out as a ways to say "hey, you're my friend and I love and support you no matter what." Making sure that your girlfriend knows this is important. You don't want it to seem like you're pointing out a flaw, because you're not. You're just trying to be totally open with one another, but if she's self conscious about the wig it may feel like an attack if you say it outright like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 17:53:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a ridiculous suggestion. If she was just no longer feeling up to sex, then sure, dead bedroom. But she is having a PTSD flare up due to trauma that HE IS AWARE OF and she is STILL actively trying to satisfy his needs in some way despite how triggering and harmful it can be to do so while you're having a traumatic relapse. This is abusive behavior on his part, point blank period. If she were dismissive of his side (which she absolutely is not and you are ridiculous for suggesting so), she wouldn't be attempting to give him sexual satisfaction despite the pain its causing her, which she shouldn't even feel like she needs to do in the first place. This isn't just a case of high libido and low libido conflict, and dismissing it as such is insulting to OP and her mental health</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 18:07:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a 40 year old man acting as though he is a spoiled, selfish child. Listen, OP. I am only 21 but I know what it's like to feel like you need to ignore your own feelings and issues to sexually satisfy a partner in order to make him happy. I know what it's like to say, "man oh man have I been in abusive relationships but this one isn't abusive, he's great 90% of the time except when he's not!" while simultaneously ignoring all of the times I've put myself before HIM, I've ignored my feelings for HIM, and I've allowed myself to let him get away with expecting that from me. I understand childhood sexual trauma. I understand abusive relationships. But please. Please listen when I and the other commenters here say that this is not normal or acceptable. Just because he is less abusive than every other man you've had in your life doesn't mean he isn't still abusive. You don't have to settle for a man who simply refuses to consider your feelings while you do nothing but consider his. He has gotten used to this from you by now. Being agreeable to a fault is a symptom of past trauma, and that isn't something your husband should ever feel so comfortable taking advantage. You're on reddit telling a bunch of strangers how you feel guilty for considering his feelings more than you have probably ever considered your own, and it's like you can't even see it. From one abuse survivor to another, it is clear to me and most people on this thread, OP. You are being mistreated. Mistreatment doesn't just come in the form of forced sex and physical blows. Having your partner completely and utterly disregard your mental health while threatening the security of your marriage because you dared to take a break from sex due to its triggering nature is abuse. Getting defensive and claiming there are no other red flags tells me that you probably already know there are red flags, even if they aren't yelling at screaming. Not caring whether or not you enjoy sex as long as you're doing it is a red flag. A disregard for your feelings and expecting you to fix his problems and always put him first is a red flag. I'm willing to bet that sex is not the only area of life in which he expects that his needs will always be met before your own.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 05:47:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>IMO, its very immature to be bothered by your partners sexual history, unless it involves STIs or unwanted pregnancies or anything else indicating that they are sexually irresponsible. If you're so insecure that you need to be the ONLY person that your partner has ever been with or else you feel slighted, that's a YOU problem, and its your responsibility to figure out how to get over yourself. Its incredibly shitty to be bothered by the sexual past of someone you care about, especially if you also have a sexual past that does not involve them. Frankly, unless it's relevant to your relationship, it's none of your business unless they bring it up themselves. Edit: I'm a female btw</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 11:34:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair enough, maybe it isn't for you, I just don't see any sort of reason to be bothered by your partners history when you yourself have a history, if its not because of insecurity or some deep seated issues with the idea of your partner as a sexual being separate from you. Sorry for being a bitch in my first comment, but asking essentially "hey, with no context at all for your answers, who agrees with this and who doesn't?" isn't the best way to ask a question if you want to actually challenge the way you see things instead of believing what you believe and allowing others to confirm or deny it as legitimate without any real input.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 15:18:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Considering that your post history contains posts in r/mensrights and r/MGTOW, I'm gonna go ahead and say it's fairly obvious by those two pieces of evidence alone that you're a misogynistic troll who is undeniably single. Anyone who doesn't believe me can go see for themselves. Quit your bullshit and get educated properly about women's rights and feminism you absolute minge</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 15:49:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, how believable, especially when you follow it up with the typical troll response of calling feminism cancerous because you're ignorant and willfully uneducated! Congratulations sir, you have certainly changed my tune, I am now 100% convinced that your long thought out posts in both of those subs with severe mysoginistic overtones were just ironic! Brava! Nobody is that much of a fucking idiot. You posted less than 2 months ago that you're single. And even if you were being ironic, get a fucking grip and stop fanning the flames of a group of men who don't "joke" about misogyny as lightheartedly as you're seeming to claim you do (which still doesn't make it okay there bub). But hey, enjoy hiding behind the veil of the internet where you can find other people to support your ideas through confirmation biases and have fun ruminating with all your other mgtow who wonder why they can't get women when they say shit like you do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 16:12:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never said men's rights as a concept are misogynistic, I'm saying lots of the people who post in men's rights are misogynistic and its, unfortunately, a breeding ground for misogyny. If that sub actually did what it's intended to do, it would be great, but it doesn't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 04:42:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Its too real" I'm flatlining omfg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 19:35:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a hard time orgasming while standing but I guess I could sit in the bathroom and do it? That could be a possibility</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 19:46:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have a stall shower which is the BANE OF MY EXISTENCE!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 19:52:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly not a bad idea, just make it super obvious and make everyone uncomfortable so that they leave me alone lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 19:54:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm super short, I'm only 5'2" so I would be all about a bathtub if we had one. The shower stall sucks and I didn't realise just how much it would suck until I discovered this problem I'm having hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 21:45:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the offer lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 06:35:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Woah that's a thing?? I never knew you could do that!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 22:11:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>The way he kept referring to masturbation as "it" led me to believe this was a teenager, so my disappointment was immeasurable and my day was ruined when he revealed that he's actually a socially inept fully grown man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 03:01:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>The problem here is not that she is autistic, "high functioning" or otherwise (though that wording can be insulting and I reccomend you be careful in trying to qualify the degree of "severity" of someone's autism). The problem is that wanting to sexually manipulate someone because you perceive them as being ignorant, defenseless, unintelligent or somehow below you is extremely troubling. If he were genuinely attracted to this girl and interested in her, there would not be a moral issue as long as she has agency over herself and is legally able to consent. What he is discussing here is taking advantage of what he perceives to be a vulnerability, and that's what the problem is. Fuck just talking him out of this, sit down with his parents and tell them what you've told us here. If you're still in school, tell a counselor. He is displaying the behavior of a sexual abuser, and that is not going to be dealt with by simply talking him out of manipulating this one girl that he perceives as unable to refuse him. There will eventually be someone else that he hunts out with a vulnerability that he feels he can manipulate. Good luck and I hope your friend gets help because he needs it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 06:25:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Oddly"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 02:06:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You look exactly like her, holy shit. You should consider being a Gaga impersonator because holy hell you could be twins</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 03:05:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had this exact thing happen a few months back. Cannabis has to be heated to a certain temp before the THC is activated so bun should be okay on that front, the tobacco is a bigger concern because of potential chemicals but one of my rabbits has eaten both a nug of weed and part of a cigarette (at different times tho) and he was fine. If bun starts acting weird AT ALL, call the vet. But it shouldn't be a life threatening, "go get his stomach pumped" type of situation. My little guy seemed completely unfazed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 03:10:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah dude totally. Shit happens unfortunately but it should all be okay! A word of advice tho, they will get into literally anything so always watch them around potentially dangerous stuff. They will immediately figure out what they shouldnt be getting into and try to get into it. They are worse than toddlers i swear lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Really proud of myself because I didn't relapse today.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 02:50:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been self-harm free for nearly 2 years (probably closer to 1.5). I have been going through a steep depressive episode the past few weeks, and i have been returning to suicidal ideation a lot lately. On top of this, my partner and i have been having some serious problems lately and we got into a big argument today. I got to a point where i felt so defeated by everything, and i started to ruminate like i always do right before i cut. I sat in bed crying, obsessed with the thought of the box cutter blades in my drawer that i bought for a recent move. As i was walking over to plug my record player in so i could listen to my favorite record to cut to, i had to move my guitar out of the way. It made me think about how long its been since I've played, so last minute, i decided to take out my guitar instead. I spent 4.5 hours playing and relearning some of my favorite songs while listening to my favorite album (Is A Real Boy). It was so cathartic and cleansing. I did something productive with the negative energy and it stopped me from relapsing. I know that things are still bad right now, but this was a small victory for me and I'm proud of myself. It makes it easier to believe I'll be able to get through tomorrow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>