<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject992</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Don't buy Salt and Sanctuary yet !</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 22:00:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know what's going on with the VITA port, but the game keeps crashing and in some areas is simply unplayable. Error C2-12828-1 happens all the time. So if you're thinking about buying, I recommend that you wait til they solve this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Getting DLC weapons/armor through revenants ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 21:26:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically the title, do you guys think that's going to be possible to get DLC stuff(weapons, armor) by killing revenants ? Like the Visitor's Dragon Kabuto ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Old Monk style boss.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-26 20:57:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm the only one who wants a boss like the Old Monk from Demon's Souls ? Controlled by the player ? Something like "The Ghost Samurai" that protects the X dojo or something like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>That's... odd...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 00:14:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://i.imgur.com/qc5OaCw.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A possible counter for "Sloth"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 17:23:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I was thinking that if we use Tiger-running scroll after receiving the debuff sloth, we could counter the effect. Like when we use Steel Talisman to counter the debuff of Carnage Talisman. What do you guys think ? Maybe that's a solution for the "sloth problem" on pvp ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So... about the Level 170 weapons ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 03:59:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, can we try to forge 170 already or we need to wait til the DLC is live ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"TROPHY - The Chosen One - Equipped +15 divine equipment in all slots."</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 05:04:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>+15 divine equiment... I just came...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Congratulations - Sloth is useless in WotD, you guys did it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-05 00:32:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>For all of you complaining "sloth makes the game too easy", "sloth is casual mode", "If you use Sloth I hope you die in a fire". Well, now sloth works for about... 5 seconds. I used to use sloth for farming, now I don't even bother.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"Deadly Eye" passive skill increase the kunai/shuriken damage ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-07 23:00:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>The title.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anyone knows how to get this item ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-07 23:41:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://i.imgur.com/Y6xNXCS.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Level 210 gear</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-08 01:47:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone know what's the best place to farm 200 ~ 210 gear ? Any mission that is more susceptible to drop ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Nioh - Become a visitor</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 21:01:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a question about being a visitor in Nioh(Random encounters), I'm from Brazil, and all the people that I visited and helped were brazilian(I don't know why). But for some reason the number of players has decreased and I don't find a lot of ppl to help(I need to farm glory after all). That's my question, the coop is fixed by country ? Like, the only ppl that I can visit are brazilians ? Because the only way that I could coop with ppl from other countries were in Yokai Realm(and most of the time they're just rushing and farming Demon King Revealed). P.S.: Sorry for any bad grammar. My english really sucks =/ Edit: My "matching area" is already "unlimited". Thanks "stealthcl0wn" for remind me to add this info.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>NIOH - Horde Mode</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 19:29:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imagine a multiplayer mode in which two(or more) players battle co-operatively against increasingly difficult waves of Yokais, and after 5 waves(5, 10, 15, 20, 25,...), you face a Boss(or maybe two at the same time). And difficulty would be something like WotD(or maybe harder). It could introduce clans too and in this mode you can acquire a lot of sweet loot, gold and exp and your clan score would be listed(just like pvp does). What do you guys think ? P.S.: My english sucks, so I'm sorry if there's any bad grammar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Follow the yellow brick road</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-11 19:17:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>NIOH - PVP Arenas</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-17 22:54:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you select the stage you want to play ? Like the boat one, or the Dojo ? Or is Random ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can someone please drop inheritable Damage from Behind</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-18 23:14:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>The title</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Arranje algu #233;m que olhe pra voc #234; como o Noblat olha pro Temer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-19 16:16:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>E agora ? Quem ir #225; nos defender ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 02:45:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ao meu ver, a pol #237;tica brasileira recente teve como topo da pir #226;mide PT(esquerda), PMDB(sentado no meio) e PSDB(direita) e na base dela os demais partidos servindo de "apoio". Ent #227;o a criatura que imagin #225;vamos na presid #234;ncia se resumiria a um candidato vindo desse "topo". Mas agora eu n #227;o consigo mais ver a situa #231; #227;o desse jeito. PT est #225; completamente queimado(mesmo com Lula prometendo uma volta a #237;), PMDB est #225; em total controle de danos(e o sonho do Temer de tentar um "segundo" mandato foi pro saco), e o PSDB s #243; aposta em cavalo manco, Vide Nosferatu, Picol #233; de Chuchu e Aspirador de p #243;. Resumindo, com quem podemos contar ? Quem podemos imaginar se aproveitando desse "cen #225;rio" que estamos passando agora, do brasileiro emputecido, e capitalizar em cima disso pra angariar votos ? Tem algu #233;m com express #227;o o suficiente pra isso ? Porque os que me veem a mente s #227;o do mesmo "n #237;vel" dos que j #225; est #227;o a #237;, Bolsonaro, D #243;ria, Marina...  #172; #172;'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Qual foi o ataque hist #233;rico(vindo de um adulto) mais escroto que voc #234;s j #225; testemunharam ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-09 20:26:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lembro que fui comprar um set de Legos(daqueles grandes) pro anivers #225;rio da minha prima, de fora da loja j #225; come #231;o a escutar a cachorrada. J #225; penso, "He he he... isso vai ser bom", entro e vejo uma criatura de pelo menos 1,60 de altura por 1,50 de largura. Junto de uma vers #227;o miniatura dela(diga-se de passagem chorando feito uma desgra #231;ada). Pego a discuss #227;o j #225; no meio, mas lembro que ela estava reclamando por causa de uma promo #231; #227;o e que queria "os direito" dela. A promo #231; #227;o era de umas bonequinhas todas juntas numa mesa e uma placa no meio dizendo "Bonecas 70% de desconto", o problema  #233; que a Gardulla the Hutt n #227;o tinha lido o "at #233;" escrito em cima dos "70%" e agora queria por que queria levar uma boneca com 70% que s #243; tinha 25%. Resumindo, entre gritos de "CALA A BOCA MENINA" pra filha dela e "EU CONHE #199;O OS MEUS DIREITO" pra funcion #225;ria, ela acabou indo embora sem comprar nada e ainda chutou um monte de bonecos que estavam amontoados perto da sa #237;da.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Aparentemente todo mundo vai estar transando  #224;s 7:37</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 05:37:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://i.imgur.com/ocTPZ8V.png Inclusive o Obama e a Ariadna pelo visto... P.S.: Esse algoritmo do Google nem est #225; tentando mais... cad #234; as mulheres gostosas que querem dar pra mim perto da minha vizinhan #231;a ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Alguma vez a pol #237;tica brasileira teve ideologia ? Ou foi sempre "conquiste todos os territ #243;rios" ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 05:49:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sempre vejo direita x esquerda, mas me parece mais grupos pequenos(mas muito vocais) tentando empurrar interesses e disfar #231;ando esses mesmos interesses como plataformas que possam interessar ao povo, usando esse mesmo povo como massa de manobra. Eu entendi direito ? A pol #237;tica brasileira  #233; s #243; isso mesmo ou eu estou sendo muito c #237;nico ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If you say so...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 06:29:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Someone recognizes this armor ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-24 12:57:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Seems legit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 01:58:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New Yokai Realm Missions ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-25 06:17:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I crazy or there's new YR Missions like Hyakki Yagyo and Restless Spirits ? I don't remember seing both in YR before the update.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Gold farming ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 21:19:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had 100 million before WOTW, and now it's all gone, god damn it soul matching it's expensive. Anyway, there's any good place for gold farming in WOTW ? Restless Spirits didn't raised the rewards for WOTW, so that's a bummer...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tonfa users in a nutshell</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 05:37:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Oh the irony...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 04:20:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.reddit.com/r/Nioh/comments/4oii9d/all_the_new_info_from_e3_in_one_place/ This is from 1 year ago, I was reading and laughing through the whole thing realizing how much the game evolved, then I read this part: "NG+ is being considered, not confirmed." LOL And here we are, with NG+++(NG++++ next DLC maybe ?)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Persistent little bastard...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 21:31:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I wish Team Ninja added a "Sort by +" option.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 08:54:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm tired of farming and having to select(block) all the +25 and above to save(for soul match) while selling the rest. It would be better if we could just select everything under a certain "+"(like, everything +24 and under that) to sell or disassemble.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Most hated enemy in the game</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 00:09:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is, in your opinion, the worst thing about NIOH ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 23:17:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Everything about the final DLC(until now)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-04 03:31:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ppl keep asking when we are going to see info about the final DLC. This is everything released until now about the matter. TGS 2017 - September 24 13:30 to 15:00 Nioh Special Program Stage: Live gameplay from the development team mixed with an introduction to the appeal of the third piece of downloadable content,  #8220;Genna Enbu. #8221; Featuring Yosuke Hayashi (director) and Fumihiko Yasuda (director). Source: https://gematsu.com/2017/09/koei-tecmo-announces-tgs-2017-lineup-stage-schedule</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Waifu Fighter - Here comes a new challenger</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 06:59:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Oh God, please don't... not another Water Level.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 17:55:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Best weapon in the game</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 16:37:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Revenants can use Quick-change Scrolls</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 23:50:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Let me tell you a story</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 19:54:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>-Player summons me(great, I need that glory) -Doesn't bow or any emote at all(Ok...) -Gets carried the whole stage(Scion of Virtue), he didn't killed or helped to kill a single enemy the entire time(WOTW). -At this point I'm ready to just pop a Yokai Incense and leave -We arrive at the last shrine before Sanada -He starts summoning revenants and walking in my direction("there you go bud, kill him for me") -I kill the revenant and do the "no no" emote, like saying "do I look like Ginchiyo to you? Don't do that again" -Guess what ? He did it again -I say "f*ck it", do the sitting emote and watch him getting killed by the revenant -30 seconds later he sends me hate mail and calls me a f*ggot -I love this game Please, share your best/worst coop experience so far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So... in which mode you're going to do the final DLC ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-20 21:38:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to rush through WOTE(or whatever is called the final difficulty) and play the final DLC in the hardest difficulty possible, how about you guys ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hitbox Porn</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 02:11:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>NIOH - Bloodshed's End New Pics(High-Res) - PS BLOG JP</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-22 13:28:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Go back to the shrine little bud</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 14:25:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Now I realize that we probably are never going to get these...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 23:17:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Abyss Mode - Live Stream</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 03:18:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bloodshed's End - Live Stream</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 03:33:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hey, guess who is useful again ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 00:33:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sloth, instead of slowing an enemy for 4 seconds like in WOTD and WOTW, the Sloth talisman now have the same duration as in WOTS. So if WOTN is giving you hell(f* you Otani Yoshitsugu) you can use that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>NIOH - Abyss Mode - Floors/Bosses/Debuffs Guide(Work in progress)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 15:24:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Where can I farm Droplet of Decay ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-28 22:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Title</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm feeling like a kid in a candy store</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 16:31:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>That moment when you realize...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 21:11:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nioh have more bosses than different enemy types. This game has around 30 enemy types(including all DLCs), 28 monsters and 2 kinds of human enemies(ninja, soldier). And 42 bosses(16 Yokai bosses + 26 human bosses). They really need to step up the enemy variety in the sequel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If you do that, you're kind of a c*nt</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 02:27:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the 3rd time this happened to me, I was doing coop in the abyss, helping ppl and all, then after some time I would be summoned to some guy who would do the 4 boat missions and when we were going to face the boss he would just kick me and the other guy out of his world. This happened with 3 different guys always after doing all the boat missions. What the hell ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"There are no plans to release a Nioh Dynasty Warriors" - Fine... I'll do it myself...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 21:14:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Has this happened to anyone else ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 02:56:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 14:57:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now I'm curious to know how this joke relates to the books.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 14:59:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.patreon.com/summertimesaga This guy is almost reaching another goal on his patreon page. He says he's going to hire another guy, try sending him your CV.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 15:31:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're stealing from other subs now ? Come on ppl... being racist/funny is not that hard...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 15:38:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I HAVE TO PROTECT MY IMAGE!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 18:53:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Patch 1.19 ? Jesus Christ, ppl are avoiding 1.20 like the plague. Patch 1.20 is the new Windows Vista.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 22:48:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or you can go to Way of the Samurai, kill Jin there until he drops the smithing texts that you need.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 23:03:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Again, get the smithing texts, forge everything you need as divine then transform it all into ethereals in the abyss by defiling it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 00:29:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>But now that you know he's not in it, isn't that also a spoiler ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 00:30:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know that the pixel art was supposed to be Black Panther, but it looks more like a pissed off black bulldog.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 02:11:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Sanada almost broke me That's what love does to you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 02:14:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do have a mic, but I'd rather throw it away than having to talk to a cunt like you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 05:45:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fixed https://docs.google.com/document/d/1c1xP5QOzmwpvnTidWkvqQRxgCWShLBKPyEyH_eOq2vM</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 05:46:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>And if you want to know which floors you're going to face Fox lady, here it goes: https://docs.google.com/document/d/1c1xP5QOzmwpvnTidWkvqQRxgCWShLBKPyEyH_eOq2vM</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 08:17:51</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Saying someone isn #8217;t in a movie isn #8217;t a spoiler. "Lady Sif isn't in T.R." See ? That's a spoiler. It doesn't matter if its about something that is or isn't in a movie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 20:12:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>310 WOTN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 02:20:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's how you get the dragon bronze armor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 02:21:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rozan Shou Ryuu Ha !!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 02:44:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>And then she got raped. Keep downvoting a joke, faggots.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 03:09:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now with 25% more glitches.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 03:28:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fernando, is that you ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bug - Boss health bar halfway depleted before the fight even starts.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 06:26:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 06:33:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>No you can't, Way of the Demon is part of the DLCs. You need to have at least one of the 3 DLCs to access WOTD.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 17:53:00</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Would I enjoy Nioh if (for lack of a better word, I #8217;m sorry) im not a weeb? I have cancer now, thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 21:32:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>They all finished the floor 999 at the same day and time. There is a limit to coincidences.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-30 02:23:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why didn't you made the "hat" a lighter shade of green instead of black ? Not complaining tho just curious, still pretty cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-30 11:02:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>And what really pisses me off about the abyss is that for some god damn reason you can't use the Daiba Washi knock down more than once against human bosses. They just roll back and get up instead of staying down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-30 11:04:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Auto Weak point Aim effect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-30 11:08:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I still think Sanada is the worst boss in the game, not in design or anything like that, but in difficulty, he's absolute bullshit, even worst than Jin. As a matter of fact all of the top difficulty bosses are humans(Maria, Date, Sanada, Jin, M. Samurai). I was glad when I had to face a Yokai boss in the abyss "oh thank God, its just One Hundred Eyes again".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-30 12:45:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>For some fucked up reason google is deeming our guide "improper" and it's not allowing sharing the file. Here is a copy: https://ufile.io/iw20y</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-30 19:54:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Ghost of Tsushima is an action/stealth open world game" #65279; - SP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is canon now</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-30 20:59:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is canon now</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-30 21:09:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 11:08:40</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;And my SO SO?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 12:03:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, I see. Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 14:09:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just reforge your gun/bow using umbracite(it's easier than trying random) until you get it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 16:33:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm 63.7% sure is purple.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 17:44:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's not entirely true. There are some examples of Cross play PS4/PC, Rocket League, Street Fighter V, Final Fantasy XIV, Atom Universe, Brawlhalla, DC Universe Online, etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 00:51:55</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Just bring us cole back sucker punch. If you really played Infamous 1 and 2 you know why they can't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 00:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Why did Second Son suck tho? Second Son is a good game, a solid 8/10. I don't know what you're talking about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 12:57:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>"You underestimate my build"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 22:33:57</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;What are your thoughts on this? I don't care, if ppl don't even consider playing a great game like Nioh because of something so stupid like that, well... is their problem...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-02 18:35:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well... the best bosses are from the DLC's, so that's that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 19:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not. I mean, if it was cross play, then yeah, I would be excited, more ppl playing together and all. But since it isn't, I don't care.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-04 04:23:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hum ? I don't get it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 02:26:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; this is Nioh so who knows lol. This sub in a nutshell</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 21:07:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I've been falling for 30 minutes!!!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 03:33:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>MARIA_XXX_NUDE_MOD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 11:11:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>This boss is a cunt, he already starts the fight using living weapon, Jesus Christ, you're already a boss you fucker, you don't need to get more op !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 11:36:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here, hope it helps: https://docs.google.com/document/d/1c1xP5QOzmwpvnTidWkvqQRxgCWShLBKPyEyH_eOq2vM/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 14:00:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://i.imgur.com/urpVnxt.png</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 14:04:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://bfy.tw/EsHA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 19:03:41</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;what kind of content would you like to see? Shitpost</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 20:59:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some few tips that can help a newcommmer: EXTRA TIPS: https://www.reddit.com/r/Nioh/comments/5pkicm/beginner_tips_and_tricks_roundup/ *You can increase ranged ammo capacity in the ninjutsu skill tree. *Skills that are passive are always active, no matter the skill tree/weapon equipped. *You can see weaknesses and strengths of enemies in the bestiary (when on the map), requires killing them to unlock fully. *Guardians give passive bonuses, "spirit" stat unlocks further passives. *Most magic and ninjutsu skills act as "free" consumables that buff/debuff/attack, which will be refilled at each altar/death/mission start - using the right weapon buff against an enemy with a weakness, can make a huge difference in fights. *Armor weight has quite an effect on your Ki recovery/usage, check the % when equipping, it changes color depending on "tier" of weight you have. *Spirit stones charge up your Amrita Gauge on use. So if youre having trouble on a boss and have no Living Weapon, pop some spirit stones and you've got it again. *Crafting new weapons/armor is the most economic way to gear up, save money for really special soul matches. *Dismantle items and selling the craft materials rewards more money than selling the item *Twilight missions are changed daily, don't worry about them if they are way over your level, can't do anything about it. *There is an enemy that makes revenants (the graves) autospawn, look for an monster sitting and playing an instrument. The instrument is their weak/crit point for shooting them. *There is a title system, and through that you unlock passive bonuses, remember to choose bonuses in the "title menu". *Git gud and learn to Ki pulse *and... FIND ALL KODAMAS ASAP, serious now, they help a lot with extra amrita or extra elixir drop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 21:05:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>PVP is dead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 21:09:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>The PVP was broke af when it was released, they fixed and balanced after some time, but then ppl didn't care anymore. It's a shame, it was fun as hell, especially the 2x2 PVP.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 21:53:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly, if it says "...using Axe" it's because it only works with Axes. =P</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 21:55:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know, you can try some NIOH community on PS4 or a facebook page and ask if ppl want pvp with you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 22:08:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know why ppl are downvoting you, you're literally warning ppl to not make a terrible mistake. Wth ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 02:54:04</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Thanks TeamNinja The New "Thanks Obama"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 11:17:18</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Yeah because TN are idiots and gave in to the whiners and made that idiotic skill BS That's not entirely true, remember when you could kill ppl on PVP using 2 kunais ? PVP was super broke, a skill based PVP was necessary, and they did both modes(skill and strenght). The problem is that they should have done it from the beggining and not released a broke PVP(maybe do some Beta Test or something like that).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 11:19:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why don't you just buy a controller ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 11:27:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>29$ in Brazil, not bad... it could be worse...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 11:32:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh shut up...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 11:36:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well... they're not wrong, there's a lot of waifus in this game. =P Joro-Gumo best gurl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 11:37:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good so far, It could be worse, Batman Arkham Knight for example...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 11:39:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>goo.gl/W2ZaVP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 11:41:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>We found our VaatiVidya, now we only need our Otzdarva.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 12:11:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 12:18:18</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Fixed a bug in which dropped equipment you picked up during a battle of skill would disappear after the match was over I'm more surprised that there's still ppl playing the PVP, I tried the whole week and always end up fighting the same guy(he was a nice guy).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 12:21:26</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Processor and core speed  gt; Ram (amount is good, speed is eh)  gt; Gpu (if it's OCed is helpful knowledge here)  gt; Storage device (for load time comparisons)  gt; Overview of graphics settings (resolution, low/med/high/ultra settings or what mixture like mostly medium/some high)  gt; Average FPS, with notes on dips and stutters And this is why I'll never try buying a gaming PC. Call "being lazy" or whatever, I just want to buy a box, turn on the box, put the game in and play the game. Edit: wow, I'm being downvoted only because I don't want to play on a PC. Nice to see how not cancerous the PC community is. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 12:29:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know, I also hope you enjoy the hell out of this game on PC. o/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 12:31:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you make a test for me ? Can you try gathering at least 6 enemies on screen and see how the fps goes ? Because this is what happens on PS4: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KQ8PgLnR3Mo It looks like they're teleporting instead of walking</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 12:34:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 12:55:13</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; You can simply ask someone with knowledge to verify the value proposal of the thing Or I can ask no one, buy a console, turn on and play. It's amazing how you pc players are, I never said "pc sucks" or "console is better", my only point the whole time was "I think consoles are more convenient for me" and you're already defensive about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 12:59:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a conversation about a game on PC and PC gaming. And in this case you can act both ways, the way jmrichmond81 did, with a polite and insightful answer or the way ppl on reddit usually do, downvote everything you don't agree with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 13:02:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please, and I'm asking you with all due respect, when* did I said that my box was "awesome" ? Even "good", "amazing", "bad", "terrible" ? Did I ? No, because I'm not a fanboy. It's just a videogame for me, a box that allows me to play, that's it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 13:27:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>First, thank you for your answer. Now, I understand what you're saying, that PC gaming is not a puzzle, and with the right requirements it can be easy to set up a PC, but that's my whole point, these "requirements". "tell them what you want", "the budget", "pre-install windows/drivers/steam", buying a controller(if you want), etc... that's what I'm talking about. You have all these "little things" that need to be done instead of getting a $399.99 box that will be ready to play. I thinks that's the whole point of a console after all, the convenience(and the exclusives). P.S.: Please, excuse my terrible english.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 13:54:43</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;No one asked for your opinion that's why you are being down voted. I... I can't even... that's not how... I give up...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 14:02:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's all I wanted, a polite conversation about PC gaming(because even that I don't have the disposition to try pc gaming, I respect who does), once more, thank you. What kinda pisses me off is that I had to endure 3 trolls and 8 downvotes for that to happen(still worth it tho).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 14:32:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly I don't care anymore. jmrichmond81 and colers100 were cool about it and it was a nice conversation, that's good enough for me. Downvote all you want, it's not like kharma is important anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 15:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was being rude ? I offended the PC community with the original post ? Because all I said was that PC gaming in my opinion had too many variables/options and that a console would be more convenient for me. This is not a rhetorical question, please, If somehow I was being rude to someone then tell me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 15:39:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's better than I expected, this port seems nice so far. And again, thanks for testing this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 15:42:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You explained in 3 lines what I'm trying to say in 50. I'm terrible at this whole "my point is..." thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 16:07:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>First, I didn't knew TN was known for lack luster ports on PC, NIOH is the first game I ever played from them. Second, I didn't shit on PC, I never said anything bad about PC this whole time, when I listed that first comment was to show how many things you need to consider when playing on a PC, GTX, RAM, CPU, i5, hell, I don't even know what half these things are for, and that it was to complex for me and more convenient just play it on a console. I didn't say it was better on a console, that it was bad on a PC, nothing of that matter. And the "jab at PC gamers", it's not a jab, if you guys start hating on someone just because he says "wow, that's a lot of stuff to consider when playing on a PC, I think PC gaming is not for me", then yeah, that's toxic/cancerogenous behavior. Half of you were cool and trying to explain how PC gaming can be simple and have a nice debate and the other half was trolling and downvoting.  gt;"Your post just comes off as "Ha! Well I don't have to deal with this on PS4!"" Again, that was not my intention, I didn't even that TN sucked at doing PC ports.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 16:08:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>So, how about it ? The port is approved so far in your opinion ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 16:24:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please, explain what was the PC negative opinion. If you're going to blind hating at least tell me why.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 16:31:15</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; PC is too complex. This is not an insult, it's almost a compliment. Not everyone can be a PC gamer, you need to know what the hell you're doing, you can't just dumb your way like on a console. And I admit I was angry(and wrong) when I wrote the edit, but I'm not going to delete it or anything(you can't just hide the shit you do). Anyway, I'm just tired of this whole debate, I never had a problem in this sub before and I love this game, this went way out of proportion. Have a nice day o/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 17:11:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>How can I choosing to play on a console means I hate PC gaming ? It doesn't make any sense. The most "negative" thing I said about PC gaming this whole time was saying that it looked too complex for me that played on consoles all the time and never had to consider CPU, RAM, etc. And that's not a negative thing, saying that on consoles its "easier" it doesn't mean that console is good and PC is bad, "easy" not always means "better".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 19:00:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is something that I always wanted to ask, if a game is released at max 1080fps/30fps on PC, can you guys mod the game to have a higher resolution/fps ? To go beyond what the game gave you to play ? I know that exist these texture mods like the Resident Evil 4 one, but I don't think its the same thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 20:09:42</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I never said you hate pc gaming.  gt;You're getting downvoted for voicing a pointless and directly PC negative opinion in a PC thread.  #172; #172;' I give up...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 11:29:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some few tips that can help a newcommmer: EXTRA TIPS: https://www.reddit.com/r/Nioh/comments/5pkicm/beginner_tips_and_tricks_roundup/ *You can increase ranged ammo capacity in the ninjutsu skill tree. *Skills that are passive are always active, no matter the skill tree/weapon equipped. *You can see weaknesses and strengths of enemies in the bestiary (when on the map), requires killing them to unlock fully. *Guardians give passive bonuses, "spirit" stat unlocks further passives. *Most magic and ninjutsu skills act as "free" consumables that buff/debuff/attack, which will be refilled at each altar/death/mission start - using the right weapon buff against an enemy with a weakness, can make a huge difference in fights. *Armor weight has quite an effect on your Ki recovery/usage, check the % when equipping, it changes color depending on "tier" of weight you have. *Spirit stones charge up your Amrita Gauge on use. So if youre having trouble on a boss and have no Living Weapon, pop some spirit stones and you've got it again. *Crafting new weapons/armor is the most economic way to gear up, save money for really special soul matches. *Dismantle items and selling the craft materials rewards more money than selling the item *Twilight missions are changed daily, don't worry about them if they are way over your level, can't do anything about it. *There is an enemy that makes revenants (the graves) autospawn, look for an monster sitting and playing an instrument. The instrument is their weak/crit point for shooting them. *There is a title system, and through that you unlock passive bonuses, remember to choose bonuses in the "title menu". *Git gud and learn to Ki pulse *Don't worry about builds on your first playthrough, but if you really want one, try using Red Demon Armor(More damage when enemy on fire) or Kingo Set(More damage attacking from behind). *and... FIND ALL KODAMAS ASAP, serious now, they help a lot with extra amrita or extra elixir drop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 11:32:29</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;so most loot are useless? Everything that is below purple gear is almost useless(not useless since you can Disassemble or Sell in the blacksmith.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 11:35:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Deus Vult, infidel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 11:36:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to be a swimmer like you, then I took a bullet to the shoulder and became a better swimmer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 14:14:45</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;since Abyss got boring after 3 stages running solo. That moment when you played the whole fucking thing alone(all the 999 floors) because you didn't even remembered that it had coop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 17:59:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>C is suicide in a first playthrough, your ki goes to hell in 2/3 strikes and since ppl can't ki pulse for shit in the beginning(me included) they will be in danger more times than necessary. B is good to go and A would be more than perfect.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 18:00:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Way of the Samurai - NG Way of the Strong - NG+ Way of the Demon - NG++ Way of the Wise - NG+++ Way of the Nioh - NG++++</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 18:01:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah... only the new "PC players" will have problems playing a game for the first time... Jesus Christ  #172; #172;'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 23:44:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's amazing how you're being downvoted for telling the truth, Nioh's(and Bloodborne) combat is better than Dark Souls, it doesn't mean that the DS gameplay is bad. Fanboys are cancer, Jesus Christ...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 00:10:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's the same on PS4, at least for me. Summoning coop I always end up with ppl from my country, only on Yokai Realm coop that I got ppl from other places.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 01:14:36</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; My kid makes my life worth living Jesus Christ... that's depressing, what a shitty life you have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 01:58:17</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;What is CTA? CTA = Change to Attack  gt;I'm guessing it means just changing the scaling? You're right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 02:18:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eat a dick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 02:27:11</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I thought like a car was going to blow her... #TransformerSex</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 02:28:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here ya go buddy, downvoted... bye o/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 02:35:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why that "smoke" looked so fake ? It looked photoshopped and I don't have any idea of why...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 02:59:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow ! That's an amazing comeback, for a 10-year-old autistic boy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 03:03:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>VOAT is for ppl that are too pussy to go to 4chan and too cancer for Reddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 03:07:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oww, that made me smile, thanks. http://goo.gl/Hz4MfR</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 03:53:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QZIR-eZdvGk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 04:23:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a difference between answering "I can't" and being a cunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 04:37:26</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;But also pc players have access to the new steam helmet And PS4 players get the Nioh set, golden Nioh set, First Sanada set + alpha/beta/last chance helmets. But I'm not 100% sure if PC players aren't getting at least one of these.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 04:41:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm loving the 500 posts like "Is someone else having [INSERT PROBLEM HERE] with this game on PC ?", it's great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 11:28:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never said that the world or level design in Nioh was better than in DS(still think Bloodborne has the best level design of them all). I only talked about the combat, the level design in Nioh is... erh... you know... ok, I guess...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 12:01:34</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;What does the kodama scroll do? You turn into a Kodama. That's it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 12:02:09</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;but approximately how long is this game with all of its DLC and difficulties? Campaign + 5 difficulties + 3 DLCs + Abyss + Coop + PVP? 900+ hours.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 12:06:03</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Anyone know of any spots they might be for those who own just the base game? Only by killing revenants(or if you have the japanese pre-order DLC).  gt;I would ask on Shinju but it doesnt look very active atm "I would ask on Shinju but it's dead af there". FTFY.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 12:56:24</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Don't know. It will be an advancement, yes? Yeah, that answer has "scientific" all over it... if by "scientific" you mean "condescending". If he just had said "Don't know", that's okay, but that's not what he said. So stop defending him, he was wrong, he's wrong, so stop sucking his dick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 12:05:05</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Hammers deal 10% less damage than Axes. But hammers deals more ki damage than Axes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 12:06:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is at the same time the best and the worst level in the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 12:12:18</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Of course it enables the neckbeards to play as their favourite waifus be careful not to cut yourself on that edge...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 12:15:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Are there any other exclusive items? +Nioh Armor +Golden Nioh Armor +Sanada(First Set) +Dragon's Visitor Kabuto +Fox Kabuto +Tanuki Kabuto</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 14:57:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Heh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 16:29:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>"PREORDER CANCELLED!!!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 03:29:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nue Mask, it's fabulous. Serious now, Visitor's Dragon Kabuto is the best looking helm imo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 03:33:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Unlimited Salt"... me dying to Sanada(WOTN) for the 500 time  #172; #172;'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 21:08:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>BEGONE THOT !!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 04:55:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate when Kintoki gets in the way and tries to "help". I'm always like, "oy mate, does it look like I need your help?  #172; #172;' Get out..."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can someone please tell me the name of this OST ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 04:11:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 01:20:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don't get any of that. Nioh set, Nioh golden set, 5 Nioh weapons, First Sanada set nor the 3 kabutos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 01:25:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you get the 3 kabutos ? Alpha, Beta and Last chance ? I heard ppl complaining they didn't get that on PC. Edit: and you can only get the First Sanada set as a rare drop in the abyss, not as a DLC bonus like on PS4.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 01:29:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>In the OP you were talking about the japanese exclusive kabutos or the demo kabutos ? I'm confused...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 11:13:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is how fighting a boss using Tonfas works: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=psYmX4n7RRA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 12:26:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>IT'S TIME TO STOP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 12:31:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's treason then...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 12:42:48</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Do you like IGN or something? No one likes IGN, but come on man, Kotaku is pure cancer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 12:59:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same fuck, different dick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 14:18:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gotta get back...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 15:05:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh for fucks sake, not again with this karma* whoring bullshit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Aquele momento em que voc #234; viaja pro interior pra visitar a fam #237;lia e perde toda a divers #227;o...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 16:42:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 16:44:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Voltei hoje de viagem e eis que encontro isso no quadro de avisos no elevador... eu amo esse pa #237;s kkkkkkk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 16:47:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, my english sucks, thanks for correcting me. o/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 16:59:56</DATE>
    <TEXT> #201; a primeira vez na vida que eu tive uma ere #231; #227;o e uma brochada ao mesmo tempo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 17:37:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone lost a hand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 17:42:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Don't upvote" Don't tell me what to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 18:39:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sua m #227;e no ponto.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 19:45:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Conseguiu e n #227;o conseguiu ao mesmo tempo, quando ele voltou pro pr #233;dio e pegou o verde acabou sendo detido. Se a anta tivesse ficado na mi #250;da e n #227;o voltasse mais aqui ele tinha escapado. Mas tamb #233;m, se fosse esperto n #227;o era bandido...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 22:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>leeching magic. Buffs attack but decreases your HP like poison.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 22:55:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Patch in 3...2...1...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 16:20:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>What you're talking about ? Odachi is one of the best weapons in the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 18:43:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Maria Dominator", gotta please the BDSM crowd.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 20:31:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can also buff your weapon with fire, it's their weakness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 05:23:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hanzo best waifu</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>For the new PC players that are trying "The Abyss" for the first time. I made this guide, hope it helps.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 06:15:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 20:45:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>"This shit game"  #172; #172;' Oh fuck off...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 03:46:18</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; It costs cracked cups? Yes, one per enter  gt; If I die, I lose item drops? You only lose the defiled items(gray items), you keep all the other stuff you got in the abyss.  gt;Does it save every few levels? It saves the last level you beat. So for example if you get out of the abyss after beating floor 134, when you go back you can start from any floor between 1-135.  gt;How does defiling work? This video can explain better than me with my limited english, hope it helps. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6-a-fTpG384 amp;t=1s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 04:13:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>You said you were in Way of the Demon ? To unlock abyss pass level 25 you need to beat(or just get, I don't remember) Way of the Nioh(NG++++)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 05:49:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Way of the Wise will get you til floor 20 I think, after that the next floors will be locked(unlocking when you reach Way of the Nioh by beating "Queen's Eye" mission in Way of the Wise).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 00:11:28</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;jelly Yum!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 13:40:05</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;but why? Butt why not ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 13:40:57</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;so cringey wow... be careful not to cut yourself on that edge  #172; #172;'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 13:49:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>HAHAHAHAHAHAHA I'm sorry, but... holy shit...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 18:27:48</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;and my god am I ever having fun! That's the important part after all, good luck with the next boss =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 00:33:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Troll ? Are you kidding ? Stone build is OP as fuck: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1kfNg5VqA_A amp;t=</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 01:39:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, you did. Now tell your former self to stop being a faggot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 21:24:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nioh's version of "Ima Firen Mah Lazor!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 14:50:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Instructions not clear, got dick stuck in Okatsu.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 22:21:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't want to be a dick, but what is wrong with your hands?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So... I was reading the DS3 Wiki today...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 02:44:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://i.imgur.com/rwm4Y0r.png</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 16:24:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Guts has previous experience with penetration" Wait... was that a joke about that time he was raped as a child ? Damn...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>At least someone is having a good time...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 06:18:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://zippy.gfycat.com/DefensivePoisedAmericanwarmblood.webm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>At least someone is having a good time in this game...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 06:20:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 15:49:41</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;passable port Oh shut up...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 22:33:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>What discussion ? You just said "the port sucks hur dur" like a dick and now that ppl downvoted you(because you didn't added nothing of value to OP's post) you're crying about ? Jesus Christ...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 23:32:45</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;The port does suck. It's functional and that's the best that can be said about it. I give up, or you're an idiot or a troll. The port works, it's fine, that's what is supposed to be, and TN keeps supporting both versions(PS4 and PC). I don't know what "sucks" so much about this game on PC.  #172; #172;'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 17:17:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dead Cells is finished ? I loved the demo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 19:23:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>1:33 Ahh, WOTN... when a fucking skeleton can almost 1HK you. Good times...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 23:38:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>My proudest fap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 22:51:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>And the funny thing is... Oda/Yuki is the easiest(not saying is easy, only the easiest) double boss fight in the game. Sanada + Masamune in floor 999 is pure cancer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-01 04:05:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be honest, the only good ost in the game is the Sanada theme and the Okatsu theme. Okatsu: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lpnx671RV9k</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 04:02:28</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;"STOP HITTING THEM WHEN THEY ARE PARALISED! I CAN ONE SHOT THEM!" ARE YOU SURE?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 19:33:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>1:47 Ogress: "STOP... DOING... THAT !"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Chalice Dungeon Level Design 10/10</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 00:15:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s8tmZ02K0FU</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 04:32:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had to kill two giants, one of them I tried to kill using the bow, that's why I'm almost out of bullets.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 16:22:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Taste like chicken</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 16:49:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't knew who Eric Clapton was. Then I Googled "Eric Clapton Drops Kid" and Holy shit...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 16:57:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Black Panther looking good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 21:20:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>If a Mission it's level 140, it doesn't mean that you need to be level 140 to do it properly, you're not underleveled. I was level 750 doing missions level 1000+. So don't worry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 22:02:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, but trust me, Level really doesn't matter in this game. It's about your build and your skills as a player. I remember facing Tachibana + Honda and dying 20 times before finally beating them. And about boss rush levels, they are there basically for end game farming, so don't worry about it now, go play the DLCs now and go back to it later.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 22:15:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't worry about +gear right now, trust me, I made this mistake playing the vanilla NIOH. Would get my gear +15, and in the next difficulty the enemies would drop +17 gear.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 22:26:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Aren't you mad that your taxes are paying for other peoples' medical bills!??!" This kind of thinking pisses me off so much. Is so dumb and selfish.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 22:41:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>+135 is the max I got, but I saw ppl with +137. Edit: Example +135 https://pbs.twimg.com/media/DLFQSqHUMAAzWfV.jpg +136 https://pbs.twimg.com/media/DLFRjgUUIAAKPSu.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 22:48:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dragon Flame https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=edLN6GISziQ Izuna Drop https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UEbKv4hCsAg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 23:26:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do Queen's Eyes(WOTS) and see if you can handle the first mission on Way of the Demon(by "first mission" I'm talking about Isle of Demons), by the end of it you'll already have better gear than what you would get on Way of the Strong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 23:32:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>And the sad thing is... it doesn't make a damn difference in Way of the Nioh(NG+4), even with a 320 +137 full armor set you still get 1-2 HK by almost every enemy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 00:41:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Easy, I just equiped anything that was better than what I was using and making sure that my movement speed was A or at least B. I didn't even thought about builds, +gear or reforging 'til Way of the Demon(when the first DLC came out).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 01:08:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus Christ... that thumbnail is nightmare fuel, it looks like William is going to rape my Guardian Spirit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 02:47:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like a VHS version of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 12:16:01</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;As a frequent user of visitors, I summon any revenant I see long the path I'm going to save a Yokai Incense just for you my friend. Can't wait to see you die. Edit: Nice to see a lot of ppl loving when a host summons every single revenant in the entire map for the visitor to kill. I think it's a dick move, but if you guys are okay with that, great!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 17:26:45</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; how often does this happens? In 999 floors, always doing at least 1 boat mission per floor I only found this room 4 times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 17:58:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only one being an asshole here is you. If I play as a visitor, I'll show you where the kodamas are, shortcuts, help you killing mobs and help you defeating the boss. But when a host like you start summoning every single revenant in the entire map for me to kill, I'm sorry, but he can go fuck himself. I'm there to help you progress through the level, not to be your revenant slayer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 18:36:07</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I summon any revenant I see long the path</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 20:05:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, it's just common sense, we play as visitors to help the host beat the level, not to be their private revenant killer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL that one of the Giant Crabs is chill</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 00:52:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HnxKdUmDJPA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 01:18:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oooooh I see what you did there...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 01:58:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, my PC can't handle DS3. Hell, it can barely handle DS1.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>After playing this game for 14 hours this was my first 1x1 duel, and it was really fun!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 03:23:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YJ-DXUUx-Ws Now I kinda understand why ppl love PVP so much, when it's not a gank squad against two invaders(I've been in both sides here) or some mess like that and it's just a simple duel, I don't know how to explain, but I really enjoyed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 03:29:57</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;There wasn't really a point to this post other than just thanking all you guys for being you. Keep being the little scamps you all are, much love. https://goo.gl/5Pyptp</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 04:22:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know who that is. =/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 04:30:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, thanks. I'll go check.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 13:05:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was killing the ones in the Catacombs(I killed 6 IIRC) because I thought they were going to drop some ring(like the ones in the swamp), them I came across this cool crab.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 04:07:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.reddit.com/r/Nioh/comments/60rji2/should_i_get_this_game/ https://www.reddit.com/r/Nioh/comments/751h4j/should_i_buy_this_game/ https://www.reddit.com/r/Nioh/comments/5t4oel/should_i_buy_the_game/ https://www.reddit.com/r/Nioh/comments/6f24ud/should_i_buy/ etc...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 13:39:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need to buy quick change scroll in the ninjutsu skill tree ASAP, it's literally life-saving.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can someone explain what the hell just happened here ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 23:13:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DEOX4P_X4Ig I was trying to lure those two dragon guys when out of nowhere the Wyvern just died, my question is... how ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 23:38:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol Thanks for clarifying this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 23:44:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nameless King - Dark/Fire/Chaos King of the Storm - Lightning</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 23:45:12</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;They wouldn't fly out to LA for just a 30 second teaser. HOLY SHIT Sure he would, the announcement is working as intended after all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 23:50:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Abyss Watchers... that boss battle would be perfect if it had a little more HP in the second phase.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 23:56:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>T H I C C</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 00:26:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>From $327 to $4.99 ? The fuck ? Did they shoplifted that skirt and now are trying to sell ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 02:39:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>So ? There was a meaning behind this or you were just being a cunt and not helping that guy ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 05:10:11</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Ahh Vaati.. Or some say LoreCancer.. Do you hear our prayers...? FTFY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 05:32:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Miyazaki: "What a pussy, asking for Poise in my game and shit..."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 05:33:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>B O I P U C C I</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 01:23:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit, this hammer is fabulous.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bloodborne - Chalice Dungeon "A M A Z I N G" level design 10/10</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 13:13:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 13:19:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you look closely you can see, there... in the middle of the fire where the poise went.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Amazing Chest Ahead</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 16:45:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 17:28:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>IMO the best bosses are in the DLC, no doubt about that. And if you think about, in all the "souls/souls-like games" the best bosses are from DLCs, Artorias, Manus, Raime, Sir Alonne, Sihn, Ludwig, Maria, Orphan of Kos, Gael, Midir, Friede, etc... And NIOH is no different, from my TOP5 best bosses in NIOH, 4 came from the DLCs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bloodborne Level Design - 10/10</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 20:20:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 15:40:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Patches</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 16:48:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh for fucks sake</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 23:25:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have 16 on me right now, is that enough ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 23:32:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where can I find you ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 23:33:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 23:34:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Done</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 23:37:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good luck mate o/ Hope the extra embers help</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 23:40:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, I just remembered, I have 29 CRE on my other character, do you still want ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 23:43:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok then, have fun on PVP. o/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 00:58:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, where can I find you ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 01:07:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there anything I can give it to you that you want ? Armor Set ? Boss Weapon ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 01:13:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you go to high wall of lothric ? I made a new character and that's the only place I can go right now to receive the items. Can you put a red sign next to the bonfire there with the password 1245 ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 01:16:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's it, I'm going to get the other character now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 01:20:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>+karma Thank you so much, if you need anything, please, just ask.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 01:21:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah... I was thinking about making the Twin Prince Greatsword, but I think the Lorian's Greatsword is better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 01:33:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, I can give you the Ring, I need a mule to give some rings and sets to my new sorcerer character, can you do it ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 01:35:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok, can you put a red sign next to High Wall of Lothric bonfire ? Password 1245</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 01:40:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>High Wall of Lothric is right in the beginning of the game http://darksouls3.wiki.fextralife.com/High+Wall+of+Lothric</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 01:44:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I saw.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 01:46:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry, I know that is a lot of stuff. Do you need anything else ? Or just the ring of favor +3 ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 01:57:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>+karma Thanks mate, good luck on your game o/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 02:27:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're welcome, but hey, you should really give the DLC a chance some day, Ashes of Ariandel wasn't that great, but The Ringed City is amazing, the bosses are 10/10.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You gotta be kidding me...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 02:55:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://i.imgur.com/IKKqkYa.png All this time, dying to those damn ringed knights + judicator when trying to revive Halflight and I could just do that faster and safer... fuck me...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 03:10:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>That Ludwig transition... holy hell that was amazing... and my favorite is the piano part on Laurence's OST.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 03:12:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>And just like Bloodborne the best OSTs in the game are from the DLCs. Gael/Gravetender/Friede, 10/10</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 03:21:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah... I tried that once, it didn't go well...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 03:28:28</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;For me, though, the overriding goal is fun. Miyazaki: "Fun ? In my game ? HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[PS4] W: Magic Clutch Ring H: Karma, Mule, Ask</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 17:24:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just need the ring to finish my early sorcerer character, can give you Karma, be a Mule, or give you anything in my other character, boss weapons, armor set, you choose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 20:46:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Umi Bozu is the easiest for me, wait, before you downvote me let me explain why. The arena sucks(you can fall to your death if you're not careful), if you don't light the 3 bonfires you'll have to face the small blobs, but the boss itself is easy. All his attacks are slow, he's extremely week to fire which you can cheese with a fire GS or that mask that spits fire and the only attack that is really dangerous(I'M FIRING MAH LASER) he takes 2/3 seconds to charge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 22:58:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can give you the Wolf Ring +3 if you get me a Magic Clutch Ring</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 23:03:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure, just drop a red sign next to High Wall of Lothric bonfire, password 1245</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 23:04:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll give you the WR+3 and change to my other character, the sorcerer one, than you give me the MGR.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 23:06:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can give you the Wolf Ring +3 if you get me a Magic Clutch Ring</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 23:18:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok, I'll put the red sign then. Password 1245</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 23:20:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your character that have the Magic Clutch Ring does have a red sign ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 23:22:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok, on my way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 23:27:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>+karma Thank you so much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 23:28:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, already got from someone else, but if you have a Sage Ring +2 I can give you the chloranthy ring +3 and the hornet ring.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 23:32:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can give you the full havel set for some soul stacks + karma.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 23:35:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 23:37:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, thats perfect</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 23:38:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Drop a red sign next to High Wall of Lothric bonfire, password 1245</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 23:39:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll give you the Havel Set first, and then go to my sorcerer character to get the soul stack, ok ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 23:40:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>sign is down, password 1245</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 23:42:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll get my sorcerer now, can you please drop a red sign, I don't have one with the new character</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 23:45:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>+karma Thank you so much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 06:40:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't have a PC(even if I had, the PC port of DS1 is cancer) and I don't have a PS3/360. I bought a PS4 because of Bloodborne and end up buying DS2 and DS3. I would love to play DS1 and Demon's Souls Remastered, this time with a good FPS. Not everyone have a PC or played DS1 when it was released.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Lorian can stand up</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 05:19:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rk6mzf240Ew#t=01m36s He's not THAT crippled after all</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 06:07:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, I loved the OST. Edit: Can you please put the OST that you use/make in the video description ? I really liked this one: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WL1vZB62i-0</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-17 07:06:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only thing that makes me sad is that we can't fight him at his prime, imagine fighting Lorian when he was all powerful, beating the shit out of Demon Prince and stuff. That would be amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I think I need an adult...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 18:56:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 23:18:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can already see the #MeToo going wild in the Mushroom Kingdom</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 23:47:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Just ignore them Mario, you have a princess to save"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 23:58:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>What happened to your best friend ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 00:36:47</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;That show is both amazing and fucked up in the most beautiful way possible. "Jerking off on a comatose girl" fucked up ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 00:55:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Add poise</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Team Ninja, I'm still waiting for these...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 02:45:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 03:10:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>New Lore, someone call Vaati.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"The future of gaming"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 13:15:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dark Souls 3 PVP in a nutshell</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 21:46:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dark Souls 3 PVP in a nutshell</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 21:48:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 02:41:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is karma in its most pure form. Remember the whole "fuck PC", "we are doing better with lawbreakers", "I'm doing the Dark Souls of FPS", and all that crap ? Yep... fuck Cliff Bleszinski</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 02:42:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's right tho</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 04:00:01</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;"Videogames don't promote killing- they actually kill! Find out more at 5." Fox News intensifies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 04:10:27</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I'm doing my best, damn it. To rape or to gather karma ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I always feel like the forest is whispering to me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 21:05:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 21:08:17</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;What is lacking in gaming forums/communities of today? Shitpost</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I always feel like the forest is whispering to me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 21:13:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 21:14:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure, but I think it has something to do with that weird dog that's on it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 21:15:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>And now we wait for the sequel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-20 21:16:34</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Bored of rap and how bad its got?  #172; #172;'...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 02:00:48</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Memes, gifs or general shite? Exactly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 16:58:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.reddit.com/r/Nioh/comments/65yxc8/check_out_this_awesome_niohsamurai_jack_crossover/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 15:15:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is a BIG difference between "this(port) isn't good enough" and "IMO Horribly"  #172; #172;' Batman Arkham Knight is(was?) Horrible on PC, PUGB sometimes is cancer, Dark Souls... Jesus Christ Dark Souls on PC... NIOH is an OK port(specially if you consider the rest of the PC ports of japanese games).  gt;Games that look better and are more graphically demanding than this game that I can run on high settings 1080p at 60 fps include  gt;Yes I have set shadows to medium, yes I have turned off ambient occlusion, yes I have turned off reflections, yes I am only running at 1080p. This is not playing on High Settings, try updating your gear...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Samaritans Christmas Message</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 02:47:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Finished The Christmas Message, boss</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 03:00:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 03:04:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love the fact that there's a fan of Nioh so talented like you to do these(amazing) shitposts. Thanks for the laughs man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 04:21:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>C R O C H E T H I C C</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 04:23:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bye Bye loot =(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The OG Barack Kodama</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-23 06:35:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sweet Christmas</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 00:56:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 01:07:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reddit in a nutshell</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 04:52:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe he's trying to compensate for something</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 04:53:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 04:54:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Pretty Woman..."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 05:02:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>And of course it's in Paran #225;, A.K.A. Brazil's version of Russia.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[PS4] W:Soul Stacks H: Mule/Ask(+Karma)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 03:32:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I need some Soul Stacks, I'll give you whatever you want, Karma/Muling/Rings/Weapons/Armor Set/etc</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 08:53:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>PWARGaming Nioh build videos R.I.P. = #180;(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hmmm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 11:20:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If you say so...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 11:31:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 11:36:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are trashy for having to warn ppl you don't fuck dogs. That's a big red flag imo. It's like your teacher showing up at school wearing a t-shirt reading "I don't fuck children".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 11:49:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trust me, he's not brazilian, I know(don't ask me why) every xxx brazilian artist out there(C. Ramos, Melkor Mancin, etc) and this cunt is not one of them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 12:02:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>God damn it, Brazil... why?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 16:31:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, he's at a Furry convention, so...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 00:56:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, and he's such a nice guy too, besides being a great artist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 01:00:51</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I come here to escape, not to be reminded. Reddit in a nutshell for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 01:43:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, I don't like or dislike Trump(I'm not american so I really don't care), so it's kinda boring when ppl keep talking about him every damn time. I even think that's one of the reasons he won after all, ppl kept bashing the guy so much, half of the U.S. started rooting for him, like he was an underdog or something, but that's just me, I don't know much about U.S. politics.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 09:25:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's amazing how you're still alive with all that salt in your system.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 09:37:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit, I know it's a bait, but... damn son...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 09:40:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QZIR-eZdvGk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 09:42:08</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Ryu hates Taylor. He's not the only one...  #172; #172;'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 10:42:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>And now we have count Dracula as president... fucking hell I love my country, but... Jesus...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 10:43:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good Meatbag</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 10:24:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's amazing how I'm the only one that you replied to, all the other guys asked nicely what you thought was wrong with the other half of the game, and you didn't say shit about that. Don't act like a cunt and when ppl start calling you out on that start playing the victim... that's just sad...  #172; #172;'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 19:59:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Patch in 5...4...3...2...1...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 20:00:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought Ohashi was the name of those sticks that we use to eat japanese food.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-03 20:10:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, I didn't know that, thanks for the info. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>IYO who's the best Crestfallen NPC in the DS trilogy ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 21:43:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Crestfallen Warrior in DS1 Saulden, the Crestfallen Warrior in DS2 or Hawkwood the Deserter(my favorite) in DS3 ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 00:56:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>And the funny thing is, he tells you he has no use for it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 00:57:04</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Nothing's hard to kill if it can be poisebroken. W O R K I N G A S I N T E N D E D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 00:58:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://conniptions.gives/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 05:49:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh Midir... It's amazing how much of a cancer that boss can be sometimes... and hello fellow BR.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 15:34:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;M A #8217; FIRIN #8217; MAH LAZER!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 15:36:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh trust me... she's not that hard when she's alone. Actually all solo bosses are fair, now Sanada + Masamune... Jesus Christ that's cancer...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 15:37:04</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Then I question came to my mind: is it possible to this boss appear on Abyss? No, you can see the full list of bosses here: https://docs.google.com/document/d/1c1xP5QOzmwpvnTidWkvqQRxgCWShLBKPyEyH_eOq2vM/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-11 16:44:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hammer time!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 03:16:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try using TNT next time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 03:27:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just play this while you watch the gif https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pfA5UqEU_80</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 17:05:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't do that, because it's going to be you and other guy against 3 bosses. Sanada + Masamune + Ican'tremember</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 20:10:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>DS2 have the best PVP and the best NG+ in my opinion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 20:12:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know what else is a godsend ? When midir fires the fucking laser beam parade and kill all the phantoms(including me) and I can see the host running for his life before the screen turns black. It's amazing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 21:50:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>God I hate that fucking boss, the only good thing about Midir is the Frayed Blade... and the fact that he made my Faith Build useful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 12:36:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't worry, the max is 3 bosses. 3x3 seems fairer. =D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 06:58:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://i.imgur.com/eV1Lj4x.png</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 07:14:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's funny cuz it's true</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 08:08:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or you can do a sith build and just buff your weapon with bleed. Done.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 08:12:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dragonslayer Greataxe, what a monster.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 08:14:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>3 after 10 hrs ? Lucky bastard !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 08:21:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's right, chaos scales with Faith + Int. One of the best infusions and one of the highest AR(Lothric Knight Greatsword +10 Chaos is a monster).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 08:33:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess he just wanted some fire damage that scales with int and didn't tried an optimal build.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 09:19:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you remove the Witches of Hemwick clothes ? You know... for science...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 09:24:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a pussy...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 10:03:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>By "all my Proofs" in two hours you mean "one", right ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 10:05:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>4(2With Axe + 2With Greatswords), area after Champion Gundyr.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 10:23:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 10:32:06</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; predictable and boring That's the point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 10:46:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mad ? Hum ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 10:56:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're really bitching about reposts on Reddit ? Come on man...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 17:57:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a fear in my heart But you're so supreme!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 05:02:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>How can you check this ? Can you share the link ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 14:17:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Well... at least he didn't tried using that giant tongue on me"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 14:20:25</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Also she's a goat. I'm sold.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 14:26:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>But he's right tho, undertale fanart is weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 14:40:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 02:25:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It wasn't "stolen", I was the guy that posted on r/DarkSouls3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 17:16:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least DS2 did NG+ right, even tho the PVE kinda sucks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 17:19:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's because magic in DS2 doesn't suck dick like in DS3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 17:36:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, Gael can teleport, so the space part is true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 05:54:28</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Easy come, easy go. that's just how you live oh Take, take, take it all, but you never give</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-20 23:17:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL Bloodborne is a Souls game and DS2 isn't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 05:47:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're in SDS, this whole sub is made of tired jokes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 05:48:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>W O R K I N G</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 20:35:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vi Car Amelia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 20:58:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everything</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Google assistant is sassy!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 21:40:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 22:41:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.wikihow.com/Stop-Taking-Jokes-Seriously</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Darkmoon Experience</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 23:09:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LxlMKg_x19Q I don't know what Miyazaki and the "A Team" were thinking...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Darkmoon Experience</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 23:11:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 17:51:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check the description of the video</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 18:08:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>The build is STR  gt;If it #8217;s not strength, why bother?  gt;Level. The. Strength.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 15:57:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Camel Toes Extra Salty!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When the Devil flips you off</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 22:19:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 08:07:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Listening</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>That Peeling Feeling - SH Edition</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 01:09:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 02:24:06</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Are you a fucking teenager or a retard? What's the difference ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 15:11:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hammer time!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 15:19:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>God damn it, Brazil. Not again...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 18:36:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>A "neutral" joke</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Now let's catch up to that truck!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 00:53:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 03:14:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>The mods finally stopped deleting shitposts ? Good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 13:46:16</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;third world shithole. Oh, Hi Donald.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-01 19:10:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brazil - 7.5/10 Would visit again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 13:48:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>"So... wanna hang out later?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"Congratulations ! You won an iPhone 8!"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 18:52:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 06:40:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, I see. Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 05:26:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>A Gif on this sub that is not META ? What kind of sorcery is this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 05:29:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I swear... I'll never understand how Reddit works, why you're being downvoted ? What was so terrible about your comment ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 05:31:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry who are you again?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 05:37:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>But what about a necrophile that only fucks dead children ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 05:54:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/jesuschristreddit/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 08:47:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well... at least the baby was already dead, so it's not THAT bad...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Wooderworld</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 12:38:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 12:52:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should be glad it's not a repost...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 15:26:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>We both know that's a lie. Come on...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 15:27:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 15:30:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh come on! That was on purpose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 20:50:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not if you go to jail.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 21:01:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow... aren't you the XxX!!!EDGY!!!XxX one ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 21:04:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cof Cof... ahum... https://i.pinimg.com/originals/20/23/dd/2023dd10112bdaf97a24a01695e0c282.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 02:13:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Congratulations!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 14:06:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Elon Musk did nothing wrong</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 14:16:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stopped working due to happiness</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 14:31:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Congratulations!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 14:45:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 16:30:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh God, what have I done? This was supposed to be just a shitpost, a fun thing, Jesus Christ Reddit...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Secret Subreddit Club</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 16:49:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The best specimen of an aussie</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 21:47:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>High as a kite</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 22:19:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 22:23:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm brazilian, can confirm.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mission Accomplished</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 22:27:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bear Insurance Scam</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 02:01:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 05:22:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>from my point of view the jedi are evil</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 15:55:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm brazilian and my english sucks. But somehow I could understand 75% of what he was saying, I don't even know how.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What happened to Ancalagon's body ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 19:40:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ancalagon was the greatest of all winged dragons, I mean, that thing was huge. In all fiction(games, books, movies) we almost always see the skeleton or scales of dead dragons. What about Ancalagon's body ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 20:20:07</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Never attack something that is not hostile to you. Lautrec, Patches, Pate, Navlaan, etc. There are a lot of npcs in this trilogy that should just die as soon as you see them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 21:14:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Blues" ? What is this ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 21:50:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've only met red, purple and gold so far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 23:08:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Playing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 00:59:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for explaining. So there's 5 colors ? White, Gold, Purple, Red and Blue ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Happiness</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 01:38:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Happiness</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 01:43:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 01:51:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>A tornado made out of porn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 02:29:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't worry, he's okay https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ygI-2F8ApUM</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can someone please make a version of Pray for Me without Kendrick Lamar ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 04:56:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kendrick Lamar ruins that song for me, can someone make a version with only the Weeknd bits ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 18:38:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit that's a sexy voice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 18:49:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hawkwood, a former AW, badass and a giant prick. I don't know why, but I just love his questline and dialogue. A well written character overwall and one of the best NPCs to summon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How can Halflight be using the Frayed Blade ?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 20:01:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a boss soul weapon, right ? Like...One-of-a-kind sword ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 20:20:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, I see. Like when we help Anri kill Aldrich in her world, right ? Every NPC/Player have his own world. But why do they hang out in our world ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 20:42:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>The NPC/Offline Boss Halflight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 20:47:13</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Is he a badass? Imo ? Yeah, he sure is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Inspector Niggadget</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 20:52:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 20:54:43</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; WTF indeed, anyone have a back story? Car went Super Saiyan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 20:59:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XFJAAMS8U5Y</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 21:10:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>based on a true story</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 11:37:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>This guy is amazing, great actor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 12:06:37</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; You don't know that it's Hundred Eyes until you enter the arena. Yes, you do. https://docs.google.com/document/d/1c1xP5QOzmwpvnTidWkvqQRxgCWShLBKPyEyH_eOq2vM/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Demonic child screams and runs through an 8 hour flight</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 23:26:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Made me smile</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 00:37:27</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I like my women like I like my toasters</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 00:49:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>turned on and in the bath with me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Walmart Sun-dress</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 00:53:11</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 03:55:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>"comment score below threshold" Holy shit, maybe he called the guy a cunt or said some crazy troll shit like "9/11 was an inside job" ~Let's see~ "TIL" Jesus Christ Reddit... I'll never understand you...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 14:07:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seu Madruga R.I.P.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>E...Ed...ward....lets..play</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 16:48:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>69</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 17:05:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Maze Pen</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 21:26:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 21:34:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chris Brown ? What you're doing here ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Floating Cup Pencil Carving</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 21:49:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>PIXAR</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 22:07:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Man Saves Puppy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 22:14:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Custom Made</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 23:02:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lawful Evil</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 23:04:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lawful Evil</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 23:14:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 02:19:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IdTzcp1YLY8</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>To destroy evidence</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 04:09:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 04:46:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mirror ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>speed bag at a bar, WCGW</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 10:08:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 19:22:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll probably be downvoted, but this made me laugh. Thanks. XD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tree Falls Over Kid</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 06:45:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thoughts and Prayers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 07:17:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 09:34:53</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; it's about whether lots of people are upvoting terrible content So... every front page in Reddit's history ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 10:41:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>womensicle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 11:08:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh shut the fuck up... if you can't take a joke just get out, it's not that hard...  #172; #172;'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So... this is how it looks in real life.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 01:02:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My kind of game</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 05:25:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 17:35:53</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;He had a high vantage point, 100 round Surefire magazines, and bumpfire stocks. His kill count could have been higher if he used a rifle chambered in .308 instead of 5.56 like a AR-10 with a bumpfire stock and X-Products drums. If he had used a suppressor, a bipod hard-mounted onto a stable surface, and did a better job hiding his position with camouflage netting he would have definitely killed more people. Holy shit! Mass shooting counseling. That's new.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Gaming industry lobbyists questioned about lootboxes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 06:20:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 01:26:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you trying really hard to be a cunt or it's just natural ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 01:40:29</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; insulting the moderator of a subreddit would normally get you banned My God... you're pathetic...  gt;how did you even enter this thread? It's been deleted I don't think so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 01:49:03</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;why the downvotes? You know why.  #172; #172;'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 04:39:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>CRAWLING</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 05:07:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>"this time only" ha ha ha HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA Yeah... sure...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>stretching</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 13:03:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 02:09:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amazing, here goes mine https://i.imgur.com/AECwQEp.png</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 02:11:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Frayed Blade, playing with it is so much fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 04:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kung Fu Panda: Showdown of Legendary Legends is the new "MASTAPIECE" confirmed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 18:25:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need PS PLUS to play online anyway, stop bitching...  #172; #172;'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 00:20:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>He was right tho  #172; #172;'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I hate when this happens</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 03:48:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://media.giphy.com/media/9MIccsE3tE8QlPMf0X/giphy.gif Every... single... time...  #172; #172;'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Everybody is doing sketch/fanart of Sister Friede, here's mine.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 19:53:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 07:02:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even piss is better than Brahma, that's a really low bar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 07:04:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're right, no butts, but here you are, being an asshole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 07:11:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Skol ainda  #233; melhor do que metade das cervejas no Brasil, infelizmente...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 07:43:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not yet!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 18:10:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really ? MM on DS3 ? Great fucking deduction ! We have a Sherlock Holmes over here... Somebody please kill me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 18:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I think the Glibglobgabgolab is supposed to represent obsession with non-Christian media. That thing has a meaning ? Holy shit...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 22:18:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Normal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fun Disney fact !</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 07:40:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Drag Race</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 07:53:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 08:44:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It sure is</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 08:45:35</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Why run from easy game? chlamydia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 04:59:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're not wrong tho</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Say what...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 05:22:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Still one of the best things to do in this game</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 07:23:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 08:10:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>My God ! Kurt Cobain is alive !</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 09:45:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>regen ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 12:08:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope that someone tries doing that on the PC version.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hmmm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 14:16:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>XCOM: Enemy Unknown - 99% to hit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 14:59:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 15:53:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ask TeamNinja, not me. I fought both of them, and they used the same moveset. =/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 16:43:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like something like this, you play the intro(like tower of london in the first game) as William, he's on a mission after Maria and he's with a small group of soldiers/pirates/etc, something happens, William is almost killed and Maria escapes, before William die he passes on the mission to defeat Maria to you(a random loyal soldier in that group/character creation).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 16:45:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL, no... Daiba-Washi is not the name of the guy, he's asking you, "did you used the Guardian Spirit Daiba-Washi against him?" The special move with that guardian takes down most of human enemies/bosses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 16:47:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here, take a look: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=elU6wxCk0WY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 16:51:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even the symbol for Dex is a hand like saying "STAHP".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tasty Soup</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 16:58:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If you say so</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 17:01:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>There was an attempt to clickbait</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 17:02:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Robot-assisted surgery is reaching an incredible level of precision</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 17:06:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Deepthroat</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 17:11:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>You can't have everything</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 17:15:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 17:20:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>If there is weaponized autism, why not weaponized gayzism</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>anime_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 17:21:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 17:30:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was way too specific</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Everyone loves</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 17:35:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 21:07:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>With a talisman</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 23:51:50</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Gonna need a bondage after that combo. FTFY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 07:34:55</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;a few times and didn't get anything Please, keep trying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 05:12:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Knight or Cleric</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 05:56:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was rooting for the train the entire time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 08:09:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope, unfortunately. Just the N64 version.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 08:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>My God... you're the perfect example of a "Hur Dur PC MaStEr RaCe" cunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 08:19:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have leukemia now, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 08:41:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't try it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 08:50:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kill me... please...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 05:18:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>LET'S BEYBLADE!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 07:06:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure if you're mocking him or...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 07:51:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>DBZ Circle jerk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 17:02:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>So... no GOT ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is so confusing...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 00:05:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>What we did in DS1 really happened ? I ask this because there's a lot of things that we did in DS1 and DS3 it's basically saying "nope, it didn't happened". 1)Gwyndolin was fed to Aldrich by Suhlyvan, but how ? Didn't we killed Gwyndolin ? 2)Ornstein somehow going to Archdragon Peak to help the Nameless King, but... again, how ? We killed him in DS1. 3)How the hell is Andre still sane ? I thought that if you go hollow for a long time you end up losing your mind. 4)How is Havel "Dwayne Johnson" The Rock still alive and kicking ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Oh Ignis...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 04:57:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Oh Ignis... come on...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 05:54:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>There are two types of DS3 players in this world...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 01:19:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The normal ones and the ones that attack Midir with pyromancies https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dhehg3MpElU</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Look! A dragon! Let's throw fire at him!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 04:31:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 05:20:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck EA, Todd Howard is a liar Never pre-order, unless it's a rockstar game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Infinity War Trailer but it's an ASMR video</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 08:21:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 03:55:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I don't want no nasty AIDS That's the spirit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 08:28:40</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;doxing will not be tolerated. Anything even remotely alluding to a witch hunt will be met with a ban. Oh suck a cock, this sub have ZERO moderation. Someone was dumb enough to post a suicide and you cunts did nothing about it, now that shit hit the fan you're gonna ban ppl for doxing? Fuck off...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 08:48:02</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;We have suicides all the time Oh... so you guys don't care that much if it's suicide... ok... but oops, someone made a piece about it... https://motherboard.vice.com/en_us/article/qvegg5/reddit-suicide-video "Quick, change the rules, now we care about a specific kind of suicide"  gt;Suicides that were livestreamed or filmed by the deceased Are you guys at least trying? This is a shitshow...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 08:55:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because this was one of the good subs, before the drama... and the mods trying to fuck each other... and the suicide bs... I love the "lol" at the end. "This sub is going to shit, but I need to finish my sentence being a cunt".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 09:05:07</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;The mods here get along fine with the cancer gone. I hope so, I really do. It's not easy being a mod(I get that), but it really pisses me off when ppl start with drama bullshit and getting power hungry just because they're mods. Reddit is big, but you can count on one hand the number of really good subs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 04:12:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder, did it ever happened? Everytime I see ppl making this assumption, but I have never seen an example of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 18:21:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know what's the worst part? It's a fun game. Not even "fun with friends", just fun overall. But the whole season pass 1, 2, 3, ... bullshit really killed the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 18:30:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Here's a video about how a Gamespot editor was "uncomfortable" with the game." So what? No, really... why you give a shit about that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 19:57:35</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; being an issue due to toxic players To be honest, tell me about one mp game that doesn't have toxic players...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 21:27:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be fair Aliens CM would probably be the most amazing thing ever 25 years ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>HOLD YOUR FIRE!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 07:29:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 07:23:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eu sinceramente n #227;o sei se esse v #237;deo foi uma piada ou um grito de socorro. Pedofilia, Incesto, Trauma... a turma toda veio pra festa... Que diabos Youtube, eu assistindo v #237;deo de auto hipnose pra dormir e voc #234; me recomenda isso  #172; #172;'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 18:10:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>N #227;o, ASMR n #227;o funciona comigo(infelizmente ou felizmente), auto hipnose mesmo, com voz normal. Tipo "feche os olhos, respire fundo, imagine uma praia, etc". Por incr #237;vel que pare #231;a isso me ajuda a dormir.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 18:13:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>E quem disse que eu n #227;o reportei? Agora ligar pra pol #237;cia n #227;o, pois n #227;o tem como saber se  #233; um caso s #233;rio ou algo pra chamar views.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 18:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eu j #225; tinha reportado o v #237;deo, s #243; que 1 reporte n #227;o adianta de p* nenhuma, se mais pessoas soubessem e reportassem tamb #233;m a #237; sim. Ent #227;o sim, foi uma decis #227;o sensata, e ainda mais sendo uma youtuber, n #227;o d #225; pra saber se  #233; uma hist #243;ria real ou algo pra pegar views, de toda forma o melhor  #233; reportar o v #237;deo. Mas  #233; mais f #225;cil ficar apontando o dedo pros outros como voc #234; faz, n #227;o? Meu saco...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 18:17:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sinceramente tamb #233;m nem sei, ligo pra pol #237;cia federal e falo o qu #234;? "Olha, tem um v #237;deo no youtube aqui, sem nenhuma informa #231; #227;o adicional, mas acho que voc #234;s deveriam olhar." Eu fiz o que pude, reportei e passei adiante pra mais gente reportar tamb #233;m.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 18:21:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Levando em conta que isso  #233; a internet, j #225; deve ter uns 5 mirrors daquele v #237;deo por a #237;...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 18:26:41</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Gostaria de imaginar, que poderia ser apenas uma personagem elaborada pela menina, que n #227;o foi realidade Essa  #233; a possibilidade que me deixa com o p #233; atr #225;s de "denunciar" pra valer, pol #237;cia e tudo. Mas foi uma hist #243;ria t #227;o bizarra e ao mesmo tempo plaus #237;vel que eu fiquei sem ter o que fazer, ent #227;o s #243; reportei e postei aqui(pra dar visibilidade).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 05:29:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KBKXu3Kg4yg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Far Cry 5 is a gift that keeps on giving</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 06:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 05:17:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a bunch of cunts, jeez...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 05:36:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>WOW, your dick is so big! /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 05:44:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why are you the way that you are? And by that I mean a cunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 06:11:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not all memes are funny.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 07:52:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll just gonna leave this here: https://vimeo.com/225558325</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 05:38:57</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Heck, the ending is literally  #8220;rocks fall, everyone dies #8221;. More like "nukes fall, everyone dies" amiright guys? Hum? Hum? I'll see myself out...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 00:14:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ninja build detected</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 06:58:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>and a new boyfriend, some surfer I think</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 07:15:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a brilliant idea to give an NPC a rocket launcher, what could go wrong?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Oh... come on...  #172; #172;'</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 05:47:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If you're going 80mph...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 06:01:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 07:46:05</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;we should suit ubisoft Don't forget about the tie too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 07:54:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus 2: Electric Boogaloo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 02:06:41</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Rework the harpoon gun into some redneck contraptions that shoots melee weapons for ammo A weapon that shoots explosive turkeys, come on, Hurk, just do it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>They did what?!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 07:33:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ant-Man saves the day</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 07:51:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 01:33:55</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Who here agrees with me? So... you're looking for validation? I'm sorry, I don't agree. Even if it's a "movie parody style" it doesn't mean it will be "shitty", only different. I play videogames for fun, to laugh, I like jokes, I don't want any of this "gritty and dark" stuff in my games, but that's me.  gt;FC5's setting and story was very dark (probably the darkest Far Cry even) You never played FC2, right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 01:45:50</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;you started it Jesus fucking Christ... it's elementary school all over again...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 01:50:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not OP, but yes, more than one weapon confirmed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 19:57:42</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I #8217;m totally the idiot here Hum... At least he is self-aware...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 07:07:06</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;The best subs are well moderated Yeah... that's bullshit. r/pics and r/funny are well moderated and both are basically cancer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 16:36:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Accurate</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 05:33:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 21:13:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you please help me, I killed 11 wolves for this week live event, the game registered the 11 kills, I even got the silver bars, but for some reason I didn't get the shovel launcher, what's going on?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The live event is glitched... again...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 21:17:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can someone please help me, I killed 11 wolves for this week live event, the game registered the 11 kills, I even got the silver bars, but for some reason I didn't get the shovel launcher, what's going on? It's the second time this happens to me =(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 21:48:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>26 wolves killed now according to the game progress bar, I give up. =/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 22:17:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Huh... mine is glitched and doesn't unlock, I already killed 26 wolves, even got the silver bars, but not the shovel launcher =/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 22:18:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you killing then with bow and arrow?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 23:52:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes =/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 05:20:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can do the whole thing in 2 minutes, I fucking timed...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 08:54:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a fucking lie and you know it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 09:32:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Name?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 17:20:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Please, do not post spoilers on a NG+ thread"... the fuck...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 01:42:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Karma? Likes? I don't know, people lied for less then that. Not saying he's lying, just stating that ppl lie.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 01:43:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's how he got AIDS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Horny</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 00:06:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 03:13:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 04:39:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh fuck off...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 16:04:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder, does it matter? The downvotes? Like, if you get downvoted enough you go back to zero karma or something like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 13:36:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>down there actually</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 13:53:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/iamverysmart</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 00:36:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh the irony...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 02:14:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Better than The Last Jedi at least...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 02:22:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Praise Geraldo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 02:57:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/ChoosingBeggars with a little bit of r/niceguys</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 03:02:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll never understand why americans throw money away, even if it's a dime, it's still money, put it in a piggybank or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 07:15:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok... wth...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>hmmm</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 05:35:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 19:05:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're doing this now? First was the "look at my family", then the "I was fat, give me upvotes", now is just random celebs pics? Fuck me this sub is going down hill...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 19:07:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Better than what I was thinking...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 19:09:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>AHHH! Too much quality for a gif! What the hell is happening?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 20:43:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;But no, this pic of a girl smiling has the sub going down hill. It's not "this" one picture, I literally listed all the other shitposts that are spoiling the sub. That one with Donald Glover and now this just points out the circlejerk on this sub.  gt;Get off Reddit every once in a while. https://i.imgur.com/rl4YiAI.gif</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 15:41:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>New copypasta?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 15:56:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>For my lady's painting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 16:19:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>On his bed waiting for him</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What, still here?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 16:23:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 16:28:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>So... a lesbian?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 16:29:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let's find out, cut your dick off, then tell me how you feel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 16:33:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know man... it's actually pretty good so far... I've seen worse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 19:53:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why you're being downvoted? Reddit is just becoming facebook, and I'm not talking about the new layout...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 19:57:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>So... no more random celebs pics? We're doing just random dogs now? That's it, I'm going to r/itookapicture, fuck this sub... Oh for fucks sake... it's even a repost...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 20:03:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>But at the same time is spreading cancer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 01:51:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>How is bringing up masturbation irrelevant when talking about Louis C.K.?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 06:10:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>HERE COMES THE MONEY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 06:13:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Death... by alcohol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 16:23:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean... who does that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 16:36:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh... shut the fuck up...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 16:54:52</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;derailed the conversation Oh for fucks sake...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 05:53:23</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Think T_D with no limits Since when T_D has limits?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 15:39:46</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;a few times That's an understatement...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 15:51:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're kind of a cunt, hum?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 18:39:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're lying Morgan!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 15:30:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>THEN YOU ARE RIGHT!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 18:32:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>He got downvoted because this sub is a circle jerk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 20:14:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe she's Legion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 04:32:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus Christ... In every sport ppl do that, use drugs, deflate balls, fake injuries, kill the referee, of course is not acceptable, but that's the world we live in... stop bitching about it...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 16:35:46</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Did I hit a nerve? No... you're just being a cunt... But that's ok, you have the right to be a cunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 16:36:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Delicious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 00:09:23</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Nioh's combat is incredibly shallow though. Hum? Did you really played Nioh? The whole skill, GS, Stance, system is everything but shallow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 00:21:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't wait for the 9000 Mudkips edition</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 06:46:47</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;There's little to no replayability. HaHaHahahahahaha Ok bud... The best NG+ in any "souls-like" game, loot, PVP, COOP, Abyss Mode, etc... "No replayability", what a funny guy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 17:34:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>The fat boss is using an Odachi(my favorite Nioh weapon) at least.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 17:37:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really hate open world games, interconected stages like Bloodborne/DS1 are way better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 04:53:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I crazy or there was a memo in RE1 or RE2 about a rat telling his story? About how he was surviving the zombies and stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 05:04:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nioh 2: Kill Maria</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 05:07:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't care as long as we keep getting Nioh. The Last Ninja Gaiden was terrible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 05:08:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, a lot of people did, wtf you're on about?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 05:16:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope they don't change the GS system, I like my NiohPets collection.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 07:31:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>She also goes by "Left"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 03:59:57</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;girls But he is a dude =\</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 13:33:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a hostile world, now get your gun and go!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 18:54:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>52 dv for a "nah"? Jesus Christ... the sub is cancer...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 22:56:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>IT'S OVER ANAKIN!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 23:52:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you explain what happens if Ellie kisses or have sex with someone? Like, she will infect that person?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 15:15:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not yet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 15:19:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even the political ones</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 16:02:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Disney have "fuck the world" money, if Comcast wins it's all on Disney for not giving a better counter-offer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 23:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Monopoly? It's all Marvel characters, they should all belong to Disney. It's not like Disney is trying to buy the Justice League.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 17:32:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Get the hell out of here with this reasonable shit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 20:45:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah... but nobody gives a shit about the rest...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 05:39:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Delicious actually.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 14:47:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mr. Neymar, 1x1 doesn't feel so good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 20:45:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah...but it's a sad chuckle, like when an old lady falls over a cat or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 02:47:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Jesus Christ... that's Jesus Christ!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 04:46:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Disney to Comcast: "aha, you're trying to fuck with me? Aha"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 21:42:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tomatoes potatoes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:35:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>And then we have the garbage PC ports like the OG Dark Souls, Batman Arkhan Knight, Nier Automata, etc. PC gaming is fine, but it has it's problems like everything else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 18:38:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus Christ... this shit was cringe...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 16:12:14</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;dude I thought it was a thot in the picture.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 16:14:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, that ghost lady at the window took me a while to see.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 14:12:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reminded me of this https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=S-ESYSGxK5g</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 14:56:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>So... we can conclude that everyone with herpes likes DC movies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 15:01:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Allowing Ben Affleck to become Batman was the first mistake, don't get me wrong, the guy is brutal as Batman(God I love the warehouse scene), but that whole "old, tired and killer Batman" was a BAD idea for the beggining off a Cinematic Universe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 15:04:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really hate CB's Batman(Bruce Wayne is fine tho)... I like the movies and the world, but I hate how bad Batman is as a fighter and strategist in those movies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 15:08:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you tried using Benadryl?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 15:25:40</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Bloodborne is not a more complete game than GoW but for some reason It has a large cult following.  gt;...some reason Yeah... I'm not falling for that bait...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 15:37:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know... I always hated snow levels. Imagine an entire game like that. By the way did you played FC4 DLC?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:10:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Didn't he draw... Yes  gt;...porn It wasn't porn. And that "youtuber", was Keemstar, also known as "cancer".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:30:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's no "interpretation" with Bloodborne's lore. You don't even need to watch a video, just read. But ppl are so lazy and "hur where's muh 5min cinematic", that every other way to tell a story becomes bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:34:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I care more for poor Gehrman than for Atreus/Kratos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 21:59:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't want to see another Silver Knight... all that farming, never again...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 06:15:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something lile the Abyss in Nioh. Fight some enemies in stages and then a boss at the end of the floor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 14:39:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dark Souls 2 fist weapons karate moveset with flying kicks and everything</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 18:09:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks like you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 18:57:02</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;You had a point? What was it? That you are a cunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 19:00:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's an idiot that does stupid shit, the mofo doesn't even know how to do a hand shake for fucks sake, of course ppl are going to make fun of him on the internet, wtf are you on about? He's an endless source of jokes/memes, is not "hating Trump", is just laughing at an idiot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 20:30:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol, I'm not american, I don't give a shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 20:53:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I choose both. You were acting like a cunt and I don't care if Trump wins or loses 2020.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 14:15:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ronaldo "I didn't knew she was a tranny" Naz #225;rio</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 14:19:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because it was funny, that's why.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 14:57:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>rated comment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 15:07:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>No exclusives = No consoles No consoles = No competition No competition = Less good/great games(aka exclusives like God of War or Zelda BOTW) I love this utopia that PC gamers spill about "consoles are evil", "exclusives shouldn't exist"... oh for fucks sake... shut up...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 15:12:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same on PS4, I bought FC5, God of War and Detroit(all first day) with 20% coupons that Sony gave.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 15:14:07</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; There should be a progression to this "meme". (?). This meme should just die. It's not funny and doesn't help anyone, console gamers won't care/change their playing style and PC gamers just look like elitist cunts because of this shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 15:15:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/woosh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 15:33:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Platform has very little to do with pushing competition between game developers, as many develop games to be used on multiple platforms in the first place. I don #8217;t know where you got that idea from. I'm sorry, I can't hear your bullshit over my Bayonetta 2 gameplay, a game that wouldn't exist if it wasn't for console competition.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 17:18:20</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;But can you honestly tell me why you don #8217;t think gaming on a pc is better? Can I play Bloodborne or Super Mario Odyssey on a PC? No? Ok, so that's my only reason why gaming on a console is better for me, the only thing that really matters, games.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 17:21:38</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Entry level is $400-$600. The same as a console. Wtf you're talking about? You can find a PS4/One for $250 easy, I bought mine brand new for $200.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 17:29:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rebel scum</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 07:55:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're kind of a cunt, hum?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 08:00:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know if you can help me, but the events stopped happening for us brazilian players. That last one that gave a .50 pistol didn't showed up and neither this punchline one. Can you please see what's going on? I tried contacting UBI BR but they didn't answered me back so far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 08:01:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fast Fast Fast I'm gonna step on the gas</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Far Cry 5 is a gift that keeps on giving</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 08:06:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 08:15:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>More like "art imitates life"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 09:11:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're a terrible person, you know that right? edit: You can ban me all you want, you're still a cunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 09:25:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is no such thing as "too many emojis"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 09:34:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you start getting paid in euros instead of hyena meat you immediately start playing better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 09:36:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>no u</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 09:44:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>1/3 of Brazil to be fair, only the south and southeast(maybe the mid-region?)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 09:51:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a really shitty way to get extinct</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 09:53:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who's "we"?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 10:02:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>But... but... she's dead, right? Oh God...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 10:55:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Ted Cruz would never have been satisfied with destroying the lives of only 5 innocent people".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 11:05:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/shittyjokes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 11:23:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's the qualifying region for the US? North and Central America? I'm brazilian and we are luck as hell for going to all WC, considering the high level of football we have in South America.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 12:21:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mr Personplacething333... I don't feel so good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 16:32:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for answering o/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 16:35:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pergunta honesta agora, alguma dessas "atua #231; #245;es" foi merecida? Algum jogador j #225; chegou no Neymar pra quebrar ele na maldade? Porque n #227;o pode 100% dessa porra ter sido ele tentando cavar falta.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 16:38:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>N #227;o culpo o cara por ter errado, ele nasceu em "Concepci #243;n del Uruguay, Argentina".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 16:41:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pra um pa #237;s do tamanho da Argentina ter representado algum perigo pro Brasil, s #243; mostra o qu #227;o fudida a nossa situa #231; #227;o estava.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 16:43:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Levando em conta os portugueses que eu conhe #231;o, eles torceriam at #233; pro Uruguai ganhar essa copa em vez da Espanha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 16:44:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Isso que d #225; colocar 1 jogador pra carregar uma sele #231; #227;o inteira ao inv #233;s de apostar no talento do resto do time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 16:46:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>N #227;o seria surpresa um pa #237;s "esquecer" de ensinar ao povo as merdas que fez no passado nas aulas de hist #243;ria. Tenho certeza que "Tiananmen Square" n #227;o  #233; ensinada nas escolas da China.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 16:47:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>T #225; levando a piada a s #233;rio amigo? Tsc Tsc... Pode isso Arnaldo?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 16:56:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bom... a gente deve ter aprendido a li #231; #227;o, levando em conta como n #243;s fodemos com o Paraguai...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 16:58:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's a piece of... art alright</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:01:14</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; they speak Portuguese and talk about favelas while stealing your boleto Wtf you're even on about? Jesus Christ... what a cunt...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:02:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have bad tourists everywhere, just ask Ryan Lochte</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:10:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hum... pior que foi, o maluco chegou seco com uma joelhada nas costas dele...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:12:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's wrong with you? All your comments are hating on brazilians... Wait a minute... r/Unexpected... r/assholedesign... r/The_Donald and here we are... that's why you're such a prick...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:18:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since when Donald Trump knows anything about the U.S. The guy probably thinks Frederick Douglass is a rapper.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:33:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL WC titles now have expiration dates</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 18:58:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bom, desejo realizado, Espanha eliminada.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 21:30:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why tho? Brazil is barely going through this WC. Mexico is probably going to win. Source: am brazilian, trust me, our team sucks(Thank God for Coutinho, because Neymar... shish...)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 01:08:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tite sucked Neymar dick so hard in that press conference that I'm surprised the boy didn't end up in a wheelchair.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 01:23:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought the old Suarez method was to suck all the blood off your oponent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 01:35:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/Soccer detesta jogador que se joga, como o menino Neymar gosta de um cai cai de vez em sempre da #237; eles detestam o garoto por l #225;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 05:03:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>The question is: why the post is still up and why OP isn't banned yet? Come on man, nazi propaganda being posted on your sub. I've seen subs going down for less.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 06:47:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>But that's the point, it's not about being for everyone, these cunts don't care about anything that is not white.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 20:50:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>NO!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 22:14:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Username checks out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 22:50:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>"solid Mexican team" So solid they looked like statues on the field. What the hell happened to the mexican defense?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 22:51:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, he needs to talk with ppl that uses literally armor to play a sport... congrats, that's the most retarded comment I've seen so far on this sub.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 00:42:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Luis Suarez:  #8220;Griezmann doesn't know how it feels to be a vampire #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 00:51:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Calm your tits mate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 01:20:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>No... he... he really isn #8217;t</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 01:24:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well... he IS a major cunt, and both Argentina WC were shady as fuck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 01:25:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just google "Pel #233; daughter dies"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 01:38:34</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I'm sorry, do you somehow think those sports have less physical contact than soccer? No, I don't, that's my point. He's comparing football with sports that are way more agressive and that's fucking stupid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 01:40:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Neymar is a football player, the guy looks like a stick, he doesn't need to be strong. You're comparing him with an american football player that is build like a truck and that's retarded, Jesus Christ...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 01:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's my fucking point.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 01:52:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>The people having a hate boner everytime Neymar does anything on this sub is unbelievable. How many times did Neymar got targeted by other players? There's a reason why he does the "rolling theatrics", because that's what you can do when you hit like a wet noodle and there's five guys ready to fuck you up on field.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 19:39:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're complaining that he didn't start rolling when he broke his back? I was kidding before, but now I really think that you are retarded.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 19:51:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im just going to leave this here. https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=qmLPvfvfrFg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 20:23:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I give up, I'm going to work in something less dangerous, like taming lions or some shit"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 20:26:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>That chocolate tho, 10/10</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 20:28:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>This sounds like a pokemon battle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 20:33:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>If ppl are saying that France is the favorite than Uruguay is going to win, this entire WC has been weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The most red cards dished out in one game(36)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 20:59:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 21:02:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, that makes sen... wait, what?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 21:08:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>A liver for an arm and a leg, doesn't look so "equivalent" to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 21:20:49</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;But you can #8217;t deny Brazil are favourites to win the World Cup this time There is no such thing as "favourites" in this WC, the favourites were all send home.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 22:14:02</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Filipe Lu #237;s, Philippe Coutinho and Neymar will miss the next match if they receive a yellow card today. Nah... I don't think that's the problem...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 22:23:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good bot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 05:03:03</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I truly hope you fuckers are no older than 12. Jared Fogle strikes again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 05:04:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's my fetish</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 09:21:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is what pisses me off the most, I really don't care about frame rate, but the crashes... hur... maybe if they released the first Borderlands instead of 2 the game would run better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 21:29:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>So what? Sekiro is not a Souls-like game, FROMSOFTWARE already said that. The only thing going against Code Vein is NIOH 2(first one is an amazing game by the way) and maybe The Surge 2.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 22:10:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know, seems half of reddit hates his guts and the other half loves him. My top post here on reddit is basicaly this in the comments: "E.M. is right/great/God" / "E.M. is overrated/shit/Satan".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 02:01:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are now banned from r/soccer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:00:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well... you can't melt steel beams with a bus can you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:25:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have to pay first</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:29:00</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;but there are also a ton more progressive ones. This is what happens when all the far right subs get banned. "Fuck it, let's just go to VOAT, right guys? Guys?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:33:49</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Every person in this thread that has replied to me I guarantee is weaker than me. Notice not a single person has said they can do more. The one guy just said he knew some guys in college that were around my strength level. Truth is, you are all the pathetic fat weaklings and wouldn't dare say anything to me in person r/iamverybadass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 23:35:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>and make T_D pay for it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 02:56:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your first mistake was believing the mods are capable of feeling ashamed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Airport</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 03:42:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Was sitting around in the baggage claim, witnessing what decades ago was a luxurious and latently aristocratic travel industry become over-democratized and degenerated. Saw the dregs of humanity pass by. It just seems to get worse every year. Normal people no longer exist. A man with long hair, a big nose and a skirt with hormone-enhanced breasts meets his female friends who do their best to endear him by complimenting his offputting appearance. Another long haired bugman with a beard in his mid to late 20s with his girlfriend both carrying large pokemon plushies like toddlers. Tattooed dykes with short cropped and partially shaven heads roving around in groups like a band of marauders from a Mad Max film. An overwesternized and aposematized Asian thot with blue hair and tattoos waits for her obviously umpteenth caucasian boyfriend. Certain themes seem to predominate among the others: obesity, self-disfigurement, complete erasure of the polarity of the sexes- all in various shades and forms. I saw two decent-looking caucasian males in dress shirts and slacks engaged in agreeable conversation. Had I been an older gentleman of means, I would have given them some money and shook their hands, thanking them and apologizing on behalf of the society they have to live in. Spent the next day at the botanical garden, watching hundreds of bumble bees furiously collecting pollen. It was the only thing that still seemed to make any sense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 05:15:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some of them were just cold and wanted to get warm and cozy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 05:49:21</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;And yet Ive met a lot of people outside the US who follow both the NBA and the NFL. A lot? Wow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 06:40:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let's see how many subs are going to ban me now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 09:30:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Full kingo set + any katana with water damage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 12:02:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>You will always be special in my book.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 13:16:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Percy Jackson really let himself go</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 13:46:11</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Guy A started it I'm so glad to be back on elementary school</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 14:53:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Miranda, eles n #227;o ligam pra gente"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 15:15:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah... imagine jerking off and laughing at the same time, that would be weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 15:19:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>But the asian died in the first panel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 15:39:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check again, they're all dead now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 15:41:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why you are acting like a cunt?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 21:18:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be fair it looks like shit in both images...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 22:23:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 07:15:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>CRAWLING IN MY SKIN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 07:28:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>CRAWLING IN MY SKIN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 07:41:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that's why they didn't put the "teen" on the title.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 07:42:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well... there's always Torrent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 08:33:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nothing is mandatory, this is the most retarded point ever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 14:17:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now I want a mini watermelon =\</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 14:20:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>You'd better run Better run Faster than LeBron</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 14:24:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I'm gonna drown in pu... river"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 15:31:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>CRAWLING</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 15:59:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know what's worse "Hur dur Trump is evil" or "but what about Killary?" Jesus Fucking Christ... when your best point is "this other cunt is bad too" you know you fucked up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 18:06:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>You watch your damn mouth, God Cage is a national treasure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 07:22:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=xzpndHtdl9A</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 04:57:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just Cause 3 is not a good game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 06:32:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no with this bullshit again...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 06:38:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bloodborne, Halo 1 and TLOZ: BOTW are great games, Sunset Overdrive is just good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 06:40:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or Horizon Zero Dawn</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 06:54:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow... don't be a cunt mate, he's wrong, but the whole kill yourself thing was uncalled for..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 07:48:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't worry, I don't think the queen can have kids anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 18:24:53</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Since the dlc was notably higher quality from the main game But that's true for every game. Blood and Wine, The Old Hunters, Artorias of the Abyss, Crown Trilogy, Ashe... aham, I mean... The Ringed City, etc. They're always better than the base game, levels and bosses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 15:45:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I had previous rape tendencies towards men... ...although I'm not bisexual or gay. I don't know mate, that sounds pretty fucking gay to me, also you're a pedo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 16:10:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/woosh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 16:22:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>and a Nazi based on the username</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 16:36:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, also that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 17:15:25</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;but I am not that inbred Oh boy...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 17:20:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>and sad... and scary...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What have I done...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 23:57:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 01:09:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brazil too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 03:44:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>The fuck...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 06:11:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>"enjoy the rest of reddit" I don't know why, but that pisses me off so much, what a cunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 01:27:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be honest I don't care about Trump, I'm not american, he's not my president. But the fact that he's so hated by 40%-50% of America and loved by the other half is so funny, and I don't even know why.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 00:09:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not with that attitude</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 06:20:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Crack is a hell of a drug</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 20:14:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Final game for the Vita on PS Plus: -Pinball -Chess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 20:15:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bad bot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 20:15:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sadly no =(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 21:07:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also the hair of ninja/samurai/mage items will disappear permanently after you get them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 21:13:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe some ninja claws?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 21:14:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I loved the side missions, and it was a great way to get good against some enemies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 21:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>So you want Nioh to become Ninja Gaiden? No thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 21:21:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>No Open world, that would screw with the loading times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 00:19:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're gonna regret saying that under president Kanye West.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 06:53:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Makes all the difference</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 06:57:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually LW itself can be parried, there was a video here of a guy parrying Sanada when he activated his LW, and another post of a guy doing the same on PVP. But you can't parry attacks done while in LW mode.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 07:03:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good luck, be patient and have fun https://www.reddit.com/r/Nioh/comments/6u8x4y/the_kodamas_directories_your_onestop_thread_for/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 07:07:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the actual fuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 16:17:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>You just feel like Batman</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 16:25:29</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;You call ME a beast?! My brother playing this part few days ago "You were eating people for fuck's sake!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 16:30:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>lmao lol omg such weeb armor amiright? Hue hue hue Shut the fuck up...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 16:32:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably 5 pieces + dragon sword + Y. Magatama(-1 set requirement)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 16:33:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fapping?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 17:28:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, I see you're a man of culture as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 17:34:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>The hell? You're lucky that you're being summoned by someone smart enough to use suppa and get out of the way. I usually just get summoned by some genius who ends up drowning or being killed trying to "Flying Monkey" a four armed Yokai.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 17:37:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>He didn't said that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 18:07:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reposts on Reddit? No... it can't be...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 23:44:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree, when I'm fighting giant demons and dodging fire balls all I want is my sword fight to be g.r.o.u.n.d.e.d. I don't understand why ppl wants to transform Nioh into Dark Souls...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 04:45:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Compared to Nioh? Yes, it does. As far as I know you can't Flying Monkey or Izuna Drop the shit out of Ornstein.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 04:47:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nioh's combat isn't "top anime shit", is perfect the way it is. Wtf you're even on about?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 04:55:24</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Here's hoping Nioh 2's PVP sucks ass, too, so the toxic spergs stay on other games. Hey man, come on, skill pvp is fun =, (</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 19:24:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can also get glory by helping ppl on coop or by killing revenants(the red graves).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 02:00:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Picard best Jedi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 02:08:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's amazing how after all this time you can still be on the list of ppl who completed the Abyss(I think the list goes from 1 to 2500, not sure). I finished in 1000 and something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 10:44:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah... Ned wasn't a manipulative cunt like Dumbledore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 11:25:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus Christ... get a room you two...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 12:34:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well when we're talking about this president, then... yeah.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 12:45:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>R.I.P. her giant tits =(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 13:40:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Comments? But you still have a point. It's a stupid system.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 13:54:41</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;An interesting title Nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 04:14:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Downvoting someone for liking a game. Never change Reddit, never change...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 02:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;is not a dude He/she/it can be a unicorn for all I care, that post history tho... still fucked up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 02:25:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you're the only one taking this seriously, we're just taking the piss.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 02:32:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh trust me, that ban is not going to stop her from producing more drama.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 12:08:03</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;she was the number 1 ranked porn star of 2014 Wow... that's... That's something...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 12:17:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well... you can slut shame and also jerk off to someone. Not saying is the right thing to do tho...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 12:18:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/notevenclose</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 22:30:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>If by "sarcastically" you mean "like a cunt"...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 06:19:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>your</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 10:44:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Weaponized batism</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 12:57:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder which OC holds the record. Just this one asshole was in 4 subs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 13:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the spirit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 13:03:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not with that attitude</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 13:08:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even Butthole and Asshole are fighting now, America really is a divided nation... tsc tsc...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 13:56:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL crows are trash</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 14:37:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Try again." Holy shit, it's the "NEXT" lady all over again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 14:59:24</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;No one is a russian bot Erh... some are...  gt;Stop blaming other countries for our own problems. Not saying Russia was the reason Trump won or anything, but they sure as hell tried to help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 15:58:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Robin is an adult in this. And Starfire is/looks old enough to be a mom. Only two of the 5 looks like kids(BB and Raven)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 17:35:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or it's like "hey, we built this awesome world, wanna skip it? Well fuck you then, because you can't" "But this is my third gameplay, I even got the Platinum, please just let me fast travel" "Not my fucking problem son"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 17:39:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why do you care that he care that you care about your trophy percentages? Literally doesn #8217;t affect you in any way at all</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 08:21:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually all the poison areas in Soulsborne games sucks. The bosses are cool tho(Amygdala, Abyss Watchers, Mytha, etc)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 10:10:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 16:52:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Come on, flip that coin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 16:58:15</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I and others are just nervous about JC Staff. Hey... at least is not Toei, I mean, can you imagine?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 17:02:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please don't use CGI Please don't use CGI PLEASE don't use CGI</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 05:30:27</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Liden Film Don't... Don't even think about it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 05:33:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go sell your plasma, the DLCs are great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 05:34:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not gonna lie, to this day I still don't know how I got the "don't get hit" title on that mission.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 16:16:44</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;to death I wis... I mean, yeah yeah, it's just terrible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 16:18:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why would he use another word? That's retarded.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 16:32:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is not a dance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 19:28:25</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;What word is retarded synonymous with in your mind? khaleesiofgalifrey</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 20:17:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't fucking do that, don't make this a "Respect Women" kind of shit. It's more about all kinds of ppl on reddit looking for karma. Not saying it's the case of OP, but there's a possibility.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 00:54:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can always go to VOAT... no one is making you guys stay on Reddit By the way, first time reading about this sub(thanks r/drama), and holy shit...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 02:11:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh amigo, I'm not american this whole Trump, Hillary, liberals, conservatives, conspiracy, true, etc it's not my problem(thank God for that). I'm just here to see how this ends. If you guys are right good luck, if you're wrong and this whole Q and NWO thing is just an elaborate joke then... also good luck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 14:03:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not in every state tho, here in Goi #225;s I see ppl bringing beer, hot dogs, calzones, pamonha, hell, last saturday I saw three guys with a large pizza.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 14:09:09</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Can you also bring food... It depends on the state/stadium you're going, but most of them allow. And alcohol is not allowed in stadiums no matter what(unless FIFA says "Fuck your laws, we're selling beer now), safety reasons and all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 14:26:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok, I don't know the word for that in english, so bear with me and google "marmita" on GI. Yeah, there's trashy ppl who brings that, and I'm pretty sure they don't have popcorn inside that thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 14:37:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sei n #227;o, aquele rato tava voando e sorrindo no v #237;deo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 14:48:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>A</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 14:55:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jon "wealthy blacks commit more crimes than poor whites" Tron</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 14:58:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>A ironia  #233; quase palp #225;vel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 14:59:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>"O Caminho da Prosperidade - Projeto F #234;nix" Jair Bolsonaro cavaleiro de bronze confirmado.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 15:07:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>O fato de voc #234; acreditar que existe inclina #231; #227;o ou ideologia pol #237;tica nesse pa #237;s  #233; ador #225;vel. N #227;o existe "esquerda" nem "direita" no Brasil, o que existe  #233; "governando" e "esperando a vez". Hur dur mas e os comunistas cantando "t #244; com Maduro"...  #201;... o Brasil vai virar Cuba desde 2002... porra, desde antes do plano real eu j #225; escutava essa merda de "a esquerda vai destruir o pa #237;s"...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 15:09:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eu tenho mais raiva de ler "cimavoto" do que ver nego se americanizando nos coment #225;rios.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 15:13:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>O motivo da reprova #231; #227;o foi "eu n #227;o quero esse cidad #227;o calmo e comedido atr #225;s de um volante".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 15:18:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/nothingeverhappens</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 15:38:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>T #225; certo par #231;a, "Chega de left-leaning politics nesse pa #237;s", tem raz #227;o, tu  #233; um centrista... Me fode...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 15:44:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vixe, vi demais esse neg #243;cio de cimavoto baixavoto aqui nessa sub.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 15:50:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eu tamb #233;m acredito na import #226;ncia da altern #226;ncia de governos, mas aqui n #227;o  #233; como na Fran #231;a ou Estados Unidos aonde voc #234; tem claramente divididos os conservadores, liberais, direita, esquerda, etc. Aqui no Brasil  #233; s #243; um conjunto de grupos de interesse disfar #231;ados de partidos, levantando bandeiras ideol #243;gicas e traindo a confian #231;a de quem acreditou na conversa quando chegam ao poder.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 15:53:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eu nem entro nesse m #233;rito, e nem vou me basear na minha pr #243;pria experi #234;ncia como muitos fazem de forma errada. "Minha vida era ruim no governo de X e ficou boa no governo de Y, ent #227;o eu s #243; quero Y agora". Esse  #233; um pensamento muito perigoso...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 15:57:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>N #227;o acho, isso  #233; um pensamento muito extremista, eu nasci no come #231;o dos anos 80, cresci ouvindo que o Brasil iria quebrar, que estava a beira do colapso, que o governo de X, Y, Z seria o fim de tudo. Que est #225;vamos tentando ser que nem os EUA, pra depois ouvir que ser #237;amos uma nova Cuba, que o Brasil  #237;a se tornar um pa #237;s de primeiro mundo pra dois anos depois ouvir que o pa #237;s estava em crise e  #237;a desmoronar. No entanto... aqui estamos...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 16:02:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>N #227;o estou determinando o que os outros podem brincar/falar ou n #227;o, s #243; n #227;o gostei muito da ideia por tr #225;s. Espero que entenda.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 16:18:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maneira de falar amigo, se eu dissesse que estava cagando e andando pra quem usasse o termo "cimavoto" voc #234; n #227;o precisa se preocupar com o pessoal da limpeza.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 16:26:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Com um nome daqueles, queria o que? Rsrs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 16:28:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sim, um  #233; um exagero de quem se importa demais, outro um exagero de quem n #227;o est #225; nem a #237;, esse  #233; o meu ponto. Enfim amigo, essa foi minha inten #231; #227;o, se voc #234; se ofendeu ou algo do tipo eu pe #231;o desculpas, fique em paz, tchau.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 16:34:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>As pessoas vivem de extremos, "ou  #233; 8 ou 80", e como todo mundo adora ver desgra #231;a  #233; mais f #225;cil exagerar pra baixo e dizer que o pa #237;s est #225; em chamas ao inv #233;s de s #243; reconhecer que o Brasil tem seus problemas como qualquer outro pa #237;s, mas no geral n #243;s estamos bem, o fato de estarmos aqui agora no Reddit podendo falar o que bem entender do governo sem correr o risco de ir parar numa sala escura j #225; mostra qu #227;o privilegiados somos. O brasileiro s #243; vai entender o que  #233; verdadeiro caos quando perder tudo o que conquistou. Espero que esse dia nunca chegue, e  #233; por isso que desprezo todo e qualquer discurso extremista, seja de direita, esquerda, o que for, nada de bom jamais saiu disso.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 17:39:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aprende? Voc #234; ainda n #227;o sabe? Sortudo...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 17:57:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meus 3 artistas favoritos atualmente s #227;o esses, vozes fant #225;sticas e o mix que eles fazem  #233; sempre de alta qualidade. [Jamie Woon - Sharpness](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8J0CjQjjy24) [James Blake - Retrograde](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6p6PcFFUm5I) [SOHN - Artifice](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9btsq496hkQ)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:01:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eu n #227;o acredito que voc #234; usou a B-word... tsc tsc...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:12:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Fuck that" = "Que se foda"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:14:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jaden Smith  #233; aquele menino que ri com a testa?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:16:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Porque voc #234; n #227;o leva seu "colch #227;o fodido" pra casa dela e dorme no ch #227;o com ele? E n #227;o, n #227;o estou tirando com a sua cara... vai que d #225; certo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:17:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>A n #227;o ser que isso seja o review de uma rapadura eu n #227;o entendi muito bem a l #243;gica.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:20:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cara, quando voc #234; faz parte de uma igreja com mais de 1000 casos de abuso voc #234; tem que se perguntar, "eu vou pro inferno?". Falando s #233;rio, a essa altura o diabo s #243; te recebe, entrega as chaves do reino e vai embora...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:22:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sim, cortei numa tal de Dalila semana passada e meu cabelo t #225; fraco pra cacete.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:22:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Isso  #233; uma nova copypasta?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:23:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/howimetyourmother</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:26:19</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Eu sento no  #244;nibus e fico jogando no 3DS Porra... tu joga o qu #234; no 3DS? Roleta Russa? Porque meu irm #227;o, tu t #225; brincando com a sorte...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:28:39</DATE>
    <TEXT> #201; o n #237;vel de dificuldade do brasileiro, tem o "f #225;cil" que morre em 2-3 golpes, o m #233;dio e o "dif #237;cil" que a #237; precisa de um pouco mais de estrat #233;gia.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:29:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah n #227;o... vai por mim... ele  #233; uma mo #231;a... "ain, tem um macho me secando" Pelo amor de Deus...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:33:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aqui onde eu moro tamb #233;m  #233; baixo, mas mesmo assim, nunca se sabe. E por favor, n #227;o confie nessa de  #244;nibus cheio, quando morei em Sampa o que j #225; ouvi(e vi) de cara esperando a parada, apontando a arma, pegando tudo de algu #233;m e indo embora...  #244;nibus cheio ou n #227;o, o que as outras pessoas v #227;o fazer? Intervir? Toma cuidado cara.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:43:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Intelig #234;ncia n #227;o  #233; bem um pr #233; requisito pra entrar no mundo do crime, mesmo assim, latroc #237;nio existe, s #243; se cuida par #231;a, boa sorte a #234;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 19:01:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Se for o que eu estou pensando ele tem o s #237;mbolo do Wi-Fi quase sempre na testa.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 19:24:29</DATE>
    <TEXT> #201; esse mesmo rsrs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 20:48:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Valeu, recomendo procurar mais m #250;sicas deles, essas s #243; s #227;o as minhas favoritas de cada um deles, mas s #227;o todas  #243;timas rsrs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:11:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow... you banned ppl, good job... Jesus Christ, what a cunt...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 03:55:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where's Britney Spears to defend Emma Watson now?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 08:03:52</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Make reddit great again by downvoting this shitheads submission Oh the irony...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 10:00:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>U</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 10:32:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because lying is easy and there's no repercussion for doing it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 20:07:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/gatekeeping/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 20:12:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>nan han</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 20:26:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's that smell? The sweet blood, oh, it sings to me. It's enough to make a dog sick #8230;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:46:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/iamverybadass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 15:58:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>YOU VIOLATED MY MOTHER</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 16:05:24</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;dead or alive You're coming with me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 16:09:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, it's here. That "SCHIN" sign kinda confirmed... and the situation as a whole of course...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 19:11:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>EA is the devil Konami sucks Ubisoft? More like Bugsoft amiright? Todd Howard is a liar Kojima is a God CDProjekt Red please have my children ... Did I miss something?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 20:05:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah... Sean Murray went through a redemption arc, he's cool now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 21:04:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, but as someone who bought No Man's Sky day one, I'm at least happy that they believed in their own game and didn't abandoned the game fucking the players. People love to say, "fuck this, fuck that, he lied, etc", but they also need to give a chance when someone says "hey, I fucked up, I'll try to right my wrongs".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 22:42:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know what you meant(I think =/), ppl don't care and still think he's a liar(not saying you're one of them).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 04:29:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>So EXP becomes useless late game right? Or there is new runics/summons on NG+?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 04:34:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hold X</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 07:36:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cracked, not even once.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:18:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wtf you're even on about? Jesus Christ...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:20:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jajajaja / hahahaha / kkkkkkkk / rsrsrsrs Did I forget some?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:40:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sou brasileiro amigo, n #227;o estou me referindo somente as risadas aqui do Brasil e sim todas as que consigo me lembrar sendo usadas na internet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:40:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eu sei disso. E tem raz #227;o, esqueci da principal HUEHUEHUE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:48:14</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; -100 karma for me is nothing, cause I have 20k. r/iamverybadass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 00:38:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Todo mundo  #233; BR se voc #234; acreditar o bastante.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 00:38:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uau... n #227;o sabia que eu era americano, a gente descobre coisas novas sobre si mesmo todo dia.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 04:09:48</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;percebi que tu s #243; era um animal mesmo Exatamente, atr #225;s da sua m #227;e por exemplo eu sou um jumento.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 04:14:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Senhoras e senhores, por favor sigamos o exemplo m #225;ximo de maturidade do senhor "LUL" aqui. Volta pro teu LOLzinho guri, e v #234; se toma cuidado com esse teu telhado de vidro a #237;...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 04:24:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I swear to God, if Oda pulls a lazy ending like that after 20years of this shit...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 04:47:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>1)Z #233; Gotinha do Tim Burton 2)Z #233; Gotinha "Get those n*ggers out of my neighborhood" 3)Z #233; Gotinha Rape Face 4)Z #233; Gotinha Partido Verde</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 04:48:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Voc #234; seria estranho se n #227;o achasse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 05:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/suicidebywords</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 16:18:01</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I never swallowed, nor do I, mainly because it does not fulfill any particular desire of mine. Just play, smear, chew, and masturbate with it. I'm done, that's it, I'm out of here...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 17:39:14</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;You can play fork knife Now I want a BR where you can only use forks, knives and spoons as weapons...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 17:40:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>So what? They still did it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 19:18:33</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Do you have to write cringy poetry your whole life because you started it as teenager? That was oddly specific</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 20:47:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hum? You can see both arms(holding the kids hand and the other giving a thumbs up).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 00:03:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really don't care to be honest, you can't even see the shield 95% of the time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 03:36:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seriously... Santos Dumont and Nikola Tesla are the most wronged inventors in history.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 19:25:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kitty: "Obi Wan lied! The High Ground doesn't work"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Weapon to Surpass Metal Gear</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 05:55:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>[That was... odd](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2s7LW2yW8dk)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This is what Hell looks like</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 06:13:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 06:31:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know that, I just want to understand the logic behind that. If you want to kill the host why not just invade? Why be a prick?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 07:17:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, It's also a good way to train your dodges I guess =)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 07:22:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That doesn't explain "why" just the "what" tho =/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 18:12:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>The first mission in Japan, with the Demon in the boat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 20:30:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit, never mind, I finally did it! hahaha I'm trying this new arcane build(99 arcane) only using hunter tools and he was 1HK me everytime but somehow I did it, thanks anyway, good luck helping the other guys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 21:27:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>The window was open haha Sorry about that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 22:37:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>no swearing on my christian sub</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 05:18:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Aha My creator was an antisemite Aha"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 05:46:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>[context](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FDezfo2w1gY amp;t=)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 05:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 07:52:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>"RAW ASS"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 08:01:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey... don't kinkshame...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 00:45:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>South Korea? South Korea!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 07:19:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your little friend</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 21:24:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Now now... relax and tell me about your day"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 21:55:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>He could upvote others, but not himself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 22:52:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>So... what's the next step of your master plan?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 23:39:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>It doesn't matter, ppl will go with the "videogames are the problem" no matter what kind of game was. =/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 23:43:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>4 dead 15 injured shooter is dead 4 kills / 15 assist / 1 death Not bad...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 23:46:57</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;"Tranny porn" is a sorta offensive term Don't... don't fucking go there...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 00:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Aaaaaand according to r/Drama they're coming from the left, HA suckers!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 00:14:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I the only one that wants to see the match he lost? I hope twitch recorded that shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mayo shooter wasn't there to make friends</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 01:04:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 01:17:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>"We need to ban bowl haircuts"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 01:32:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well... you can be his friend or you can die. Your choice...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Well... you're not wrong...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 01:33:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 02:08:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh boy... this REALLY didn't aged well...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 02:22:07</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Stay in school "I'm planning on shooting that too"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 02:28:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>[It's only a game...](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xzpndHtdl9A)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 02:55:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love the american way of thinking "If doesn't work here in the U.S. it's because it's impossible everywhere"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 03:18:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wtf you're talking about? Jesus Christ...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 03:41:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looking for sympathy on r/ImGoingToHellForThis? Good luck with that...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 03:45:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're cool... by "cool" I mean a "cunt".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 03:48:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nothing is 100% safe, what kind of stupid question is that? I really don't understand how a first world country like the U.S. can spill this stupid backwards bullshit that vaccines causa autism and other things. You guys are supposed to be smarter than that...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 03:56:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congratulations! It's a boy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 04:14:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>So... honest question, what happened to "The Wall"? We're already 2 years in and I don't see anything about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 04:16:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still disrespectful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 04:23:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh... I'm sorry, I think you misunderstood me. I'm not trying to insult you. I'm stating the fact that you're acting like a cunt on this thread.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 05:28:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, yep... I think the Wall is not going to happen and he's just going to do a "hey, if I get re-elected I'll build the wall, believe me" or some shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 06:35:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why not? They did it in the original trilogy. In GOW2 was Zeus being a dick with the Sword of Olympus, in GOW3 was Kratos dying and being depowered by the river of the dead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 07:04:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me: "Why "bagel"? I don't ge... oh... OH..."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 07:08:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>The fuck?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 07:09:21</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;is gaming related So is a picture of Yoshi wearing a bikini, yet you don't see me posting this shit here...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 15:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know Leeroy Jenkins was fake, right? Like, they did it to promote the clan. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vvXRcwcIJh4</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guess I'll Die</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 17:05:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 17:09:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good grief...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 17:13:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>See the red laser on the black guy's hoodie? [Context](https://edition.cnn.com/us/live-news/madden-19-jacksonville-shooting/index.html)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 17:59:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really don't give a shit about Obama or Hillary.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 18:03:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>[X] Sunday [X] Monday 2 out of 7 already, not bad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 18:55:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 20:56:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm brazilian, so not only in the U.S. I guess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 04:45:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>What happened? The furries are back on his twitter?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My God...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 04:56:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 05:19:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh boy... I can't wait for JAWS 19</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 05:22:39</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;but the children ended up being collateral damage The fuck...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 05:23:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a lot of disgrace out there then...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 05:33:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>and your point is?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 05:51:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't wait for Pure Chess and Arcade Essentials next month.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 06:14:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really don't understand you americans... your kids are dying almost every day and all you care about is which politician the shooter didn't liked, for fucks sake...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 06:21:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're the one bringing up the same retarded agenda about "hur dur can you imagine if he was..." and I'm the stupid one? Jesus Christ...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 06:41:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Do you have any last words?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 15:03:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Get a room you two...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 16:44:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 03:29:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't wait for the ove... I mean... Go Musk!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Cell Phone in Microwave</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 05:25:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 05:42:40</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Prison Architect It's the kind of game I would love to play on my Vita</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 06:17:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no... don't worry, these comments you made don't make you a pedo, just a cunt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 06:18:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Oh boy, I can't wait to see those baby elephants, uhum"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 06:23:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Especially when they're dead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 06:27:00</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;very suspicious "AND THAT IS WHY I AM 100% SURE HE IS A PEDO"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 06:31:27</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I wasn't worried You are worrisome tho...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 06:36:59</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;School shootings are statistically insignificant events in the US. Yep, that's it... now I'm sure you're just trolling</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 06:50:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Jokes on you bitches I've only been here for two years! "And I only fucked half a kid"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 07:00:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;pornsick Oh no... people watching porn?! Not on my christian site! Jesus Fucking Christ...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 14:04:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 14:30:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm outofloop here, who's the Mr. Fantastic post hangover?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 14:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree, that's a sexy ass treadmill</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 14:45:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only if I can watch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 15:11:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just a lil bit of "FREEDOM"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 15:20:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>3 minutes on google and I'm already cringing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 15:23:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I look like a shark. r/suicidebywords</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Not Perfectly Balanced</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 17:03:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 19:45:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's because most human beings don't have patience to deal with cunts, even when said cunt is right about something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 19:48:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, the flip flop and the drug cartel part I got it, it's just plain racism and stereotype, but why the machete?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Simple jiujitsu lesson</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 05:27:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 05:29:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>The fuck? How many cancers do you have?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 01:09:33</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Soviet Russia created genocide It may not have "created", but it certainly has perfected.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 01:23:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Minha vida fora.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 01:25:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Recomendo jogar o DS3 com algum amigo/familiar, o jogo fica 10 vezes mais divertido.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 01:25:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vita?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rainbow: A Story About Life</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 01:34:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 02:41:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can be a murderous piece of shit and still love your family =/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 02:41:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/therewasanattempt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 04:12:01</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;TotalBiscuit and people like him at least make serious videos where they explain their views in a pretty decent and in-depth way Not anymore</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 19:29:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder what they do with the dick, just put it in a jar with TFF or some shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 20:47:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Holy shit: When your ass is blessed by holy cum"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 02:30:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you were this supposed dickless soldier, would you accept another man's dick?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 02:32:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm pretty sure it was the green one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 03:06:28</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;How can we not ping these people. Because for some reason is considered a form of witch hunt and Reddit doesn't have the best track record about that. A.k.a. "We did it, Reddit"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 03:07:46</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;doll-pimp I want to die</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 03:12:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm really conflicted right now, I'm against kink-shaming but this is on another level of fucked up...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 03:38:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, there are retarded cunts in every group.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 03:41:37</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;You wouldn't want your country invaded by Italian-Americans would you? I can't even... what a piece of shit...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 04:54:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eu diria que o Haddad  #233; uma p #233;ssima escolha pra vice, mas levando em conta os vices que o Bolsonaro e o Ciro escolheram... Eu sei que vice n #227;o importa em 90% dos casos, mas poxa, melhorem...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 04:56:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>"We'll get em' next time" There won't be a next time...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 04:57:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Da  #250;ltima vez que o povo soube quem era o candidato do Lula as coisas n #227;o acabaram muito bem...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 05:25:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mas s #233;rio, qual era o plano do PT? Encontrar a fonte da juventude e enfiar goela abaixo do Lula? Eu tenho certeza que ele nem sobreviveria outro mandato(levando em conta que Presidente envelhece que nem cachorro). S #233;rio que n #227;o tem NINGU #201;M no PT com carisma(porque vamos ser honestos, compet #234;ncia e honestidade nunca foram exig #234;ncias pro cargo)?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 05:28:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>"T #195; T #195; T #195; T #195; T #195; T #195; T #195; T #195; T #195; PAM PAM PAM PAM PAM" Puta merda, quem morreu? "Lula ineleg #237;vel" Filhos da...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 05:31:27</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Bem, alguem vai chegar. Esse  #233; o tipo de coment #225;rio que o Destino l #234; e fala "ohohoho e se n #227;o tiver um segundo turno?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 05:40:34</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Aposto que o plano do Lula  #233; que o PT morra com ele e os seus eleitores jovens se dissolvam entre os outros partidos (PCdoB,PSOL,PCO,PSTU,MDB,etc.) Eu n #227;o duvido nada, rancor  #233; um sentimento poderoso...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 05:41:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bolsonaro nunca ganharia em primeiro(ou segundo) turno contra Lula, ent #227;o de certa forma teria feito diferen #231;a.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 05:53:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Pior que a m #250;sica  #233; boa mesmo sendo zoeira](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Sb4LGQPGPLg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 05:58:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>por favorzinho</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 06:00:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah claro, a famosa voz e entona #231; #227;o do Bolsonaro, t #227;o singular, t #227;o marcante, t #227;o... de sacanagem com a minha cara isso sim... a imita #231; #227;o ficou boa, os trejeitos da criatura est #227;o todos a #237;, s #243; faltou a flex #227;o de pesco #231;o.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 06:26:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Marina Silva  #233; bastante carism #225;tica.](https://media.giphy.com/media/PSOjGYetmREs/giphy.gif)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 06:51:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>That moment when you remember Thanos killed his own mother...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 07:01:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok... ainda n #227;o vejo como isso melhorou a situa #231; #227;o...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 07:04:40</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I'll have you know... [...that there's no...](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yuO9HdFEJLE)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 07:19:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>=(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 16:50:04</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;And Starks were never big on sentimental sharing anyway. That's wrong, Bran is very sentimental.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 18:14:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>How the fuck do you get banned from r/movies? Did you posted that "White Chicks was awesome" or some shit?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 18:17:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't understand, r/Drama is nothing like r/CringeAnarchy or r/The_Donald, I mean, we have some edgy cunts now and then but nothing like what happens on those subs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 20:18:22</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I hate reddit [Well... there's always VOAT...](https://media.giphy.com/media/PSOjGYetmREs/giphy.gif)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 17:25:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course, he's not a burger...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 17:42:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>GO FIND THE INCEST STRETCHER!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 17:47:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean... who's going after the Vale and why? "YEAH! We conquered the Vale, 75% of our men are dead but we did it, now we can... now we... wtf we do now? There's nothing here!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 18:08:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>And his against the Mountain was still the best fight in GoT so far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 18:11:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well... TIL that I'm 6'1'', whatever that means...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 18:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>No one expects the spanish chainsaw</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 18:28:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Come on man... stop digging...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 18:34:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL that every VIP ROOM is segregation, fuck me...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 20:23:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>"The difference between fiction and reality is that fiction has to make sense"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 20:30:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tom Clancy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 20:34:38</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;GallowBoobs a Trap? Nah... just a cunt...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 23:01:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>This sub is dead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>