<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject8481</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 08:45:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>All hail the mighty changer of ways. The true lord and savior of us all. The enlightener and protector. The highest among all dieties. Praise be to Tzeentch!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thousand Sons semi-competitive army list ideas</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 06:11:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just recently started to get into thousand sons and need some opinions on list building. I play against mainly Grey Knights and a combo of deathwatch/ultramarines (Guilliman and tactical marines). I #8217;m perfectly fine playing a unit I like even if it #8217;s not the most competitive. So far I only have Magnus and 3 squads of Rubric marines (unassembled). My most recent plan is something like this: Battalion Detachment (+3 cp) HQ - Ahriman on disc of Tzeentch (166) Exalted Sorcerer on disc of Tzeentch w/ Dark Matter Crystal(141) Troops - Rubric Marines - Aspiring Sorcerer, Inferno Boltgun x 8, Soulreaper Cannon (220) Rubric Marines - Aspiring Sorcerer, Inferno Boltgun x 8, Soulreaper Cannon (220) Rubric Marines - Aspiring Sorcerer, Inferno Boltgun x4 (107) Elites - Scarab Occult Terminators - Scarab Occult Sorcerer, Inferno Combi-Bolter x 8, Hellfyre Missile Rack, Soulreaper Cannon (438) Heavy Support - Predator - Twin Lascannon, Lascannon x2 (190) Dedicated Transport - Rhino (72) Super-Heavy Auxiliary Detachment Lord of War - Magnus the Red (445) - Warlord Basically one 10 man squad of Rubricae will come in from the warp and the other will ride around in the Rhino. Everyone else just supports each other and smites the life out of all my enemies and the predator is there to deal with any vehicles basically. I dont love Tzaangors but I #8217;m open to them. I #8217;d like to keep it strictly Thousand Sons for now and stay away from Daemons until I get competitive with the list. Basically my questions are -Will this list hold its own most of the time? -Are rhinos worth it? -Are Daemon Princes better than Exalted Sorcerers? -Are Helbrutes worth it? -Should I spend that many points on Termies? -Should I delve into Forgeworld? is this too assholeish? Literally any advice is appreciated. Thanks a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-14 16:55:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>So basically despite how much I might hate it, to be competitive at all I have to use Tzaangors and the such. I #8217;m curious tho, should I go ahead and buy the Battlefirce Tzeentch Arcanites Changecult and just convert the Acolytes to Tzaangors? I can #8217;t find an actually box of Tzaangors anywhere. Anyways, how does this new list look? Also will it fair decently against elite armies? **++ Battalion Detachment +3CP (Chaos - Thousand Sons) [66 PL, 1174pts] ++** **+ HQ +** **Ahriman on Disc of Tzeentch [9 PL, 166pts]:** **Daemon Prince of Tzeentch [9 PL, 180pts]:** Hellforged sword, Helm of the Third Eye, Wings **+ Troops +** **Rubric Marines [27 PL, 433pts]** . **Aspiring Sorcerer:** Force stave, Inferno Bolt Pistol . **17x Rubric Marine w/ Inferno Boltgun:** 17x Inferno boltgun . **Rubric Marine w/ Soulreaper cannon:** Soulreaper cannon . **Rubric Marine w/ Soulreaper cannon:** Soulreaper cannon **Tzaangors [7 PL, 150pts]:** Brayhorn, 19x Tzaangor w/ Tzaangor Blades . **Twistbray:** Tzaangor blades **Tzaangors [4 PL, 70pts]:** 9x Tzaangor w/ Tzaangor Blades . **Twistbray:** Tzaangor blades **+ Elites +** **Tzaangor Shaman [5 PL, 90pts]:** Dark Matter Crystal, Force stave **+ Fast Attack +** **Tzaangor Enlightened [5 PL, 85pts]:** Aviarch, 4x Enlightened, Fatecaster greatbows **++ Super-Heavy Auxiliary Detachment (Chaos - Thousand Sons) [23 PL, 445pts] ++** **+ Lord of War +** **Magnus the Red [23 PL, 445pts]:** **++ Battalion Detachment +3CP (Chaos - Daemons) [25 PL, 381pts] **+ HQ +** **Changecaster [4 PL, 78pts]** **Fluxmaster [5 PL, 99pts]** **+ Troops +** **Horrors [8 PL, 140pts]:** 20x Pink Horror **Horrors [4 PL, 32pts]:** Blue Horror, 9x Pair of Brimstone Horrors **Horrors [4 PL, 32pts]:** Blue Horror, 9x Pair of Brimstone Horrors **++ Total: [114 PL, 2000pts] ++** I might end up substituting certain units for more fun ones but this is a good base for a competitive list? Any advice on where to get Tzaangors?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 03:33:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>1) The app BattleScribe is completely free and (after figuring out how to navigate it) has all of the info needed on units and list building. Favorite app of all time. 2) Yes they are 3) Yes, one of the cheapest units, decent as massive blobs, wrapping up opponents in combat, or even objective holding. Not an auto-take but definitely have their uses 4) The AoS Tzaangors and 40k Tzaangors are the exact same models except for an extra sprue of autoguna/chainswords in the 40k box. The daemons are the same as well. Don #8217;t be afraid to ask opponents about proxying before battle, most everyone will be okay with subtle differences. Just don #8217;t be the proxier in this video: https://youtu.be/1_UXan8lQa4</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Heavy Support help</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 06:09:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just wondering everyone opinion on Defiler vs Forgefiend vs Maulerfiend vs Heldrake vs Hellbrute vs Predator vs extra Termies. I have somewhere around 400 points to throw around and no real threat in my army (besides Magnus).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-15 07:16:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would just like to say how much I love you for breaking all of this down for me, definitely narrowing it down to Hellbrute or Defiler (Maybe both).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Fine detail paintbrush?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 17:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just started a Thousand Sons and want to paint them really well which I know happens with patience and practice but also all of my fine detail brushes don #8217;t ever seem small or fine enough. I know about the xs artificer brush but it #8217;s hard justifying $20 on a brush unless someone can convince me it #8217;s worth it. Just wondering what you all use.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-16 17:51:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very blue</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Vallejo #8217;s Metallic Medium</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 00:00:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Going to paint my Rubric Marines (Thousand Sons) soon and considering adding some metallic medium to the blue to make it really pop. Has anyone done this or something similar? What is your opinion on this material?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 02:15:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Competitively? Probably not Guardians are decent as a buffer unit but it #8217;s not worth it IMO to tie them down with a heavy weapon. Dire avengers will be better in pretty much every way. If you really want heavy weapons you can use the Vaul #8217;s support battery or (my personal favorite) fire prisms and other tanks of the sort. If you doing the Wraith type list than you will need some wave serpents, more wraithguard/blade, a spiritseer/wraithseer to support and then possible a wraithlord/warwalker. If you are going with the wraithlord I prefer kitting him out cheaply with cannons, flamers, and ghostglaive. War walkers can be used as heavy weapons platforms basically with dual bright lances for av or other weapons depending on role. However, if you are okay straying away from the Wraith type army then aspect warriors are very powerful. Dark reapers are one of the best units right now, set them in a corner, protect with smaller units (dire avengers or guardians) and blast every to oblivion. Fire dragons are great at av but very fragile. Howling banshees and striking scorpions are your best melee units (besides wraithblades) but once again, very fragile. No matter what you do, you will most likely need a wave serpent or two. I personally love two or three fire prisms all working together (if they all sit still they can each fire the Cannon twice and for only 1 cp you can fire them all at the same target, ignoring range and los effectively, and rerolling hits and wounds. (Amazing combo)). HQ wise, you farseers are some of the best psychers of the game, definitely want at least the one it comes with. Warlock spam is very powerful as well, most all their powers are good (I prefer the single warlocks compared to the conclave but it #8217;s up to you). Autarchs are you only way to get command points back as far as I know and can also fulfill vital roles on the battlefield. Consider getting the Triumvirate of Ynnead as well, Yvraine is another extremely powerful psycher. Feel free to message me about any other questions, hope I provided some insight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ITSOKTOCRY + gothboiqlique?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 03:27:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Title pretty much says it all, does anyone know if there is still any beef between them or if there is any possible projects between anyone? Absolutely love ITSOKTOCRY #8217;s new music and think it would work great with most of gbc? What are y #8217;alls thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 03:46:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean if y #8217;all did fuck then you most likely basically fucked peep. If so I hope you never wash your dick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 04:26:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ngl this is shit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 03:14:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would just add some highlights, both blue and gold. Looks great, just kinda flat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 19:01:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has potential, not that good honestly but I didn #8217;t expect much. Obviously sound quality and length can be improved but I don #8217;t hate the style of it all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 20:52:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely provide some nice mobility and decent shooting, not the best unit in the codex but definitely top half imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 05:25:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blue knights</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 05:32:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Despite being obviously 3 dimensional, it seems very flat. More like they are stuck in a giant puddle of Marshmellow cream then snow. I prefer a clean edge of the base and then material on top of it but obviously do whatever you like. As to how to make more realistic snow I #8217;m not quite sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 18:50:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://goo.gl/images/UuLyTB possibly?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 03:19:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t know man, it #8217;s gonna be costly whatever you do</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 06:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally just cause they look cool and fit in with the fluff</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Honest opinions on my WIP Magnus</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 06:52:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 06:54:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Specifically curious about your honest opinions on my wings and crotch cloak. Trust me when I say you won #8217;t hurt my feelings if you don #8217;t like it, I #8217;d really like to hear if you don #8217;t and why. All C amp;C welcome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 06:58:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Specifically curious about your honest opinions on my wings and crotch cloak. Trust me when I say you won #8217;t hurt my feelings if you don #8217;t like it, I #8217;d really like to hear if you don #8217;t and why. All C amp;C welcome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Honest opinions about my WIP Magnus the Red</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 07:08:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 07:09:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Specifically curious about your honest opinions on my wings and crotch cloak. Trust me when I say you won #8217;t hurt my feelings if you don #8217;t like it, I #8217;d really like to hear if you don #8217;t and why. All C amp;C welcome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 09:42:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re telling me that if you saw someone that you knew did drugs and passed out a lot, you would check on them to see if they are alive? No one thought that he was actually dead and obviously didn #8217;t want to disturb him. Don #8217;t go around calling people that you most likely loved before Peep #8217;s death  #8220;fucking idiots #8221; because you don #8217;t know how to handle your fucking sadness and need somebody to blame. Don #8217;t act like you would have done anything differently than his best friends, no one fucking murders their friend cause he was gonna leave the group. Stop acting like a crybaby and just accept that Peep is gone and it #8217;s nobody #8217;s fault.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 16:52:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>First of all, I don #8217;t hate you voice at all. Secondly, yeah day to day i normally find something new to hate about myself. As far as I know there is no real easy way to overcome this other than just accepting that life is shit and so is most everyone around you. Once you can appreciate the fact that you not a snobbish asshole that loves every part of yourself you can be glad your on the other end of the spectrum and other people won #8217;t hate you near as much as the snobbish asshole type people. As for actually dealing with it? I just make a bunch of self deprecating humor and make sure to just live my life, do my shit, and stay out of other peoples business.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 23:35:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>It took 10 years just for some Kabalites? Will take at least 15 more for the scourges I #8217;d say..... seriously tho they look great</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[H] dark eldar, eldar, harlequins, ynnari [W] 1k sons, PayPal, any other offers [LOC] TX, USA</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 02:55:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a lot of Drukhari/dark eldar I am willing to part with as well as some eldar. Everything is built unless stated otherwise and if it is listed as painted than I can guarantee it is not to the standard you would want but not lumpy at all so easy to paint over. Out of print models will be marked as well. LOTS SELLING, CONTACT ME IF YOURE STILL INTERESTED IN ANYTHING! Drukhari: HQ: Troops - Fast Attack - Heavy Support - Flyer - Dedicated transport - Eldar: HQ: Farseer - (singing spear) Warlock on Jetbike - primed (singing spear) Autarch with swooping hawk wings - (fusion pistol) Troops: 15x dire avengers - painted Elites: 1x bonesinger Fast attack - 6x windriders - painted (scatter lasers) Heavy Support - 2x wraithlords - (2x bright lances, 2x flamers, 1 ghostglaive each) War walker - (2x Shuriken cannons I think) Warp hunter - painted very well (not by me) Dedicated transport - Wave serpent (Shuriken Cannon I think) Harlequins: 2x skyweavers - primed (zephyrglaives) Ynnari : Feel free to make me an offer on anything you see. Also willing to make deals for larger purchases. (Items you see are still available). Thanks a lot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 04:17:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry man, trying to focus on 40k rn. Shoot me an offer if your interested in any DE models tho, like I said, lots of spare parts as well (guns, heads, spikes, etc.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 04:50:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Criticize? It #8217;s shit, probably like your painting and modeling skills. Your gonna spend half a year painting up a bunch of miniatures that no one gives a shit about just to show them to your girlfriend that you only had cause she thought you were normal and she #8217;s gonna break up with you because of how much a nerd you are and you suck at painting. Then you #8217;ll get depressed, never find love again, resort to loneliness, start painting professionally, actually become decent at it by the time your depression/loneliness catches up to you and you finally end it all. But other than that, I like it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 06:07:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>The dick drapery probably looks like it is not actually highlighted because it isn #8217;t. I #8217;m gonna redo it, probably a stereotypical clean, white one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 06:49:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/gallery/Xj1d3 that should have most of the pictures. The voidraven might sell but everything is first come first serve so feel free to make me an offer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 07:00:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with everything your saying but don #8217;t dismiss a sorcerer in terminator armor, he #8217;s cheap, durable, and doesn #8217;t use your command points to deep strike behind a unit of Tzaangors/rubricae/SOT to support them. Just one of my personal favorite strategies concerning hq #8217;s.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thousand sons rules question + forgeworld opinions</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 03:23:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>First of all, just curious, if something has d3 or d6 damage, would the all is dust rule apply if they roll a 1? I would assume not since damage is rolled after save but I am curious. Secondly, I would just like to say that I do not play competitively, just for fun. I am acquiring a storm eagle and kytan soon and curious if anyone has used them or has any opinions about them. I #8217;m looking at putting 20 rubricae in the storm eagle, I probably won #8217;t use the Kytan since I own Magnus but Kytan just looks so badass that I feel compelled to at least try it out. Finally, how do you feel about cultist spam?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 03:49:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol thin your paints</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 16:58:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tzeentch daemons are great but they work best when mixed with thousand sons in my opinion to provide some stronger units. Horrors are great, 9 brimstones with 1 blue (to cast smite without dying) is one of the cheapest smite batteries coming it at only 32 points. Also the best way to fill up a battalion. The changeling is pretty much your best buff hq along with the your heralds. Whether you take chariot, disc or just on foot depends on what you are going to be running it alongside and how many points you have to spare. Flamers are some of the best anti-horde units right now due to their weapons being pistols and you can use them in combat. Exalted flamers can be used in pretty much any role. Screamers are your objective grabbers, somewhat underrated imo. Kairos/LoC are good just overpriced. Other units all have their uses but are not standout units imo. As for allying with thousand sons, rubric marines are very durable and provide good consistent fire if you have the points. SOT is great alpha strike units, but once again, expensive. All daemon engines can be great, I prefer using them as distraction carnifex rather than actual damage dealers, but they can be that as well. Tzaangors are your best melee unit you have available to you (despite how ugly they are). Exalted sorcerers and the like are great support units. TL;DR I suggest allying with thousand sons. Horrors, screamers, flamers, exalted flamers, rubricae, SOT, daemon engines, and exalted sorcerers are all great and will fill vital roles on the battlefield. Also look through r/thousandsons. They have great unit summaries including daemon ones.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 17:25:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>As someone who play dark eldar, the best thing about them is that they are fast, don #8217;t bother trying to hide valuable units far away or in cover because somehow dark eldar will get within range with something you forgot about. Dark eldar are literally a glass cannon, very powerful (most everything either wounds on a 4+ on everything or is s8 ap-4 d 3 or 6) use whatever units you like just know to focus fire on a single unit until it is destroyed. Units only get more powerful as the turns go on so I suggest not trying to wait then out by just sitting on objectives. It #8217;s hard to give strategies without knowing his list but I hope this helped.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 21:02:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friend says I play competitive LEGOs but not really made fun of no</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 04:43:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gotta love those transgenre men</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 19:59:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Talons are normally your best bet in game, however also look lame af imo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[H] $$$, PayPal [W] Thousand Sons/Chaos [LOC] Tx, USA</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 20:05:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Title basically says it all, I #8217;m looking to purchase thousand sons/generic chaos pieces. I #8217;d prefer nib or nos but am open. The only thing I don #8217;t need is Rubric Marines and Magnus so don #8217;t bother with those but pm with any offers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 22:25:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good lord, people really don #8217;t know how to google things do they. Her name is lulo, her insta is itslulo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 22:28:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Np :) let me know if I can be an asshole again. Glad I could help buddy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 22:48:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not a perfect list but it #8217;s the best I could make from what you have  #160; **++ Patrol Detachment (Chaos - Thousand Sons) [30 PL, 521pts] ++** **+ HQ +** **Daemon Prince of Tzeentch [9 PL, 180pts]:** Malefic talon, Wings **+ Troops +** **Rubric Marines [14 PL, 220pts]** . **Aspiring Sorcerer:** Force stave, Inferno Bolt Pistol . **8x Rubric Marine w/ Inferno Boltgun:** 8x Inferno boltgun . **Rubric Marine w/ Soulreaper cannon:** Soulreaper cannon **Tzaangors [4 PL, 70pts]:** 9x Tzaangor w/ Tzaangor Blades . **Twistbray:** Tzaangor blades **+ Fast Attack +** **Tzaangor Enlightened [3 PL, 51pts]:** Aviarch, 2x Enlightened, Fatecaster greatbows **++ Battalion Detachment +3CP (Chaos - Daemons) [64 PL, 1144pts] ++** **+ No Force Org Slot +** **Chaos Allegiance:** Tzeentch **+ HQ +** **Fateskimmer [8 PL, 150pts]** **Kairos Fateweaver [19 PL, 370pts]** **The Changeling [5 PL, 100pts]** **+ Troops +** **Horrors [12 PL, 190pts]:** 10x Blue Horror, 20x Pink Horror **Horrors [4 PL, 32pts]:** 3x Blue Horror, 9x Pair of Brimstone Horrors **Horrors [4 PL, 32pts]:** 3x Blue Horror, 9x Pair of Brimstone Horrors **+ Elites +** **Flamers [4 PL, 84pts]:** 2x Flamer, Pyrocaster **+ Fast Attack +** **Screamers [4 PL, 93pts]:** 3x Screamer **Screamers [4 PL, 93pts]:** 3x Screamer **++ Supreme Command Detachment +1CP (Chaos - Thousand Sons) [18 PL, 312pts] ++** **+ HQ +** **Sorcerer [6 PL, 104pts]:** Force sword, Inferno Bolt Pistol **Sorcerer [6 PL, 104pts]:** Force sword, Inferno Bolt Pistol **Sorcerer [6 PL, 104pts]:** Force sword, Inferno Bolt Pistol Total: [112 PL, 1997pts] I don #8217;t love Kairos or LoC but you need some sort of big threat imo. You don #8217;t have to include the flamers/screamers in the list if you #8217;d like and instead summon them in but I just put them there for point values. Basically the big block of pink horrors is that big so as to bump up weapons to assault 3, the blues are just there to kill of first as a buffer. The brimstone/blue groups are just cheap objective holders/smite batteries/detachment fillers, nothing special but make sure to cast smite with your blues so a brimstone doesn #8217;t die every time. The sorcerers work best as buff units, not sure if you need 3 of them but it gives you an extra command point so might as well. The daemon prince works well in the midst of the fight buffing and attacking everything around him. In the future tho I would get more tzaangors so they can become your threat instead of Kairos (nice but not very competitive for the points), a block of 30 tzaangors supported by a shaman can do some crazy damage. Rubricae are great for durable units which you don #8217;t have a lot of. Other than that just play a lot of games against different armies to figure out what you like and what works best for your play style Let us know what you decide and how it goes :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 23:00:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m sure you #8217;ve heard countless people tell you to pick what you like aesthetically so I will spare telling you again. Eldar - one of my personal favorite armies, a wraith army is completely viable. I absolutely love all things wraith. Wraithguard with d-scythes can absolutely destroy most infantry and basically anything else within range. I #8217;ve dropped down 10 wraithguard with d-cannons and dealt 23 wounds to an imperial knight (not statistically correct but possible). Wraithblades are some of the best melee units available, I prefer their shooty cousins but it #8217;s fun to switch it up. Wraithlords are great as either cheap dual flamers/ghostglaive melee units or weapons platforms with a couple bright lances on the shoulders. Spiritseers, warlocks, and farseers all support these units extremely well. I still love my wraithknights as if they were my children but sadly it is hard to justify 500 points for 2 cannons... feel free to pm me for any questions about eldar/allies/strategies Orks- never played them myself but have played against them in 7th edition they were the army that was for people that just wanted to have fun, however, they know are up to a competitive level as well due to the horde meta right now. Before you commit to playing orks make sure you really love the look of them because you will most likely be looking at a lot of them. I can #8217;t offer many strategies other than buy units you like the look of and have fun with them though. Tyranids- definitely a very powerful and versatile army right now. Gaunt spam is a meta list rn but once again, only fun if you want to build and paint and transport and repair and care for that many models. However they also have the ability to run as a more elite army and dish out some nasty mortal wounds. I am partial to eldar but they are all amazing armies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 23:06:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was just for points, I initially had a separate but of 10 pinks before getting rid of it and forgot to put the pinks anywhere else. It #8217;s a loose list, just giving you ideas. If you #8217;d rather run 10 pinks with the ability to split into 20 blues and 20 brims then go for. That is 230 points for the most annoying unit anyone will ever face ( except for 30 pinks splitting into 60 blues and 60 brims of course). Don #8217;t expect to learn you #8217;re entire army from staring at datasheetd, scrolling through forums, and playing 1 game. Learn from experience and have fun while doing it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 23:15:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel that, try cheating and telling your opponents that units are stronger than they are, sneak models onto the table, pick up dice before you opponent can see them, forge your unit prices, etc. make sure to accuse your opponent of cheating as well to make sure they don #8217;t do it to you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 23:16:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol meant to come out sarcastic, might have sounded serious, my bad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 07:39:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well well well, welcome to the universe that will soon take over your life if it hasn #8217;t already. I #8217;m not sure how much you know so I #8217;m going to try and be very basic, I apologize if this is all repeated information. The best advice I can give is to find someone that is either already part of the warhammer universe and can mentor you or someone just starting out as well that can learn with you. Learn about your local game store and go and meet the people, don #8217;t be afraid to talk to someone and ask about their game or advice or if you can just watch them play, as far as I have seen the warhammer community is one of the nicest groups of people. As long as your not rude about it, I promise that people won #8217;t mind helping you out. Aside from that here is my best introduction/army overviews/where to start Warhammer is divided into three groups, imperium (good), chaos (bad), and xenos (aliens (neutral?)) Within each of these groups is many different factions, each of them playing differently from each other Imperium- these are your main protagonists in the stories and the armies consist of: countless chapters of space marines, grey knights, Astra Militarum/imperial guard, adeptus custodes, and other factions and smaller sub factions as well. Most of these armies are going to more elite armies: less models, more versatile, stronger individual models. Chaos - these are your main antagonists in the stories and the armies consist of factions devote to the four chaos gods: World eaters (Khorne), Death Guard (Nurgle), Thousand Sons (Tzeentch ), and Emperor #8217;s children (Slaanesh). As well as other neutral factions and daemons. These armies are somewhat elite normally as well but also include many gruesome monsters and other beings. Xenos - this is pretty much everything else. The main factions are Aeldari, Tyranids, Tau, Orks, and Necrons. These guys have your main horde armies as well as some elite aspects as well. Obviously that was a very brief overview of each faction but from here you have to decide on an army to play. The best way to go about doing this is to look all over the internet at pictures and things like that and decide based on an armies aesthetic first, background second, and playstyle lastly. Many armies have their own Start Collecting boxes which involve normally all the models you will need to build a small fun detachment to build off of. If you are interested in space marines or death guard then they can be found in the Dark Imperium or First Strike boxes You will also need a rule book, your armies codex if they have one (if not their rules can be found in an index instead), and countless other accessories that will accumulate as you begin to truly model and play. I hope I answered some of your questions TL;DR You #8217;re local gamers will be able you much more than anyone on the internet can. Choose an army that you like the look of and dive in headfirst. Please message me if you have any questions about specific armies/strategies/rules questions/embarrassing noob questions/anything else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 07:57:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>*insert name* words can #8217;t explain the way I feel ABOUT U. No other GIRLS come close to you. THE LAST THING I WANNA DO is miss an opportunity to be with you.  #8220;One more chance baby go to prom with me? #8221; Capitalized words are song names. The last line is a line from Kiss: one more chance baby give me a kiss. He also has a song called YOUR EYES which you could incorporate. He also has one called NUTS which could be funny if you could work that in. As for as inside jokes there not really many unless you wanna make some perverse joke about Peeps friends killing him and you would never do that to her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 15:26:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is no army that is going to get crushed every time, everything can be built well enough to hold its own its 8th edition which is why I emphasize to buy what you enjoy looking at and build and paint them really well so you have something you #8217;re proud of</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 18:59:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Short answer: no, one is not necessarily better than the other. Long answer: games workshop released Warhammer Fantasy and Warhammer 40k around the same time a long time ago. Warhammer fantasy was discontinued in 2013 and age of Sigmar is basically a continuation of it. 40k is more futuristic, space related, big guns, giant tanks, things like that. Sigmar is more fantasy creature and monsters, dragons, ancient fantasy stuff. Gameplay wise they are similar in the aspect of someone new looking at them both but they are different to most actually players just between strategies, typical gameplays, etc. 40k is more popular atm and I suspect it will stay that way but Sigmar is not far behind at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 19:03:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you thinking more wise? If so then spiritseers would typically lead a wraith army, they also do well in game. Other options for in-game strategy would be warlocks (I prefer desperate than in a conclave) because most of their powers buff wraith units very well (quicken is an amazing power on wraithguard). Avatar of Khaine is expensive but provides a nice little buff, not very accurate fluff wise I suppose. Obviously farseers are your go to universal hq tho. Edit: archons are not great imo, I only use them because they are cheap and can help fill a battalion, their 2++ is nice but other than that they do not have much of a role on the battlefield. Shadowseers are great models imo and a good way to get access to harlequin powers. Never used them myself though so can #8217;t speak to much about them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 19:08:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks good so far, just be patient, take your time to work on those little mistakes that will really help bring the model to life. But on the contrary not everything has to be perfect, there is a point of diminishing return. Find that balance and you will be cranking out beautiful models in no time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 17:57:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks good, only thing I can think off is it #8217;s weird seeing such clean fur with such bloody wounds, you could have some of the blood from the wounds kind of trickle down the legs and stain the fur or something like that. Realistically the blood wouldn #8217;t just pool in the wounds and nowhere else</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 23:43:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Instead of chaos forming from the gods decieving Primarchs I would assume that the emperor would build his perfect webway and all Primarchs would come together and even most of xenos would either be dead or allied with imperium for a very small time until someone got really pissed about something and basically the [insert name] heresy happens. Disagreement would be inevitable imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Forgeworld/Kytan ravager question</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 02:33:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I understand from the forgeworld faq that the kytan ravager cannot take the thousand sons keyword (correct?) anyways, if I take him in a seperate super-heavy auxiliary detachment it doesn #8217;t really matter the keyword, I would still be battleforged wouldn #8217;t I ?just asking for clarification about the keywords and all</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anyone else stay up until 7am painting and watching Netflix?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 19:07:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 16:30:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>End of the f***ing world was great, but short. Supernatural is great and long if your into that, arrested development is funny. Just a few of the things I watch while I paint</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 16:52:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks good so far, imo opinion I prefer flamers/exalted flamers instead of the heldrake, but the heldrake is a great model if that is why you like it. Also I would consider a sorcerer in terminator armor instead of the second daemon prince, that way you can support a unit that deep strikes in. Other than that, looks pretty good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 17:02:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, I love every part of it. However, I can #8217;t see warhammer changing this much anytime soon. Sooooo..... MAKE YOUR OWN GAME!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rules question</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 20:39:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there any firing arcs in 8th edition? Mostly asking for vehicles, for example can a vindicator only shoot straight forward or can he also shoot sideways as long as he has los, or could he even shoot backwards? Logically firing arcs should be a thing but I #8217;m can #8217;t find anything about it. Is it more of a house rule or is there a specific rule stating firing arcs/los. Thanks a lot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 20:42:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>So a vindicator Cannon can shoot backwards? Or would los come from the Cannon itself and since the tank is in the way it would block los?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 01:54:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ulthuan gray-nihilakh oxide-celestra gray-white scar gives a very nice light gray imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 18:15:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would drop the chaos spawn and either change to a patrol detachment and add more tzaangors or just replace them with enlightened.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 22:52:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not in love with the blood covered bases but other than that they look really nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 01:45:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good trade!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anyone know where I could get these or similar headpiece for my Kytan I am going to convert to use in my thousand sons army</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 04:31:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m aware the kytan cannot actually take the thousand sons or Tzeentch keyword but I still want to use him and am wondering if anyone knows where these headpieces might be from https://imgur.com/gallery/Q9PnQ . Specifically the one for the kytan but the knight would most likely work as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 16:24:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks great, are most of those conversion parts from SOT? Also where is the base from. Sorry if these are obvious questions but planning on making one soon and that is basically what I am going for. Any help would be appreciated</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 18:02:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because I haven #8217;t died yet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-10 00:54:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly the army painters wargamer regiment brush is very universal imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 03:57:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Best way to get steady hands is just take a bunch of drugs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 05:03:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not sure how much you know but  #8220;old warhammer #8221; (fantasy) is actually discontinued by games workshop. Age of Sigmar is supposedly a continuation of it. Technically you can still collect and play fantasy but it #8217;s is very hard to actually find the pieces/someone to play with. Sigmar should have most of what you are looking for in the fantasy realm without being actual warhammer fantasy. I don #8217;t know too much about Sigmar but it is popular in some places, sometimes even more than 40k. That said, 40k is easily the most popular imo. It won #8217;t have as much fantasy aspects but does have some great lore and storylines if you are interested in that. 40k probably has the best gameplay atm just because it recently had a new edition and faq #8217;s and things come out. TL;DR play whatever you want but 40k is most popular</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 00:30:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks great only thing I can see is that the green stuff looks exactly like what it is, green stuff. If you could somehow incorporate into other parts of the model maybe, not sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 00:58:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eldar can be built somewhat like that: wraithblades, wraithlord, and wraithknight combos. Outside of wraith units you have striking scorpions, howling banshees, storm guardians, and shining spears. Very versatile and fun army to play. If you want to be more competitive back then up with some dark reapers or rangers for some good firepower.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 02:30:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely, the meta army rn is dark reaper spam combined with some fast troops but if you are looking for a fun CC oriented army then you would be looking at things like: Storm guardians - not my favorite unit. Literally just your average guardians but armed with pistols and twin-linked blades. Best part is they are cheap at only 7 points a model. Could be nice combo due to shooting pistols in combat but not real game changers imo. Howling banshees/striking scorpions - both very similar units. Decent point cost (13/14 respectively), pretty fragile, hit decently, pretty fast. Banshees are more defensive and scorpions more offensive but both can be used as tarpit units or melee counters for melee heavy lists. Do decently against MEQs, die very easily to shooting. These are decent overall, fun to play, definitely not game changers though. Wraithblades - extremely fun/scary to play. Very powerful, high point cost, somewhat survivable. Only reason I say they are survivable is due to 3 sounds a piece and a 3+ possible 4++. If plan on hitting MEQs or other infantry units, you might want swords to be able to get an extra attack but axe/shield combo is always justifiable imo. That sweet 4++, +2 strength along with d3 damage can kill just about anything you send it against. I find them best in wave serpents so as to keep them alive until they are needed. Your opponent will target these because they are scary and powerful. These are expensive though, 29 for swords and 39 for axe/shield. Shining spears - I know you don #8217;t like jetbikes but I can #8217;t not mention these guys, I #8217;ll keep it short, but just let me have my fun. These guys can charge in a literally kill pretty much whatever they want. 2 wounds a piece and 2 attacks at s 6 on charge, -4 ap, 2 damage is seriously no joke. One of your best melee units. Wraithlord - your main big boy this edition. Arm him with 2 flamers and a ghostglaive for 131 points of 10 wounds, 3+ save, 8 #8221; movement, 4 attacks, s 9, -4 ap, d6 damage, kill everything around it monster. I am a little biased due to the fact that I just love this model. It can definitely make up its points though and has the capability of being a heavy weapons platform as well. Honestly not to expensive imo as it is basically eldar #8217;s dreadnought. Wraithknight - sadly you will not see much of these big(ger) boys on table anytime soon. Clocking in at 452 points it has an impressive 24 wounds but less impressive 3+ 5++. T8 is nice but doesn #8217;t make it invulnerable. S x2, AP -4, 6 damage is great at killing larger models but rarely makes up its points imo. It can fall back and charge/move over infantry models which removes any tarpit threat. It #8217;s hard to not include the signature of big model of eldar but sadly it takes up too many of your precious points imo. HQ- if you are taking aspect warriors then their corresponding Phoenix lord is a nice buff. Warlocks are amazing due to their points and access to 12 powers in total. Autarchs are a nice way to get command points back. Spirit seers are great buffs for wraith units allowing them to reroll 1 #8217;s. Farseers are you main HQ and give some great psychic support for not too many points. Avatar of Khaine is somewhat hard to justify for his points but really fun to play imo, he also allows retooling of charge ranges within 12 inches. If you want one of the best psychers in the game then you can take eldrad as well. Outside of melee units, dark reapers and rangers are still nearly auto includes even in a melee list simply to provide needed firepower from the back line or any objective you are camping. Wave serpents obviously are you only transport option so should consider a couple at least to move around your most important units. 3x fire prisms is a deadly combo with their strategem and special rules. Hemlocks are nice (honestly a psycher flyer is just badass imo). Craftworld attribute - Alaitoc is pretty useless considering you want to be within 12 inches. Biel-tan as well considering you won #8217;t have many Shuriken weapons. Iyanden is decent but you have better options. Saim-Hann is definitely nice being able to reroll charges. Ulthw #233; gives a little more durability and should be considered. The only other thing you might consider is running an ynnari detachment. FAQ definitely needed them allowing only 1 of each choice and not on your opponents turn but a max unit of reapers firing twice, a melee unit killing one group only to automatically charge into the next, some of your faster units moving double up the field are all helpful. Ynnari also gives access to any of the three characters (which all can hold their own) and Drukhari/harlequins. Drukhari might completely change with the release of their codex but wyches are similar to storm guardians but faster and a little more fragile. Incubi are really cool and hit decently hard. Harlequin troops are very fast and can provide some very powerful melee attacks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 04:26:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Skills</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why Right Here w/HorseHead by Lil Peep is the best lil peep + horsehead collab song</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 04:38:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because fuck you that #8217;s why</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Every time I build something</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 04:53:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Before actually building:  #8220;I #8217;m gonna magnetize every arm and sub-assemble everything so I can paint it perfectly. I #8217;m gonna paint the base before putting the miniature on that way it #8217;s perfect. I #8217;m gonna take my time and do everything right. #8221; 12 minutes after receiving my package from gamesworkshop: *everything assembled, glued on the base, and covered in super glue and sprue bits*  #8220;Maybe next time #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 04:56:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kraft world eldar: the galaxy of crappy cheese</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 05:41:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>sOuTH ParK PrEDicTEd liL pEEp #8217;S DeaTh?!?!?!?!?!?!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 20:21:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>R/40klore</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shooty or melee helbrutes?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 20:55:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am building my thousand sons army at the moment and so far I have: Ahriman on disc Sorcerer in terminator armour 3x rubricae 2x SOT Magnus 2x Helbrutes 60 cultist I #8217;m planning on deep striking in a big block of rubrics, SOT, and sorcerer. I #8217;ll have 2 MSU rubrics and cultists holding objectives/cleaning up etc. Magnus will try to cast as many powers as possible and butt rape everything in sight. Ahriman is mostly to support where needed but can also neuter some characters. My questions comes with whether to have some missile/Lascannon helbrutes sitting in the back and popping off the strategem do double shoot the closest vehicle or just go crazy with fist and scourge to turn the butt rape into a gangbang. Keep in mind I mostly play against grey knights paladin spam and a really crappy ultra marines list that I beat everytime without trying (my friends are broke boys and won #8217;t upgrade their armies). Any and all help is appreciated</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 03:11:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why twin fist instead of fist + scourge to add 3 more attacks? Just points?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 03:12:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely going to magnetize. Has the reaper auto cannon worked for you? Seems like a waste of points imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 03:12:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree about the contemptor but my friends don #8217;t love the idea of forgeworld so I #8217;m trying to get something more casual</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 03:14:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have never loved predators in a thousand sons army. Just don #8217;t seem to fit. They might perform well in game but not what I #8217;m looking for</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 03:14:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I definitely like the Decimators a lot but trying to stay away from forgeworld at the moment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>8th edition Kill Team?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 04:07:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone know the release date? Also, is it similar to 7e kill team?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 05:57:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very very light/watered down nuln oil should work. I cannot emphasize on how light this should be though. Just the tinies amount actually in the creases otherwise it will darken the entire pieces and make it look dirty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 08:57:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks great, for some reason I don #8217;t love the blue feet. Not sure what to change but just seems very...blue... also, what #8217;s your recipe for the flesh?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 05:09:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks great, personally I just hate the look of powerfists, never have liked them, doubt I ever will but that #8217;s just me. Also I don #8217;t like the skull on top of the angel baby thing, looks out of place. Love the paint job though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 05:19:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ooh buddy, always glue a piece on right after cutting it out or have a designated place to put it specifically for that reason. Building should be one of the quickest parts, take your time but probably not that much time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 06:05:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do some cocaine, balances it out. Trust me I #8217;m a doctor</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any and all prayers for my sanity in this time of need are appreciated. 30x Rubric Marines</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 06:08:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Possibly alternate color scheme for rubric marines (view latest post)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 19:20:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/gallery/l4vLf What are your thoughts? Traditional or reverse? I #8217;m leaning towards traditional. Everything is WIP so don #8217;t judge quality yet, only have the base colors on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 19:35:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mixed thousand sons blue with Vallejo #8217;s metallic medium but all I really saw it do is brighten it up, not really make it metallisized. If I paint more like this I will just use the regular thousand sons blue with a light nuln oil wash.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 23:04:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dark eldar wise you basically just want them for blaster spam. Either MSU of kabalites in venoms (4 rifles, and 1 blaster + double cannon venom=145 points) or blasterborn (true born w/ 4 blasters and 1 rifle+ double cannon venom= 210) a few of those will deal out some major damage but make sure you have some sort of distraction carnifex (big scary defensive model that the enemy will dump shots into and focus on for hopefully multiple turn) a sword+shield wraithknight could definitely do the trick. So now your looking at a big wraithknight with some psychic support swinging at everything in range, probably 2 squads of d-scythe wraithguard in wave serpents or webway striking into the battlefield and absolutely raping everything in sight, a few squads of blaster boys to pop any vehicles/multi-wound models. Throw in a couple razor wings for more firepower or even a hemlock for some fun flying psychic shenanigans (not great this edition but definitely fun). You could consider kabalites in a raider with 9 rifles and 1 cannon. Within 12 inches these guys are throwing 24 shots hitting on 3+ and wounding on 4s always (consider shooting at high toughness targets with these guys), these aren #8217;t great against hordes as their special rule is actually worse then just strength 4. I #8217;ve had these guys take down Guilliman single-handedly before (not likely but possible). One of my favorite eldar combos is 3 fire prisms. Put 2 in heavy cover in the back corners and the other somewhat in the open so it can see targets. As long as they move less then half distance and can see each other you can fire 6 shots of your choice at a single target rerolling hits and wounds for 1 cp (linked fire + special rule). Also remember that there is a big FAQ soon and Drukhari will get a codex soon so everything I said might change.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Psychic phase clarification</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 23:39:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>When in the psychic phase does each character have to cast as many psychic powers as he wants and then move on or can I alternate psykers? In other words can Ahriman cast 1 power then Magnus cast 1 and then Ahriman cast another? Or can I not go back to a psyker after another has already casted. I know it #8217;s confusing wording but I hope you understand what I #8217;m asking</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 01:58:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you don #8217;t mind me asking, what lightbox did you get?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 03:16:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you look at my later post, I have painted one where I painted the trim and the other where paint the flat spaces and honestly I didn #8217;t find much differences. The main reason I do this is because it is actually retributor armour spray so if I need to touch something up I can with retributor armour paint instead of spraying some random blue and touching up with a different one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 08:00:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks good for a first attempt. Just work on that blending to make it more gradient and no sharp lines. https://youtu.be/hWfSMYJg9Kg this is a great reference video to help with wet blending. Obviously you don #8217;t need as many colors as him to start out with but working towards that perfect gradient is your ultimate goal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 08:23:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically it #8217;s to keep the tip of the brush at a point and to clean it off so he can go right on to his next color without having to dip into water jar. Definitely not necessary step. He has very little paint on his brush anyways though that it doesn #8217;t really matter, nor suggested with a loaded brush</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 17:49:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly I use the superglue from the dollar store right next to my house that way I really don #8217;t care if it dries out cause it was only 50 cents a tube. It works fine for what I do, probably not a professional level but like I said, it gets the job done</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 05:35:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great video! Love the editing and clips you chose! Stay grinding</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 05:38:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>She #8217;s still going to painting those when her great grandchildren are born</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 05:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Feel like his crotch area needs some more contrast, maybe a darker color or something but it just kind of blends in imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 05:47:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I accept donations</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 05:48:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn good job spraying them all the same color. You gonna paint them? Lol jk, they look really good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 06:09:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>tWO tHiN CoATs!!!!!!!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 06:11:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally instead of thinning my paints I just drink the whole jar and then when I pee it out it is about the perfect consistency. Side note: Metallics have a fun effect on your poop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 01:56:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lick your brush, sounds stupid but it makes I into a super sharp point. https://youtu.be/hWfSMYJg9Kg this has some great tips</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hellbrute melee options</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 03:56:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just curious, I #8217;ve heard a decent amount of people opting for double fists on hellbrutes. Is there any advantage to double fist or a single one? I mean as far as I can see there is no difference since you just pick one weapon to fight with so I suppose it is just for points? Any enlightenment would be appreciated as well as how you like to run them, I plan on magnetizing but just curious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 04:43:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where does it say it gives an extra attack? I couldn #8217;t find that anywhere</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 05:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol my bad apparently I #8217;m blind</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 14:50:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>He bout to twist his ankle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 15:45:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Merch or music? Or both?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 21:01:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>None of my friends had seen it so just thought I #8217;d share in case</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 21:06:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely Horus, freakin loser got owned</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 21:53:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>The number of attacks a model has is solely for close combat (fight phase). In the shooting phase you can shoot as many weapons as you like at as many shots as each has (assault 2=2 shots (some exceptions apply)). In the fight phase a model gets a certain number of attacks that it can split among however many weapons it wants, if it has 2 attacks and 34 weapons then it only gets to hit twice with one or once with one and once with another. If it has 34 attacks and 2 weapons it can divide those attacks up or use one weapon for all. I #8217;m not sure the exact model your speaking of so I can #8217;t clarify that but I hope I helped, let me know if you have any questions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 20:54:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would use thousand sons blue + retributor armour. All hail Ahriman, Magnus did nothing wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 04:15:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imo it #8217;s a little corny but corny tattoos are the best, personally I absolutely love just crybaby album cover or even just the word hellboy in his font but you do you man, if it has meaning to you then do it for sure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 14:17:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Magnus did nothing wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 15:32:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>More of those bases, just put those on the field and proxy whatever you. 12 of them glued together? Wraithknight! 40 of them glued together? Titan!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 20:48:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>1 thick coat is always better than whatever attempt at even coloring he did</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 02:14:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you are using the sorcerer in terminator armour the chaos terminator lord comes with a little guy that you can put on the base</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 02:40:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some paints</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 02:44:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you ever considered joining the medical field? An IQ like that could cure cancer in no time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 02:56:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, those brushes should do just fine but I can #8217;t guarantee it because I have never used them, imo 12 brushes seems a bit excessive but you do you. I bought the Army Painters Wargamers most wanted brush set https://www.amazon.com/Miniatures-Paint-Brush-Miniature-Brushes/dp/B007H4YR8S . Honestly these have been the best for me, the insane detail brush is one of my all time favorites for detail and the regiment is great for any kind of base coating or medium-large size miniatures. The small drybrush is great for highlighting and (obviously) dry brushing if you #8217;re into that (you should be).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 04:18:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could just do the helmet because faces are for pussies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 17:53:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thousand sons? Not much unit variation but if you haven #8217;t killed yourself by the time you finish painting them then you #8217;re well along your way to a beautiful army</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 17:56:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only thing Magnus has done wrong is not smite your puny ass into oblivion yet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 00:06:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Favorite song</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 00:08:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where did you get the head?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 00:46:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait, doesn #8217;t everyone? Is this not normal?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 15:03:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely the hub, looks the most realistic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 23:51:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Needs some sort of cohesion between top and bottom, I have no problem with different colored tops but it needs to tie in a little more imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 23:58:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Surprise! Everyone #8217;s a pussy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 06:49:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally I would drop the predator you already have and run double hellbrutes. You still have twin Lascannon and then the missile launcher replaces your auto cannon so you have generally the same load out. However you don #8217;t have a degrading wound chart and have better strategems available. Also I personally don #8217;t think boxes fit a thousand sons army very well, I like the hellbrutes model as well. Edit: it also saves you some points to put somewhere else (about 33 per model)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 17:19:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>OP was using predators with 2 Lascannon sand reaper autocannon so I was referring to dropping the predator he already has and replacing it with a Hellbrute and then also filling in his extra spot with a Hellbrute. Hellbrute is 147 and predator is 180.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 17:29:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Magnus did nothing wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 17:58:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be amazing for kill team or other small games like that. Looking forward to the finished project</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 05:18:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Correction: ...on a 1+... no one can ever fire</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 06:20:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Easter daemons if nurgle never fail</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 15:22:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, if you haven #8217;t already, look at the Drukhari previews that have been released, they were a very challenging/unforgiving army to play previously but I think their codex is going to round them out very well so they are both powerful, tough, and fast. I would wait a little bit until the codex fully drops though as I think list building might be harder than playing them due to so many different  #8220;alignments #8221; so to speak. Edit:also I love all of the drukhari models, nothing is really lacking imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 07:20:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>A lighter and hairspray</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 21:26:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good job</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 04:33:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>4x wraithknights. Would suck but might be fun in a doubles tournament or something paired with a horde army to overwhelm them then blast them into oblivion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 16:37:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t know exactly what you #8217;re talking about because I don #8217;t play ig but there should be a small list at the front unit pages where it introduces the data sheets, it #8217;s after all the lore and photos and lists not only the army special rules but the weapon lists. There there should be a  #8220;ranged weapons #8221; list. Hopefully some of that made sense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 17:18:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Asurmen: The Men of Asur*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 17:49:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Recipe?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 17:55:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly? I don #8217;t think any of them will blow up to Peep level or beyond. Peep was starting to get to the point where even people that didn #8217;t listen to this genre knew his name (sometimes). But the music industry is so saturated atm that I don #8217;t think there is room for actual talent and hard work to be famous. I think all of them deserve it but being famous right now comes from making one song that everyone loves or from being famous in 2012. I just don #8217;t think any fits that criteria</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 17:56:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh lol, looks beautiful though, have to commend your work</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>subject8481 #8217;s anus</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 20:16:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Paint scheme question</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 20:32:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I #8217;ve started painting rubric marines and I have thirty to do so I am wondering, I already started a few of them as a traditional color scheme but I #8217;m am curious as to whether or not I should switch it up for my next squad and do some other color scheme or just keep the same throughout. My only concern would be if I wanted to ever do a squad of twenty then I would have mixed paint schemes and also it wouldn #8217;t really look like a coherent army. Your thoughts? TL;DR same color scheme or switch it up? Edit: also, according to lore, would different sects ever be working together? For example maybe Ahriman brought his own and my sorcerer terminator lord brought his own and Magnus brought his as well? Just curious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 20:44:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s still ugly af imo, would prefer pretty much any other weapon simply for aesthetics, I don #8217;t care if it #8217;s the best melee weapon ever I #8217;m not putting a massive fucking swoled up hand that looks like he tried steroids for the first time without knowing he #8217;s allergic to everything in them but thinks that #8217;s all part of the process so keeps pumping steroids into his fucking hand. Why couldn #8217;t they just make some advanced robotic arm that punched harder than normal instead of some hand 180x bigger than a normal fist. Sorry, might be a bit biased but I don #8217;t like them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 20:52:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah the legendary headless marine, feared by all for being unstoppable as he can never be shot in the head</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 20:56:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Change them from crimson fists to headless marines, never take moral due to not knowing how many brothers have died. Absolute monsters in close combat as they swing so wildly they all get +1 attack but every hit roll of 1 hits the closest friendly. Also unit coherency is not a thing as they don #8217;t know where their brothers are so you can spread them out anywhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 21:23:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>hehe, Drukhari boob</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 08:01:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>F</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 06:06:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>My guys were just extra asshole-ish and got banished but then formed their own cult of the asshole</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to strip resin</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 06:15:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I recently acquired from a trade a Kytan ravager that is partially assembled and has a little bit of paint on it. I #8217;m assuming it was super glue but the guy I got it from did not know as he got it off eBay. Anyways, just wondering if there is any product that is great at removing glue bonds and paint but won #8217;t damage resin or plastic. Is there any products I should for sure stay away from? Is there any products I should for sure try out?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 06:20:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>He #8217;s red</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 06:26:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I found one from some sketchy site on the 3rd page of google results. Persistence is key in this situation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 19:00:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like some really great strategies, as for the support for Magnus, consider some tzaangor enlightened, they only move 12 compared to his 16 but that #8217;s more than any other infantry. Either have them throw some spears or charge in with him. Also if you want to get less competitive but more fun have a pair of heldrakes start on the back line then jump ahead first turn and tie up something for him to come destroy, alternatively they could clean up after him. I don #8217;t see the appeal of daemons other than horrors and changeling but that #8217;s just me, maybe save you some points in the future</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 20:41:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pussy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 05:00:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Use masking or painters tape to get straight lines, for example on that shield, paints could use a little more thinning in my opinion but it should look great once completed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 13:17:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really any hardware or even just department or grocery store should have it. It #8217;s pretty common. Bassically just paint the whole shield whatever color you want one side to be then once it is 100% dry you can put the tape on on half of it and paint the other, the tape is literally just not-as-sticky-as-other-tapes tape. You can paint the other color on then peel the tape off and theoretically no paint should be where the tape was. There should be tutorials online as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 14:13:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think this is in my garage somewhere still....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 00:07:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it #8217;s Chris Brown</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 00:47:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>They might (hopefully) be revamping the model but I haven #8217;t heard anything about it. Archons are such a crucial part of any de army that it #8217;s either just a glitch or something will be coming soon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 00:50:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>For sure, if anything does change I bet it will just be something along the lines of a dynamic pose or something. But this is completely speculation/what I want to happen. I doubt it actually will</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 21:44:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks great!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 22:07:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>The exalted sorcerer kit comes with tons of extra bits to make him more thousand sonsy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 05:19:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of the bluest blueberries to have ever blueberried</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 02:58:54</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8216;Ello</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 16:07:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m actually pretty colorblind so can never pick out colors for myself, I rarely ever paint anything without a tutorial or at least a bunch of research on the citadel paint app to make sure I #8217;m gonna buy the right color line. The app is amazing, I can look through all sorts of color gradients and just basically memorize what works well together instead of seeing it. But I have messed up more than a couple models by being lazy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 17:22:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would love some more angles</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 16:15:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Magnus did nothing wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 16:20:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just thin down some dirt and put it straight in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 20:09:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.forgeworld.co.uk/en-FR/Thousand-Sons-Legion-Transfer-Sheet-FW</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 15:23:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m not sure about some of the heads but the majority of everything is kabalite Warriors, I see body #8217;s, arms, extra bits, dark lances, and then also a dark reaper cannon at the front I believe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 15:52:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Upon further inspection, I #8217;m retarded. It #8217;s a disintegrator cannon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 02:18:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you used to many colors, I find it best to stick to only the 3 primary colors yours looks to colorful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sus boy waaaayyyy over sized</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-21 20:21:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just got my sus boy x lil peep shirt in. I legitimately thought they had sent me an XXL at first until I looked at the tag and saw it was in fact a L. I had heard they were oversized but never thought this much. Luckily my friend is going to buy it from me, I just wanted to rant/inform potential buyers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Did 6th edition exist?!?!?!?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 17:50:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everytime I see a  #8220;returning player #8221; or anyone like that, they have always  #8220;not played since 5th #8221; or before. From what I can see, 6th was only around for a couple years before 7th came out but did anyone play it? Did it suck? Was it the same as 5th? Just curious</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 00:56:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t know my dad is pretty old</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>More efficient warlord titan</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 04:34:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like with such a big body it would be more efficient to just duct tape as many bolters to it as possible. Can my mathhammer people calculate how many could fit on an average warlord titan?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 04:47:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright so duct tape guardsman to the titan and give them all modified bolters</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 04:54:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright but guardsmen attaches in any way to a warlord titan is a lot more intimidating then just a bunch of losers running on foot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 05:52:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read it at  #8220;Happy Allen Day #8221; and was confused as to why that little guy was Allen but I was okay with it honestly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 18:22:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Magnus did nothing wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 02:16:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>The main difference is that the older one doesn #8217;t come with/on a disc of tzeentch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 16:36:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree aesthetically/quality I just meant in-game differences. But yes you make a good point. OP - I suggest buying the newer model and magnetizing ahriman to the disk and the base so you can switch it out if needed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 22:39:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I still hate it when my brother rapes me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Favorite completely illegal combos?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 01:49:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Comment some of your favorite/most op completely illegal combos For example: d-scythe wraithguard in a raider Soul bursting an imperial knight Summoning primaris marines Etc...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 19:57:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depending on what he has either a nice painting station (however the best ones are diy so itd be hard to make without him knowing) or a nice airbrush/compressor I don #8217;t know much about them but the community sure can help, especially with that kind of budget</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 20:04:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can buy organizers and things like that but personal preference is what really makes them stand out. Maybe instead of surprising him you could just commission a really nice one. Basically set your budget and ask him what he wants them make something he will use everyday and remember</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>C amp;C my aspiring sorcerer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 21:41:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Recently started thousand sons and created my own custom sect and attempted to freehand some runes/iconography. Let me know what you think, no criticism is too harsh. https://imgur.com/gallery/dPLfnal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>C amp;C my aspiring sorcerer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 21:42:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Recently started thousand sons and created my own custom sect and attempted to freehand some runes/iconography. Let me know what you think, no criticism is too harsh. https://imgur.com/gallery/dPLfnal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 22:31:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate it, as far as finishing it: no I have not shaded or highlighted it yet, and I #8217;m aware I need cleanup, just got tired after like 4 hours straight working on it and needed to make sure I #8217;m headed in the right direction. And all of those symbols are just random lines I painted on, glad you like them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 15:56:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m colorblind</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 18:58:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t know man riding around with no hands is pretty dangerous, I say every time you move you have to roll a d6 for each model and on a 5+ they fall off and turn into a wych.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 19:53:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about literally just vomiting onto the field at the beginning of the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 19:54:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks great, personally I would do just a tad shade lighter because some of the details are obscured imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 06:09:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this an official model? I #8217;ve searched around and can only find some (seemingly) fan-made art. If you don #8217;t mind enlightening me as to what that is</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 06:51:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>The emperor is actually a hamster</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 18:37:43</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128525; #128525; she #8217;s perfect</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 18:46:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://soundcloud.com/joshua-holm-671521536/sets/lil-peep https://soundcloud.com/user-393552993/sets/brennan-savage https://soundcloud.com/user-942299448/sets/all-itsoktocry https://soundcloud.com/lilcynic/sets/wicca-phase-springs-eternal I don #8217;t know how emo you want to go but these are some of my favorite artists in order for those times where you would really just rather not exist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 19:46:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bring happy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 19:47:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 19:49:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Life is worth it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 22:13:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Helbrutes with double fists pop tanks with ease, 6 attacks on 3+ most likely wounding on 3+ with -3 ap and 3 damage is nothing to scoff at. I suppose it is more situation than say charging into a group of MEQs with a MVB (which I agree does amazing) but saving a Hellbrute, terminator sorcerer, and SOTs in deep strike until you can pop them close enough so you Hellbrute and can make a charge and SOT can shoot everything else is a decent strat imo. But I understand the versatility of MVB I just don #8217;t think they fulfill the same role and cannot be compared 1 to 1</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 00:27:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Turkey shuttles might be the best/most accurate description I have heard yet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 19:12:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean Magnus didn #8217;t do anything wrong so I see no reason not to play 1k sons</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 19:16:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>On a more serious not though I does fulfill your criteria of decently low model counts (in between Custodes/Grey Knights and regular marines) and also you will feel great after actually finishing a full squad. Personally I prefer actual thousand sons (Rubricae) then goat boys and flying goat boys (tzaangors). Also some of the best advice I can give is paint them with whatever colors you want, you can literally do anything</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 20:58:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly why to play 40k version, because she #8217;s a demon with a legion of automotans</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 21:04:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That pan is too hot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 21:05:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Daddy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 22:15:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then paint em red.... or orange or yellow or purple or black or any other color you want, tzeentch will approve, I promise</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 16:16:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmao nice meme</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Friendly-ish list (no possessed goats)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 16:32:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Playing on of my first really games with my thousand sons soon and just curious what you think of my list, gonna play against gray knights in just a show up and kill each other type of game, if any objectives they will just be collected at the end of the game. Any and all c amp;c is appreciated, main strategy is to march up with Magnus, Ahriman, and 10-man squad with the two MSU squads flanking/prioritizing target. SOT and sorc in term armour are deep striking in turn 2. Also, what psychic powers would you take? Any specific strategem in need to use? I #8217;m assuming DMC over HoTE to provide mobility for my SOT **++ Battalion Detachment +5CP (Chaos - Thousand Sons) [81 PL, 1526pts] ++** **+ No Force Org Slot +** **Relics of the Thousand Sons (1 Relic)** **+ HQ +** **Ahriman on Disc of Tzeentch [9 PL, 166pts]:** Diabolic Strength, Glamour of Tzeentch, Prescience **Sorcerer in Terminator Armour [8 PL, 140pts]:** Dark Matter Crystal, Familiar, Force stave, Inferno Combi-bolter, Warptime **+ Troops +** **Rubric Marines [14 PL, 220pts]** . **Aspiring Sorcerer:** Force stave, Inferno Bolt Pistol . **8x Rubric Marine w/ Inferno Boltgun:** 8x Inferno boltgun . **Rubric Marine w/ Soulreaper cannon:** Soulreaper cannon **Rubric Marines [7 PL, 107pts]** . **Aspiring Sorcerer:** Force stave, Inferno Bolt Pistol . **4x Rubric Marine w/ Inferno Boltgun:** 4x Inferno boltgun **Rubric Marines [7 PL, 107pts]** . **Aspiring Sorcerer:** Force stave, Inferno Bolt Pistol . **4x Rubric Marine w/ Inferno Boltgun:** 4x Inferno boltgun **+ Elites +** **Helbrute [7 PL, 157pts]:** Power scourge . **Helbrute fist:** Combi-bolter **Helbrute [7 PL, 157pts]:** Power scourge . **Helbrute fist:** Combi-bolter **Scarab Occult Terminators [22 PL, 472pts]:** 2x Hellfyre Missile Rack . **Scarab Occult Sorcerer:** Force stave, Inferno Combi-bolter . **7x Terminator:** 7x Inferno Combi-bolter, 7x Powersword . **Terminator w/ Heavy Weapon:** Power sword, Soulreaper cannon . **Terminator w/ Heavy Weapon:** Power sword, Soulreaper cannon **++ Super-Heavy Auxiliary Detachment (Chaos - Thousand Sons) [23 PL, 445pts] ++** **+ Lord of War +** **Magnus the Red [23 PL, 445pts]** **++ Total: [104 PL, 1971pts] ++**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 16:51:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Concentration of psychic powers, more shots (9 shooty guys instead of 8), taking advantage of dmc. Is there any advantage to 2 5-man squads?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 16:55:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m playing against my friend and I know what he has (a bunch of paladins basically) so I opted for the melee helbrutes instead of Lascannon/missile launcher I would usually take.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 17:51:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Battlescribe formats a little funky but it is 10 models, 1 sorcerer, 7 dudes, and 2 big gun dudes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 19:24:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Currently I don #8217;t have any of those models so that #8217;s what I #8217;m trying to do with the melee helbrutes. The only reason why my army is so elite is because this is what I have atm and also I prefer pure thousand sons (not possessed goats, flying possessed goats, or different colored blobs)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 21:25:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Magnus did nothing wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 04:56:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only 8 lighters?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 15:14:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 07:30:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Multi class with a light cleric for some fun</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 07:30:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dead</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 07:32:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>He has Tourette #8217;s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 05:25:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you Perturabo?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I am confusion</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 00:39:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>So just got back into the game after a decent break (maybe 6 months of so?) and I #8217;m exploring the new-to-me interface in the bag and I #8217;m pretty sure I understand the refinement points and all that but I have seen a couple places now that you can refine artifact weapons into each other (ie: refine weapon A by using weapon B) however when I try to do this is it always just gives me the option to convert weapon B to RP (like 75 (doesn #8217;t seem worth it)). I remember seeing something about it being double refinement when going into other weapons so I assume there must be a different way that I #8217;m missing. (Playing on ps4 btw) just looking for some clarity/refining strategy as well. Sorry if it #8217;s a little confusing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 00:42:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>75 if you include the goat daddies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 08:52:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you tried using magnets?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 15:29:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally I like semi-circles</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 16:07:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are feeder artifacts still a thing?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 18:00:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>With the new rp process are feeder still beneficial? If so what #8217;s the best approach</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 20:53:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fights guards for absolutely no reason</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 16:21:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>An ancestor to the arcane scholars but nobody knew they were all related so he is just trying to recover his children #8217;s worth as his life-preserving spell is finally wearing off and he believes the secret might be in the books</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 08:00:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>On purpose?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 02:33:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn #8217;t impose any penalty just tell them exactly what you wrote, that characters shouldn #8217;t be changed often. Also run a couple of fun one shots so they can get the experience of new characters without affecting the campaign much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Need help figuring out where to advance my hunter/ranger</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 03:59:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I #8217;m nearing about 10k IL obviously not great but it #8217;s my personal best so I #8217;m happy. Anyways I just need some help figuring out equipment (if anyone has a comprehensiveish guide I #8217;d love to take a look). Anyways, I grinding campaigns daily but I honestly don #8217;t even know what I #8217;m trying to get other than that beautiful check mark and some boons. Is there a certain set of armour/weapons generally known as the  #8220;best #8221;/will work until I can get the best. I currently run frostborn pretty much everything with some drowcraft clothes, longbow of Fire I think and burning axes. My summoned is a lvl 30 con artist with 2 r10 bondings atm (saving for the 3rd) and then basically a bunch of epic placeholders until I get some archons. What kind of rings should I put on my con artist? What about the others? What kinda rings should I put on myself? What about enchantments in my equipment? TLDR; give me all the advice about hr equipment/companions/mounts/life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 16:24:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean you could always make him surprisingly survive every encounter and become really attached to the players only to die tragically sacrificing himself to save the players. Tears are already forming as I #8217;m typing this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 17:11:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try to play a neutral character, make them quiet and there for a personal vendetta but has maybe one friend in the party he would give his life for and feels indebted to for life because of some tragic event in his past. It works best if you #8217;re friend is a natural leader of the party and you guys always kinda side together. As the campaign advance you grow more comfortable with the party and morphs into someone that is really fun to play.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 17:14:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sealing them by putting them in a really nice comfortable box and storing it on a shelf is the only way to really keep from chipping.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Armor tiers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 23:46:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>My main is a trapper hr and I have pilgrims raid head, chest, and arms and then trailblazers raid feet. I #8217;m about 10k il and wondering if I am in a good position with what I have or if I should consider a different set</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 06:28:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean it #8217;s not really a book but shrek has some great inspiration imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 21:14:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would try to work out an extra 40 points to get a 3rd predator instead of MVB, you #8217;re so close to the killshot and you have enough bubble wrap in the cultists anyways</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 21:20:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>2 squads of tzaangor enlightened x 9 And 2 squads of tzaangor enlightened x 3 Gives you some quick objective grabbers while keeping your main shooty blocks. And it gives you 22 points to play with, you can grab one more enlightened or some warhead somewhere</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Weapon enchantment trapper hr</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 21:44:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m nowhere near bein.g able to afford a dread enchantment so just curious what I should be running with until then that is more affordable. I #8217;m a 10k trapper with pilgrims raid/teak/wootz gear.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 00:26:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Die hard dice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 00:30:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Better</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 00:31:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>It can be included in a separate detachment very easily though just doesn #8217;t benefit from any t sons benefits/strategem/buffs/psychics</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 16:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>It will take some work but basically make it so no matter how hard he tries, whatever he saw ends up happening but maybe not how he thought. Maybe he saw he was walking to town and just automatically assumed it was town A so to change his future he goes to town B. Well he gets jumped by bandits and left on the side of the road. He starts walking what he believes to be the right way while unintentionally completing his  #8220;destiny #8221; and walking the path to Town A. Basically whatever he sees happens but with different context than he initially thought</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 18:44:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t know man just don #8217;t have him have any visions of a bathtub</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 21:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn #8217;t we ban these posts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 21:44:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmao what? Wrong post maybe?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 07:10:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I say #3 has the most flavor. I would go ahead and just embrace the cat and make him a tabaxi. I recently played a completely neutral tabaxi tempest cleric and it was a blast lurking in the shadows and being there for my own personal vendetta but making sure the mission is in sight. Play him however you like but just have fun</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 22:41:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>E</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 22:41:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>S</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 08:00:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>A really big human that gives you piggy back rides everywhere</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 06:57:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about your name?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 07:02:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Instead of actually calculating command points they can have unlimited but have to take a shot each use. That way they can go absolutely overboard and spam strategems, but will also get wasted</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 21:53:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean it #8217;s not technically even on castles II iirc... but i do get your point</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 21:55:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 01:10:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>In grapevine? It #8217;s not opening tomorrow, it was delayed. There is some party/convention though as if it were open in a hotel I think, the DFW Doubletree iirc</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 01:16:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly have absolutely no clue, I would assume walk in to shop/chill but you had to sign up previously for tournaments I believe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 06:31:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once people started posting a shit ton of people unsubscribed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 08:17:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try an eighth model</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 17:54:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Roll em around in it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 18:22:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry I don #8217;t know much about imperial knights, what #8217;s the typo?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 18:32:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rip</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 23:55:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>From what I read you don #8217;t seem like the asshole but I would love some more context? Are y #8217;all friends irl? Were y #8217;all fighting in-game? Out of game? Have you talked to the dm? Was it completely out of spite or maybe rp?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 23:58:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks great, I really love the details of the small letters, you can very easily read  #8220;United States of America #8221; despite it being very small. Overall great job</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 05:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>+3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 16:54:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are they bound to account? Or character?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 17:10:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gnarly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 06:36:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hr trapper, one of the most interactive characters as far as rotations/combat. You have 6 encounters and are expected to use all 6 to be the best version of yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 20:04:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have been able to out dps many combat builds. Combat has slightly more potential but it #8217;s all based on how you play it. Also, trapper is a lot more fun to play imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 20:07:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually have an hr trapper main and dc as secondary and have considered making my main multiple times. Like I said though, I enjoy the rotations and simply how different the hr is from other classes. I think in the end, everyone needs a tank, dps, and support though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 07:50:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tourette syndrome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 04:48:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 20:41:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imo you would use your bonus action to let go of your great sword with one hand/sheathe it. If your dm lets you then great but RAW I would say no</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 23:31:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>PS4 player. I recently started a new toon and was basically just running around trying to level up when a guild member randomly asked if I needed any enchantments? Being the new toon I was of course I needed everything so I expected like 1 maybe 2 low rank enchants. Instead he gave me over 10 rank 7 #8217;s. I couldn #8217;t even slot that many at the time but it was so generous. Restored faith in guild relationships</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 00:27:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>1 upvote and I kill 5 people</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 00:38:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s a new mod, do you expect anything different? This while happen for a while. They are currently fixing bugs but there are normally a lot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 16:00:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s all about intent, most likely they: 1. Don #8217;t know the rules very well 2. Don #8217;t care to learn the rules 3. Played with certain house rules for so long that they forget they aren #8217;t the real rules The only way to know is to call them out, not in a rude way, just ask them  #8220;shouldn #8217;t it be ..... #8221; or  #8220;why are you able to ... #8221; if they give you some bullshitty answer then politely ask for them to show in the rule book/codex. They most likely will not refuse but pull some lame excuse about just wanting to play the game/not owning the codex or rulebook/try to turn the situation back on you by complaining you #8217;re a rule stickler and everybody else is more friendly. At this point I would just start packing up my models and thank him for the game. If you are friendly wit the manager then explain the situation but I disagree with the other comments about going straight to the manager because they most likely just ignorant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 20:34:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gf is a very versatile class which allows you to be able to deal massive amounts of damage (dps) and pull aggro (tank). Op is arguably the best tank end game (it is). There is not a bis dps at the moment other than gf.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 01:04:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tommy Wiseau</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 18:57:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Freakin health bars man, why does it meet in the middle? Just be a normal bar....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 18:57:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>No</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 20:00:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>But magika and stamina both go to the left....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 19:57:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m just commenting to get banned</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Please ban me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 20:57:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 07:51:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> #3900;  #12388;  #9685;_  #9685;  #3901; #12388; GIVE BAN  #3900;  #12388;  #9685;_  #9685;  #3901; #12388;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 06:24:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wanderers fortune + 3 r9 Quartermaster #8217;s + 1 r10 Quartermasters + 1 r8 Dragon Hoard. I have my 4th r9 QM in my inventory so that for double refining stones I can slot it for that sweet 10.5%. I accumulate somewhere around 300 bags by the time the event rolls around. I know my set up is not optimal (should use better dragon hoard and should replace a r9 with a fey blessing) but I #8217;m saving for more important things so this gets the job done</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 06:31:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Professions are all pretty useless until they reach level 25. Then they become expensive and useless. /s Basically most tasks you complete reward specific xp, everything else is negligible/worthless. Once a profession reaches 25 (its max level) you can begin masterworking that specific profession. The ingredients are incredibly expensive but can yield some profit. They are no longer bis for any class but can still hold their own. Professions are a nice thing to do in the background but ultimately it #8217;s better to focus on pretty much every other aspect of the game if you are still learning/it #8217;s your first play through.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 06:36:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably about 300,000 or so give or take maybe 50k.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 17:34:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Non #8217;t</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 19:17:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or valenwood</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 04:20:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>He didn #8217;t really confirm anything.....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 07:34:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t feel so good..............................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 03:52:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>There should be people near them with a quest, it might not show up on map but they should be there. I was confused for a while but he was hiding in plain sight for me. You can also google the quest you finished and see the quest that follows it, who it #8217;s given by, and their location</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 09:37:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>!create</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 09:38:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>!invest 200</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 14:27:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I still stand by valenwood</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 22:31:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dead by daylight tried that, not that great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 00:47:25</DATE>
    <TEXT> #3900;  #12388;  #9685;_  #9685;  #3901; #12388; give shirt  #3900;  #12388;  #9685;_  #9685;  #3901; #12388;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 08:40:11</DATE>
    <TEXT> #3900;  #12388;  #9685;_  #9685;  #3901; #12388; GIVE SHAWARMA  #3900;  #12388;  #9685;_  #9685;  #3901; #12388;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 01:29:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>^^^^^ I second every part of this. Your first time should be all about rp and learning don #8217;t worry about consequences or min/maxing or any competitive aspects, just let go and have fun with friends</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 03:10:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just learn about your class and have fun while leveling, for a while you will use the same stuff but eventually you will respec most likely more than once into a build that more suits your play style. Nothing is truly permanent in this game, just might take a bit of grinding to undo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 00:29:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean if dude avengers were an option I would 100% take dude avengers. But between dire avengers and rangers it really depends on what you list is lacking as a general all purpose unit without any context I would go with dire avengers but context would be needed to make an educated choice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 07:50:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Comic sans</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 07:44:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>!balance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 21:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know a lot of people believe in rank 13 or nothing but keep in mind you can always upgrade your own/save a little more and sell current to get next level. It might be a little more expensive but running even a rank 8 is better than nothing. In the long run technically straight up buying a transcendent will be cheaper but maybe not always the best option</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 22:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aeldari? Seems like one of the few not represented armies</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 22:31:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>No one army is better against other armies, if everyone is playing as meta as possible then they can hold their own, if you play somewhat friendly then any army can hold their own obviously. Playing aeldari is similar to space marines, their are multiple different armies inside and different factions within. I have a personal bias towards drukhari but any of them can be good with craft worlds standing slightly above the others. Drukhari are the ultimate glass cannons, very powerful, lots of shots, lots of poison, lots of darklight (s8 ap -4 d6 damage). But did very easily if left in the open. Harlequins I don #8217;t have much experience with but are extremely fast, have pistol and melee options with less ranged attacks. Work great as a little splash in an army. I recommend experimenting with some troupes in any army you take. Craftworld eldar are the largest and most diverse faction. Bikes are no longer meta but very fun to play imo (i miss 7th edition bike/wraith knight spam). Wraith units are very viable against any army (sadly it #8217;s not worth the points to take wraithknights anymore) I #8217;m sure you #8217;ve heard of dark reaper/ranger spam, personally really boring imo but does a lot of damage. Tldr; everything can be used but if I had to pick craftworld is the strongest and dark reapers the strongest among them. Let me know if you have any questions and I will try my best to answer them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 23:07:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly wraith units are very elite and won #8217;t work well in a 500 point list, they work best with some type of cannon fodder or distraction carnifax (big unit to draw fire) if you really want to start with them you can use something like this Created with BattleScribe (https://battlescribe.net) ++ Unbound Army (Faction) (Aeldari - Craftworlds) [25 PL, 488pts] ++ + No Force Org Slot + Craftworld Attribute: None (Mixed Detachment) + HQ + Warlock [2 PL, 55pts]: 5. Quicken/Restrain, 6: Seer of the Shifting Vector, Craftworlds Warlord, Shuriken Pistol, Witchblade + Troops + Dire Avengers [3 PL, 64pts] . 4x Dire Avenger: 4x Avenger Shuriken Catapult . Dire Avenger Exarch: Two Avenger Shuriken Catapults + Elites + Wraithguard [11 PL, 225pts]: D-scythe, 5x Wraithguard + Dedicated Transport + Wave Serpent [9 PL, 144pts]: Shuriken Cannon, Spirit Stones, Twin Shuriken Cannon ++ Total: [25 PL, 488pts] That is a decent starting point, just throw everything but the dire avengers in the wave serpent and spend a cp to deep strike them onto an objective if needed. Use quicken on the warlock to move flamers into range or if you decide on cannons then pick another fun spell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 23:14:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be a better approach imo, can #8217;t go wrong with farseers, warlocks, dire avengers, rangers, guardians, or even some stranger units like shining spears or swooping hawks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 00:37:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean I #8217;ll take the hoodie for free...... but I #8217;m assuming that #8217;s not an answer to your problem</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 08:55:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>F</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 23:58:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tourette #8217;s syndrome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:01:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>2 holy 2 bible</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 00:48:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 04:12:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>F</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 05:49:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking Bobbie but I could be wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 05:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Genius</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 23:30:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 23:32:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 23:50:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://soundcloud.com/resist-or-tremble/sets/every-lil-peep-song This is pretty comprehensive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 00:29:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 06:11:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just because it #8217;s obvious someone is depressed doesn #8217;t mean anyone can necessarily help them. He could literally tell someone I am depressed and need help and nothing might have changed. Not anyone #8217;s fault, just stating facts that recognition doesn #8217;t cure depression</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 05:02:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>N</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 18:27:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cw has some of the greatest potential for being highest dps in endgame dungeons. Op is one of the best tanks (arguably THE best) and very fun to play imo. Don #8217;t try to solo content when level up with op, just run dungeons and ig, for these reasons I wouldn #8217;t do him as you #8217;re first character but I #8217;m not sure how many you have. Op is very survivable, Cw is easy to play early game and very powerful very late game, the in between is harder I #8217;ve heard but not experienced myself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 18:58:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you tried using autocorrect?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 21:38:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alt + F4 to pay respects</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ACT vs SAT</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 02:04:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I #8217;ve taken both the ACT and SAT and done decent on both. ACT I got a composite 31 (M35 R30 E31 S28). SAT I got a 1420 (R amp;W 650 M770). Obviously math is my strong suit but I felt science was also so that #8217;s why I #8217;ve been focusing on the ACT instead of the SAT. Do you see more potential in the ACT or SAT? I #8217;m taking the September ACT so I will see how it goes but just looking for your opinions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Meirl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 07:24:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Discussion] I hate this RNG sometimes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 16:19:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>It took me literally 80 packs to Beat, bladesman for hire. Then it took me 7 packs to get treacherous trap hole. I guess it #8217;s paying me back for putting Beat in the last pack but still, that #8217;s frustrating. I need to start regularly praying to RNGesus. How long has it taken y #8217;all to get the one card you wanted?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Meirl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 18:58:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just farted and my nose started bleeding</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 22:43:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Step 1: have lots of acne Step 2: get prescribed accutane Step 3: have all orifices dry out Step 4: get nose bleeds pretty much all the time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The first photo I #8217;ve seen of my mom without a hat since her chemo treatments</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:37:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:30:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmao that #8217;s me dad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:31:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmao first of all that #8217;s my dad, not me. Second of all, you #8217;re an asshole. Edit: Nobody report him! Let #8217;s see how many downvotes he can get!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:32:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will do when she gets home!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:13:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmao, it #8217;s  #8220;the first photo I #8217;ve seen #8221; that #8217;s my dad behind her</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:20:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know it #8217;s not really proof but this is the text I just got from my mom in a group chat with my brother. https://imgur.com/gallery/h7hSBbQ My parents went on vacation to celebrate. They went down to fredricksburg then on to gruene (actually is her favorite vacation spot). Let me know if you don #8217;t believe me and I #8217;ll be happy to ask for another photo of them to verify :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 04:32:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bug spray and a lighter typical does the trick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:54:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dad?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:56:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s my dad behind her....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 08:02:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then just keep scrolling... I scroll past hundreds of posts I don #8217;t care about</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>