<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject9961</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 06:28:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think so. I know it was a stardardized test. Actually, I'm prety sure it was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 07:04:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>What score did you get on your exam? Did you expect to gr the score you did?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 15:38:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not too long ago, as I was getting a cup of coffee at the train station I'm at, a guy I just met called me hot. I'm a guy. It was quite a surprise this early in the morning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 17:32:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I normally am not hot at all</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 19:11:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>what the fuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 08:21:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will strongly recommend you go to Codingbat.com to practice with Java. I used it in my AP Computer Science class, it's fun, challenging, and set-up in a very simple and organized format. You're given challenges, some harder than others, and you receive instant feedback and grading if you get stuck. In fact, go to CodingBat right now and do a warmup problem. This will make you become a better programmer and problem-solver</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 23:18:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Screw me, this post is nuts!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 23:22:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Screw me, this meme is nuts!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-06 10:16:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this even legal</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 10:23:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yummy in my tummy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 10:44:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't talk shit about my boi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 20:58:29</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;admittedly I only started a few days before the deadline, but nothing was said in the group chat during this time. Well there's the problem. You were excluded because you procrastinate</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 01:45:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 01:46:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 01:48:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 01:49:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>big, if true</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 01:53:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 01:53:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 10:28:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 10:30:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 01:37:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 01:43:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>meep</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 04:24:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>it aint Wednesday until it's Wednesday in the US</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 21:21:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>The rim of the cup is slightly uneven, so I think it was able to squeeze through any small gaps</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 08:24:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>MODS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 02:03:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>When will the results be released?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 02:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>U</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 02:08:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>E edit: Why are people saying 'Goodbye'?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me #128026;irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 21:46:21</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me #128056;irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 18:09:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>2meirl4meirl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 18:21:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 18:50:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Especially when you're helping your crush</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 18:06:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 18:14:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get sad when I my answers are wrong. Red pen correction unnerve me now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-09 18:27:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>The biggest ouch I can get is when someone says, "I thought you were smart" or some other variation. Like... c'mon man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me #128546;irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 10:09:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 16:46:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, cancer just doesn't want to quit it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-25 20:28:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seeing that this thread is over an hour old and that you haven't replied to any comments, I kinda see why this thread might be removed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 09:56:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>OH BOY, THE YEAST IS RISING</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 09:56:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>no u</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 09:59:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yo tambien, gra #231;ias</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 08:28:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ditto, my dude. Chem 02 was kinda annoying. For the most part I was floating along the B/B- range. But the final, jeez, I forgot my calculator and just barely got a C</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 08:45:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm really sincere when I say DO NOT get any graphing TI. Those calculators are overpriced, primitive garbage because Texas Instruments used to have a near monopoly for calculators. There are much more affordable or powerful calculators you can get that will last a long time. I personally use a Casio fx-9750Gii (I know, long name) I got for $39 at Target four years ago. It can do anything you can do on a TI for a smaller price with added/removed features here and there. E.g. derivatives, integrals, hyperbolics, unit conversions, statistics, finaces, programmable. The battery life is amazing, I've only had to replace the 4 AAA batteries three times, ever. If you have the money and want possibly the most attractive calculator in the market, get an HP Prime. I don't exaggerate when I say it can do anything if you have the right inputs. E.g. Indefinate integrals, limits, reimann sums, parametrics functions, dozens of graphs at once, conics, and MORE. It's even touchcreen for navigating graphs easier. Tl;dr: get a Casio if you're short on money, get an Hp Prime if you can afford it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me_irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 08:59:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 17:35:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are many ways to find a place to live. You can talk to your academic advisor during walk-in hours and ask for places that off campus students already live. Or you can go on CatLife, there's some people who advertise rooms in large houses (often you'll live with other renting students). Or if you have friends who rent apartments, you can ask them how to apply for their spot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 17:37:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Username checks out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 21:01:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, my bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 04:43:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>We really are in the middle of nowhere. If you want the "college experience" you might be dissapointed since all the fun things are in the neighboring cities. Our campus is under heavy construction, so you'll have to get used to the loud noise. Like in any school out here, you can find things to keep yourself busy, but if you want to go to a school that's far from home because it's far from home, then visit home every weekend, you might as well stick with what you know and pick SJSU</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 04:37:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>You trogladytes, I save my memes and read them from my saved section.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 05:28:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Normie get out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 06:27:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>This could be great at r/fakealbumcovers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 08:07:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>DEUS VULT You're at our mercy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 08:26:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorting by new</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 08:30:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's so uncanny. I thought this was r/reallifedoodles for a second</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 08:37:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like a cool project. Will your cut be the length of a movie?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 08:58:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have fun, and hopefully you share the final product</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 08:06:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know too much about the Chemistry program here, but I do have some insight. There aren't many Chem/Physics majors here, so you'll eventually have really small class sizes towards the end of your first year, so you'll have to get used to not being a stranger. However, since there is a basic chemistry requirement for most stem majors, the first year chemistry classes you'll be in will be packed with around 200 other students, then slowly dwindle. But if you take/took the AP Chemistry test or do well on the chemistry/math placement tests, them you'll be able to skip the basic requirements and get a head start!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>me irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 09:19:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 09:23:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>delet!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 09:32:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes. At least twice a year this video appears in my suggestions, and I always watch it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 09:35:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>ok</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 12:39:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alright Vanessa, let's do something freaking epic here. What you need is a game plan for how you want to approach things with this guy, whom I'll address to as "Guy." And as a fellow dude and fellow over-thinker, I figured I'll procrastinate on my essay that's due in six hours by helping you start talking to Guy. ##Stage One: An Excuse to Talk From what it looks like, you're been dreaming about Guy for a while. The best time you should have kindled some kind of communication with Guy was August 2017; the second best time is now. I've looked into your case here's how we're going to start: **Sit next to Guy**. That's most of stage one! When you begin sitting next to Guy, simply ask him if anyone is sitting next to him. If yes, then do; otherwise, try again tomorrow. Keep this going for a few days and learn to get familiar with being uncomfortable. We're not "just gonna go for it," we want to optimize your interactions with Guy. We don't want you to be awkward and get rejected. Even the best public speaker get nervous, but it's not the same kind of nervous you may feel. I still feel tingly in my hands and feel fuzzy in my head when I present in front of my colleagues, but I've learned how to get comfortable with the uncomfortable, to the point where it's not a new state of being. You should feel this way around Guy after about 4 days of sitting next to him. ##Stage Two: Learning Social Cues Small chit-chat may arise while you're getting used to being around Guy, for example, I'm sure you just ended spring break. Simply ask "How was your break?" and hear about his interests. If he's an extrovert/self-centered he may talk for a few minutes. If he's an introvert/uninterested in you, he may keep talking to a minimum. If Guy asks you about your break right after he's done talking, yay, he has some empathy/cares, so he may be a decent person separate than the one you've created in your mind. Oh yeah, that's important. Try and eliminate all previous ideas you have of Guy, because he may not be the person you dream of holding hands or eating lunch with. If no talking takes place, that's fine too! In some strange way it's better to be ignored than hated by your crush. Have a few days gone by and you're used to seeing the side of his face? Great! Now, you need to give Guy a reason to remember Vanessa from government class? But how will you do that? It's as easy as forgetting a pencil or extra sheets of binder paper. Doesn't matter if you have both of these, ask Guy at the beginning of class if he has any extra. If he doesn't and tries to ask people around him for any extras, yay, he has empathy/cares. If he doesn't have extras and doesn't ask anyone else, or appears to be annoyed, that's not good. Now here's the important thing, whatever you choose to "make your thing" that you frequently ask: **keep it consistent and make it something that isn't easy to give away**. If you Guy to borrow a pencil, and he has an extra, and he's generous, he may just give it to you. No good. Asking for more things to borrow tomorrow may just make you look needy/annoying. Every other day you can shake things up and "forget" to bring assigned readings to class. Ask Guy if he'd like to share. yes == good, bad == oof. After three total days of sharing assignment sheets, start small chit-chat about the government class you both are in. Ask Guy if he likes the class, if not then ask him what his favorite one is. Let him do the talking, and let him talk about himself so you can find out as much as you can without interrogating him with cliche questions. Then ask Guy what his grade in the class is, if it's higher than yours, ask him if he'd be willing to help you memorize some vocabulary/supreme court cases/do homework/understanding today's lesson. If yes, good. If no, whoosh. _Keep in mind Vanessa, we should be at least two weeks in before this stage (close to Finals season), so don't stress about it too much now_. This is a task for future you, but future will still need your help in the present. ##Stage Three: Outside Interactions This will be the lighting round of things to do around school **after** you feel like Guy knows who you are. Hint: Guy should be thinking, "hey it's Vanessa down the hallway," **NOT** "Oh crap, not this girl again." So when you see him in the hallways, you don't even have to say anything. Literally just wave and smile, or better yet, do something silly like dab, finger guns, give two thumbs up, or just say "hey." Why am I telling you to make yourself a fool in front of your crush? it's so Guy would have a reason to remember you out of a mundane day. Whatever you choose to do, it has to make Guy grin or do a "double-take" or even smile (whether ironically or not). This will initially make Guy think "wtf," but as you sit next to each other more and he begins to associate government class with sitting next to Vanessa, it will make Guy think "Vanessa's gonna to the thing!" or see your adorable awkwardness and grow fond of it and maybe even dab back at you for shit and giggles. Try and wear the best clothes you have on days where you have government sitting next to Guy. See if you can catch him staring at you, or even complimenting (Keep in mind, don't start wearing your best clothes right away, you want Guy to notice your new attire.) ##Final Stage: Summer Break As stated before, the best time you should've started some communication was last year, the second best time is today. In finals week, assuming everything has gone well and Guy helps you with class work when he can, waves at you in the halls, and/or starts conversation with you in class: Ask Guy for his Snapchat or Instagram (Facebook is already on it's way out). What's that? You don't have a Snap of Insta? Make one tonight and add a few people you know. If you were hesitant to make on in the past and your classmates ask you why you're making one now, just say you don't have unlimited texting _(But really you're gonna make it so Guy doesn't see that he's your first/only contact because that would be weird)_ Hey, it's summer! You may not see all of your classmates in the same room, which can be a double-edged sword of sadness, but we're gonna us it to your advantage. **Get Guy's social media before the last week of school and use it to ask him for help on work or just talk**, but don't feel obligated to talk online everyday. Many guys start conversations with girls and continue it everyday, and eventually give up when their crush is fed up and mentally filters them out/ignores them. But now that it's summer and you're done with your first year of community college, send Guy a message asking him if he's interested in getting ice cream and walking around town (or whatever you're interested in). This is a date you will be asking him out on. If yes, yay, send a postcard before this thread in archived. If no, well, hope you're not the same major and that you'll avoid awkward interactions. Best of luck if you decide to go through with this. If you think of cooler ideas, do those, this comment can just be a start. Sincerely, one neato mosquito edit: a few words</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 18:26:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, asking if you can sit would be more kind than just swiping the seat next to him and sitting quietly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 17:02:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe the Lantern takes CatDollars. You can also pay with cash.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 17:03:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you guys take contrusctive criticism?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 17:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean constructive criticism on the concept behind the app</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 17:21:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>It fucking sucks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 08:15:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheers to that _tap tap_</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 07:22:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>eww stop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I can get my grades up anytime I want...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 06:34:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 19:20:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I low-key wanna kms, but never will</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 18:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once again, no one expected the Spanish Inquisition</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 07:09:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'M DOING VERY WELL IN MY MATH AND PHYSICS CLASSES BUT MY ENGLISH GRADES ARE SHIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 08:25:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tough to tell. First, disregard any of those personality test results; No internet test can tell you how you think. What made you want to major in Electronic Engineering? Why do you want a bachelor's degree? And do you know what you can do with your future degree? If you're two years into University, a very costly decision, and are struggling to determine whether or not you want to be here, that ain't good. It's not the worst thing ever, but still worrysome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 08:34:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm having a bit of trouble understanding you. Can you explain what you said?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 08:41:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think you should be asking someone else to make one of your life decisions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 08:45:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>You do you. Just keep in mind that casual conversation doesn't mean she's into you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 21:14:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hamsters are not allowed. Really the only non-guide animal allowed is fish.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 01:16:57</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8710;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 10:10:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you want to attach your self-worth to a number, you're gonna have a bad time. Don't attach youself to a self-fullfiling prophecy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 10:16:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>good luck; have fun. Internet people can't relieve this situation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 10:29:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>maybe</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 03:11:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like this thread! I'll contribute with a playlist of fun songs without lyrics. It's short enough that I hope you try to them all: "Spain" by Tito Puente "That's All" by Barney Kessel "Hitchin' a Ride" by Carface (this only has like 12 words)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 03:12:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 03:24:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe don't go if you're really having a miserable time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 03:33:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then you should find a way to turn that frown upside down. A college degree is only as good as what you can do with it. A degree doesn't automatically equal high paying job.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 09:24:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>About to catch some Zzz's. Thanks for asking!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 09:28:22</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8710;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me #8710;irl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 09:32:14</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8710;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 09:32:39</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8710;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 17:53:08</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;I dont want to be a 9 to 5 robot that hates his life. So you'd like to be a 9 to 5 robot that likes his life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 17:56:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/thingsforants</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 18:07:53</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8710;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 18:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 08:35:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>...that's all you have to say? oh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 09:00:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>no</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 09:02:17</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128029;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 07:28:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice. Happy birthday  #127930;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 08:16:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmmm... If you're asking others if you should kill yourself, then you need help</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 08:33:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definately apply for a job before you graduate. It seems that you have some work experience. But with a 2.6 GPA and no research/internship experience, you're gonna have a hard time landing anything. You should've gotten the experience during college, not after, and getting to know proffesors throughout your college career could've opened you up to better career options. Really, stalling any longer or trying to delay graduation is a bad move.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The flowers are nice, and so are the trees,</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 08:53:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 08:55:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>hoot hoot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 09:03:52</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128029;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 08:55:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everyone has a place in this subreddit, some just haven't found this place yet. Welcome! My dessert of choice is something my best friend and I made up a long time ago: hot pancakes with potato shreds covered in applesauce and honey.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 07:27:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>How about working on not costing them money or stress?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 07:43:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do good in college, obviously.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 07:45:30</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128076;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 08:00:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great for you man! You should include some cardio in your workout as a warm-up for your main workout.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 08:17:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>No</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 08:38:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>no</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 08:45:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Car Frog isn't Dat Boi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 08:45:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Car Frog isn't Dat Boi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Am I shadow banned?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 08:25:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 15:59:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>*sweats profusely* Shit this guy's good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 23:27:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 18:39:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rip in spaghetti, my guy. Hope it works out for you. Don't burn out with 5 classes!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 19:10:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/Bee_irl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Meme War 2: Electric Bogaloo</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 21:02:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 21:50:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeetus</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 22:06:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>To rate it 1 star</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 22:07:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got a shoutout?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 22:23:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sheeeit. Can I get a link to check it out?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 18:06:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>*korea intensifies*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 18:09:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>## *korea intensifies*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 18:40:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>That dog threw the biggest yeet of 2018 omg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 23:43:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/nocontext</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 23:45:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/evenwithcontext</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 23:45:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you just reply to yourself?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 23:46:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shut</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 07:37:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>After seeing the mid-credits scene I'm gonna try and predict the post-credit scene for Captain Marvel and the beginning of Avengers 4. We all know Capt. Marvel will explore the quantum realm, and I believe that post credit scene will be something like AM amp;W's where Capt. Marvel goes back into the quantum realm and says something like, "I'm not here alone" while we hears echoes of Scott. Then in A4, we'll see Scott get stuck time vortex. Janet was still affected by aging in the quantum realm, but I think Scott will not age in a time vortex. Afterwards, we might see Capt. Marvel pull Scott out of the time vortex. Since he didn't age in the vortex and doesn't know how long he's been stuck, Scott will freak out about his daughter aging and the whole snap and look for Tony Stark and hope he can do anything with the quantum energy. Stark, suprised that Scott hasn't aged, will use the quantum energy to enter a time vortex and travel to the first Avenger movie. If this doesn't happen, I wonder what Marvel is planning. If it does...you read it here first.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Finally balanced...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 04:35:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 16:26:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>u/sayswut</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I wasn't even subscribed, but got banned.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 04:36:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just posted a meta shitpost and now I'm here, but I ain't complaning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 16:55:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>You ain't fooling anyone you muppet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 04:11:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>banana slugs  lt; Other UC Mascots</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 04:12:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 04:13:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can confirm. At Merced</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 00:39:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alexa play Despacito 2</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Man, screw this</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 06:07:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck UC Merced. Denying my SHIP waiver when I answered with the same answers as last year with no previous problems. Charging me more fucking money for the premium when I'm already having trouble trying to pay for a place to live. Bullshit. This shit makes me want to fucking hang myself in front of the chancellor's house. Edit: I'm less angry now and my appeal waver had been accepted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 07:21:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>UC Merced? More like, fricking stupid</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 08:16:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can if I don't throw myself under the Cattracks too soon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's that season, High School seniors</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 05:36:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>For those of us on the semester system, who's ready to go back to school next week?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 05:53:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had so much ambitions for this summer, but accomplished none of them. I looking forward to a change of pace.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 06:56:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/engineeringstudents where dedication and distaste are one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 07:14:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Merced. How about you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>