<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject569</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-21 13:49:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just recently hit level 30 about 2 months ago, and am excited to try out ranked. Before going in though, I wanted to get a better handle on who counters who, so when I'm in champ select I don't end up picking silly stuff. Mainly, I play Jhin (adc) Ahri (mid) and Volibear (top/jungle). Who are their biggest counters that I should look out for?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 05:08:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Warwicks missing their R for a gank and just kind of awkwardly shuffling back toward the jungle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 08:25:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I've only really seen them in places like Disneyland or a super touristy town in Washington during the summer. Though I guess there aren't very many alternatives to keep tourists cool in extremely high temperatures.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 08:38:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Time for a tsunami wave</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 08:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once you go black..... ( #865;  #865; #176;  #860;  #12388;  #865; #865; #176;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 08:48:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>These look great! Do you sell them anywhere else? Or were these your last copies?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 08:52:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait. A Scooby-Doo crossover with Supernatural? I stopped watching season 10, what the heck has been going in in that show since then?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-22 08:55:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>And Grunkle Stan would be Bobby! Though I could even see Ford kinda in that role, with all his knowledge of supernatural stuff. This is a crossover I somehow never even thought of, but now absolutely love!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-26 11:44:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>How often do they do My Shop sales?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-28 09:18:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>What elo do ranked placements put you? I'm new, and while I've done good in blinds/normals, I just get utterly pooped on by everyone else in ranked. (Both solo/duo and flex)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 01:54:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was the answer I was looking for, thanks! I was wondering what rank I was being pitted against during placement matches. Silver 3-ish seems to match up with the kind of people I see my friends against.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 01:58:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it bad that I end up using the exact same build path every game? Save for inserting a Dominiks or something if their team is particularly tanky, I always end up falling into the same build path. (Mainly an adc player) Also, could someone please explain the late game potions for me? Like the ones that make your character huge/when I should buy them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-30 20:34:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blood Moon Jhin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 03:36:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn that looks good. I'm too protective of my Superstars to hardly even wear them though haha, but I'd love a pair like that! Is that drawn on? Or a sticker of some sort?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 08:50:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pickle DIIIIIICK</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-20 00:42:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my gosh I saw this exact place when I was in Garmisch two years ago! It definitely needs a "????" sign in front of it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 00:29:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only reason I'd get a DVD is to put on subtitles for a few parts. Maybe it was just my theater, but it was a bit quiet in some parts, coupled with some thick West Virginia accents that make it a little tough to understand at times. Other than that though, it was fun to see it with a crowd that laughed enthusiastically at the jokes and got hyped for the twists and stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 09:40:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice, hope you guys enjoy it! And congrats on your engagement :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 10:54:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>My ex ended up being a cuck. I know some people are into it and everyone's different, but I felt kind of sick when he told me he wanted to watch me fuck other guys. At the time, I loved him and loved being with him and it really threw a wrench into stuff. I tried incorporating it into some dirty talk once to test it out though, because I wanted to try to have an open mind and do what he wanted. He ended up crying and asking if really meant it/still actually loved him. I know his new girlfriend does it for him, and I hope he's happy with it now, but fuck. There's gotta be something genuinely wrong with a person. I see it as a really strong inferiority complex that's (gone sexual)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 23:40:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I know Fiddlesticks isn't exactly a great pick right now, but I wanted to try him out in some norms just for fun. What roles would he be viable in at the moment? Could I support with him, and what skill order would you suggest?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-14 06:21:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can Kindred be played adc? Like I was just trying them today in the jungle (I'm a slave to the free rotation) and during team fights, especially after finishing Bloodrazor and runaans I found myself thinking that she might work in the adc role. Any one have any idea?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 01:05:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jhingle? Jhungle? But also now I really wanna try this lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 05:29:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god, I actually kinda want a tattoo of this. Like it's such a cool cross over of two things I absolutely love, and done in a totally unique way. Great job!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-05 19:36:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>The same thing happens with [Guardian of the Sands Rammus!](https://imgur.com/gallery/hxk2S)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 20:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it's a kink, then you shouldn't have to be trying to defend it. That's pushing your own kinks/fetishes on other people, when it should just be your business and yours alone what you're into. No need to force it on anyone else, or try to "convert" someone. God I hate cucks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 21:47:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Were there any other alternate ult lines for the new Cultist skin that you may have preferred or tested out? (Instead of "experience nothingness")</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 19:53:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even though Mobafire isn't the best, some popular junglers will have suggested clear paths in their guides. I usually like to look up one beforehand so I have a path in mind. Warwick is a fun and easy jungler to try out and have as a back up for auto fill/a new role experience. Depending on your rank, you may also want to give Kindred a shot. They're not in the best place right now, but build/kit is somewhat similar to an adc role.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 03:12:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>First off, congrats! :D https://www.reddit.com/r/artcommissions/comments/78hfm8/for_hire_cartoon_portraits_for_150_200_disneyrick/?st=J96CB3GC amp;sh=b48a415a Looking around for commissions is usually a tough process, and works best if you've found an artist you like. But a quick check on a commissions sub found this post that kind of fits your idea for a portrait of you and your husband. They offer international shipping, and could possibly rush your order to get it there in time. Hope this helps a bit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 19:10:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>"My booty will be understood - eventually" All of Jhin' quotes are great though, with or without booty</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 17:09:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ghost blade is only worth it if you can snowball super hard and close out the game early with your initial lead. Other than that, best bet is getting a BF sword your first back and building IE first, then Shiv and RFC.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 18:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I #8217;m rushing Hexdrinker for the MR, do I still end up building a Maw of Malmortius in the end? Or do I end up selling the Hexdrinker for other late game items further on down?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 19:26:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Watched it a week ago with a friend, he absolutely hated it but I loved it. The time setting was so interesting, coupled with amazing dialogue and costumes that really set the scene. The horror elements were perfect, with some genuinely chilling and alarming scenes. The ending felt so perfect too- given all the things Thomasin had experienced and witnessed, her joining with the devil/other witches was almost satisfying in a way. Also, the brother had a great child actor, and his possession scene read like something straight from the Bible/the Salem Witch Trials. Such a great movie, glad you enjoyed it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 18:56:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Should I #65039; not upgrade champs to Mastery 6 or 7 right now? I #65039; remember hearing there was a huge increase in needed BE so should I #65039; wait?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Hunt | PROJECT: Hunters Animated Trailer - League of Legends</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-21 07:32:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-22 01:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m torn, because I want to support a Jhin merch and help ensure there #8217;s more stuff made for him, but I also don #8217;t want to support this kind of crappy merch haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 22:08:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>This was my first time ever posting to a sub/forum like this, and god I #8217;m glad I did. Thank you for your incredibly kind reply. I was seeing a counselor my first year, and for a while in the beginning of this semester, but missed an appointment and got bumped down to the bottom of the wait list so it #8217;s been a while since I talked to someone. I #8217;ll start there before considering anything else. Thank you for that last comment, I truly appreciate it- and you for taking the time to reply and make things seem a little better. Hope you #8217;re having a good holiday season and a good day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 19:02:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I completely relate, I adore Jhin and playing as him genuinely makes me feel hyped for a game. If I start tilting a little or getting dicked on, just hearing some of his voice lines fixes it right away. So I think, you should play whatever the heck you want. Right now, Jhin does have one of the worst winrates for ADCs in the game, but that doesn #8217;t mean picking him is an instant loss. I #8217;d suggest checking out IKeepItTaco #8217;s stream on Twitch- he #8217;s a Master-tier Jhin one trick with a couple of smurfs in high diamond. His stream has helped me improve on my mechanics with Jhin immensely, and he #8217;s a fun streamer to watch in general. Best of luck with the virtuoso! Never stop creating art 8D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 19:03:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got a bottle of this from the Smashbox try it primer kit at Ulta, and wow does it do wonders. Even with the Nyx No Filter and Smashbox Photo Ready primers, my dry skin would still flake and crack. With this spray though, my makeup stays absolutely perfect and my skin nice and hydrated. I #8217;ll definitely get some more now that it #8217;s on sale!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 20:43:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Heh, I have that exact same Dota 2 mousepad!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-05 20:58:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow that looks absolutely amazing! Did you make it yourself or buy it online?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-06 03:02:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kinda reads like one too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 19:01:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>It saddens me deeply that support Jhin is the only way I #8217;ve gotten an S+ on him in the past couple of months. Feels bad as heck man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-14 23:54:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit (heh), I didn #8217;t either. Coven was pretty wild looking back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-18 23:24:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>The hips just don #8217;t seem womanly, usually they #8217;re bigger and more defined on a woman</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 21:29:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope he comes down my chimney and shoots me in the head</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 00:57:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah yes my favorite level in The Last Of Us</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-27 09:31:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it supposed to be suicidal  #8220;tendencies #8221;? Or do I still have it wrong?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 05:56:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Sound of Music, partially for nostalgic/personal reasons, and in part for the gorgeous scenery and singing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-28 07:04:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>My ex who I still feel attraction and love for keeps messaging me- the convos start off friendly and innocent, but always end with him trying to initiate sexting and stuff. I feel like I keep falling for it and just don #8217;t know how to properly shut him down. I try to tell myself that I #8217;m a single, independent adult who can do whatever and sext whoever I want, but I keep feeling disgusted with myself in the end for giving in to his advances. He #8217;s in a relationship, but it #8217;s open (both he and the girl actively sleep with other people) Would it be best to sever all ties with him, or would it even be worth trying to maintain a regular friendship?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 09:39:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well they #8217;re about to perform in Oahu tomorrow so I feel like it might be possible</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-31 08:16:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only good one that actually showed both theaters of war was Red Orchestra 2 and the Rising Storm expansion. It #8217;s such an amazing and fun game, but dead by now with empty servers. Really a shame</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 07:14:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I absolutely love that song- it definitely resonated with me the first time I heard it, and it #8217;s time I actually followed the advice she sings. Thank you for your comment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 07:30:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sums it up, I feel like less of a person every time. I should seriously just read a book or something instead haha. Thank you for your comment and advice, I appreciate it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 21:15:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>My parents actually heard about it on one of the major US news stations (CBS or something). My mom asked me about it, which surprised me, and took a second to rant about how awful it was. So at least in the US it got some news time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 21:34:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ho brah!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 21:42:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>O</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-04 21:43:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Goodbye</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 08:49:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>G #8217;day mate!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 02:10:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was amazing, and so well written! Let me know if/when you update it with another chapter please!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 23:55:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rocket Fizz in Lincoln. NE?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 22:33:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck, I #8217;m from Hawaii but currently on the mainland for school. I got a text from my mom begging me to call her cause she thought they were all about to die. Fucking terrifying</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-18 09:37:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Got ghosted over the summer by my bf, when we got back to school he avoided me at all costs. Wouldn #8217;t even say a word to me, and would cross the street to avoid me. People are cowards and you deserve better. Hope things are going better for you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ghosting sucks</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 04:52:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>My first semester of college went horribly. Then I met him. He approached me, asked for my number. He was the first guy to ever do that; to make me feel special and wanted. The only other guy I #8217;d been with at that point just waited for me to get drunk enough to be willing to fool around. We smoked together, loved the same shows and video games. We were good friends who spent a ridiculous amount of time together, making out between Halo rounds and walking downtown holding hands and cracking jokes. It felt like a perfect relationship, or at least the closest I #8217;d ever been to one. I was dumb and nervous a lot of the time but I never felt like he judged me. Then summer came and his texting just...stopped one day. I couldn #8217;t get a reply, snaps would be opened and then ignored. I tried to send gushy messages, asking what #8217;s wrong, why he was distant. At first he promised to work on responding, but the next time he didn #8217;t even react to the attempts. We got back to school and he ignored me in person too, scurrying to the other side of the street so he didn #8217;t have to walk near me. I finally texted after about a week, asking to meet and talk in person and he responded with a  #8220;sorry, but no #8221;. And that was it. It may have only been a 4 month relationship, but it still hurt- and being ghosted, with no real break up to end it made seeing him every day hurt. I wish I could know what exactly I did, or why it deserved such shitty treatment. People who ghost others suck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 05:20:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. I keep having this idea that I should try to text him and apologize for some reason, like I need to save face for whatever dumb shit I did to warrant the ghosting. But then I feel like that #8217;ll make me look desperate and even more lame haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-26 07:00:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bonus: [Here's that moment from Calvin's POV] (https://clips.twitch.tv/BlazingKindCoffeeMVGame)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ohana Family Means No Means Is</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 07:19:56</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 17:57:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kinda similar, but at a party last week or so, I was drunk af with my date and we kinda ended up in random corners making out, and I kinda slumped over a few times cause my head was spinning. Every single time, a different girl would come up and make sure I was okay/was feeling alright. It was so sweet and now I want to make sure I always look out for drunk sorority girls at parties in return : #8217;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-03 18:27:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who #8217;s gonna hook a pal up with the emoji copypasta</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 03:47:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh man, I wonder if they #8217;ll also have BoTW Princess Zelda! That #8217;s actually such a cool thought, though Twilight Princess Zelda sure was a gorgeous design</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 06:02:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just checked around me, looks like the artsy theater (the one for award-type movies) won #8217;t have it until the end of March. You might have to give it a few weeks for it to show around you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 06:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, like I can #8217;t see current smash Zelda #8217;s move set with a BoTW model. It just doesn #8217;t mesh well. But it #8217;d be weird to see Link and Zelda in two different styles in the roster.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 06:36:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aloha brah, I #8217;m glad to hear you #8217;ve made a beautiful life for yourself :) I hope you can make it out to the Big Island if you haven #8217;t, it #8217;s such a different world from the other islands. Just go up to Mauna Kea for star gazing some night, look up at the stars and bask in the glory of life out in the middle of space. It #8217;s such an amazing sight and feeling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 08:26:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pharah looks a lot like Korra in that spray</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I feel so small and unimportant</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 08:10:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just got broken up with by probably the best guy I #8217;d ever dated. He said he needed time to be alone, that he needed to figure things out about himself. I wasn #8217;t mad at him for that- I get it. I understand what it #8217;s like to stop and think hard for once and get drowned in your own thoughts and get lost in your own head. But that marks my third time being dumped in a row. I feel so chewed up and spit out at the end of each of relationship. I give my heart, feelings, love, and body and get it crumpled up and thrown back at me in the end. I don #8217;t have any friends here at this school- I fucked up and didn #8217;t click with anyone. I didn #8217;t form any real social bonds and that #8217;s why I find myself crying in bed alone, furiously typing this post because I realize I don #8217;t have anyone to talk about this with. I know how I must look to everyone else. I #8217;ve only been seen with a bunch of guys, a few of whom I #8217;d fooled around with or dated. I #8217;d be grossed out by me, too. I just keep thinking that I #8217;ll find love, or getting caught up in how good it feels to be wanted and liked by someone that I base my whole self worth around it. And yet I can never make them stay long. The first one was almost a year, the second one about 2 months, and now this one just a month. I #8217;m so pathetic, I feel like there #8217;s nothing more to me than my skills in bed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 16:08:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my god, when I posted this little rant, I didn #8217;t expect someone to take so much time out of their day to analyze and spread such kind words. First off, thank you. I got to wake up in the middle of the night and have an incredibly uplifting message to read. Really, thank you. I had about 10 months between the last two guys, and I really tried to take that time for myself and figure some stuff out. But the way the second guy ended things (by just ghosting me and running away any time he ever saw me...yeah, a college age guy would bolt across the street anytime he saw me. I have kinda shitty taste), I was really down on myself. I felt like I had to have done something really dumb, or been really awful to warrant such treatment. By the time I met this new guy though, I was feeling better. Him liking me was a confidence booster, and then suddenly losing that interest just felt like it put me back to square one- hence my little breakdown on here. I don #8217;t know who I am, I don #8217;t really have any specific hobbies or talents. I want to gain those things and I want to be a more well rounded person who doesn #8217;t break into pieces the second some guy breaks up with me. Honestly, you #8217;ve given me the courage to believe it #8217;s a lot more possible, and that there isn #8217;t too much to it. I appreciate you so much, and I wish there was something I could do in return!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 18:20:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see you mentioned the VA. Both my parents and both older brothers served. If you need to talk about anything, I #8217;m here and willing to listen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 18:23:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve found one of my old notes that I started writing in November of 2016, and while I #8217;m not entirely okay yet, I know that I #8217;ve improved since then and I don #8217;t feel that same urge anymore. I wish you all the best in healing, happiness, and good days ahead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Indifference</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 18:41:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Days keep going by, and I feel stuck. I do enough to get by- bare minimum to pass classes, to keep at least a few acquaintances around to play video games with, but other than that, I #8217;ve isolated myself completely. People here don #8217;t really seem like the kind I #8217;d want to get along with, anyways. I feel exhausted after talking, and disingenuous with who I am. Plus, my reputation succeeds me, so I know I have no shot interacting with certain social circles that my ex or my previous roommate are in. My thoughts of suicide are near constant again, though. I don #8217;t have any active desire to go out of my way to end my life, but I spend so much of the day imagining various ways to kill myself. Cutting used to be a way to distract myself, and I still get the urge pretty frequently. Yet I know I can #8217;t/shouldn #8217;t- I #8217;d cut my thighs, but I live in a warm climate and shorts weather is nigh. My other scars are almost all completely healed and white; old and faded. Plus, I don #8217;t want that to be who I am, anymore. And yet it feels so tempting, so comforting to think about. I feel resigned to living life- at least, until my parents die. I feel like that #8217;d be when I could finally just let go if I still needed to or wanted to. The only thing keeping me would be the guilt from leaving them in such an awful way. But these days are getting unbearably long, and the future increasingly dark and cloudy. I can #8217;t see myself in 10 years, 5 years, or honestly even imagine what life will be like next year. I wish I could start over everything. I wish I wasn #8217;t so mentally unstable and broken. My walk to classes takes me across a fairly busy street, under a sketchy overpass. The other night, I took a breath and walked across without looking. I felt so calm, so at peace. My headphones were in and I could tune out any sounds of traffic. When I got to the opposite curb, unscathed, I kept walking and tried my best to keep from bursting into tears. I would have been okay if it was done then. I #8217;m thinking about doing it again, and again. If I should continue to live, then I guess it #8217;ll be some sort of sign.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I think we could have been more</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 13:45:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Our relationship was short, passionate, and ended far too soon. You were healing, I thought, but a week apart let your dark thoughts catch up to you. I am not her. I would never be her. Our names may be strikingly similar, but that #8217;s where the resemblances end. I noticed those scars the night I met you. I had no idea they were a result of the mental pain from her leaving you. I thought back to the night my first boyfriend of a year dumped me over the phone; how I sliced my skin open, too. I never told you that. I went through that heartache, but I spiraled in horrible ways. Your recovery was going well with new friends, new clubs, and I thought I was helping, too. But I guess now I know it wasn #8217;t really enough. I want you to love yourself the way I could have loved you. But I wish you had given me more time. For us to walk before we ran. For us to find comfort and healing in ourselves, and each other. I feel like when the time comes, and you #8217;re ready, you won #8217;t even think of me. There will be someone new for you. We could have been so much more, as individuals, as a couple, as friends.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What did he expect?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-31 05:06:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>My first college boyfriend ended up being a complete asshole. Things were good while they lasted, but when summer rolled around, he ghosted me completely. I couldn #8217;t get a reply. Months passed and when we both showed up on campus, he ran away from me every chance he got. He #8217;d cross the street and bury his face in his phone like a coward. I tried to reach out and asked him to talk, but he simply refused. So I left it be. He continued to avoid me blatantly, but I tuned it out. I kept going with my life and chalked it up to a crappy encounter with a douchey frat boy. And now, his name popped up on my phone for the first time since September.  #8220;He #8221;  #8220;Hey #8221;  #8220;Are you in town for break? #8221; Those were the three texts I received in quick succession last night, at 1:52 AM. I was playing a game with League with some friends and I instantly blew up. I was disgusted, humiliated, and appalled. My friend instantly went  #8220;it #8217;s like 2 AM, that #8217;s so obviously sleazy #8221;. I hate that it made me cry in frustration. After ghosting my ass like a dumb teenager, instead of talking it out like adults, he waited the 8 months to send me a (probably) drunken booty call text. What a waste of my time and a sad, lonely human being. I refuse to reply, though I hate the small part of me that keeps lingering on the message, wondering what his true intentions are. I don #8217;t want to be thought of as just an easy piece of ass he can text up late at night when his dorm is empty. I wonder if he woke up sober and regretted the message, or if he even thought I #8217;d actually reply. What angers me the most is that I can #8217;t figure out what he expected to happen, or why he #8217;d attempt to open contact with me after so rudely cutting ties beforehand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 00:34:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for sharing this! I had my first experience getting one of these from an awful ex, and a small, weak part of me was tempted to give in and reply to see what he would say. Its been 3 days since the message, and I haven #8217;t replied. I plan on never replying, and focusing on myself and being ready to meet someone who will prioritize and love me the way I truly want to be treated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 00:45:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t think he would have even asked me out again, probably just wanted to hook up or something. I #8217;m sorry things went that way, but atleast you can rest easy knowing it #8217;s not meant to be, and you can look forward to the bigger, better, and more lasting relationships ahead of you. Stay strong, and best of luck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 00:50:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>So would you say it #8217;s probably best to just ignore the text entirely? I haven #8217;t answered him yet, and break ends tomorrow anyways. He still goes out of his way to avoid me in public though, which is why I can #8217;t figure out what the heck his intentions were behind the message. One of my friends said he wouldn #8217;t go from running away from me to wanting to bang, but I can #8217;t imagine he wanted to apologize or just hang out like a couple of chums. A small part of me wants to send a biting reply, but I figure it sends a better, stronger message to just ignore him entirely. I just want to save face after being humiliated and ghosted from before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 00:55:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s always kind of funny to see an ex doing something they used to claim they never would. I remember bonding with my ex after all the Greek life recruitment- how he passionately talked about his distaste for frat life and how he #8217;d never rush. After breaking up over summer, I saw him skulking around in a suit on campus during recruitment week, and a proud display of Greek letters in his Instagram bio. Seeing an ex change and become someone you no longer have feelings for can be kind of bittersweet. They can become so different from the person you originally fell for that it #8217;s easy to move on and recognize they #8217;re no longer someone you #8217;d want or need.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 01:45:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, I #8217;m in a similar place where my mind is just filled by thoughts of the guy I love and can #8217;t be with. I got a glass of wine I #8217;ll toast to you! Feel free to message me if you ever want to talk about anything and everything</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>League of Legends role shirts/lanyards</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 20:37:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw that they were offering free shirts to groups of five with the various lanes on them. And that you could also find an employee with a specific lanyard and ask for one for your favorite role. I was just wondering if anyone snagged one, and what they look like!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 21:27:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those look pretty cool, thanks so much for sharing! Do you remember what the other shirts said for the other roles at all?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>To the boy who doesn #8217;t know what he wants</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 18:32:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re in a dark place. Your heart is too big for your own good. You have too much love to give, and it #8217;s spread too thinly over too many of us. Your ex who broke your heart for the first time is still holding onto a few shards. You called me in, drunk at 3 am to cry and tell me you loved me. But then I hear there #8217;s another one who #8217;s caught your interest- someone you actually intend to date. You don #8217;t know what you want, because none of us are who you need right now. You need to find confidence and love for yourself first. You need to heal those scars, the ones on your arms and the ones on your heart. I wouldn #8217;t say I hate you, but I hate that you took me that night. The same night you cried about your love for another, you confessed your love to me for the first time. Was it real? Is any of this real? The only thing that seems real are the bruises on my skin from your rough hands that night, and the empty pit in my stomach whenever I try to fight through the fuzzy memories to figure out how clothes even started coming off. I was willing to wait. But I can #8217;t be second to someone else. I don #8217;t think I #8217;ll be the one you choose, so I need to distance myself from you. I need to get it through my head that some things, no matter how perfect they may have seemed, just don #8217;t work out. You may not know what you want now, but I hope you figure it out one day, and that you end up okay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 21:37:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve been watching my older brother fall into alcoholism and it #8217;s devastating for everyone around him. My parents found emptied handles in his room, where he would sit alone drinking and playing video games. I watch him pour a drink, half vodka and half grapefruit juice in a tall glass- probably about 4 or 5 shots worth. He gets angry the second you tell him to stop or slow down, and downright terrifying if you ever accuse him of being drunk. I hope to god he slows down. He #8217;s lost girlfriends and friends and made an ass of himself in front of people but never seems to learn. Just drowns the pain with another drink. I miss his sober self.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lobe piercing post stuck in ear</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 21:36:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, so I got some cheap yet cute earrings from an art store by a local artist, and enjoyed them for a month. Then I started having severe pain and lots of redness, so I decided to try and swap out the earrings. It was then I noticed the post was completely embedded in my ear. Scared and in pain, I went ahead, got a decent grip on the front and the back, and pulled. I could feel it literally slide out of my ear (the part that was stuck was actually a flared base, so it ripped my ear a little). It started bleeding and throbbing, so I rinsed it with my usual salt water spray and put a small bandage on it over night. I was wondering how long I should wait before attempting to put in new earrings to keep the hole from closing, or if I need to wait longer than usual because of the injury. Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My dad #8217;s (and now my) favorite whisky- best way to chill while my ex takes his new girlfriend to the formal he promised to take me to!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 02:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 02:58:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rest in piece to your fluffy buddy. They were lucky to have a life full of love and friendship from you. Wishing you all the best in healing and comfort</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 07:35:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh that looks like such well made mochi! Back home one of my favorite snacks is the reverse of this- mochi balls with a center of brownie! This looks so good though, hope you enjoy them!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 17:02:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Going by your username, I #8217;d say you do too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I watched you walk away</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 17:42:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sat on my bed and looked out my window that morning, after you left. I #8217;d let you lay down in my bed after you drank too much, until you called me in that night. Crying, embracing, you told me you loved me. Then clothes came off and hands were everywhere. Night turned to dawn while we were still wrapped up in each other. And then, you took your leave. I can still hear my voice, small and hoarse as you dressed yourself.  #8220;This doesn #8217;t change anything, does it? #8221; I asked. You gave me a small, sad smile and told me it didn #8217;t. We would remain broken up, and you would go back to that new girl you met over spring break, who caught your attention away from me. I watched from my window as you left my building, heading back towards campus to your own room as the first lights of day illuminated the sky. I cried as I watched you, feeling more used, more depleted, and more sick with myself than ever before. Now, I #8217;m glad you left. I #8217;m glad I got to watch you disappear down the street and be reminded that you would never stick around. You looked so small in the distance, and you #8217;ll look even smaller when I look back on this part of my life. I hope you find your own happiness one day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 17:55:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! The sentiments at the end only just came to me today, and inspired this last little unsent letter for my own closure. I appreciate you reading my rambling!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 19:40:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, thank you! I definitely am not looking for reconciliation with this guy, I #8217;d rather take the time to get to know/fall in love with myself for once. I love that quote though, thank you for sharing it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 23:12:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>This comment melted my heart, thank you so much for taking the time to say that! I wish you all the best in everything, and I #8217;ll keep trying my best, too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 19:41:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I knew it was 4 Mile right away! Kinda crazy to see it on here haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 05:42:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh man your stuff is amazing, I really love the Gravity Falls stuff! Did your drawing of Rick and Stanford Pines sell, or would you ever do prints of it? I #8217;d be super interested in either!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 00:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d love a print! Would you add it to your Etsy store?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 11:33:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like she #8217;s been splicing up a little too hard down in Rapture</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 08:04:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s kind of interesting, I saw the original play about a year ago, and as I recall, he gets his store broken into in the very beginning of the play. Sucks about the show though, I heard pretty decent things about it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 00:11:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god, what ended up happening? Did they apologize and recognize their fuck up or were they oblivious?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 18:56:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>They change daily. Today is Lucioball</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 19:12:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait...what? What happened in that scene?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 19:38:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the actual fuck happened to that show? I actually read the book when I was a wee, sad little teen and there was nothing like that in it. That just sounds so unnecessary and outlandish...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 03:07:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in Hawaii, so I #8217;ve grown up with common house geckos and Madagascar Day geckos crawling all over my walls. My parents never let me get a dog or any other kind of pet, so I just considered all the wild guys my pets. They would keep most of the other bugs at bay, so they were not just cute-but also super helpful! It #8217;s illegal to own any other kind of gecko (leopard/crested/anything) as a pet in Hawaii, but I plan on moving to another state at some point and I #8217;d love to own one or two of my own :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 03:48:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I slugged through the first episode of season 2 but it just left such a sour taste in my mouth. Cringy sums it up perfectly- Skye and Clay #8217;s relationship was annoying and cringy to watch, and Tyler is just an awful, sleazy and unsympathetic character regardless of what they were trying to show through the flashbacks. I didn #8217;t mind the first season overall- I actually liked the book when I was younger and I thought certain aspects were well done. Hannah #8217;s actress acted her heart out, too. But I don #8217;t think I #8217;ll be able to finish the second season, and already knowing the major spoilers just solidified that choice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 03:53:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;d like to believe that people can differentiate between real life shooters and a poorly written character in a drama series, but I definitely could see horrible backlash if there was a full blown shooting scene. I wonder what kind of reaction a scene like the one in the first season of American Horror Story got when it first aired. That was right around Columbine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 04:17:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depending which island you #8217;re going to, you have absolutely nothing to worry about. If you #8217;re visiting the Big Island, the only downer would be not being able to visit and enjoy the National Park. Other than that, there #8217;s still amazing opportunities and sight seeing at Mauna Kea (a dormant volcano where the observatories are located, great for star gazing!), gorgeous beaches on the Kona side, or amazing hiking in Waipio Valley. If you #8217;re visiting another island, you don #8217;t even have to worry about the talked about vog- trade winds have been keeping the plumes south of the island chain. If you have any questions or want any suggestions, feel free to ask me anything! Hope you enjoy your stay and feel at ease. Once you see how gorgeous and relaxing the state is, I #8217;m sure you #8217;ll be able to relax and enjoy yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 04:19:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rude</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In Hawaii, Madagascar Day Geckos have free reign of the place and are all over the walls of my house. Found these guys in my kitchen the other day!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 04:27:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 20:12:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see you #8217;re a man of taste as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 20:55:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god, the cockroaches. We used to see them pretty frequently, and only the brown geckos. A few years back, these green guys started showing up and now they keep the mosquitos and other bugs at bay! Haven #8217;t even seen a cockroach in over a year or so now, so I for one welcome my new gecko overlords</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 20:56:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha the cup was just water, though I wouldn #8217;t blame that guy for going after my Grey Goose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 21:02:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope, the visitors center, where the star gazing is, is about 9,000 feet up and above the inversion layer. Skies should still be clear and gorgeous up there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 03:29:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry I #8217;m out of the loop, what was the story behind those two items?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 18:51:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I looked further back and he claimed to be a 15 year old in one of his posts. So there #8217;s that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 20:01:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>[It #8217;s referencing a silly meme](http://knowyourmeme.com/memes/you-know-i-had-to-do-it-to-em) so I #8217;m pretty sure it #8217;s just Futaba appreciating him playing into her internet/meme love</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 18:35:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ay, kind of reminds me of the Chinese Lunar New Year skin for Mercy in Overwatch! I like it a lot!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I had my first hook up</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 22:54:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know this story is in no way unique or anything, but reddit is my go-to rant place, and I have no one to talk about this with. I #8217;m visiting a large city with my parents, and it #8217;s the first time I #8217;ve had an entire hotel room to myself. After about a year-long dry spell, I was a little restless. My only sexual encounters had been with the only two guys I #8217;ve ever loved. Sex was supposed to be reserved for only people I loved...it was about the closest to a moral compass I had. None the less, I made a Tinder account, slapped on a bio saying I was just looking for hook ups, found my most flattering selfies and began swiping. Within minutes it said I had over 99 likes, and I was seeing super likes every few profiles. Ah, the magic of casual sex. A few guys were pretty funny and quite a few were pretty cute, but I finally found one who messaged and didn #8217;t beat around the bush. After snap chatting a bit, he gave me his address and I snuck out of the hotel, my parents sleeping peacefully in their room a few doors down, completely unaware I was on my way out the door. I hopped in an uber at 1 AM to the other side of a major city to meet and have sex with a total stranger. It was good, I mostly enjoyed myself and he was very considerate about making sure I was comfortable/having a good time. I left a few hours later, climbed into another uber at 4 AM reeking of sex and sweat with frizzed up hair. The driver eventually rolled his window down and I did the same. With my head out the window, I finally felt the tears come. It all still feels like a weird dream and I don #8217;t quite know how to process it all. In some ways I feel like I lost a part of myself, while in others I feel like I gained new freedom, confidence, and experiences.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 02:04:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know what, that #8217;s super true. The ride out there was surreal, just looking at the city lights and seeing new places, all because of some crazy sex adventure. I just hope I can look back at the memory fondly rather than regretting it too much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 21:16:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why would you get back with her after what sounds like a rather toxic and shitty (pun intended) relationship?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 05:30:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely report those guys in the uber/Lyft app. You #8217;re probably not the first or last woman they may harass or make uncomfortable. I #8217;m sorry you #8217;ve been subjected to such scummy guys though, there #8217;s absolutely no excuse for that kind of behavior.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 22:01:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;s a good way to look at it, I appreciate that sentiment. And as for the sense of loss, I guess the only way to explain it is mentioning the fact I was raised in a very Catholic family and went to a very Catholic school. I didn #8217;t even get sex Ed in high school, and my mom firmly advocated for abstinence until marriage (which is what she did). I used the whole  #8220;only have sex with someone you love #8221; rule as a way to circumvent abstinence but still retain some standards, and breaking that just felt like...well, losing a past self. But at the same time, I recognize the rules and regulations I was placing on myself was still a bygone of a religious upbringing that I no longer believed in or practiced, so maybe it was best to be broken. Sorry, thank you for letting me rant a little more : #8217;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 22:31:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did that habit continue into other grades? Or have you weened off drinking?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This 60 year old messaging me, a still basically teenage girl</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 23:10:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 23:55:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re right, a golf ball clit does sound pretty enticing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 16:55:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ve been wanting to watch another LP of the game (I really don #8217;t plan on playing it myself, at least not any time soon). Could you recommend some good ones? I definitely wanna see one where Connor and Hank get along for all the Buddy Cop stuff people keep raving about, but really just any play through that #8217;s doing a different path would be interesting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 00:04:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I took a picture of this little guy just the other week! Good ole lil #8217; toot toot is famous now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 17:40:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Met up with a random dude on Tinder while blowing through a big city. He was adorable, looked a lot like a guy I had a giant crush on in college so I said fuck it and invited him to my hotel room. With no further ado, we start making out. I had wanted to maybe talk a little first, but I figure he #8217;s only here for one reason so we keep going. He #8217;s making these really loud, really frequent moans and his mouth is basically completely open with his tongue just flopping around my mouth. We lay back and he asks to finger me, which I say sure to. He starts jack hammering me with two, then three fingers. It hurts, but not too bad. He eventually moves down to start going down on me as well, but he #8217;s just got his tongue out while shaking his head back and forth. I let it go on for a little bit before pulling him back up to move on, and he starts feeling up my breasts too. I instantly notice a very...distinct smell. Blood. I look down and his hand is practically covered in a red glove, with blood now smeared all over my bra, stomach and thighs. He #8217;s completely none the wiser, still making those moaning noises while kissing on me but now I #8217;m freaking out, trying to figure out if it #8217;s my period or something. I finally tap him off, run to the bathroom to wipe off and grab him a wet towel for his hand. It definitely wasn #8217;t my period, the fingering had just been too rough or something. I then go down on him, only to discover the smallest penis I #8217;d ever seen. He cums in maybe a minute or two, then starts thanking me. We cuddle for a few minutes, then he pulls out a condom. While I #8217;m riding him, my mom starts knocking on the door. Apparently my dad is having chest pains and we have to take him to the hospital. Tinder boy dresses, I apologize, he leaves, and then spend the night in the ER with my parents.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 18:22:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, the first time he approached me about cuckolding and humiliation, we tried it out a little bit until he called me crying asking if I still actually loved him. I put a stop to it then, but a month or so later he wanted to do it again, assured me it was something he really liked/wanted. I know he and his current girlfriend are in an open relationship so I sort of figured he #8217;d really embraced the life but I guess was wrong. I definitely accept fault and know I wouldn #8217;t have said nearly as much if I wasn #8217;t so stupid drunk. I honestly don #8217;t even remember exactly what I said- my friends told me the next day</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 22:29:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I second the Fallout recommendation, either New Vegas or 4 would probably be good for her. 4 has the customizing your  #8220;house #8221; (settlements) and pet/companion aspects. I know one of my friends got his non-gamer girlfriend into it and she sunk a lot of time with the settlement building and such. Also, if she has a decent enough computer, just have her look around Steam for anything that catches her eye, and offer to watch her play, or both play your own games while Skyping/on discord. EDIT: I #8217;d also recommend Binding of Isaac, Bioshock, or Skyrim.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 00:09:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cuckolding is basically an unfaithful/adulteress wife. Usually the cuckold is aware of the cheating and gets off to the thought of it. Hope that kind of makes sense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 00:46:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with the part that we weren #8217;t in a relationship so it wasn #8217;t appropriate. In all fairness, we were still talking and sexting while playing into these fetishes, and before/after I hung out with my friends he kept expressing his desire for me to humiliate him with them and such. I honestly had no intention to actually talk about that stuff with my friends though.... He #8217;s several states away, and I #8217;ll probably never see him in person ever again in my entire life, but I miss him as a friend sometimes. We talked a little while after this incident, and he wanted more details. He then asked me to do more, to show them pictures and stuff which I said no to. I feel like he #8217;s not as upset, but it #8217;s hard to read and I don #8217;t know if it #8217;s worth approaching the situation anymore. I was a young, dumb teenager at the time, and discretion is something I definitely value a lot more now, especially with fetishes and kinks. Thank you for no longer thinking of me as a horrible person though, I know that title paints a bad picture haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 15:58:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>And don #8217;t forget your Patagonia jacket when things get a little nippy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 18:28:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait what #8217;s Matt #8217;s Snapchat?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 00:13:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love this style! How did you describe it to the artist, or did you just use reference photos?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 00:35:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I totally relate, I #8217;m pretty darn pale and looking to get a floral tattoo this fall. The size of the lines is perfect! Thank you for the link, I just looked through her work a little bit and it #8217;s exactly the sort of style I was hoping to show my artist as a reference! Congrats on a gorgeous tattoo :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 00:38:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s definitely worth a shot, plus Mabel #8217;s voice actress is in it. Kristen Schaal is a treasure :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This thing I saw on a flight from Boston to San Francisco (was closer to San Fran)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 22:17:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 22:24:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Solved! Thank you, I thought it might be some sort of solar power array but wasn #8217;t sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are these good parts?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 21:43:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I found a rig selling for $500, and would only be using it for light/moderate gaming. Stuff like League, Overwatch, Killing Floor 2 and Dead by Daylight. These are the specs he sent AMD 8350 8 CORE CPU ASUS Formula-Z Motherboard 16 Gig RAM 250 GIG ssd WINDOWS 10 GIGABYTE R9 380 4 GIG CARD GM V8 CPU COOLER If something would need to be upgraded or swapped out, or if you think it #8217;s not a good deal, I #8217;d appreciate the insight. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 00:16:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>( #128065;  #860; #662; #128065;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 13:29:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>( #128065;  #860; #662; #128065;) got any proof?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 13:30:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have only one question... OwO what #8217;s this~?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 13:33:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Strangely kinda wholesome. The sentiment on its own is words to live by, but distasteful in context I guess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 13:34:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>( #128065;  #860; #662; #128065;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 13:39:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I loved playing the Diamond City radio station while in game, cause my dad would usually walk by and recognize almost every single song and be able to sing along to it. He #8217;s in his 70 #8217;s and would sit while I played for hours just enjoying the music : #8217;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 13:43:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>My man</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 21:12:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! Saved some cake for you bby</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It #8217;s been over a year</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 23:33:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>My last major cuts were right after my first boyfriend broke up with me. Dumb, cliche and over reactive. I know. But those cuts were the deepest I ever made. Over a year later now, and they #8217;re still a light purple, raised and prominent. I started wearing shorts again. The other scars are white and hard to see, unless you really look. My second boyfriend noticed them and didn #8217;t say anything, but I assured him I didn #8217;t do it anymore. I thought that was all behind me. But now the urge is back. I saw a girl the other day. I sat next to her during some street performance, and happened to glance over. Her legs were covered in cuts, along with her arms. There were so many cuts, a few rather recent looking. I couldn #8217;t stop thinking about starting again, making new scars as large and deep as the others. But I want to be able to swim again. To join the campus swim club and be in the water again. I #8217;ve been joining my mom on her daily mile swims back home, and it #8217;s been so nice. Cutting again would make wearing a swimsuit in front of her impossible. But the thoughts are there, the mental images of blood and the memories of the familiar pinch and burn of a blade. I hate it. I hate that I #8217;m still seemingly in the same mindset as a year ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>