<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject9492</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-03 12:55:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Priestess Dantalian performed a dark binding ceremony between Zile and Prue, which forcibly made her evil and affected her sisters, and the book, as well, because of the Power of Three. However, Cole and Phoebe were married through a dark wedding (at night, in a cemetery, where the groom drinks the bride's blood). This was voluntary and dark weddings are not used to pollute families like the binding ceremony is. It serves simply to join two together "as one, till life be gone". Think of the binding ceremony as a spell, and the dark wedding as a gothic vampire handfasting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-03 13:05:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it was generally accepted that Prue was "meant" to die, so the Cleaners didn't intervene. However, the comics refute this by saying that the Power of Three was never meant to transfer to Paige. There's also the possibility that the Cleaners were only created by the Tribunal after Prue's death, but they seemed familiar with Andy Trudeau and Reece Davidson (even though they called him "Inspector Reece"; awkward). I don't think that there IS an answer, just a big sucking hole of nothing (Paige; 8x01/02). PS, it's "Tempus", not "Tempest". It's Latin for "time".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-03 13:15:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, yeah, Gerald Robotnik made Shadow, using Black Doom's DNA.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-03 13:31:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's not true. There was... Tiki... Umm... Her grandfather... Carter the carnival worker... Uhh... Katherine's coach driver in 1864... Okay, it's a little true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-04 20:40:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see that you probably have your answer. I don't care. The Chaos Emeralds are seven (sometimes six, sometimes eight) jewels that contain extraordinary power when used in unison, and that can be controlled using the Master Emerald. All eight gems were kept safe at a shrine in what would later be known as Mystic Ruins. They, and the chao creatures that lived at the shrine, came to be protected by Chaos, a chao that became a warm-hearted watery monster thanks to exposure to the Master Emerald. 4000 years before the present, the echidna Tikal was born. The daughter of the Chief Pachacamac, she was raised by her grandmother. After Grandma (that's what her people called her) died, Pachacamac became a power-hungry warlord, conquering nearby tribes in the name of his subjects. Tikal wasn't too happy about this. She befriended Chaos and the chao, her trusted her enough to show her the Emerald Shrine. Pachacamac learnt of this, and tried to steal the Emeralds. Seeing the chao hurt by Pachacamac's warriors, Chaos absorbed the power of the Seven Emeralds and killed Pachacamac, his people, and ruined their civilization. Tikal used the power of the Master Emerald to seal herself and Chaos inside of the jewel to prevent further destruction. The island on which the shrine existed was raised into the sky. The Chaos Emeralds dispersed elsewhere. Some members of the clan survived, and presumably lived in the ruins of their once great city. They made a mural depicting Chaos in his perfect form. Others lived on the floating Angel Island, protecting the Master Emerald so that Chaos could not be released. Thousands of years later, the United Federation has become one of, if not the, most powerful country on the planet. Gerald Robotnik, who studied Chaos and managed to create creatures based on him, was asked by the President to discover immortality. His granddaughter, Maria, was dying, so Gerald agreed to. He created a life-form named Shadow, thanks to the help of the alien Black Doom, who asked only that Shadow collect the Chaos Emeralds for him in return. However, the military saw Shadow as a threat, so all those involved in the project were killed or arrested. Maria herself was shot after helping Shadow escape to Earth, where he was captured anyway. The vengeful Gerald Robotnik managed to modify Shadow to seek revenge by collecting the Chaos Emeralds and using them to initiate a program that would send Space Colony ARK towards the Earth at far too great a velocity. Gerald was later executed, and Shadow locked away. Modern day; Gerald's grandson and Maria's cousin, Ivo Robotnik, plans to rule the world. He is stopped by Sonic the Hedgehog, and later his friend, Miles Prower. By this time, the guardians of the Master Emerald are all extinct except for one survivor, named Knuckles, who joins Sonic and Tails after Dr. Robotnik tried to trick him into collecting the Emeralds for him. The series explores several plotlines --- Dr. Robotnik finding stone tablets that told him about Chaos; Shadow being freed by Robotnik and using him to get Gerald's revenge for Maria's death; what happened to the ancient world after Pachacamac and his tribe's deaths; and the constant search for the Chaos Emeralds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-02-09 19:38:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, Damon was accidentally cured in Shadow Souls, so the question is if the TV series will follow the same road.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Pick a Takeda</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-03 17:39:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Due to scheduling issues, Takeda was recasted (if you didn't notice). What are everyone's thoughts on the new Takeda?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-03 17:50:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mm. In the books, Damon actually IS the crow. He can transform at will, as long as he has enough blood in his system. Katherine can transform into an owl, and Stefan can transform into a hawk or falcon, I believe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-03 17:55:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder how Katherine knew that... I doubt Elijah or Klaus would have told her while they were in England, Rebekah acts as though she's never met (or at least had any extended interaction with) Katherine and Finn was "daggered" long before Katherine was born. Did Katherine have a run in with Kol at some point...? (Food for fanfiction)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Who's the good one?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-09 21:10:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I am righteous", says both Light and L in the English translation of Death Note. Or "I am justice" in the anime. But, justice or righteous, who was right? Who was the righteous one? L or Light?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-10 10:40:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Opinions. It's called asking for opinions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Von Swartzschild or Petrova?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-03-10 11:10:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was wondering --- who is everyone's favourite Katherine? The childlike German noble-turned psychopathic killer, or the vulnerable Bulgarian girl-turned vindictive seductress?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>