<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject9249</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 19:50:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hola!! Ok so I noticed someone mentioned Isdin and I am so glad someone did because I personally think it is great. They are a large umbrella company and have things from skincare to antibiotics so it's a lot of stuff but I really like the Acniben line! It is meant for teenagers, (which I am not, I am 28) but have many problems with PIE and spots and their Acniben Control de Brillos y Granos Gel Crema has been a dream for me. Ingredients include Glycerin, Niacinamide, Zinc, Lactic Acid, and Madecassoside (tiger grass) It has noticeable "clean" fragrance which is not so hot, so watch out if you have a sensitivity to this also spanish farmacies carry a lot of french farmacy brands (we are neighbours after all!)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Routine Help] I love my skincare routine but I also love wilderness camping so...what do you do?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 11:48:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone! Background: I am 28 years old with pretty normal skin except for a patch of oiliness right in the center of my forehead between my eyebrows, have some PIE/PIH/scarring from severe skin picking disorder(much better now!), and the only thing that really freaks out my skin is stress (very good because I have a life long battle with anxiety disorders ha ha ha) But with a lot of lurking on this site I have figured out a skin routing that makes my skin quite happy! I will detail below, but I use several skincare products. This is only a problem in that my boyfriend and I are also very heavy duty campers! We like to go for usually 2 weeks at a time to do pretty remote beach camping, mountain camping, etc. during which we usually have limited access to clean, running water (maybe only once every two or three days). So I would like your help in trying to adjust my routine for these trips while trying to maintain as many benefits as possible! Does anyone else have this problem?? AM: Caudalie cleansing milk, LRP sero zinc toner, Timeless vit c+e+ferulic serum, dr. jart ceramidin liquid, Isdin Acniben oil control gel-cream, drop evening primrose oil + drop rosehip oil + vera green cream (Spanish aloe vera based natural cream) for moisture, LRP anthelios XL 50+ PM: ultrabland lush, caudalie gentle cleansing foam, LRP serozinc, (sometimes) origins essence in that pink bottle, 3x per week Earth Science Naturals a/b rejuvenating serum (AHA/BHA combo), TO niacinamide 10% + zinc 1% (alternative with the exfoliator), dr. Jart+ ceramidin liquid, neem oil+sea buckthorn oil+ vera green cream European products please! Especially if you can find them in Spain/Greece (our two home countries  lt;3) thank you so much for your help!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 12:24:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Turning off the mobile phone for days at a time does wonders for overall health, don't you think??  lt;3 what type of cleanser do you take? something no-rinse?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 14:50:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>to be honest, I haven't ever really used micellar water. which do you suggest? I know there are different caps on different brands but I dont know what each is for...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 15:09:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah, sunscreen is a must! this might not be a bad idea. fresh air and relaxation do wonders (I also get like, really good sleep when camping which helps a lot) last time we went, I remembered to bring a rosewater spray but not enough underwear and my boyfriend will never let me forget it, so maybe leaving skincare aside is for the best hahah</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 16:51:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you! and definitely anthelios, my mediterranean genes failed me and I was born lily white *cries in spanish*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-26 16:51:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 17:16:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>you can do it! I don't know if you're into skincare at all but something that really helped me was starting to take care of my skin, even in simple ways! I though, well, if I'm going to touch my skin, why don't I do something nurturing like rubbing in lotion? cut your nails, use hydrocolloid bandages for the big scabs, be patient and forgiving with yourself! also big thing with doctors that I don't think gets said enough is that while they are doctors, you know better in some things than they do about your anxieties, triggers, what is a problem and what is not. Many doctors can be very dismissive about skin-picking, and if yours is, either make them listen or drop them!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 17:28:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>you are not alone for sure, I've picked at my face and legs like almost wanting to rip the pore out. Have you tried any cognitive behavioral therapy? it might be able to help with replacing those thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 17:34:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>snaaaaaaps</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 17:34:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>so exercise doesn't make anyone else here look blotchy? just me??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 20:36:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>still fit though :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 22:20:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've had these and it turns out it was actually a blackhead so it seems like it could be that. especially if it's overnight</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 22:26:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like this must be said, but it seems you aren't using SPF and you MUST use SPF! even if it's cloudy outside, heck, even if you're indoors but near windows a lot, always wear it! UV exposure will contribute to any inflammation (acne is an inflammatory issue) you have, will sensitize your skin and leave it vulnerable to new bacteria, and prevent healing. You also seem to be using serums with active ingredients morning and night so it's extra important. there's a whole HG thread on sunscreens here and a lot of existing threads to help you pick one :) for reference I use the La Roche Posay anthelios XL 50+ good luck!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 22:29:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>well you know your skin best! it might just be a freckle :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 22:32:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>during! but it calms down back to pasty white after stopping pretty quickly. but maybe all the increased circulation from exercise helps your face? not a derm but seems logical enough haha!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-27 22:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>hiii! first of all, keep fighting the good fight with skin picking, i've left a couple nasty marks on my face too, but we've got this :) Second, have you thought about switching the AHA to a different spot in your routine? using both AHA and vitamin C in the same AM routine could be causing your skin irritation that is aggravating your acne. I looked up the vitamin A serum and it seems to have Hydroxypinacolone Retinoate (HPR) which is apparently a much gentler member of the retinoid family. I would move your AHA to the PM routine and alternate days between the AHA and the Vit A serum. Third, I think you need to up your SPF game especially using so many actives! Look for 30+ I'd say (I personally use 50+ and also use a vit C, vit A, and AHA/BHA combo)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 00:40:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I personally don't know any, but there is a Scandinavian skincare sub red if you're looking for recommendations!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 11:04:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>of course!  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 12:40:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I literally bought three different cleansers in the past 2 weeks, for what could arguably be defined as "no reason". you're not alone. which of the balms do you like best?? these are my current new obsessions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 17:17:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Should be right around your skin's natural pH, which is to say about 5.5</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 17:18:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is using a stand alone product like niacinamide serum really that necessary if I use other products that also include it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 17:21:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you're probably safer adding it to your evening routine and not every day since it's an AHA and a pretty loaded one I think. What's your evening routine look like?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 17:26:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a big fan of aloe for this! But be careful because a lot of the cheaper aloe based products have alcohol which also help. I've also used the LRP cicaplast baume 5 to soothe my skin as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 21:04:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>hang in there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 00:37:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love Caudalie so much, a few months ago I went on a search for other brands but I did a full 360 and came back. the gentle milk and foaming cleansers, the cleansing oil, the glycolic peel, and the overnight detox oil are all in my rotation</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 11:37:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>My bf, despite having pretty bad acne as a teen and having been to a dermatologist to help clear it refuses to put moisturizer on his face. He also uses his beard to cover acne marks and COME ON it's not fair, he gets to cover up his scarring AND look sexier at the same time for FREE? jesus christ</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 16:08:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've heard some people have this reaction and often it's attributed to the presence of fatty alcohols/esters in the PM version of cerave and opposed to say the AM or the version in the tub. Could be this maybe?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 16:19:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>still wear sunscreen (I'm wearing it in the winter even when I don't go outside and we've gotten like over two weeks of rain every day) also look at things like setting sprays (or like facial sprays in general) with SPF! Shiseido, Supergoop, amore pacific have some!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 21:39:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>well technically, anytime you see sunlight, you have exposure to UV rays, so like through windows or clouds. as for the setting sprays? that I have no clue, sorry :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-01 21:43:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>hahahahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 22:29:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>YES! i know the feeling my dear. take your freedom and glow on!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-02 23:40:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>don't do exfoliating scrubs! if you feel like you must do a little physical exfoliation, I usually like to rinse off cleansers with a warm washcloth which can provide a little soft exfoliating action :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 14:21:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have an incredible ability to sober up for just long enough to do my full routine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 18:51:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahahajaja</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-04 21:48:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Muy bien! I found this thread that could be helpful to find new products! https://www.reddit.com/r/SkincareAddiction/comments/30zddd/scaeu_part_two_help_me_guys/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 13:14:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh goodness I thought I was the only one! the cucumber one doesn't for me though. shame because I love the smell of rose</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 13:25:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am so glad they sell Nuxe in a pharmacy near me in spain because the r #234;ve de miel baume l #232;vres is an HG for me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-05 14:13:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>saludos!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 20:58:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love this stuff. Use it every day</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Cringe] please pray for my boyfriend</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-06 21:06:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>he tried to get into skincare after much of my insistance by putting on some 13yr old Aveeno on his face that he found hoarded in his teenage bedroom</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 00:17:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you noticing any irritation? if you notice your acne isn't budging you could just be increasing inflammation from too many actives. I personally dont use acids and retinols on the same day because it sensitizes my skin, nor do I use acids every day, only 3 times a week to give my skin time to heal and recover from the exfoliation</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 00:20:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in Europe (spain) and I buy witch hazel toner with no alcohol from a local ecological store. if you have any that sell natural or ecological products, you might find some!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 00:30:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>i like the full of grace serum ok, I think it smells really nice (it has like...a lot of fragrace according to cosdna, so if you're sensitive to that i'd steer clear) and hasnt broken me out. probably won't repurchase just because I have a lot of other oil based serums I want to try</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 11:58:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean it's worth taking a look at the HG thread to the side for moisturizing options. I hear you on the zero waste thing though...I'm trying to avoid plastic myself</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 15:05:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>i SwEaR its just waterrrrr</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 18:14:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>second caudalie cleansing milk!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-09 21:43:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>as a fellow skin picker, carry around hydrocolloids! i slap them on anything i've picked so if my hand goes back up to the spot I get deterred by the bandaid. plug for therapy here, it sounds like you've got some negative energy towards yourself and your body and it's ok and getting help works for a lot of people. AND if you can't get help there are a ton of CBT (cognitive behavioral therapy) exercises you can find online. it's a technique that can help with compulsive disorders like skin picking. edit: be kind to yourself and be patient with yourself. you don't have to fix everything all at once :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 01:23:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>holy mother of god she looks GREAT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 18:50:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi! Ok so generally you want to do cleanse - tone - treat - moisturize - protector, then within each category thin to thick application. So I'd do azelaic acid (needs no wait time) - gt; niacinamide - gt; marine hyaluronics - gt; first aid - gt; squalane to seal it all in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 19:07:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you got them in the right spot! But is the vitamin C l-ascorbic acid? If so it is pretty finicky so wait 10-15 minutes after you apply it before putting anything else!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-11 20:55:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah the niacinamide has that weird stickiness afterward. I don't know so much about mixing products, but I've heard that formulations tend to be made to work on their own and so maybe not mix them? (don't quote me on that haha) but layering moisturizer over the niacinamide like 30-45 seconds I've applied it does help with the texture at least for me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 00:28:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>this is SO good. well done!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 01:10:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a big fan of lovely textured moisturizers for these things, anything you can give yourself a nice facial massage with. I'm currently a big fan of balms, they serve this purpose really well haha. I've been using the Leahlani Bless Beauty Balm. the best way to get over a broken heart is to be kind to yourself and live your best life!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 11:13:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>oops, wsn't aware. listen to this person who knows more than I!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 23:44:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are some good chemical peels that are not MUA? MUA sadly does not ship to spain it seems.... I'm dealing with light PIH and atrophic scarring.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 00:08:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah, unfortunately under thein "chemical peels" section there is only a recommendation from MUAC as well :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 00:10:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's really weird. MUAC will ship to Kiribati but not to Spain...?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 00:11:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>hmm I'm really into using oils right now, which I'm not sure if they are your jam. I like passion fruit oil :) But! maybe check in the HGs and read the descriptions of the textures? or heck, go to sephora and get all the samples! I feel like something "whipped" would be nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 15:54:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>hahahahahahaha omg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 23:45:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>have you tried including any other actives in your routine? maybe an AHA?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 12:26:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use the caudalie cleansing milk and I personally don't use cotton at all as I find it wasteful. I pretty much just use it as one would use a cleansing oil. I massage a pump or two into my face for a few minutes and then remove with a damp washcloth. whether or not this is the "correct" way to do it, I can't tell you but it works well for me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 22:59:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>besides the fact that you are BEAUTIIIIFUL you give pickers like me hope :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 23:09:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I personally rinse off my cleansing milk (the Caudalie one). Ive wiped off with cotton rounds in the past when I haven't had access to a water source but I don't like it, I feel like it leaves surfactants behind on the skin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 23:11:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have been eyeing there! let me know what you think!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 23:50:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>so CosRX a korean beauty brand has an AHA/BHA clarifying toner you could try! a lot of people on this sub also like Paula #8217;s Choice Skin Perfecting 2% BHA Lotion Exfoliant. this would go after the facial wash and before the moisturizer. BUT may I suggest you try a gentler moisturizer? expecially if you want to add something with additional actives like an AHA/BHA treatment, if your moisturizer ALSO has actives you may risk aggravating your skin and increasing your acne! So for moisturizer I'd stick to something soothing, moisture focused, and with a gel consistency. Neutrogena Hydroboost I think would be a good one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 13:04:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>haha sorry, yeah I know this stuff can be overwhelming. There are a couple of guides in the side bar that might be really informative! AHAs (alpha hydroxy acids) and BHAs (beta hydroxy acids) are exfoliants, the former more for skin texture and evenness and the latter better for cleaning out pores and healing acne. Salicylic acid like in your current neutrogena moisturizer is a BHA. Actives are pretty much anything that is supposed to deliver a benefit or treatment in your skincare. These can range from acids, retinoids, and even certain vitamins such as vitamin C. While Actives are great, too many of them can end up damaging your skin. Your skin needs just as much rest and healing time as it does treatment time (kind of like everything else!) Also. may I recommend this blog! It's from a guy who really managed to get some severe acne and other skin issues under control, and has a great way of explaining things simpleskincarescience.com</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 08:38:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>i'm drooooling</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 11:33:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>well played!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-16 15:22:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does it tell you the estimated value of the bag?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 17:57:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>None. Literally nothing. I dont remember ever using anything con my face beyond water. Had perfect skin. You never know what you have until it's gone CRIES</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 18:01:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nuxe r #234;ve de miel. Its thick AND MATTE. I will never use anything else on my lips</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 18:08:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hematite and malachite extract? As in the fucking stones? WHAT PLACE DOES THIS HAVE IN SKINCARE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 21:20:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love Apivita!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 10:24:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>what is the stuff in the pretty gold dropper??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 13:54:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>ugh, BAMBOOZLED by pretty packaging</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 11:39:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Calloo! Callay!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-20 23:07:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>hiiii!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 00:23:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would suggest them to look up any of the many different societies in which more than two genders exist. If they say those cultures are wrong, proceed to point out their western colonizer mindset</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 00:49:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have several of these from severe skin picking and while they have faded a bit with time, you can still see them, especially if the lighting is right. And let me tell you, not a single person has ever commented on them. They don't distract people when speaking to me. They don't stop me from modelling for portrait photography (nor do the artists try to cover them up!). They don't stop me from having a loving (and super hot boyfriend). I am the only one who cared about them until I decided to not care anymore. Just from what you're saying, I think your depression and anxiety feeds off of these scars and makes you focus on them, not that the scars cause the anxiety and depression. At least with me and other body focused anxieties (I had a severe eating disorder for 10 years) it was so. So don't worry about other people! And any person who would focus only on your scar and judge you for it is not a person worth your worry. Stay beautiful!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 11:30:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Based on a recommendation I read elsewhere, I never wash my face in the shower. Shower water if often too hot to wash your face in. So try washing it with luke warm water or cooler in the sink. Especially if you live in an aggressive climate, you should try to definitely moisturize and use things with which to protect your moisture barrier. Check the side bar for recommendations!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 23:16:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>it shoul be at least....three times this size!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 23:18:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I literally just forgot to wash my hair for over a week so.... that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-23 23:21:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>hola compatriota! se necesita receta para el retinol?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 13:05:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>gracias!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 22:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes... this is exactly what I say to myself...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-24 22:58:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>YESSSSS stay safe, keep that face clear</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 15:02:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check the HG thread on the side. Also no real such thing as "moisturizer for men". You can use any moisturizer than works</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 17:32:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>The US (BP) versi #243;n or EU one?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 18:15:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think its a gender debate, its just that with regards to skincare formulations, skin thickness doesn't actually affect how these products work. So "men's" and "women's" skincare products are essentially the same thing, with the exclusion of fragrances and good marketing. Especially when you get down to treatment and active ingredients. You dont see "mens tretinoin" or "women's chemical peels" . So if a "women's" moisturizer has the ingredients you need that's the one you get.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 22:45:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>omg the soft moisturizing lotion costs the same as my rent * crying * edit: I realize this was not the point of your review, so I should actually say thank you for taking the time to do this! Unfortunately, La Mer also has a lot of ingredients that are not good for acneic or sensitive skin so people who are interested in purchasing should definitely check those before they buy!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-25 23:29:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>if you love lip balms try the Nuxe Reve de Miel! It's matte which I love and very rich. Nuxe is not in every farmacy, I had to look up on the website which farmacies had them here in Bilbao and it was easy enough to find!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 01:00:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>come to Spain!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 01:01:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>in exchange you can also earn half of what you earn in the US (if you're lucky and actually find a decent job)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 01:42:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>The darphin balm has a buttload of citrus essential oils in it so if your skin is sensitive to this beware!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 12:16:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi! I'm interested in the Biologique P50 (I'm in Spain)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 12:26:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>and I can't read on there (I don't have my glasses) what is the ml cuantity?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 12:29:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you! I will take it :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 12:32:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>is it just me or are the people on this sub generally just very very good looking?? I love the increasing smile on the second image :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 21:06:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you tried a body wash with salicylic acid? Or a moisturizer with Urea in it (like Eucerin). Both provide exfoliation that isn't physical, and urea is even moisturizing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 18:31:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi! I am also in Europe (Spain) and azelaic acid is found here at farmacies without a prescription under the name finacea (15% gel). Have you asked at a farmacy in Finland?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 18:37:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Besides the dryness, did you notice improvement with the stridex? I'm thinking that keeping an active in would be a good idea if you up the moisture! Add moisturizer in the morning perhaps. Also foaming cleansers can also be very drying too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 11:40:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm as far as suggestions for moisturizers and cleansers, perhaps look at the HG sidebar! I am unfortunately (fortunately?) in Europe so my selection is probably quite different from yours! I have heard good things on here about the CeraVe AM lotion for a moisturizer https://www.amazon.com/CeraVe-Facial-Moisturizing-Lotion-AM/dp/B00F97FHAW/ref=sr_1_2_sspa?s=beauty amp;ie=UTF8 amp;qid=1522921150 amp;sr=1-2-spons amp;keywords=cerave+am+facial+moisturizing+lotion+spf+30 amp;psc=1 and Vanicream gentle cleanser https://www.amazon.com/Vanicream-Gentle-Cleanser-sensitive-Dispenser/dp/B00QY1XZ4W and you can definitely do stridex every other day or even less to start with until you can see what your skin tolerates :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 18:56:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I swear getting regular, good sleep is like 60% of my skincare routine. If I dont get some solid sleep my skin freaks the fuck out Edit: I can't spell skin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-06 00:02:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friend has been looking for a hooded eyes smoky eye look, please share! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-07 13:38:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>you're very welcome :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 14:28:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I personally love hemp seed oil for OCM, and sometimes I mix some rose hip in there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 14:29:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I heard purges can last up to even a month so it might be worth sticking it out?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 14:39:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is also an LPR cicaplast gel which avoids the white cast all together if you can find it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 14:48:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use neem oil and I love it. It keeps breakouts to a minimum, especially when I take a break from actives Edit: it smells BAD. now I'm used to it but it kind if smells like old Chinese food</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Product Question] Farmacy sleep tight</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 19:32:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love me some balms. My skins react really nicely to them as a night step and have been looking for a new one. Has anyone tried this one? It seems to have some nice oils that I like. Thank you for your input in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 22:21:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>would be greatly appreciated! thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 22:30:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a vegetable oil, not an essential oil so you don't need to dilute it if you don't want to. I personally mix two drops of this and two drops of sea buckthorn oil together for my face at night. doesn't do much for a smell though... however I really did get used to it, the human nose does that quite easily as a defense mechanism haha!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 01:15:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes this has been an issue for me too...I'm not sure how old you are (I'm 28) use a retinol and while it has kept me free from fine lines, nothing restores the youthful look of a little fat in your face :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 01:19:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>As far as I know, a facial oil is not an occlusive so it should be OK to put under a moisturizer. I do, and have not noticed a decrease in the effectiveness of my moisturizer! You can even mix them together</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 01:21:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>You might purge a bit, perhaps some flaking. Be sure to step it way up with your moisturizing steps!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 21:48:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>the pink is so prettyyyy and I'm looking for something with peptides!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 22:05:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>My personal thing I do is use a make up remover prior to working out, apply sunscreen, do full double cleansing when I get home</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 15:21:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>where do I even START?? ok: - my morning routine I use a combination of Pracaxi and Rosehip oil - to oil cleanse I use hemp seed oil - for my evening routine I use a combination of Pracaxi, Neem, and Sea Buckthorn oil I also rotate Maracuya, A #231;a #237;, and Evening Primrose depending on how I feel I love oils. I use them for everything Edit: I have pretty normal skin, though sometimes dry, with the occasional pimple. I mostly have scarring issues from pretty severe skin picking disorder for many years</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 15:45:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>are you using any sort of moisturizer? your exfoliation and cleanser might be stripping your skin! also you might want to try chemical exfoliation rather than physical exfoliation. I know the oiliness can be frustrating but it really is better to start off with less then build up with exfoliating. try not to do it every day!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 16:13:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, I don't see a problem with a little tingling or redness immediately afterwards if it fades and doesn't cause any other sort of problem?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When looking "non-binary" ONLY means looking "masculine" if you're AFAB</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 16:31:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I'm AFAB, non-binary, and am generally read as female in daily life. I don't bind (though I've toyed with the idea, but I'm already pretty small chested), I have long hair (also playing with it, I liked my short hair too and may go back to it), and I wear bright colors pretty often (despite them being often "men's" clothing or generally oversized). I also dabble in glitter and makeup when I'm feeling fancy (NOT FEMME). I move through the world being perceived as a woman, when I'm not. This has caused a fair amount of conflict within myself. Back when my hair was short I was able to "confuse" people a little bit more (and yes that brought me quite a bit of joy) when I wore more masculine attire and on my non fancy days. And I felt as though even within my queer community I was accepted more as non-binary when I looked like that. And when I avoided color. And when I shunned make up. But I dont ALWAYS want to look like that. And I don't think it's fair that people still, even subconciously stick to the canons of appearance when it comes to non-binary people. I don't want to give up my style, and the fluidity, and experimentation, just for the sake of being visibly recognized as non-binary. It's very frustrating. Has anyone else had to deal with this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 18:24:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am also thinking of a stamp across my forehead</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 18:31:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>agreed. I was actually doing some reading for my thesis from activist Riki Wilchins about whether this distinction is even possible, that is whether identity, presentation, and performance (in the classic speech-act sense) are distinct enough inherently to be separated from one another into meaningful categories. In general the whole idea of "identity" is so incredibly unstable and fails to have a consistent definition across multiple disciplines in the social sciences. ughhhh #queeringmythesis</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 18:32:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>if you're a man who glams up, you're gay and confused if you're a woman who glams down, you're a woman who might've kissed another woman in college and probably also confused *long deep side eye*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 18:35:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>A way I've also kind of worked on this is just being visibly hairy hahaha. I don't shave my body hair (and I am a hairy mediterranean) and it provokes some of the confusion. or maybe just disgust. either way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 18:37:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>right. and I sometimes on rare occasions love dressing very high femme, but it feels like drag, like an exagerration of a presentation that is not my identity at all, but it's like wearing a costume on halloween. of course, explaining this to people is a nightmare, especially because it's perceived as "ooo see? this is how you should be dressing, I knew you were a girl"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 20:48:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>real talk, while I don't wear them often, I love dresses because I'm lazy and like the fact you can just put on one thing and be done with it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 20:49:36</DATE>
    <TEXT> lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 21:21:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>unfortunately I don't live in an English speaking country, and our language is entirely gendered (Spanish)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 21:41:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>rose hip and pracaxi oil before morning moisturizer hemp seed oil cleanser pracaxi, neem, and sea buckthorn oils after retinol in the evenings</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 21:53:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>your skin looks amazing!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 22:31:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just use it straight, then remove with a warm damp wash cloth and follow up with a foaming cleanser. I think it removes make up well! I can't vouch for eye makeup or very very heavy makeup as I usually stick to foundation, blush, and some concealer for my makeup. I really like it, it smells only the faintest of weed but I'm not mad at that haha. it also seems a lot of skins tolerate it really well!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 22:32:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>hahaha I had about one year of my "sorority girl costume" before I depledged and went rogue!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 22:37:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know how old you are, and if you're a minor it can be especially hard (though at any age not being accepted by your parents can be very hard) but remember that you are allowed to PROTECT YOURSELF from people like this in your life, whether family or not! he is not entitled to access to your life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 22:48:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I own some expensive stuff, but it's mostly for collection purposes, novelty, the scents, and just feeling fancy once in a while. All my skincare doing the actual work are pharmacy products!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 22:50:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>LRP cicaplast baume/gel b5 heals like a dream, calms my skin, have come back to it multiple times over the years!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 23:06:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do! usually I put the oils on first and moisturizer immediately afterwards. I just think it's less messy than mixing the oils into the moisturizer as many people do</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 00:27:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>what a beautiful response. I apprecite it very much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 10:59:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>chemical exfoliation is usually seen as a much more effective means of exfoliating. I would get, for example, a toner with salicylic acid, or glycolic acid (things that say AHA or BHA) and start slowly, once a week at first, then two, then three, etc. I personally dont think you ever need to use an exfoliant every day...you swkin needs time to regenerate and heal!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 11:00:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>much love back!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 16:28:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>this can also be used as a great at home cure for lycanthropy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 17:41:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're going to use honey, make sure it's the good stuff! (which is, obviously, a little pricier). or else you're just rubbing sugar on your face</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 18:32:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>no, there haven't been sufficient clinical trials</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 18:40:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>there's a couple of ways, and none of them are fool proof, but the default is that most honey in supermarkets is bad haha. good honey is smooth in texture but it is not runny, it's thicker, it tastes better, actually smells like honey, and tends to pricier. your best option is always to buy local and know the supplier. for the record manuka honey from new zealand is the only one FDA approved to treat wounds I'm pretty sure, and since I am not from new zealand I order it on iHerb</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 19:06:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I here, a European representing all Europeans! It's hard to pick down a European skincare regime since with so much globalization and access to international products and routines, people are replicating te same skincare routines everywhere. Also, what does "European" even mean? Probably not Lithuanian, or Slovenian, or Irish. I'm gonna guess they actually mean "French" So with that in mind, this "European" skincare routine probably mean a heavily pharmacy based product routine. European pharmacies are not like American pharmacies. They are wonderful places full of stuff for your face and you don't panic over how much your medication costs (I lived in the US and this was traumatizing). Skincare-wise, they tend to be much more low-key, stick to the good stuff they know and love and has been around forever, and generally this stuff is pretty well formulated HOWEVER the whole "let's get rid of fragrances in skincare" hasn't quite caught on as much, which is sad. French pharmacy staples like Avene, LRP, Uriage are used a lot, but there are also other country specific brands which are quite nice like Sesderma in Spain and Apivita in Greece! I literally don't know anyone with a skincare routine as in-depth as mine. A friend of mine and I were having a conversation about skin and how she was on accutane but hated what it did to her body, and afterwards just washes and moisturizer and does nothing for her scarring because "my skin is healthy now, that's good enough, it doesn't have to be perfect".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 20:39:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't speak for France since I'm not there (we're neighbors though) but yes! as far as I know people do use RoC since forever. I think my mom used to use it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-11 22:06:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>me too!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 13:48:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>looks like you were trying to beat your skin into shape before! glad you were able to start simplifying and being more gentle :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 15:21:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>ugh my partner just fucking refuses. I have literally picked flakes of dry skin off his cheek and showed them to him and been like "DO YOU SEE THIS? DOES THIS LOOK NICE TO YOU??" he just genuinely doesn't care</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 16:01:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>looks like it, or maybe fungal acne. I believe the current HG thread is about products for CCs, but in summary, the common theme seems to be that CCs are best eliminated with AHAs (as opposed to BHAs) and with removing the product causing the CCS in the first place. Are you using anything with an AHA at the moment? (Glycolic, lactic, mandelic acids?)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 19:08:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>you look amazing! please tell me those are the natural colors of your lips omgggg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 22:30:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>it sounded more aggressive than it actually is, and we have that sort of dynamic jaja</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 22:32:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's also more that he believes dry skin is a myth and that that's what skin is supposed to look like</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 13:10:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I usually apply the bp or sulfur or other on top of the moisturizer so that the moisturizer acts as a preparing agent for the treatment and have it be less irritating</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 13:19:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>some of this looks like PIE (red marks caused by inflammation) and these sometimes take a looooong time to go away. while all the actives listed could be useful, I dont want to understand the importance of continuing to moisturize! especially if you start using things like glycolic acid or retinoids you might want to start thinking about increasing your moisturizing as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 13:34:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have recently begun to include a product with retinol in my skincare. I am currently not using any other exfoliants exceot for the pixi glow pads (20%) twice a week. I have been using exfoliants for a long time, however, mostly AHAs increased over the past year and a half. However, I'm breaking out from the retinol in what seems to be a small purge. I'm curious: will you always purge after using a new product with an active like this? even though I'm used to increased cell turn over?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 17:29:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>cc's are non-inflammatory little white heads</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 19:05:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>at that point they're probably papules or pustules, and are inflammatory acne</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Humor] the rest of my life is in shambles</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 01:38:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>me: *boom* nails skincare routine *boom* has first clear day in months *boom* bathes in the finest facial oils *boom* "I'm so ToGeThEr" also me: has all but abandoned doctoral thesis, aliented friends and family, can't run brush through hair, has been wearing pajamas underneath her sweater to work all week, regularly forgets to put underwear on</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 16:27:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>if we can't see it, it can't see us!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 16:30:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so beautiful I want to cryyyy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 16:45:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not a lotion but I bought the shiseido eudermine essence just for the bottle and while I don't think it does much, I REGRET NOTHING https://goo.gl/images/xoT8CC</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 18:58:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>What was your experience with the vitamin F from TO?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 22:32:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>i can only focus on one aspect of my health at a time, sorryyyy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 13:13:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am very very pale but I have a true neutral undertone (probably because I am mediterranean) and I never get red at all</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 13:18:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>the product description says it's a moisturizer, and a look at the ingredients seems to show there are moisturizing elements in the cream. however, I think it depends on your skin! if you use it and note that your skin is not feeling hydrated enough, I don't think adding another moisturizer would hurt :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 13:27:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>are you using any products with actives? while that's healing it might be best to cut them out!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 14:01:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>So for healing purposes you might want to cut out pretty much everything that isn't the buffet or the NMF. pretty any acids (except hyaluronic), vitamin c, niacinamide, etc. and just stick to hydration hydration hydration and anything you find that might be soothing! unfortunately, a week might not be long enough. if you think about your skin, it renews itself pretty much every 4 weeks, so you should allow about that time for healing. i'm currently doing the same haha and am dying to put all the stuff I love on my face but its really much better to be safe, give a good month, and then slowly introduce things back in one by one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 14:08:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>of course! good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 14:09:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love the book "GenderQueer: Voice from Beyond the Sexual Binary" by Riki Wilchins</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Personal] Things I'm not willing to give up for perfect skin</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 15:21:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wanted to share a little revelation I had today and was wondering if other people have had this sort of bargaining conversation with themselves: So....it's been a VERY rough winter on the Cantabrian coast. I'm talking cold, periods of over two weeks of straight rain, horrible winds, snow, despair, etc etc. Thankfully spring is starting to make its way here finally and today is a BEAUTIFUL day. It is warm and it is SO SUNNY. I had almost forgotten what the sun even looked like. I went outside and I sat in the sun, and it felt SO good to feel the sun on my face. And despite my whole skincare journey up until now struggling with breakouts and scarring and pigmentation, I realized I'm not willing to give up the feeling of the warm sun on my face (with sunscreen of course). I hear SO MUCH about the things we have given up to achieve good skin on this sub: direct sunlight, sugar, gluten, dairy, caffeine, alcohol. And I realize this is extremely personal and that what you are willing to do to acheive skin you're proud of or comfortable in varies from person to person, but I would just like to share the things I am not willing to give up to acheive perfect skin. These are the things I am willing to enjoy (in moderation of course) in exchange for "flawed" skin: - the feeling of the sun on my face - a couple glasses of wine on the weekends, especially as sangria season approaches - ice cream (the full fat, sugary, creamy, good stuff from the local ice cream shop that has been there since forever and reminds me of my childhood) - milk chocolate (because I don't care if dark is more "sophisticated") - spontaneous sexy time with my partner post-night routine Has anybody else decided things they are not willing to give up even if it means your skin won't be "perfect"?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 15:29:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>So Dr. Davin Lim (board certified dermatologist in Australia and a favorite on this sub) actually states that with a .5mm needle, the correct technique should cause pinpoint bleeding. I would assume for a 1.0mm it would be the same, but since this is your leg (and thus thicker) skin, you may not? He demonstrates good technique in the video below https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R5o_EWxI23Y</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 15:30:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>AND wine is good for the heart. wine! wine all around!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 15:48:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>*covers ears* la la la la la :P</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 15:58:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>exactly! This is really I think my whole point. I'm not going to guzzle a bottle of wine everyday, or spend 5 hours in the sun, or eat 500g of chocolate, but I find being so strict out just from the fear of breaking out or getting a wrinkle here or these is really not constructive. We can all live a little!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 16:26:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>a person after my own heart</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 16:26:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes, they wear hats and stuff and stay in the shade</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 18:48:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had read a thread some weeks ago about sex after PM routine and how to deal with this, like reserving sex for only morningm or like telling their partners to avoid any contact with their face during. and i was like whaaa</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 18:53:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have some pretty large, noticeable atrophic scars in the middle of my forehead from some really bad skin picking. they're there, i'm not going to pay for lasers or peel or fillers, so with me they'll stay and it's just fine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 21:20:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>ok, thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 12:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>but I dont LIKE dark chocolate. and I want ice cream from THIS place. Giving up those things would be giving up the things I like. I already pretty much live dairy free throughout most of my day, these are just the indulgences I want to keep</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 13:58:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>you seem to be missing the whole point. as I said, what you choose to eliminate from your diet is personal. I will continue to eat what I'm eating because I have decided that I do not care enough to change it. If this is different for you, that's great! But I feel like trying to convince people to change their diets or habits is the antithesis of this post. I am not looking for suggestions, nor are they welcome at this time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 15:46:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's decent I guess. I would like to say it helped with my PIE but I introduced it with other products so I can't really say with certainty. Does help with shine though. I wont repurchase because I use other products with niacinamide high up on the ingredients list and I dont feel as though I need it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 23:21:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>i'm using the holy snails hanbang shark sauce and it's 3rd on that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 01:21:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use the Mebika Moist Lotion which I buy on Amazon JP and it literally has ALL the ceramides and a ton of moisturizers and I love love love it. with shipping it came out to be like 17 euros but it's a 500ml bottle which will last a long time and also shipping pretty quickly considering the distance</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 13:05:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>1) find a new therapist 2) therapists exist to help you process and navigate YOUR journey. they have the degree, sure, but you ultimately know your life the best. so wear that make up!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 16:47:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>second this! there are two LRP cicaplast: baume and gel. The gel one has silicone in it and is much more cosmetically elegant and easier absorbed than the baume</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 17:44:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes, usually on japanese products "lotion" means "toner"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 18:58:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do order online, though I order from Amazon JP (just because I'm in Europe), but I directly followed the links on this review blog entry! https://vanityrex.com/2017/05/15/comparison-review-of-5-japanese-ceramide-toners/ edit: I use the Mebika one :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-19 19:10:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel personally attacked by this post</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 01:40:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>what's your current routine? also LOVE the medusa piercing. I've been thinking of getting one :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 21:35:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Propanediol is added for viscosity to cosmetics so I'm going to assume it's this and that it just has a not so great formulation</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 21:37:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I honestly dont know how things work in the UK but could you see a dermatologist?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 12:46:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>DoubleSpace to create separate lines!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 12:52:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gaaaaa I just drank the BR koolaid! I got my analysis. I can't pay everything at once so I'm starting off with placenta creme and p50W. My order comes on Tuesday! What are your faves??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 13:03:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I LOOOOVE this stuff, I think it doesn't get enough credit. It lasts forever, I pat 3 layers of this stuff every morning. Literally has all the ceramides</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 14:59:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>The masque is my next purchase!! Im actually excited about skincare this is a new feeling</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 16:48:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>ME TOO. the wind blows and I get PIE now. I need answersszz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 17:43:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I should be getting my p50w in the mail this week and I'm soooo excited</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 00:06:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I slather my face in manuka honey and its my HG facemask</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 00:12:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>i've vaped for like 4 years and I haven't had any cysts as a result</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 00:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>the cetearyl alcohol can be comedogenic to people who are sensitive to fatty alcohols</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 11:59:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>on another post she says she spends 6-7k a year on skincare like you know, that isnt a 3rd of my income</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 13:15:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>can both of you teach me your ways? I literally cannot organize to save my life. I literally cannot do it, I have tried all types of tips and tricks but I always devolve into panic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 14:28:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a Eucerin 5% urea cream you cana find online! I think hada labo also has a gel-cream moisturizer which also features urea</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 14:30:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would argue that besides spf you should probably wash your face like once a day (in the evenings), maybe with a gentle non-foaming cleanser</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 15:10:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes, you absolutely can! in fact, over moisturization can lead to increased acne. I know there was a post about this recently but I can't find it in which the OP really nicely details out the reasons for this. However I think this was mostly referring to people who live in humid climates, where moisturizing is extra. but even if you dont live in a humid area, if you notice less moisturizing improves your skin, then there must be a good reason for it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 15:50:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually am a minimalist! I think I might be the only disorganized minimalist haha. I only own 2 suitcases and a backpack full of stuff. That's all my belongings including clothes, shoes, skincare, and general life stuff. AND YET I cannot wrap my mind around organizing this small amount of stuff. It just ends up everywhere. I really have started to believe my mind doesn't work that way. I often got this criticism in school and university....a professor told me that I think like fireworks, bursts of ideas with seemingly random connections that only I understand</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 15:56:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>My grandmother always said a woman can take care of her face and look ten years younger, but her hands will give her away. So yes, I moisturize my hands everyday and put spf on them edit: says* not said. she is still alive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 16:41:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I reapply pretty much when i'm reapplying sunscreen to my face. which is also after I wash my hands, so I guess?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 16:45:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>As far as I understand, skin that needs hydration needs water, and skin that needs moisture needs oil (think of the prefix hydro). however, I think colloquially everyone calls everything moisturizer. grrr I wish I could find this post about the australian study, it would be so relevant here!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 18:16:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>it was that one! and it wasnt truuue?? noooo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 18:17:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>i must keep trying! thank you! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 18:24:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>nope! dry skin needs moisture (oil) and dehydrated skin needs hydration (water). dehydrated skin is a condition while dry skin is not edit: I failed to write correctly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 19:08:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are gorgeous, youve got this, and CONGRATS on graduating!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 21:12:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I swear that from my first time entering the bathroom in the morning to the second time I get like 3 white heads</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 21:14:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lance it and slap a hydrocolliod bandage and leave it alone. Those bandages literally save me from picking</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 12:43:42</DATE>
    <TEXT> lt;3 I have looked the same. I think people dont stress enough the physical pain of picking like this. I remember how much it hurt to put on tighter pants, or long sleeves shirts, or my swollen face. I dont have pictures to remind me of this time but I do have scars. You are very brave and am so happy you're doing much better!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 13:21:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>you've got yourself some dehrydrated, acne-prone skin?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 15:06:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>aaa but I love the serozinc though, I'm on my 4th bottle. I think it calms my inflammation and is mattifying. Goes to show you, how different skins are!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 15:07:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I pat it in!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 15:09:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I highly recommend gauze over cotton, I feel like you lose less product. To start off, you can also dampen the gauze first if you're afraid of your skin not being so tolerant!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 17:54:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just wanted to drop my love for ultrabland!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 18:13:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>gimme the sauuuuce</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 18:38:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have heard that the Tarte knockout makes a decent dupe. Smells similar and the ingredients are actually astonishingly similar as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 11:37:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, usually I love when my spots finally become whiteheads because it means I can lance them and get on with the healing process! as for your moisture barrier, it seems as though you're not using actives which would be the biggest thing to remove from a routine. As for things to add, maybe something with ceramides would be really helpful. A lot of people like Dr. Jart's ceramidin line but I personally think it's over fragranced and you can find products with better ingredients at a better priced. I bought Mebika moisturizing lotion (though its actually a toner) from amazon japan and i'm very happy with it and you get 500ml for like 7 #8364; + shipping. Are you happy with your moisturizer? It's possible it might not be doing enough! And adding an occlusive at night over the moisturizer such as aquafor or vaseline might help with sealing that moisture in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 12:33:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>correct! AHA/BHA, Vitamin C, retinols.... these are all acids and things you dont want to be using if you want to repair your moisture barrier. And by all means if you like the cetaphil moisturizer, go ahead and use it! I don't think using more of it would be effective though. You're much more likely to get effects with layering a toner or hydrating serum and then your moisturizer and an occulisive barrier. I really like the mebika toner I'm using, and ceramides are in a lot of asian beauty products so maybe going to r/asianbeauty you'll get some good recommendations :) ceramides are essentially naturally occuring lipids on your skin that help retain moisture</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 11:44:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can only reply anecdotally. Dermarolling stimulates collagen production and serum absorption (at the .25mm length) and so it might help prevent fine lines and wrinkles but there is not a product in the world that will replace the youthful look fat deposits in your cheeks give you. Its a sad story, I have come to terms with this :'(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 11:47:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Removing foamin cleansers from my routine was LIFE CHANGING. Their pH is generally too high and are stripping. I used to have combination skin until I stopped using a foaming cleanser</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 18:10:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate Glam Glow. I CANNOT take seriously a company that makes a face mask with glitter in it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 00:37:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>so those look like they might be close comedones. BHA (your SCA pads) is good for inflammatory acne, but not so much the non inflammatory. have you tried any AHAs? (glycolic, mandelic, lactic acids)?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 00:48:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>you can for sure! but I would definitely start introducing it slowly, and at different parts in your routine (if you do BHA morning, do AHA night) at least to start until your skin builds up tolerance. I use a toner which is a combo of both,</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 10:58:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>GET YOUSELF SCOUTED. ASAP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 14:00:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>like is it fun? probably, i love gitter. but I would never take them seriously as a skincare company just because it's neither beneficial to the skin, could be bad for the skin, and is not good for the environment (glitter)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 22:04:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>meeeee too. I thought I got off so easy....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 23:28:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>IT ME</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 23:42:41</DATE>
    <TEXT> #947; #949; #953; #945;  #963; #959; #965;!! korres has a rose serum with vitamin c that I really liked  #945; #955; #955; #940;  #949; #943; #957; #945; #953;  #955; #943; #947; #959;  #945; #954; #961; #953; #946; #972;....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 23:59:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had no idea who this person was before I clicked that link and she's SO beautiful like whaaat</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 12:06:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it bad I think it looks beautiful?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 13:45:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>this literally happened to me 20min ago and it truly feels like such a burden</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 13:51:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>you sure as hell can!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 00:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally like two days ago I was thinking "this is it, I have everything I have lusted for and my routine is complete" and today I was looking at new cleansers. Guys I have so many cleansers. I need to finish these cleansers. And they're FINE cleansers, cleansers I like, and are doing their jobs! If it aint broke don't fix it....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 12:20:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I havent patch tested anything in my life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 12:22:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>NO. ALL COUNTRIES BESIDES FRANCE AND KOREA HAVE JUST NEVER ADVANCED IN ANY SORT OF SKINCARE SCIENCEEEE edit: south korea</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 12:31:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love that one of those derms was like "well the rest of the skin on your body regulates moisture just fine without constant moisturizing" and I'm like bitch have you taken a look at the rest of my skin on my body? Its so dryyyyy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 12:35:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>THANK YOU. I literally have had skin infections that needed medical attention and have had to miss days of work because my face is so swollen and sore from dermotillomania. So shut up about your fake "picking problem" Yeah should you pick your skin? No. But if you want a real look at what compulsive skin picking looks like head right over to the r/CompulsiveSkinPicking sub</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 14:02:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Rave* BR P50W (sensitive skin version) Sorry everyone, I drank the koolaid. I have been using this every day for a week and I am obsessed. This is the first product I have ever used where I noticed improvement in my skin within just 2 days. Breakouts? Don't know her. Oily forehead? Never felt that emotion. My PIH is fading, my skin is soft, my skin hasn't felt this balanced in maybe 3 years. I didn't want to like it (I mean, I did considering I spent coins on this) but sorry, this went to HG status really quick *Rave*: Cosrx Snail Mucin 96. I bought this specifically to help heal scabs I get on my face and its really doing a great job in helping my skin scab over faster and fall off in record time. I tried using this alone as an essence without my Mebika toner with ceramides and it definitely doesn't provide enough moisture on its own, but that's also not what I bought it for</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 19:02:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi! ok so I have never been on tretinoin and I've heard it's heavy stuff so take what I say with a grain of salt! Also I have used AHAs for over 2 years at this point so my skin tolerance to actives is pretty high. that being said, I also use vitamin c, azelaic acid, and retinyl palmitate in my routine (probably the weakest retinoid) so far with no problem. I do know people who use P50 only once or twice a week and people who use it successfully with other retinoids, Do you use tretinoin every day? if not, it might be something you can use on your off days! and as with everything, a slow introduction into your routine :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 20:25:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>as far as LRP sunscreens I use the ultra-light anthelios XL SPF50. It doesnt leave a white cast, absorbs really nicely for me, and doesnt break me (no cystic acnes) or my friend (severe cystic acne) break out. It doesnt leave you looking like an oil slick but might have a bit of shine to it, but I wear powder mineral make up so for me this isnt a huge concern</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 20:31:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have the placenta cream and I really like it, even though it smells like yeast (took me a while to figure out what the smell was). I've been meaning to eventually try a serum but they are SO pricey. Like I can dish out 40 #8364; for the cream and 60 #8364; for the toner because they are both effective products, they last a good while, and the rest of my routine is pretty low budget. but the serums??? like 40 #8364; for 8ml??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 21:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use products with fragrances and some essential oils. I really like my skincare to smell good; it really is an important part of the soothing process for me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 10:59:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol it's a spa brand so you have to buy it through one of those. they have a website which lists the spas that have it. I'm in Spain so maybe because of proximity to France we have at least two of those spas in every major city. I don't know if it is so accesible where you are</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 11:01:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>and actually the price is not so crazy in comparison to other high end brands like DE. DE I believe in some products is more expensive per ml. The P50 is just under 60 #8364; for 150ml, and my moisturizer from them is 39 #8364; for 50ml</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 17:22:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't have very reactive skin, but all the garnier sheetmasks made my skin itchy with some small pimples</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Routine Help] My eyes decided to return to heroin chic without telling me</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 17:34:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 17:40:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello everyone! So I looked in the mirror and suddenly realized the skin around my eyes is much darker than the rest of my face and I look like Jamie King in the 90s. This is totally new to me, I drink plenty of water, and sleep a good amount on the regular. Now, I have never used an eye product because I low key believe they are a lie. I am willing to reconsider this. Any suggestions? Thank you!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 18:25:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait can I get a bundle of each of the minis except for the eye treatments? What would that go for. Also shipping would be to Spain</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 18:49:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Done! With international standard please! pm me your paypal :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 22:06:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>* shakes fist at sky * AGIIIING oh well, I guess it makes sense since my face has generally thinned out a lot over the past two years as well. what can you do. with regards to health it's really ironic I was so bouncy and beautiful faced and clear and even when I was at my most, pretty tragically unhealthy in my early twenties with my bad drug habit and long-term eating disorder haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 22:11:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>don't buy it from BanishAcneScars, it's incredibly overpriced. You'll see some places where it costs like 70$??? you WILL have to throw this away after 3-4 uses at the very most. buy a cheap one, you'll have to replace it soon enough. I got mine on amazon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 22:54:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>oooo boy. well I don't worry about them enough to have fillers at this point!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 22:55:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>why ARE eye creams so disproportionately expensive? I've heard a few derms that its essentially diluted face cream?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 22:57:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>hmm actually this is the first spring i've had in this city so it could be!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 23:18:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get mine from Koi Beauty on Amazon and the're really nice and stable, and actual needles. The problem becomes when you buy them and they are not individual needles but serrated disks. I will show an example in the link below. The left one is the one to avoid, the right one is a good one: https://is.alicdn.com/img/pb/891/335/457/457335891_857.jpg the one I buy: https://www.amazon.es/Koi-Beauty-Microagujas-Microneedle-Cellulite/dp/B0183MXZIA/ref=sr_1_12?s=beauty amp;ie=UTF8 amp;qid=1525122750 amp;sr=1-12 amp;keywords=dermaroller</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 01:34:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>because the needles become dull and you run the risk of causing tears to the skin. also, despite soaking in alcohol, there is really no way to effectively sterilize them over a long period of time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 11:05:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>it depends on the length of the needle. At .25mm, you'll improve serum absorption, .5mm works best for fine lines, texture, and light acne scares, and at 1mm and above you'll start to work on deeper wrinkles and more severe acne scarring. Its important to note that .5mm is the longest length that any professional will ever recommend that you do at home by yourself. have people done more than .5mm at home? sure. Are you running a much greater risk of infection if you do? also yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 11:11:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>ALWAYS READ THE INGREDIENTS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 15:18:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes, doing things slowly, I like to put on a really thick nourishing mask and leave it on for a while AND deep condition my hair while I'm at it. I also have like a couple unduly expensive balms that I use just a tiny bit on these occasions to top off my skincare at the end just because they feel so nice and are just very aromatherapeutic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 15:32:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>this video I found super informative on dermarolling, proper technique et al. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R5o_EWxI23Y amp;t=3s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 20:59:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>If the price is what's deterring you, I would not go for DE. Theyre both in the same price range</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 23:39:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>what do you think of the moogoo serum?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 12:14:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>there's some CBD skincare out there toooo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 12:49:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's important to contextualize the creation of these thermal waters (avene, LRP). Paris has extremely hard water, whose alkaline ph can be extremely disruptive to the skin's acid mantle. Often these are sprayed after rinsing the face so as to balance the ph. So, I think that if you live in a city with hard water, this can be a very nice addition to your routine! I was just in a city for a conference with very hard water and my skin freaaaaked out. It was as though I has washed my face and body with swimming pool water!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 13:38:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh yessss I have perfect, and I mean perfect skin until I was about 25 and then I started getting slight acne, started picking at my skin, and got oily on my forehead. I am turning 29 this year</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 15:33:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>me toooo. it heals just much quicker</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 23:25:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use the caudalie gentle cleansing milk daily!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 23:37:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>also, for moisturization you could use something like the 7 skin method where you pat 3-7 layers of a hydrating toner into your skin!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 23:39:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol are you me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 23:41:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>not going to another dermatologist for a second opinion... went to a dermatologist who told me I had acne and entirely ignored that my pimples were due to a skin picking problem</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 23:46:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh lol that makes sense</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 00:27:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>well a hydrating toner is just a toner that has hydrating elements vs others which might have "purifying" or exfoliating elements. elements that are good would be hyaluronic acid, panthenol, glycerin, ceramides. they're very common in asian beauty! I use the Mebika Toner from Japan. Hada Labo is a common one people love as well. you might want to head over to the r/asianbeauty sub for some suggestions!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 13:09:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh god the bottle. i need it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 15:15:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>only as an answer to #2 yessss that is definitely overkill. you should introduce retinoids slowly, only once or twice a week for the first week and then build up from there. also do not use any other exfoliants in the same routine the days you're planning on using the retinol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 16:41:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>which vitamin C serum do you use?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 00:39:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>really? I feel like I haven't heard it talked about too much on this sub? I've been looking for a new serum</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 00:46:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>all facts. team P50 for life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 00:48:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's a spa brand so you have to find a spa that offers it as a treatment. I'm in Europe so I'm not sure if there is a location finder on the US site to find a spa that carries it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 00:49:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use finacea but yes, azelaic acid was life changing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 00:58:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I take off my makeup right when I get home from the office aroundn 16.30 and I take off my make up with Lush's ultrabland and then pat in a hyaluronic acid serum \(some 10 #8364; one from my farmacy\) and then go about my house things before I go to the gym. When I return from the gym I then do my full routine</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 01:02:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>remove your face. just throw the whole thing away. all is lost.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 01:07:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>the Mebika moisture lotion is my favorite!! light, easy to pat in multiple layers, and has all the ceramides in the world I think</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 01:53:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude what's your routine tho</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 01:55:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is literally the saddest thing I've heard all day</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 11:26:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>your skin looks really good!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 14:07:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>is this the definition of freedom?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 21:08:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>literally did this today</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Misc] Help, I finished my night routine and still went out afterward??</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 02:21:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just kidding. I'm not redoing it, but just hoping everyone has a safe and fun weekend!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 15:14:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>cerave PM is also not FA safe, and some people react negatively to it because of the esters it has. so patch test patch test patch test! i've known a few people to get cysts from it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 17:50:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm so glad my partner's roommate is a woman and one that's willing to share in a pinch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 18:29:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yessss neem oil, I rarely see it around here but I love it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 22:11:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>How long have you had this routine? And problems just recently occurred?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 23:01:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>have there been any other changes? stress, diet, environment, even something like laundry detergent?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 00:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to point out that it's not entirely true that she did "nothing". Factors that changed include: \- amount of exercise \- air quality \- food quality \- water quality \- sleep quality not to mention she was probably having a GREAT TIME and trust me there are few things that do wonders to skin like being on vacation and having a great time consistently for a long while. you cannot compare your skin journey to hers are there's no way of telling how your skin might've reacted under similar circumstances, and your friend's circumstances are certainly extraordinary. I know it's tough, and it's an uphill battle but do your best not to compare yourself to others and do your best to deflect unhelpful, unsupportive commentary</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 00:24:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had been thinking of trying the instanaturals serum! what are your thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 00:29:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>rose hip oil is quite a dry oil and is not very good for moisturizing. you might do well with adding more hydration? I found that to be very helpful when I got frustrated with my plateaued routine. I know you said to minimze not increase buuuuut</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 00:30:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>i saw the similar set on iherb and have kind of just had it lingering in my cart! maybe I will take the plunge once my current one runs out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 16:11:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>bienvenidx a espa #241;a!! your skin looks great. I have used azelaic acid to help much with remaining spots and redness. In spain you can buy it at any farmacy under the name Finacea for about 21 #8364;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 17:52:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>have you tried any green concealer? those are good for neutralizing redness. I use it, then use flesh colored concealer over it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 22:49:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>i've tried that essence lotion and it was actually the first essence I ever tried! it's nice, I liked it, it has salicylic acid in it which I dont really feel like I need right now. it has a fragrance i really like, but it's still a fragrance so there's that. I still have some left to use, but I felt like I could get the same results with a cheaper AB product with ingredients that I liked more. but it's nice and I think it has Magnesium Ascorbyl Phosphate \(vit C\) in it too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 00:00:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>an interesting note on teenagers, adolescence is a very recent development in human history, and one that was created after the turn of the 20th century as 1\) life spans increased 2\) child labour laws encouraged continued schooling. Typically the progress was from child directly to adult. Even today adolescence is really only something that occurs in countries and communities beyond a certain level of economic development.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 11:33:41</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Heimish All Clean Balm if you didn't respond well to oil cleansing, I might be hesitant to try this. it's full of esters, coconut extract, shea butter, and other oils. it's definitely a balm\-to\-oil cleanser and a first step cleanser</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 13:28:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>following! I just ran across it too and would also like to hear feedback</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 10:56:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>bummer!! but thank you so much for reporting back. much appreciated!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 12:45:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have tried a few lush products on and off, but I love love love their ultrabland cleaser</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 17:24:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>sadly I have very curly bangs and rollers are just begging to cause chaos in my hair :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 17:48:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>i adore this stuffff</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 17:59:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>they are! I've had them since 8th grade when I became extraordinary self conscious of my enormous forehead haha. they're kind of a thing now! for many years style rules said this was a no-no</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 18:01:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>this is so real. I used to have cheeks until like at some point in the last 2 years they've disappeared and I got dark circles in exchange....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 18:07:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>me too! I dont do wispy bangs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 22:39:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>where do you live?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 00:38:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I put vitamin C serum on before my toners and essences in the morning</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 00:40:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have generally been told that you shouldn't apply any actives to microneedled skin until a week after the treatment, but tret seems much more hardcore, and I would truly ask your specialist</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 00:44:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>these look like CCs to me, and there is a recent HG threads on how to deal with them and perhaps a stronger AHA is your best bet. Have you tried glycolic? also what about your pillow? any new detergents? my experience with CCs is that they are caused by something that has touched my face like a product rather than say, and internal issue as my inflammatory acne is caused by</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 01:25:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi! Ok I have a few comments on your routine: First it seems pretty harsh on your skin, which is why you might feel dry, unbalanced with oil production, and causing acne. You use a foaming cleanser \(irritating\), a scrub \(irritating\), and a clarisonic \(irritating\). I would: \- use a physical exfoliant \(clarisonic or the positively radiant scrub\) only once or twice a week, but definitely not both, and definitely not twice a day \- switch to a non\-foaming cleanser \(I use a cleansing milk, and I think cerave has a non foaming one, but you should check the HG thread for cleansers in the side bar\) I would try this for a while and see how your skin reacts! I looked up your serum and it seems like a nice hydrating serum so that I think can stay. If the pimples persist, I would then recommend getting the Stridex pads in the red box as a chemical exfoliating step. This would be used 2x a week to test it and see how it does, and then use them more often as you see fit. If you chose to chemically exfoliate, don't do it in the same day as your physical exfoliation Overall, remember that acne is a wound, and that we shouldnt treat it aggresively!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 01:49:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>a cream cleanser BR P50 Mebika ceramide toner BR placenta cream LRP anthelios ultra light fluid 50</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 01:53:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>AA is really great for pigmentation issues. It also doesn't make your skin photosensitive and fights acne and doesn't really cause any irritation as long as you dont have very sensittive skin. It's truly my HG ingredient \(I use finacea gel which is Rx only in the US, but OTC in my country\)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 11:15:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It depends on the needle length. .25mm is fine 1x week. If you use .5mm you should really wait 2-3 weeks. Any thing larger always give a month</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 11:21:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes! good quality water is so important. you look much brighter and even toned! well done</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 12:44:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>there is definitely a difference! Most notably there are much fewer blackheads and that your hyper #236;gmentation is reduced</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:36:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>this was a truly perplexing question to me before I saw the gauges</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:41:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>where did you get this picture of me i can't believe you posted it without my consent i'm calling the police</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 22:49:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>A\+\+</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 00:58:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>um their packing though I am OBSESSED</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 01:09:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Weleda is a really nice German brand! Their most famous item is their Skin Food lotion which is a nice thick moisturizing cream. Also Dr. Hauschka! Edit: both are bio as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 09:56:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>best of luck!! i'm hoping to hear some signs of progress :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 10:52:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi from Spain!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 12:46:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>"what heartache they bring! For lines soon mummify your skin, blighting its youthful freshness." I truly wish advertisers still wrote like this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 01:18:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheering you on!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 16:59:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Two questions: Over what period of time are the photos? I just got retain-a (.025) and I'm scared also because of my dry sensitive skin. Any tips?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 19:02:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Drinking water is the least effective way to hydrate the skin. It is the last organ to receive water. If you're super dehydrated you might notice a difference after starting to drink water, but beyond a certain threshold it doesn't really matter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 12:05:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>this brought me such peace</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 13:16:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Srs why are we jerking the post if she actually has a serious allergy to plant derived things?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 15:26:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>agreed, came to comment how jealous I am of your beautiful full brows!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 15:34:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>why is he sticking the lancet so deep though??? doesn't that fucking hurt??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 17:02:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Srs Since when is 35 old??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 17:12:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seconding everyone, and I think it's most likely fine, but I really think men are at a disadvantage when it comes to these sort of health concerns. At least we folk with vaginas get gynecologists and we visit them fairly regularly. I don't think men get this sort of regular sexual health care, correct? If it's within your means, always ask a doctor when you have doubts!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 22:25:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>if I don't get at least 6,5 hours of sleep a night my skin takes it very, very hard. I get red, wake up with several spots. Also my anxiety gets incredibly triggered by lack of sleep and I am more likely to pick my face. btw: I know 6,5 seems like not really worth claiming "sleep deprivation" to a lot of people, but I work full time, am a student, and work out pretty intensely 5\-6 days a week so I really need a lot of rest</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 23:11:08</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;The sparseness around the temples is still problematic here meeeeh this is my problem too and I have so much hair elsewhere!! bangs forever!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 23:23:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>i'm gonna shove this in my partner's face now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 23:32:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>can you please link teh etsy store for the reusable rounds?? I have been looking for good ones :\)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 23:40:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>you can also use it as a spot treatment!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 23:51:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Strange as it may seem, this thought literally had never crossed my mind with regards to skin picking! I have a tendency toward a couple compulsive behaviors and one of my most costly \(in every regard\) had been bulimia, binge\-purge type. Even after having worked on the psychological aspects behind it, purging had become so much of a habit, I was doing it mindlessly. Until I was too broke to buy binge\-food anymore. This kind of extended 7 month period of no income and barely any savings, while really rough \(like I don't wish being food and shelter insecure to anyone\) it really snapped me out of the habit, and I have pretty much entirely stopped! \(not perfect, but what recovery is?\) so yeah, don't end up broke because of your compulsion, but consider the financial incentive!! edit: some typos</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 00:20:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 11:18:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>but how often to men see urologists? I had the impression it was only certain age to test for prostate cancer. I guess it's different here. In Spain you have to see a gynecologist for things like smears, getting birth control prescriptions, family planning, etc. your primary doctor doesn't really do anything specialised</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 11:23:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>aaa got it. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 12:26:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>you can look your age and still look good and healthy....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 13:38:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>have you tried any exfoliating acids? I made the decision to start dermarolling a few months ago following two years using glycolic acids. You could try some peels, though the most I have done are just the pixi glow pads 20% I definitely did a ton of research on dermarolling and while I don't feel comfortable recommending it for the risk associated with it, I think if you decide to do it, get very informed!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 16:48:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>hmm peels then might also be pretty rough to start off with. I would look into starting with a chemical exfoliator a few times a week first. I think you can find good ones in the HG side bar! I would go for something simple like a good glycolic acid toner which is easy to incorporate (right after cleansing). You'd do this twice a week, then three times, then eventually just build up to every day. A few that people like are the P #238;xi Glow Tonic (they also make the glycolic acid pads I mentioned, but those are a high concentration), The Ordinary Glycolic Toner, Paula's choice has one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 17:37:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just because you can't drink the water doesn't mean you can't bathe in it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 17:38:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>not to mention just because you can't drink the water doesn't mean its battery acid for the skin...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 17:43:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>srs who even uses the term "3rd world" anymore, especially what you're trying to avoid saying is "poor". read a bookkkkk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 17:48:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>do you mean the OP? because I mean, they probably can handle sex. It'll hinder how much they enjoy it, and that is what makes me sad, but I don't think it makes them immature. Its a little insulting to say someone is immature just because they might have a real body insecurity. If the person wont have sex with them because of their imperfections, THAT person is immature.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 17:50:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>how do you combine retin\-a and p50 in your skincare routine together?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 21:12:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>looking back at the original comment and clicking on the user, I do see now that we're actually talking about a child hahaha. your comment makes sense, I missed that. I was just kind of worried about your comment because considering I have friends who have had cancer or other major surgeries, have not bounced back from their second child, etc. and have had issues with intimacy because of new insecurities with their bodies I thought it seemed way harsh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 22:30:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>hahaha yeah sorry!! once I realized it was a kid I felt pretty silly. You're entirely right</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 00:40:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>what is this? any comments on why you finished it so thoroughly?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 07:52:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just as a warning, sunscreen should always be your last step! Adding moisturizer on top interferes with the effectiveness of the sunscreen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 07:55:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are your skin goals for dermarolling? I've been doing it for a few months!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 13:30:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I started using my .5mm dermaroller about two months ago and so I've used it about 4 times. A general guide is: .25mm is good for serum absorption, .5mm for fine lines, very light acne scarring, and collagen inducing, and longer than that is really not recommended for home use. Needles at this shorter length really need long term consistent use to see results. For me, so far so good! I think some of the scarring on my cheeks is less evident, but it's atrophic scarring rather than hyperpigmentation. I might move up to .75mm (again am NOT recommending this for safety reasons). If you choose to dermaroll, do your research!! I liked this video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R5o_EWxI23Y amp;t=7s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 18:16:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>SPF in moisturizer is like meh, and is inconsistently effective. I actually read recently that if you're in a humid climate, you can just skip the moisturuzer all together since the sunscreen also has moisturizing properties!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 18:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>make up should be a ok!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 14:16:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>General Practitioner. It's like your primary physician</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 14:50:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me, looking at spots that I have picked at every day and have not healed for a month</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 15:30:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm considering getting the placenta serum. I already use the cream. Do you recommend?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 16:35:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love their ultrabland cleanser</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 00:28:06</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; close your eyes and try to figure if you have enough time for a sleeping pill to wear off by morning. lololol this is me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 13:15:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>the ice thing is great! I used to put ice packs on my face immediately after a long picking episode and it helps tons with the swelling</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 13:45:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll buy it off you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 22:47:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>New Purchases: tonight is my first night of tret .025! wish me luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 01:34:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>good call! will do :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 21:27:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>i may be biased but we have a very similar curl pattern and i cut my own bangs and look like yours and i thinks it's the best</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 23:09:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>For me, besides azelaic acid, the thing that helped most was hydration, hydration, hydration and avoiding products that were in any way irritating</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 23:35:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was more effective in preventing PIE and preventing breakouts and some redness</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 00:12:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I also use the snail mucin \+ hanbang shark sauce in combination! love it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 11:35:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 11:47:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I legitimately thought this was an image of a child when I saw the thumbnail</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Product Question] Tretinoin with a Different Carrier effects? (Spain)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 22:21:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone! It just came to my attention that the Spanish tret Retirides, has an entirely different carrier composition than Retin\-A in the states. Namely, it has a LOT more stuff. Besides seemingly having more comedogenic ingredients, it also contains things like urea and lactic acid. CosDna list below: [http://cosdna.com/eng/cosmetic\_3ff6101297.html](http://cosdna.com/eng/cosmetic_3ff6101297.html) With that in mind, I am assuming my experience with tret here will be very different than others who use the USA version. I was wondering first if anyone has used Retirides specifically and second if anyone could possibly hypothesize what effect the different ingredient list might have on things like effectiveness, tolerability, etc. I am 29, have mostly issues with scarring and pigmentation from compulsive skin picking disorder, and like occasional acne \(one spot a week, usually a papule\) thank you for your insight!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 01:22:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you so much from Spain!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Tretinoin with a Different Carrier effects? (Spain/Retirides)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 11:05:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I posted the following on r/SkincareAddiction but with no responses, so I was hoping maybe someone here would have some insight! \-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\-\- Hi everyone! It just came to my attention that the Spanish tret Retirides, has an entirely different carrier composition than Retin\-A in the states. Namely, it has a LOT more stuff. Besides seemingly having more comedogenic ingredients, it also contains things like urea and lactic acid. CosDna list below: [http://cosdna.com/eng/cosmetic\_3ff6101297.html](http://cosdna.com/eng/cosmetic_3ff6101297.html) With that in mind, I am assuming my experience with tret here will be very different than others who use the USA version. I was wondering first if anyone has used Retirides specifically and second if anyone could possibly hypothesize what effect the different ingredient list might have on things like effectiveness, tolerability, etc. I am 29, have mostly issues with scarring and pigmentation from compulsive skin picking disorder, and like occasional acne \(one spot a week, usually a papule\) thank you for your insight!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 11:11:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use the Lipikar Baume as a moisturizer! I also have the cicaplast baume b5 and alternate between the two</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 12:24:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi! If I may ask, how did you get the custom made formulation? I didn't even know this was an option!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 12:27:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi! Thank you for your response. I am also using the .025 cream formula. I have been using the LRP redermic R retinol cream for a few months up until starting now. It seems like we have the same idea with application, I buffer first with some layers of hydrating toner (Mebika moist lotion) and then wait 30m, apply, then moisturizer after another 30min. Well, let's see how it goes! good luck on your tret journey!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 15:03:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>unfortunately the one in Spain also has isopropyl myristate, it doesn't have stearic acid. It has other comedogenic esters as well. My skin is not acne prone and I am using retin\-a for anti aging so I hope this will not be too much of an issue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 15:04:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have heard that using azelaic acid with retinoids can ease purging, however in these cases it's only been when people have already been using azelaic acid. I would not recommend starting both at once</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 16:51:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>the glow up!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 00:17:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally every person I've ever spoken to at a beauty counter has told me I have combination skin, despite me insisting my skin never gets oily, I'm truly just wearing sunscreen and a dewy finish foundation. It's really aggravating, like dude, I live with my skin every day, I know what my skin is like</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 00:55:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Srs though i did use to do this when I was seven. I have since evolved</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 01:12:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually love this stuff. I use a cleansing oil first and this is my second clease. You need to wipe it off though, I use a clean wash cloth. My skin feels really happy though. Great if your moisture barrier is sad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 01:15:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it's of any consolation, your skin looks really bright and healthy! Hope you find something that works for your cysts soon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 17:32:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>of courseeee</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 02:06:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>this actually sounds like a psychotic break</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 02:16:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>it depends where you are in Europe, and depends on the brand. I use a lot of LaRoche Posay because it's easy to find in Europe, and each of my items from there \(cleanser, a couple of spot treatments, moisturizer, other stuff\) are between 12\-20 #8364; each for example</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 12:27:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh wow! I had no idea this was an option. I will see how the retirides goes and from there I may bring this up if I need a change. much #237;simas gracias!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 12:39:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>My partner is concerned about some first wrinkles and expression lines he is noticing in his forehead and some crows feet as well. He is 29, was on accutane as a teen and doesn't struggle much with breakouts, though gets the occasional pimple. his skin is very dry and he puts absolutely nothing on his face. just water to wash it. I know he wants to target the wrinkles now, but would it be better to maybe work on the hydration aspect first before even considering an exfoliant or retinol?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 13:56:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use a warm wash cloth to remove, but you can use cotton rounds. I would definitely follow up with an additional cleanser to remove any traces of the oil</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 14:18:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks! my inkling was correct :\)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 14:49:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>seconded!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 19:31:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>your haircut is the fringed lob of my dreams</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 01:30:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm fairly sure Brandon has said he wrote all the descriptions for NIOD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 01:38:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>How long have you had this routine though? i think you should stick out a routine for 6 months to see just how effective it is for you, but you can have some flexibility to try new stuff out! I was reading something recently, I think Caroline Hirons \(whatever your opinion of her may be\) and she was saying you have room to play with the ends a bit, like you can usually switch up cleaner, toner, and moisturizer to an extent, but you should be persistent with serums and targeted treatments.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 00:07:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have both and just use them as a final moisutrizing layer. I use the cicaplast if I've been picking at my skin, and the lipikar if if've been overzealous with the exfoliation</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 00:09:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>wait, what is the benefit of getting botox at 21yrs old?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 00:13:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>the thing is, it could be purging or it could be irritation from the increased frequency. I would go back to your old frequency and see if these stop appearing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 00:30:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>fat fills your wrinkles though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 01:33:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the only picture of older redditors whose ages surprised me. Damn!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 03:00:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn't you know looking at screens ruins your skin too?? I wouldn't risk it. Bathe in SPF 100 and then sit in black out darkness until the day you die</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 03:06:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am obsessed with your hair color</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 03:15:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw you only ship to the US which is sad, but since I had been thinking about buying it, what do you think about the kypris antioxidant dew?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 03:23:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in Spain, and I don't want to be much trouble, but I would take it off your hands if no one else wants it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 12:16:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>hmm not sure, I have never shipped a cosmetic thing to the US (to the EU it is different). but I did find this http://www.dhl.es/en/country_profile/import_guidelines_express.html</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 14:18:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have been using LaRoche Posay for my whole life. My uncle a dermatologist recommended it to my mom after I developed photosensitivity as a little kid. I personally use the ultra light one for under makeup but all come pretty well recommended</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 14:34:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>wait, as a fellow skinwitch, I'm interested in your tinctures....I have my own propolis one, echinacea, and am thinking of getting a cbd tincture</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 21:54:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw your previos response to this. point taken</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 22:46:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>srs is breaking LG bottles the official SCA sport now?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 23:21:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Y'all, you wont get Sun spots and wrinkles if you're dead and embalmed so why don't we just to that this summer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 18:21:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>this can also be done in Spain!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 01:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am just starting with tretinoin and I love buffering my face beforehand with Mebika moist lotion! I pat a few layers on then wait about 30 min for it to dry completely, then use tret. It's really helped keeping any irritation at bay!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 01:39:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>there is new evidence suggesting increased heat exposure \(not just sun\) can cause hyperpigmentation. there was a recent post about it yesterday. That being said, you can always check with your derm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 11:47:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>so we're all just going to sit here and not mention THOSE EYELASHES?? I would kill for those</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 12:29:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>\- Cosrx Snail 96 Essence \- Shark Sauce \- Finacea azelaic acid \- Retirides \(tretinoin\) \- This one is really a super combo influence between SCA and ITG but all my Biologique Recherche stuff \(p50V, placenta cream, and placenta s #233;rum\) \- The concept of using an occlusive. I now use one from Spanish farmacies which is called Halibut and uses lanolin, petrolatum, and fish oil</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 16:19:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I truly had not thought about all your base in YEARS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 23:14:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>you look great!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 11:17:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh shoot! thanks for letting me know!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 11:52:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>how do you use your vitamin c powder?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 11:54:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>what does the rest of your routine look like?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 17:27:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>omgomgomgomgomg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 17:29:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol wait, was this miss cracker</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 17:38:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>her face is made of pure steel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What ethnicity do you think I am</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 21:47:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>sorry for the blurry photo but my camera is not very good. I was wondering what ethnicity or race you think I am? Where do you think I am from? [https://imgur.com/a/77az1UG](https://imgur.com/a/77az1UG)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 00:31:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are very welcome!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 02:08:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like martian</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 02:09:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>black and white (spanish)!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 02:32:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>not all oils are occlusives! check to see if the ones you're using are</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 13:50:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh this is amazing!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 16:36:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am a replicant</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 00:49:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>complicated</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 01:20:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes it can, but it takes patience and gentle treatment. the gentler you are with your skin, the better. lots of hydration and no actives and time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 01:21:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>get you some nuxe r #234;ve de miel lip balm. It's super rich and applies matte!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 10:58:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>what would shipping to Spain look like? I'm interested in the CEO serum</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 17:45:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Im seconding the hydrating toner! I pat on a few layers of Mebika Moist Lotion, which is milky but very thin so it absorbs well and is full of ceramides. Then I wait 30min and then tret</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 20:45:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>YOUR EYES OMG</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 11:28:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>it's literally the first thing I look at</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 14:05:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>it looks great! the way it frames your face is lovely</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 23:31:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>srs wasn't this an actual svu episode?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 00:22:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>they absolutely would and do</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 02:55:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>don't be silly! it's a noticeable improvement! your skin is clearer, less red, brighter, and more even toned!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 22:34:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>when she was perfect?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 00:51:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>have you tried anything so far to get rid of them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 00:53:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think thos drinks typically have a lot of sugar, which is really not the best for your skin or anything else</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 00:55:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really don't see any reason why not, BUT extractions don't treat the causes of acne, and as "gentle" as they may be, it's still causing trauma to the skin. I would try to avoid them</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 00:58:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>as a general rule, you don't want to combine too many actives in both your AM and PM routines to reduce the risk of irritation, you could put them in your morning routine. I don't know about alpha arbutin, but azelaic acid doesn't photosensitize your skin, so I use it in the morning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 01:00:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm usually good to go after 3 days after a microneedling session. I use a .75mm needle. As long as you're diligent about not using anything irritating and moisturizing a lot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 01:50:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>they would, that's correct, so whatever you decide to try, I would start only a few days a week first just to try out how your skin tolerates it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 17:39:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>graphic eyeliner is life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 23:50:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>that's such a cute cut</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 23:52:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>pretty much never unless I know that they've been having skin troubles and we've discussed it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 01:20:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>this is so creative, jesus christ. I wish my brain worked this way</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 11:37:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have been eyeing that LXMI Creme du Nil! How do you like it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 14:24:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>for some products it extends the shelf life, like some L\-AA serums. I personally just like to keep any of my "soothing" products in there, gel creams, face masks, etc. just because I feel it adds to the nice sensation if your skin is irritated or angry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 15:21:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol this is me. I never use the dishwasher and do it by hand, and my partner thinks it's so absurd</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 15:22:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>that's kind of funny though. I hope you didn't hurt him too bad!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 15:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 15:39:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>true, especially with your pregnancy so advanced!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Happy Pride Haircut!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 18:48:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gave up with my long hair so I queered it :D [androgynized](https://imgur.com/a/4Lh38v2)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 18:54:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I truly enjoy Mebika Moisturizung Lotion (toner). very light, tons of ceramides. Iuse it to buffer my tret!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-07 19:14:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>my partner likes to blame everything on "The West" and "The Americans". I mean, he's right a solid like 70% of the time but sometimes it truly is irrelevant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 00:09:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>yessss! welcome to the curly fringe club!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 11:13:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 11:51:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>did someone really just go and ruin some perfectly good breadsticks with their face??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 14:35:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am HERE for this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Big Chop success!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 15:26:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi Guys! So I went for it, the big chop (it's not my first time cutting my hair this short) after trying to grow out my hair over the past two years to get rid of the bleached and dyed mess it had become. It's not a deva cut because I'm not sure I can even find a devacurl stylist in my country... so I was unsure of how a hairstylist would handle my hair here. I am biracial, so my hair texture is quite different from other curly hair here and so you can imagine how hard I was crossing my fingers! I am very happy with the result I'm a solid 3b and I co\-wash my hair everyday with the Garnier Original Remedies Tesoros de Miel (Honey treasures I guess?)\- I really like the whole line, but mostly use the intense conditioning mask and the oil. My hair really takes well to oils as final styling products. https://i.redd.it/88ys95kz3s211.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 15:40:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>is it possible what washing with a mandelic fash wash twice a day is just too harsh on the skin? A foaming cleanser in the morning AND night seems like it could be really irritating your skin. I also did a quick look at your skin script moisturizer and it's full of essential oils which can sensitize your skin and make it angry. What is your curology prescription? Depending on what it contains you could really just be overloading your skin. Perhaps look into switching to gentler products!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 17:53:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 17:53:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 17:53:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 19:03:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>its normal to get moles throughout your lifetime. just make sure to monitor them, that they dont change in size, color, or shape!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 03:29:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>FUCK YEAH, if you're ever feeling down in the future, remember you did THIS. and you can do it again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 17:28:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have bangs because I have an enormous forehead but they work well for me! I think the trick is for them to be full. a couple of wispy curls doesn't look great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 17:31:41</DATE>
    <TEXT> #204; think people are capable of change, but only if they want to. My SO and I also started off with a lot of problems, a lot of fights, and inability to communicate. It's gotten better, it's definitely a work in progress. But they'll never change for you. It has to be self motivated</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 19:35:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used it and didn't repurchase. It's more that I don't feel it did anything special, it really felt like any other clay mask</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 19:51:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>manuka honey as a mask. healing. moisturizing. the bomb dot com</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 19:53:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I personally love the konjac sponge. I use it a few times a week with my cream cleanser and it's a really pleasant experience; it doesn't even feel exfoliating at all it's so gentle!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 23:30:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>animal friends are the best</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 19:09:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is the vitamin c serum opened?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 20:40:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh totally, the big forehead was just my excuse!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 22:57:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>when was it opened? do you know?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 00:22:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>As far as I understand it's not!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 00:29:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>OK! I have a few suggestions! I don't think you have to wash your face in the morning, especially with a foam and clay cleanser. Also, your last cleansing step shouldn't be micellar water. It contains surfactants that should be washed off. My suggestion then is that you should rinse your face with water in the morning and instead cleanse with the micellar water, then the l'oreal cleanser, then the rest of your routine. Hope that helps!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 02:02:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh I see how my response would be unclear! It would be: AM: a) rinse with water OR b) if you're feeling oily in the morning do micellar water and then a water rinse PM: micellar water, l #243;real cleanser, then everything else! And of course! Of course, stick with the new routine for a few weeks with the products you have, then you can reevaluate if you need to switch out anything. But if what you've got works, why not try it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 02:12:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>adorable!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 15:23:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>moisturize, moisturize, and sunscreen! these are the most important things. The red marks are essentially inflamed blood vessels from where your skin was attempting to feed and heal your wound. These marks take time, and patients. but if you look at them as inflammation, then you can see how treating them kindly and gently will help them fade faster. They can take up to a could weeks to a year</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 15:27:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>S E A M L E S S N E S S</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I really don't know what to do, I'm anxious all the time</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 18:23:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I decided to stop listening to Crosby, Stills, Nash, and Young to write this out after lurking here for a bit. This is the first time I've talked about this, and I almost feel bad seeing as it's not as severe as other people's problems, but I really need to get it out. So my SO and I have been together for a bit over a year and it's been... a challenge. For a number of reasons. The main one right now is that I'm doing my PhD and we are long distance. Our countries are 4 hours by plane apart from each other, and we have gotten to see each other every 2\-3 months and when we are together things are great. But the long distance is taking a toll, especially on him. We have had many conversations about it, and while we make time to speak to each other regularly, help each other and support each other via skype (studying for tests, reviewing work for each other, etc) and generally trying to be good partners, he is often distraught on this dependency on technology and screens to connect with each other. Now this wouldn't be so bad I think if he had been at all stable in any point in our relationship. When we met he was on active duty in the military, which was an enormous stress on him and he really suffered it a lot. Then when he came back he was unemployed, intermittently getting temporary contracts which paid little money. He's been applying for scholarships with no success (he fucked up pretty bad in high school and university and it's making things difficult now). He fears having to move back in with his parents, as he has a pretty tense relationship with his father. Getting a job in his country is really difficult right now, with no signs of improvement, His anxiety is constantly through the roof, and he feels like a failure most of the time, And this manifests in anger, mostly at me. He can be so hurtful sometimes with the things he says, and I'm not proud of it, but when he reacts this way I sometimes match his nastiness. I'm working on it. He's working on it, but how much can a person work on themselves so much when they're a couple of euros away from not making rent every month? I'm not a piece of cake either. I have major depressive disorder, PTSD, generalized anxiety, bordeline personality disorder, and a stubborn eating disorder. I financially support my sick grandmother while in school. My mother is bipolar and living with the consequences of many poor financial decisions (I've been helping to financially support my household since I was 14 as well). I'm on medication and I have 15 years of therapy under my belt, and so I consider myself to be fine, comparatively, and willingly take on the caretaking role for people who are struggling. You know, "the strong friend". But I feel like I'm fraying. My baseline anxiety keeps rising. I've started grinding my teeth in my sleep (when I do sleep, since that's getting weaker as well). And I hate to say this, but I know this relationship is the cause of a lot of this anxiety. I keep telling myself to push toward the next time we see each other where everything will be great again. I love him. More than I've loved someone in a long time. When we are together this shows. We deeply connect, and understand each other, and he makes me feel safe and happy. But through a screen we end up being mean to each other and it hurts me, and I know it hurts him too. I feel helpless that I can't provide more support. And he feels helpless that he's not in a place where he can help himself either. I don't want to lose him, and I want to keep pushing to be able to be together for longer periods of time until I finish my doctorate. I feel very lost. I don't know what to do. I just needed to vent. Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 22:39:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spain (me 28) \-\- Greece (him 29) edit: this was the last time we saw each other over easter break. I'm going to Greece to live with him for the summer in one month! the distance has been difficult lately, but I love this man so much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 00:05:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for responding. Is it bad that I don't want it to be true? :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 10:55:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks so much for your response  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 11:01:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>this might be a good post for r/JustNoSO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 14:00:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>It can get up to around 9\-10 hours. I usually have to take a 4 hour bus to Madrid, then a 4 hour flight to Athens. Then add in wait times in airports and public transit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 14:05:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>my husband</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Me (28NB)/ Him (29M), wrapping up first year of PhD long-distance +2 more??</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 14:22:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone! I just wanted to express some of my nervousness about the progress of our relationship and would like to see if anyone else has dealt with such a time frame. We met while I was living in his home country of Greece and I went back to my country Spain to study my PhD after getting some very generous funding. We had only been together a 4 months (knew each other a bit longer) when we decided to continue long distance. We have fortunately been able to see each other for 2 weeks twice since october, but it's still tough (moreso for him). We have to repeat this for 2 more years while I do my doctoral studies, and have started to think about whether this is sustainable long\-term. We will be living together over the summer for the first time (6 weeks) and hoping to kind of test that compatibility and make a decision about continuing or not over the summer. It's hard, however, to think there are still 2 more years of this (unless he decides to come here, or I spend some of my writing time the last year with him). Has anyone survived a time frame like this? can it work? Are you happy? thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 16:55:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think "too short" is up to you to define! do you feel comfortable at this length? if so, then it's fine. you can always wear shorts underneath :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 23:19:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>i'm going to start using the phrase "rich people skin"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 13:29:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you so much for your words of encouragement :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 13:45:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been on .025 for a month now at every other day and I also have no peeling!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 14:38:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>possibly! I also was using a retinol before hand</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 23:10:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's just so frustrating. I haven't been in a relationship in 5 years after my last boyfriend committed suicide and I finally was in a place where I really felt like I had healed enough to try again and I found someone I really fell for and for this to fail just feels like such a hard blow. sorry for the run-on sentence</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 11:26:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>omg this is so cute</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 11:28:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had this haircut a few years back and I loved how easy it was to manage</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 18:41:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>like right? I feel like I need to breathe into a paper bag and take a walk after seeing this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 22:49:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>exfoliate with it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 23:39:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>27 days until Greece!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 14:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meeeeee. I just assumed my face is made of iron</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 15:09:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bioderma cicabio has I think 4 different centella components!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 14:33:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I use a hydrating toner (Mebika Moisture Lotion from Japan) prior to using my tret</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 17:24:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know what is available in your country but in Spain I have found CBD in hemp oil as a carrier, which has some good positive effects for the skin I hear.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 22:30:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I started after a nasty sun allergy I developed when I was maybe 12. Since then it's a must.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 16:15:50</DATE>
    <TEXT> #960; #959; #955; #955; #941; #962;  #953; #952; #945; #947; #949; #957; #949; #943; #962;  #954; #959; #953; #957; #969; #957; #943; #949; #962;  #963; #949;  #972; #955; #959;  #964; #959; #957;  #954; #972; #963; #956; #959;  #941; #967; #959; #965; #957;  #960; #949; #961; #953; #963; #963; #972; #964; #949; #961; #945;  #945; #960; #972;  #948; #973; #959;  #966; #973; #955; #945;.  #916; #949; #957;  #949; #943; #957; #945; #953;  #954; #940; #964; #953; " #945; #956; #949; #961; #953; #954; #945; #957; #953; #954; #972;".  #916; #949; #957;  #949; #943; #957; #945; #953;  #959; #973; #964; #949;  #941; #957; #945; " #948; #965; #964; #953; #954; #972;"  #960; #961; #940; #947; #956; #945;...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 22:47:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't pick it up as a habit if you're not already a smoker. to be honest, I went from cigarettes to a vape and I spend so much more time vaping than I ever did smoking cigarettes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 23:12:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok so my partner and I love video sexting, like through skype. It allows for some visual interaction, you can flirt a for a bit, maybe have a drink "together" if you both drink, if she likes to see you wear something nice, do so, then she can also enjoy watching you disrobe, then get down to business. I personally think it's really fun, and you have to plan for it so it's more of an "event". And you can get really creative with it if you want. It seems silly, but I think it does help to feel a little closer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It has proteins to rebuild your moisture barrier though!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 12:53:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 14:58:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>omg you look so much like my best friend. you hair cut is adorable!! I might show her a pic for inspiration</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 23:07:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone posted a while back about tracking coverage with LRP anthelios 50 with a UV filter (or something, I don't know science) and her coverage lasted completely intact for several hours. I use the non tinted one and I love it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 23:11:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used this as my intro to retinoids and I went through a purge at first, freaked out, stopped using it, then slowly reintroduced it. once I was done, I upgraded to tret .025. When I eased into it , it went much better. I would vouch for it as a solid retinol for beginners</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 10:19:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do, but only because I tend to work out in the afternoon and so I wipe off my make up, work out, then reapply sunscreen then. Otherwise I don't bother since I work in an office with no windows...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 14:16:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's actually already a cream, and has several moisturizing agents, so you might not need a moisturizer. I started using it in the winter and my skin gets mas dry so I did use moisturizer over it, but not necessarily because I wanted to buffer it. If you're scared about introducing it, you can always start off mixing it with moisturizer for the first two weeks or so!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 22:26:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, we can all be honest with ourselves, this sub IS petty. it's fun, but petty (most of the time)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 23:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>literally was about to say the same</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 17:27:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>i'm not usually squeamish but I literally couldnt watch this. you weren #180;t joking when you said butcher</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 01:46:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>this was downright violent</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 01:28:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi! Ok, so I really want to put this as kindly as possible, absolutely respecting how you feel right now, but the likelihood of this working out is really low. You both are really young, and you\`re at an age where you can feel things really deeply, I totally get that. But you are growing at such a fast rate right now that it's very unlikely that you two will grow up in compatible ways, especially if you're far apart. Moving is a big deal, you'll need to adjust to a new place, new school, new friends, and you'll need to be present in that and not a long distance relationship. that being said, if you two want to give it a try, you are within your right to do so. You can keep in touch for sure. But just don't feel like you've failed if it doesn't work out, ok?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to advance with tret .025?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 18:41:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello everyone! So I have been using my treat every other night buffering with a light moisturizing toner 30min before and a moisturizer 30min after. I have been at this step for a month now and I have no real irritation or flakiness. How should I move forward from here? 1) remove the buffering toner and use every other day? 2) remove moisturizer and use every other day? Or 3) keep buffering and use every day? Thanks so much in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 20:56:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you for your response! I hadn't considered this and it sounds pretty viable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 19:42:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>could you maybe comment on some of your favorites?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 20:11:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm prone to compulsive disorders (skin picking, drug use, food restriction, compulsive exercise) and there are days I wish I hadn't discovered skincare.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 21:33:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 21:35:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel it definitely has sharpened my body dysmorphia to an extent. I think I remember that thread</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 18:18:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>like wtf is that "glow"? like I have never seen skin look like that in real life??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 00:09:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey! I'm about your same age and I also had to move away to start my PhD, and one bump we had to overcome was that when one partner moves away to chase an opportunity, there can be resentment from the other. Like they chose an opportunity over them, there could be jealousy...these sorts of things need to be nipped in the bud if they come up and worked through. Resentment is not good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 22:11:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>that top is cute af! you look great. wear it with confidence!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 12:06:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was using azelaic acid for several months prior to beginning tret. I think that most of the reason I haven't had a heavy purge has been due to this keeping acne at bay. It hasn't caused any additional irritation for me (actually, besides a tiny bit of redness when I apply products, I haven't had any irritation at all!) and azelaic acid doesn't increase sun sensitivity so you aren't compounding that with the sensitivity from the tret</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 19:10:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>As far as I understand, tret can take between 6 months to a year to truly see the full effect, especially for antiaging as opposed to acne.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-28 22:34:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah I think because of the aggressiveness tret can even aggravate PIE if that's wha you've got. Maybe talk to your derm about increasing to .05?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 00:32:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Essential oils can be really harsh on a lot of people's skin, just as a warning</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 01:52:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love the Medusa. I've been too chicken to get it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 19:18:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>orgasmic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Broke down for the first time in a long time</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 00:07:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I self harmed today for the first time in almost a year. I had really been doing well, but I had a breakdown after my emotionally abusive bf and I had an exchange of words. I felt so beat down by the end of it, and it hurt so much this time that I went and just burned up my fucking forearm with my lighter. Maybe not so coincidentally the last time I burned myself was also after another session of him demeaning me. All in all, I feel pretty disappointed in myself. I hadn't been feeling the urge to do it, so I'm not sure why I reached for it this time. I'm trying not to be discouraged but, like, fuck. I'm already prone to feeling like a failure, so how do I bounce back from this tumble with grace? Any tips appreciated. Also, how the hell do I cover this up in summer?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>