<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject8064</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-05 02:49:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>326, 132, 354 Max awakened. Working on leveling her up + egging her as well. Up 2/3 times of the day. (rotates between Krisnha and Kushi)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-19 20:15:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sent an invite. IGN:  #9734;  #40614; #12431; #12425;  #9734; I say you work on U amp;Y since his Uevo will be coming soon. Plus he seems fun to play.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-21 04:24:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>love live! school idol festival lol. no shame bc cute girls + catchy songs = win. its a bit like osu if you know what that is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-22 02:36:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Been running the dungeon on legend since I don't have a team for mythical yet. 3 runs so far and not one drop e_e So far this has been a traumatizing experience for my first descend... probably will attempt it again with the little hope I have left in a couple of hours.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-31 03:53:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>4 rolls. Dupe Dark Golem and Water Dragon Swordsman but rolled Haku and LMeta afterwards. I'm pretty much set for a while.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-07 18:36:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mind if I ask where you got the transparent dc collab images from?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-08 04:24:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol if i win i'll split the prize with you. thanks btw!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-08 04:26:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>my submission: http://i.imgur.com/71QqjJo.png got a lot of inspiration from others on this thread pls dont kill me bc of that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-08 05:47:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks;; yeah i realized the whole retro pop art thing was never really dc's style but its fine i was trying to do a jjba thing instead but sadly i cant make my graphics really 3D or super fabulous like jojo art.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-10 03:44:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>everyone had really nice submissions! makes me kinda nervous yet excited at the same time lol. good luck to all!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-10 20:04:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>its fine! i dont really have a problem with gunghoplshire me winning if its to get gungho to notice him and finally hire him! plus the fact i usually lurk here on mobile so i dont see the banners anyways. entering the contest was a way to try to improve my graphics skill and im really happy people liked it which is good enough for me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-11 00:29:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>i can probably make a wallpaper version for you when i have some free time;;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-18 10:00:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>"My treasure? If you want it, you can have it. Seek it out! I left everything in my life at that place!" *crowd goes wild*. ONE PIECE IS OUT THERE!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-03 08:40:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I might take a shot at this since I have a couple of cards that are gonna be in the scouting. Hopefully I'll get a duplicate to idolize my girls  lt;3 Really appreciate the heads up!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-03 09:22:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably Ochako. Really cute girl who has a nice ability which can definitely be useful later on. Character who I want to know more about would be Shouto. He seems like a beast like fire vs ice powers... Also in Top 3 rank out of the entire class. Also shoutout to Iida. I always tend to be bias towards the dorky meganes so I can really see appreciation in the role he will play later on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Compilation of early character designs/sketches</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-04 05:51:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-04 06:26:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>My bad. I wasn't too sure if it was really spoiler-y since these are from way back when the first chapter came out. I believe some of the spoiler characters are shown in newest chapters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-04 07:10:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like [4] please;; Himeno up on the top row: http://i.imgur.com/Nk625uA.jpg Edit: I'm on Android</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-04 10:21:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! One of the first heroes to show up in the manga. His name is Kamui Wood.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-05 00:34:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>believe in me who believes in the you that will not roll until the end! lol the best resolution is to save those friend points and just roll those whenever your tempted. that way you can save yourself from the evil that is rng. also don't look or think about any UR or SR in the time being, it will only anger the desire sensor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-05 20:13:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like a 126 Nishikino Maki [Initial] for a friend. I'll update with the OS once she's back on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-06 02:08:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's fine! Apparently she has no more space for the newest update anyways D: Good luck giving out the rest of the accounts^^</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-06 07:24:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don't necessarily have to FC the songs you play you can do a pretty shitty job on score/combo and still get gold/silver drops depending on your luck. Usually if there is a friend or student popup before the song starts and if you get a friend popup it will give a higher chance of those gold and silver drops I believe along with other boosts. Or if you have the coins to spend just pay for 100k coin boost to get a increase chance for g/s drops (the first option when you go to pay for boosts)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-06 07:35:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah definitely! if you dont feel too confident in your score/combo you can try purchasing the boosts and see if that helps but personally i would just keep rolling with the 3x hard songs only w/ the chance to increase event points boost (2nd to last option) good luck you'll get maki in no time;;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-07 03:28:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>i think the vocals are pre-recorded and then remastered with the original audio. anyways im down for this i can lend my 5 year old voice for the high notes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-08 01:03:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>The current honor student scouting is not SR guaranteed so definitely don't scout that one unless you want a bunch of R :/ The lily white scouting is nice if you like the subunit girls but there definitely a high chance you'll get more Rs rather than the wanted SR/UR. Save your loveca until next SR guaranteed or if you really can't wait go for lily white</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-08 01:38:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can probably try to get yukata umi again once smile scout comes back around or wait until next year for august-november ur/sr scout or second years only scout other than that your best would be right now. If your feeling lucky I say go for it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-08 02:02:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rin is my number 1 girl because despite having a lot of similarities (interest in sports, being really determined, both of us loooove ramen, etc.) we are also totally different from each other (she wants to be more girly, while i want to be more boyish) Rin is also a little ball of sunshine since she is always very positive and eccentric while in terms of personality i'm more Hanayo then anything... both very awkward and shy. Whenever I see Rin and how energetic she really makes me want to go out and try something fun and break out my awkzone kinda like how she pushes Hanayo out there to become something she loves which is an idol. I really admire Rin for being so hardworking and caring towards her friends, honestly she makes me want to be a better person for my own sake and for the people I care about. Ok sorry that got really personal and super long but yeah... Anyways you're art is super cute! (your one piece art  lt;333) I think might purchase a charm later on since those are really nice especially the Saitama one;;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-09 02:54:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>"finally got something other than a scouting ticket" i wish i can say that too :cc all i get are alpacas...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-10 08:36:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have obviously have never read "Oppa, Watashi Wa Sarang Tu, Mi Amor Desu Ne!" http://i.imgur.com/XKpNhe7.png</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-10 09:41:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's from a fanfic that makes fun of (kpop) fanfics. Not really love live related but ironically similar to that fb post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-11 04:51:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have a pretty ideal Pandora team (minus haku but ronia is a good as well) Pandora / Loki / Hanzo / Ronia / Dvalk / Pandora You can either go either D/D Loki or D/B Loki depending if you want a future balance team or not (since you have couple of good balance subs) however he does lose his God subtyping. Also with the Dvalk Uevo out I would switch Persephone out for her. Dark enhance, 2 prong, and a skill boost will definitely come in handy later on. I also run have Pandora first slot fully awoken + egging her so feel free to add me! My id is in my flair.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-11 09:26:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had to delete some games off my phone for SIF but it was worth it...not so sure about the toll it had on my social life tho.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-11 12:25:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can see how it can be offensive considering it originated from a mocking manner of the term "wife" and how it's usually associated w/ otakus and weaboos... which is not a good thing at all really. But it's gonna be really tough for people to cut back on it let alone grasp the context behind it since it's such a commonly used word nowadays. While most of the time people do not mean harm by but it is still an "engrish" mocking term. Same goes for husbando. Tbh I was a repeat offender of using this term but after learning about it I tried to cut back on it as much as possible seeing how it is associated with such things. It'll usually pop back into my vocabulary now and then but not intentionally tho so I still gotta work on that. tl;dr: word is associated w/ weaboos not a thing to be proud of. use the word best girl/guy/god/monster/dragon/whatever in replacement</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-11 12:45:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Kaneki never stood a chance against the Coco mob* I bet most players were like "wth is a coco" or "oh look another free win!" since we all dodged so much...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-11 13:20:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>The scene from Azumanga Daioh the teacher says "my wife" so joking about mispronounciation of an non-native english speaker is ok I guess? I never really touched onto the topic of how it can be offensive to some but believe it or not behind all that modern day technology there is an actual person! And that person may be offended by things you may not find offensive for whatever reason. Am I saying you should be offended by it or stop using the word just because I or the mod says so? No of course not but I am just saying people should take into consideration of updating their vocabulary for words that are less tacky.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-13 08:04:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>good thing it's only an itunes card.... ~~or else i totally would have bought a couple of these~~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-14 06:49:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>now we just have to wait for a challenger named rice cream to *step up to the plate*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-15 09:07:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>woo umida! it was a wild week filled with riots, pad hype and lots of rice! you definitely deserved that 1mil. once again congrats and looking forward to your future 2mil stream! \\\insert kappa here//</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-15 09:44:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>first time aiming for tier 2 and i actually got it. ofc i was aiming to be rank 420 but overshot by quite a bit ended up getting 369 on rankings which wasn't too bad. overall 6/9 for rice. will be aiming for tier 1 next first year event.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-19 03:00:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>got 3 R umis in a row  #65077; #12541;(` #1044; #180;) #65417; #65077;  #9531; #9473; #9531;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-19 05:03:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>i seem to get a lot of cool umis too. like 25% of my account is umi at this point ;__; it must be the curse of the sea maiden</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>100 Love Live! Icons</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-23 04:03:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi everyone! Since it's winter break I decided to use some of the free time I have to make some icons. These are all 285 x 285px so perfect for twitter or you can resize them to use on any other forum, blog, etc. The album includes 10 icons for each  #956;'s member + 10 random normal cards. [Icons](http://imgur.com/a/d3XH1) + [bonus nico](http://i.imgur.com/dAXtALx.png) I will also be taking requests for things like wallpapers, headers, and icons for the time being so feel free to ask for those too! **Edit**: If you are requesting something like a wallpaper please be sure to give me your screen resolution or what phone you have so I can make the graphic the best fit for your desktop/device!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-23 04:27:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm assuming the idolized Nozomi vers? Do you mind telling your screen resolution? //just so i can make sure it fits on your desktop//</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-23 06:12:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Harasho] (http://i1.minus.com/iSbNkmhLuOLfh.jpg) for you~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-23 06:17:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually got all the transparents from a file someone shared with me but apparently whoever uploaded the .pngs removed it x.x You can find some transparents on this [blog] (http://kousakayukihos.tumblr.com/) tho</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-23 06:24:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh I wasn't too sure which Eri to pick so I just went with the wedding dress o: Feel free to request another one if it's not really your style only problem is it might take a while x___x</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-23 07:03:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Washi] (http://i5.minus.com/iB5lA9FgTJvnh.jpg) [washi] (http://i2.minus.com/iCKUiEzLVy0JX.png) Sorry if the positioning is a little weird :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-23 07:28:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>[it's time to d-d-duel!] (http://i.imgur.com/MQtxOwe.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-23 07:47:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don't have to credit!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-23 10:27:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Maki] (http://i2.minus.com/iRLimgTD0ihnk.jpg) for you~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-24 04:26:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's your [rice] (http://i2.minus.com/iQW7FQbOc7ENk.png) ~ Since I don't have an iphone I'm not too sure how it looks if there is any problems be sure to tell me so I can fix it;;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-24 04:49:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeessh. My twitter is @soulgab</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-24 11:10:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Maki] (http://i1.minus.com/ifc67kBT1Ll20.png) ~ Sorry for all the slowness. I'll finish the rest of the requests tomorrow @.@</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-25 02:52:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Umi] (http://i5.minus.com/ihCbVFCCm65BZ.png) ~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-25 04:34:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Here] (http://i1.minus.com/i3bLegNK3gX4W.jpg) you go;;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-25 13:19:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahh it works fine when I tested it out as a bg @.@ I can just crop it out for you to fit sometime in the morning^^ (already turned off my laptop D:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-25 13:27:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you plan to have some type of big giveaway I have some accounts that I'm willing to donate to the cause~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-26 02:04:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's still the 25th over here in PST. Murray Christmas everyone \o/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-26 02:45:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>[!!] (http://imgur.com/a/4VY6u) I cropped some of the transparents I already had. I'm not sure what size the side images were so I just kept them at full size x___x</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-26 03:01:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry it took me half a day to get back at you D: buuut [here] (http://i4.minus.com/iKFZIi9V3S6jZ.jpg) is the cropped version for your other monitor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-26 03:26:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait do you have one of those dual monitors? If so I messed up and thought it was two separate desktops this whole time ORZ ~~I'll just reposition Umi for you so she'll be in middle~~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-26 04:27:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry about everything DD: [Here] (http://i2.minus.com/iCYWLQpAm1Mpk.jpg) is the new version. Let me know if it works^</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-27 11:43:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like to enter for JP account 24;; Honestly I shouldnt be entering in too many giveaways since I had my fair share of winning some... however I had lost my main JP account recently and rng hates me with jp rerolls so I really appreciate this chance to get second best girl!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-27 12:08:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Makirin ~~aka best girls~~] (http://i4.minus.com/irFPMkQVsS12R.jpg) Also sorry to you and everyone else since it's taking so long for all the wallpapers ;-; It may look like I skipped some people but I promise you guys I didn't! Some people requested two wallpapers so I was just planing to do the singles first.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-28 09:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Catman] (http://imgur.com/F6VqaEi)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-28 09:56:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>congrats on that fc! and i feel u on the whole right arm is numb thing. been grinding on an account for my friend... 420 points away till umi and main account... well i have no idea i havent logged onto it yet. also i keep hearing "you know me, i know you something something we are friends" in the back of my head. yeah i might be going crazy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-29 10:21:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for having the giveaway! If you don't mind me asking but can I swap Pure Maki for a Cool Maki or any Rin SR account? ofc if it's too much of a hassle I'll gladly accept the original account that was assigned to me. Thanks again~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-29 23:09:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>~~Oh how Rin tempts me so...~~ I'd like to enter for [34] on android!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-29 23:56:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Best girl: Rin nyan~ Nice: Maki, Nico, Pana Pls no: Umi, Eli I like all the girls but my Umi and Eli curse is too much for me to handle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-30 02:54:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it would be hilarious if Todoroki did a commerical for IcyHot cream</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-30 22:18:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>apparently code 14 is expired ceris D: ~~if it wasnt expired i would have entered as well~~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-31 05:12:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>$48.85 for me. Maybe different OS? I use android btw.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-31 05:18:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in California^^</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-31 05:24:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>~~Looks like it's time to move. Better start packing now~~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-31 07:08:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Ranpha] (http://i.imgur.com/heQfopU.png) [for] (http://i.imgur.com/TJlBJmi.png) [sure] (http://i.imgur.com/BKk8xFf.png) I have a full Ranpha team on eng vers. I would post a pic but I'm currently not logged into my main account</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-31 09:28:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rin and Rice ORZ</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-31 11:10:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your experience reminds me a bit of my own. My neighbors and I found a lost kitty a couple years back. I was the only one who couldn't play with her because of my allergies to cats but I loved the fluff ball from a distance ;~; A few weeks later we found her under someone's parked car DD: It was a really traumatizing for my 6 year old heart. //end sad story here// Anywaaaays, I always assumed you liked Rin because of the whole ending everything with nyan~ but I never knew she was in your top 3 o: Another thing we have in common because Rin, Maki, Nico are my top 3 as well;; And to stay on topic w/ the thread: Did a 10+1 on jp... my umi curse still lives to this day even on the other side ;__;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-31 13:32:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kalina the number one player in [Japan] (https://twitter.com/lovelivelover_/status/550230730219855872) Also good luck to OP on starting the new year w/ a fresh start~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-31 13:49:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ehhh I think it's more because some people want to just move forward and better their life? (I don't know how to put this in proper english ;__;) But yeah what better time to start fresh than in the new year? The OP seems to have been contemplating on whether or not they wanted to give up on their account (?) in the past and seeing how a big player gave everything up to move forward inspired him to do so as well. I don't see anything wrong with that. If a person wants to give up their account good for them if another wants keep playing then also good for them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-31 13:56:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>She was so young too I hope the felines in our stories are in a good place now;; And yesss you have great taste as well c; And I got 2 SRs Umis.... still have 2 other accounts to scout from tho. Hopefully my lucky turns around this year</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-01 04:55:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Na na na na na na Catman~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-01 05:05:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tier 1/2 for Rin (5th) and Maki (7th) score match + Maki SID. And hopefully Top 5 for Rin SID \o/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-01 14:14:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rank 999? They should take it to over 9000! //Also good luck on becoming f2p//</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-02 03:28:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since it's a new year, I have decided to get off my lazy bum and go job hunting to feed my mobile gaming addiction ~~and to lift some weight off my parents shoulders.~~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-02 03:38:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>If only being lazy can somehow pay the bills *sigh*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-02 03:42:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ty, I'll check this out later. A little side money is good but I still think it's best for me to get part-time work and save up for my future aka going to an anime con w/ my friend flying in from Canada D:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-02 03:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmmm I have never heard of RES before so idk what you are seeing o.o</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-02 03:55:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably bc I make wallpapers for people on the subreddit :P Sadly I am a mere mortal who is still working on some requests but got distracted....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-02 04:13:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since your favourite series is Monogatari and currently attending college... I highly recommend [The Tatami Galaxy] (http://myanimelist.net/anime/7785/Yojouhan_Shinwa_Taikei). The show has a very flat artstyle, fast paced, and repetitive with a twist. Also noticed that you have seen Arakawa Under the Bridge one of my favourite shows  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-02 05:20:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>maid cafe is a must buuuuut if you visit any nearby shrines please take pictures for ~~me~~ us!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-02 14:02:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>starting with a fresh JP account over here~ 359168151</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-02 15:01:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same can be said about your account;; Maid Rin and Pana ;-;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-02 15:11:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nico is another one of my favourites *sobs* now if you had a 4th UR being Maki i'd be turning green out of envy D:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-03 05:30:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Entering for code 2 since Nico and Maki are in my top 3;; I never entered in any previous promo code giveaways because I never had a set JP account and once I did get a main JP account I lost it for a stupid reason a few weeks afterwards ORZ. I recently got a purrrfect new JP starter from a very kinda user the other day and plan to be very active on it! Really appreciate this chance to maybe get 2 of my favourite idols. Good luck to everyone as well~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-03 06:11:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be Gainax however I think the director for the series left the company and he ended up forming Studio Trigger so yeah.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-03 07:40:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uhh you can try downloading a cloning app apk? I have the link for one but I have never tried it so might be bit of a risk ://</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-04 10:55:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's gonna haunt the rest of your life for not asking the mods to empty that account bc this Rin is absolutely beautiful. Especially when her skill activates and goes "nyanyanyan"  lt;3 Anyways good luck to those participating~ I'm curious to see how many the EX songs op fc w/ one hand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-04 12:43:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>how about how many songs you have perfect full combo'd with one hand? (  #865;~  #860; #662;  #865; #176;) ~~i think i can guess this one~~ if more people heard rin's active skill i think they might want to join even more? its pretty darn cute but idk where to find clips of those D:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-05 05:07:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>id (jp): 359168151 i have around 3 friend slots left so feel free to add~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-05 05:26:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>accepted! also your rin urs D:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-05 08:51:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Single idol scouting? Like honor scout only featuring one girl (so you can be trolled by only Rs of your fav girl.) It could be like a limited edition thing only on their birthday. Or free loveca on the seiyuu's birthdays bc ~~free loveca~~ they are important to the franchise as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-07 02:18:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You forgot TuPana and Nyatorious R.I.N ~~i suck at this lul~~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-07 08:23:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do we have to select an account from both lists? .-. I'm really only interested in entering the giveaway for a friend and her fav is Nozomi so I kinda only want to enter for something from List A. //sorry if I sound kinda snappy but I don't want to take away the chances of getting those really nice list b cards from others//</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-07 09:12:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like to enter for A[7] then~ I have been playing SIF since the Eli token event. Despite Rin being my best girl my fav card would have to be [New Year's Honoka] (http://decaf.kouhi.me/lovelive/images/9/9c/Honoka_cool_ur222_t.jpg) everything from the hairstyle to posing is just gorgeous. Anyways thank you so much for holding this giveaway and good luck to everyone;;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-08 03:25:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol yes. I thought she was female Jotaro when I first got her card. There is also [Fumie] (http://vignette1.wikia.nocookie.net/love-live/images/2/20/N_6_Fumie_Nishimura.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20140717040007) who is reading Battle Tendency. ~~jojo x love live collab when?~~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-08 03:43:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's pretty obvious the cover is [Joseph] (http://img1.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20140713194351/jjba/images/9/93/Joesephjoestar.jpg) ~~the headband he is wearing makes it more obvious if you know it's origin~~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-09 09:26:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats! I was really tempted and took your bait.... got a SR Nozomi thanks :p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-09 18:49:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could have been worse. You could have not full combo'd the song while everyone else got fcs and then let out their last wimpy battle cry "Nice Full Combo!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-12 07:00:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Going to Anime Expo this summer as a lone wolf Maki (china dress ver) //if anyone sees me there be sure to say hi! i may or may not give an impression or two//</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 05:06:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm watching Drrr x2, KNB S3, JoJo, Seven Deadly Sins and Death Parade. From this season I really recommend Death Parade (and the ova Death Billiards) and Seven Deadly Sins. **Edit:** I heard Rolling Girls was a really good show as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-23 21:50:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got the account thanks! It's such a beautiful account too. I'll be sure to take care of it well ;w;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-23 23:09:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry to say that it was Eli fans... D:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-23 23:19:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>i love these guys. their other parodies are hilarious as well. i just wished they blessed us w/ their singing to go with the opening tho</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-25 05:30:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Before listening to  #956;'s I listened to Kpop and still do to this day. I think I started listeing to korean music in 2007-2008? Somewhere in that time period when Big Bang debuted. After that whole phase I stopped listening for a while then listened to whatever including some J-Rock/Vocaloid. I got back into kpop in 2011 when it started becoming more popular over here in the states and been on that train ever since. Talking to other kpop fans introduced to me to Jpop idols which I wasn't a fan of before but now I love japans giant idol groups. I was into AKB48 before Yuko graduated and into Momusu before Reina graduated as well. I was also obsessed with Weather Girls when they debuted with the super catchy [Doki Doki Typhoon](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jd2-Nf86jvA). Nowadays I'm not super into groups anymore but listen to soloists or bands + anime osts but I still love idols like  #956;'s  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-25 18:51:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>SNSD are considered idols as well. They are just korean idols. IMO A-RISE is more a Orange Caramel than 2ne1.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-31 08:54:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Next event is probably Honoka. KLAB seems to do events by subunits. Hanayo and Kotori were the last events sooo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-02 22:41:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>HERE FOR ROLL CALL. going for tier 1/2 on two accounts. best of luck to everyone's health!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-03 00:07:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah playing on multiple accounts has become second nature to me. Maybe one day I can go as far as getting #1 for best girl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-15 08:21:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>i saved loved enough loveca for 3 10+1s and a blue ticket scout o: i swore it was going to be umi though so i was planning on saving up more welp. i hope i get her anyways~ praying for the best</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Next JP event is Rin!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-19 07:14:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-19 07:22:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Forgot to include in the title but I believe it is a token event~ I have never tried to go for a tier in token events but anything for Rin. even if it means spending $$$</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 01:09:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>someone gave me reddit gold on a post. i have no idea what it even does lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 01:24:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>oooh thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 01:25:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>would you accept a gold sticker instead? -3-</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-27 00:34:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>my favourite hairstyle would definitely be the hime-cut also super popular in the lolita community. i personally like it because it just looks really edgy and cute;; [bambi on the right is rocking the hime-cut](http://40.media.tumblr.com/6954332e50236cf688cf98916f766cbe/tumblr_nilhfhPsJI1u5l9q1o1_500.jpg) [bomi w/ another variation of the hairstyle](http://cdn.kpopfighting.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/53913-289163-540x834.jpg) i also love [choa's hair](http://40.media.tumblr.com/22ed61da71f65503fd2c17c5010aed5f/tumblr_nevmp0goez1tk0sfho2_1280.jpg) in like a cat and plan to get my haircut just like hers when i can!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-15 06:21:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>That dedication for Rin. Been there, done that as well .-. If you don't mind me asking but do you accept donation accounts? I have some a few UR accounts (from trying to roll rin as well) that I have been meaning to giveaway but honestly I'm pretty lazy to make one myself if not I'll just crawl^back^into^my^hole</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-15 06:47:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll pm you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-27 20:53:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello! How much would [this](http://www.ratzillacosme.com/sun/sunkiller-perfect-strong-moisture/) and [this](http://www.amazon.co.jp/%E3%83%9C%E3%83%BC%E3%83%80%E3%83%BC%E3%82%AA%E3%82%B1%E3%82%A4%EF%BC%88Border%E3%80%80Okei%EF%BC%89-%E3%83%9C%E3%83%BC%E3%83%80%E3%83%BC%E3%82%AA%E3%82%B1%E3%82%A4%EF%BC%88Border%E3%80%80Okei%EF%BC%89%E3%80%80%E3%82%AB%E3%83%A9%E3%83%BC%E3%83%A9%E3%82%A4%E3%83%8A%E3%83%BC%E3%80%80%E3%83%A9%E3%82%BA%E3%83%99%E3%83%AA%E3%83%BC%E3%83%AC%E3%83%83%E3%83%89/dp/B00GZL0TL8/ref=sr_1_1?s=hpc amp;ie=UTF8 amp;qid=1432752543 amp;sr=1-1 amp;keywords=%E3%83%9C%E3%83%BC%E3%83%80%E3%83%BC%E3%82%AA%E3%82%B1%E3%82%A4) cost shipped to the US?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-28 02:45:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll take them both!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-14 02:51:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would love a tarot card theme. Where all the girls are dressed up referencing different cards with Nozomi being 1 of the UR pairs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-15 23:14:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>3 scouting tickets got me nothing. 1 10+1 got me another cool nico sr (nico nico nii cursed account) and sold the new event nozomi and a kotori sr for a blue voucher, only got a pure maki sr. i was getting annoyed even by getting some of my best girls so i grinded for some more lovecas and did 2 solo yolos and got a smile maki sr. overall not too bad but still sad since there was no rin in sight :c</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-20 23:14:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>those rins;; would you be interested in [this](http://imgur.com/a/GC9Yz) maybe?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-21 04:36:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>your rin curse is amazing. hopefully my slight nico curse will sway you~</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-26 07:55:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>[this](http://i.imgur.com/Bm9dvUv.jpg) march rin starter w/ 8 lovecas in the present box for the maki acc. maybe?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-27 00:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>not really nozomi blessed but will take a chance for the 1st account anyways ;A; http://imgur.com/a/GC9Yz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-27 00:30:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>i have a march rin account! but is it 2 starters to trade for 1 of your accounts or...? in sorry i dont really understand what you mean by that  gt;_ gt;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-28 20:04:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>i have [this](http://i.imgur.com/zg2rcL1.jpg) starter-ish const. rin which is around rank 14 (bc i played some songs) and it still has extra loveca in the presents box. im interested in your valentine rin for this account.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-02 04:06:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>If possible can I get Viola and Venus Osequens shipped in the states?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-02 07:12:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds good. PM me your paypal!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-03 00:59:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I refuse to let you feed that March Rin away so I'll be at the stream making sure that doesnt happen and making the moola rain. Also **#TeamRin**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-03 04:10:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just ran out of some sunscreen so this would be a life saver ;~; Could I get the Mizon eye cream and Benton steam cream samples as well? Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-08 19:52:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>**[US][Perfume][Smelly Yeti + Sixteen92][Samples/Decants]** **Smelly Yeti:** Hey, McFly!, Queen of Damned, Purgatorio **Sixteen92:** Gothic Lolita, The Tea Party, Rei, Theda Try me on any other peach or tea scents!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-09 06:01:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm interested in Snow White Tea and Gypsy Curse!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-19 04:22:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi can I get CosRX Honey Ceramide Full Moisture Cream and Innisfree Apple Juicy Cleansing Oil.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-19 05:15:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Payment sent!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-19 06:16:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Submitted!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-19 07:40:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll go for airmail. Please pm me your paypal :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-31 23:01:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>**[US][BUY][Perfume]** Smelly Yeti - Princess Jellyfish (FS/Decant) Smelly Yeti - Hey, McFly! or any root beer-y smelling perfume</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[REQUEST][US] Nars Audacious Lipstick Jane  amp; Becca SSP in Opal</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-06 00:48:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just looking for whats above. I prefer the lipstick to be BN and the highlighter in liquid form but I won't be too picky :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-06 01:10:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>How much would be for each size shipped to California?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-06 01:28:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>PMing you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-06 17:31:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely! Do you have any verification pics btw?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-06 17:32:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll pass on it. Good luck tho!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-06 21:57:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry but I'm only looking for Jane!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-19 08:44:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>**[US][BUY][Perfume]** Smelly Yeti - Princess Jellyfish (FS/Decant) Smelly Yeti - Hey, McFly! or any root beer-y smelling perfume Sixteen92 - Lolita (Full size oil please!) also try me on any peachy or apple scents!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[REQUEST][US] Holika Holika Pro:Beauty Bloody Oil Tint + Sheet Masks!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-23 20:50:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn't really plan out my most recent jolse haul too well seeing as I forgot to add this tint in my cart! Looking for the Bloody Oil tint in the color Bloody Vampire only. Also interested in purchasing sheet masks (My favs are the MBD masks) Always interested in trying new products too so feel free to link any decants posts!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-18 19:23:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>[US][BUY][Perfume] Smelly Yeti - Princess Jellyfish (FS/Decant) Smelly Yeti - Hey, McFly! or any root beer-y smelling perfume Sixteen92 - Lolita (Preferrably a more recent batch) also try me on any peachy or apple scents!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-18 22:57:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>How recent was the purchase for them both?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 07:46:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe you #8217;re thinking about La Bomba! Was there earlier, that place is packed with clothes like every different style you can imagine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 06:35:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>just came back from seeing the movie. it was sweet and decent despite how initially corny it seemed. the thing that probably surprised me the most was how many older people they were for my screening. i would say 75% of the theatre was people over the age of 35 and the rest of the seats were filled with teens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-17 22:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Interested in the Stunna Lip paint if the other person falls through!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 08:37:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>sent you a pm :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 19:33:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just got tattooed by Joy as well! Her work is always lovely, especially here  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-15 21:02:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got a small [lil](https://i.imgur.com/pYDHqCN.jpg) tattoo for Friday the 13th!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 04:51:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I definitely recommend getting to the festival through the shuttle. They usually have a little dedicated area to strictly for festival goers and have several in rotation at a time. I went to Tropicalia last year and it looked like hell for everyone taking ubers/driving.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 07:28:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, it was mainly getting out. Your plan of getting out through the shuttle is probably your best bet. Another interesting way to get to the venue is also through the aqua bus. Long Beach just started doing this Free Ride bus that covers a majority of downtown. A driver suggested to me that you can catch a ride to an aqua bus and they possibly give discounts as well for the aqua bus (don #8217;t quote me on this lol)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 02:00:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you are planning to live closer to downtown lb I recommend @aerialbutterflies on ig! They have classes inside Groundwork Fitness on Pine :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 20:57:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Valley - Miguel West Coast - Lana Del Rey Gooey - Glass Animals Two Weeks - FKA Twigs (anything by fka twigs really)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>