<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject6284</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guard cat protecting us from dangerous flying bugs</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 21:18:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 22:10:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's why what he's doing is so great #8212;someone that *is* famous using their fame to help bring attention to the issue. It serves to help the not-famous.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 22:11:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's wrong with the narrative? e: dude said something like "ITT: comments going against the narrative are being removed".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 22:14:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, but isn't it a positive that someone famous is talking about it? How is what he's doing in any way harmful to you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 22:49:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>-Michael Scott</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 23:03:23</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; it hasn't helped at all. I'm as invisible as I ever was. That's why he's doing it. If you're mad that it isn't happening fast enough, that's because he's the only one speaking out against it. Give it time. Support the cause. It's beyond me why you'd be complaining about this. Best case scenario, more attention is brought to the issue. Worst case scenario, you're exactly where you are now. It really feels like you're complaining for the sake of complaining. Nothing at all about what he's doing is in any way a negative for you. I'm truly sorry you're a victim. But complaining about those advocating for people like you on a public forum only serves to encourage victims to remain silent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 19:30:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Po9Z5yr9aU4</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 04:43:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://media.giphy.com/media/5xtDarDFtx1uQhOC44E/giphy.gif</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 07:03:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can literally open the door to my balcony and hit Aldi with a rock so I go there for quite few items. Milk, eggs, rice, their fiber one knock-offs, and their red bull knock off are all good. However, their produce, bread, and their meats are complete dogshit. I bought a pack of processed turkey for sandwiches that's completely inedible. I also got one of those "heat and serve" packs of meat, which normally are delicious from HEB, that tasted like it was created in someone's basement lab. Overall though, I love ALDI. The last time I was there the cashier even bagged my groceries for me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 15:59:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I'm American. I've noticed a lot of their stuff is made somewhere in Illinois so that may be the difference/problem. Not that there's necessarily anything wrong with Illinois, just that Aussie Aldis likely have better sources.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 01:11:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The wife and I typically don't leave the house on weekends except when I venture out to gather supplies (food/beer). We day drink, eat food of questionable quality, and watch baseball or catch-up on the DVR. I'm ashamed to admit that I typically only shower if I have something to do or if she agrees to blow me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 14:15:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://old.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/8wc343/lady_killer/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 15:11:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same. I was on the cusp of spending north of $100 for a gigantic teddy bear that would no doubt tie this room together but the chance someone might hollow it out and hide inside to scare me is the one and only deal breaker.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 16:58:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>do you look like a thai version of JD?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 18:09:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://youtu.be/vZTUf7TD8lw?t=1m17s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 19:06:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>YES I'M STILL ON THE PRINGLES THING</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 19:18:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or way over head. rip</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 19:19:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>So what like, you just walk your flat-tire-having bike back up the mountain with your bloody knees all full of pebbles?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 19:37:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah that makes sense</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 03:14:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know you're looking for vet advice here but I think you should take him to get checked out. Our male cat started peeing outside of the box and testing revealed struvite crystals as the cause, meaning they weren't getting enough water. We always knew they loved drinking water from cups left on the coffee table so we purposely put out a cup of water for them, which lead to leaving a tupperware bowl for them, to now having a giant glass bowl of water for the cats on our coffee table. Could be anecdotal but he hasn't had an issue in over a year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 04:34:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't bought a lemon since</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 03:52:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that's the plan. I hope so, anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 18:43:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Another classic from the same era: [Group X - Johnny Poo Poo Pants](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s7U0aLk5Js4)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 05:06:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed, there's no way that's their house. Her parents seem like they have more money than that, plus they were eating on paper plates and plasticware. Seems like they knew shit was gonna go down so they told them not to bust out actual plates or wine glasses glasses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 07:34:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just raised both of my arms into the air to ensure I wasn't having a stroke</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 07:41:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Imagine if it had arms</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 06:12:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Diagnosed at 33. The drugs are awesome and do exactly what they should, however, I don' take them because while my ADHD is a mild hindrance to my life I enjoy my brain as-is. It sucks for when I need to study or when someone is telling me something important, but the other 99% of the time it's like a fucking constant stimulus-seeking fest and it makes me funny and personable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 03:46:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was taking 50mg of Vyvanse and it made me a fucking mute. I hated it. I did try taking the capsule apart and taking less of the meds, which did help, but honestly it still has such an impact on my personality I'd rather just deal with having to use other techniques to study. It helps that the education I'm getting now is a specific medical career that I find infinitely fascinating so the ADHD isn't too bad. Just takes me a while to get settled. I still re-read things several times before it sinks it but whatever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 21:41:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Many years ago my dad gave my dog a t-bone steak bone (cooked) as we'd always done. At 4am she woke me up puking. Then again at 5, 6, and 7am. I thought she was just sick so when I took her outside at 7 to pee I googled it and it basically said "TAKE YOUR DOG TO THE VET IDIOT" so I did. X-rays showed she had a giant, triangular piece of bone shard stuck in her stomach. Vet suggested I feed her cotton balls to wrap around the bone so she could pass it. Easier said than done, but it must've worked because she's still alive 9 years later.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 07:54:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL I'm vegan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 16:54:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Same.](https://imgur.com/TywhJ83) I'm liking DeMar_DeSpurzan</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Did Andrei approve this first???</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 22:40:52</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 05:24:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sent it to my wife with no context and she shit her pants</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 06:03:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty sure 3 is Jorge</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 02:16:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love this comment so much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 04:10:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're on demand with comcast</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 04:11:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>My wife accidentally found 2 episodes on demand through our cable provider. I think they're early releases</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 04:14:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My handsome Buddy</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 16:56:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 10:17:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; When they are directed to Rosa Parks their asses Fucking hilarious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 12:06:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude's a fucking lyrical genius. It's crazy that he pulled that out of his ass right there, in the same conversation where he addresses failing the 9th grade twice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A young Dave Matthews stimming before a show</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 04:09:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 22:00:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.criminaldefenselawyer.com/legal-advice/criminal-defense/drug-charges/jail-selling-fake-drugs.htm https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Counterfeit_illegal_drug_selling#Legal_status</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 22:31:19</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; if he recieved the oregano from someone else We're talking about selling oregano to people that think it's weed. No one said anything about receiving oregano so I don't know what you're talking about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 23:46:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm no lawyer but having a bunch of individual baggies of oregano on your person would seem like enough to charge you with a crime. Just like having 1oz. of pot in one bag looks like your personal stash but 1oz. divvied up between several bags looks like intent to distribute.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 23:57:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I knew a dude who got busted for "intent to distribute" for having 3 baggies of 1 gram each. Obviously, he was intending to distribute, but he wasn't caught in the act. This is a very different crime than possession of 3 grams of marijuana. Point being, they don't have to watch you doing it to charge you with the crime.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 00:31:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I made it all up. Good talk. All the best to you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 19:42:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mom dicks used to be bigger in the 80s and 90s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 22:38:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah man, I wish I could go back and un-see it just so I could watch it with fresh eyes. It's so good. You're in for a treat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 23:22:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, you used "black market" because that's what it's called. I have no idea why someone would think that makes it sound sinister.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 23:26:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Common sense says people too poor to afford baby formula/food don't steal it. Just like every other state, [Florida offers WIC](http://www.floridahealth.gov/programs-and-services/wic/). There is help for the poor. Breaking the law because you're poor doesn't make it okay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I just wanted a magnet for my phone</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 20:31:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 04:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>You disgust me. I like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 04:38:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Andy Dwyer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 02:46:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember that case. Ruling handed down by the honorable judge Nana Nabooboo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 02:57:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>This backfired on me. Lived in downtown Houston, had a pickup, they busted the door lock and stole a $50 CD player. Decided not to fix the door lock since that was the most valuable thing in the truck. A week later they incapacitated the truck by trying to steal it Terminator style with a screwdriver.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 05:38:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>A lot of your personal info is visible, fyi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 17:28:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qEGFaOeUm2A</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 23:26:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Luckily, there are Chrome extensions that'll [automatically tag these people](https://imgur.com/lCbXwel) so you can avoid arguing with them entirely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>On a video of Tom Segura and Joe Rogan talking about Louis</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 04:44:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 04:53:52</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Fuck christina p Did she say something recently?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 05:27:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>The context in which Tom used 'retard' *wasn't* making fun of disabled people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 05:44:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. Apologize.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[TOMT] old iPhone game</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 21:37:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You #8217;re a small, triangular jet avoiding colored blocks by tilting the phone left and right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 23:06:56</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Cubefield Yes! Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 05:15:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you OP?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 05:58:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah it was a super cute photo but there #8217;s lots of creepers out there, unfortunately.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 06:17:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s a reference to Your Mom #8217;s House podcast.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"Man Smells Glue." Oil on canvas. 547x894</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:13:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:59:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not new. I found it on a backup of one of my phones from 2014. It was my background for a while.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:00:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m asking $1/download to fund my cat food needs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:36:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have my blessing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:44:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I found this years ago on reddit but I #8217;m pretty sure [this](https://www.deviantart.com/annarcase/art/Updated-Charlie-Kelly-188578708) is the original artist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:22:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>[already got one](https://i.ytimg.com/vi/XNyUALnj8V0/hqdefault.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:09:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everybody's doing it though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:51:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>A man's gotta sleep</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:38:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>[here's the original](https://www.deviantart.com/annarcase/art/Updated-Charlie-Kelly-188578708)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:44:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am a strong independent man who don't need no man but [she painted it](https://www.deviantart.com/annarcase/art/Updated-Charlie-Kelly-188578708)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>