<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject1786</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-02 19:30:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice pictures.  #128077; #127996;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 21:56:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much, you don't understand how much I appreciate you sharing. Much love!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-30 22:03:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right? I figured. But I am looking into switching doctors/clinics because this isn't a one time thing with injections that I have pain/bruises whether it's blood work or shots. Thank you for sharing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 22:33:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post is me in a nutshell. :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 03:39:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have the straightest teeth, love your smile. You look stunning.  #9829; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-27 00:02:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looking for (2) 3 day GA passes before tonight maybe would be great thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 05:17:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still for sale, lmk looking to buy one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 05:19:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>ALL SET THANKS FOR REPLIES!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-29 17:40:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>The smell of fresh cut grass is the best.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[skin concern] Bug spray ruining my skin but I desperately need it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 14:39:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey everyone, I'll keep this as short as possible. Before vacation my chest area was smooth and soft, but now that I'm vacationing in Puerto Rico for the rest of this week until Monday since last Friday and I've noticed: very textured almost developing into a sandpaper feel on my chest with small bumps, spraying on my back and chest literally feels like it's burning my skin, and even with the bug spray on I keep itching where there isn't any mosquito bites. I need bug spray due to the humidity and plenty of mosquitos just floating around that already completely bit my calves. I can't even enjoy my vacation due to the burning and how I can feel my once soft chest become all rough and very sensitive to even touch to how much it feels like it's burning. I've been using OFF with 20% DEET and applied aloe Vera to soothe but to no prevail. I have a feeling I might have developed an allergy even though it's been a few days but the amount I'm applying is probably a couple times a day because areas we are mostly in (forest, rivers, beaches) contain the most mosquitos here in PR. Any advice will be great, I'm desperate to end this burning sensation and feel my last resort may be going to the hospital here in PR if it continues. Thanks so much in advance. TL;DR: Vacationing in tropical island for about 10 days , tons of mosquitoes, before vacation skin was normal and soft, after use of 20% DEET OFF on skin for first few days skin is now burning, itching, has rough sandpaper texture, hypersensitive to touch and water.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 05:42:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everyone is definitely right, I should've been more careful but excitement got the best of me and I'll pay the consequence for it. Thank you for answering, very appreciated and much love.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-07 02:28:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would say it's a 8/10, it felt like my septum around the same pain as that. But tbh, the initial pain is a really hard pinch/poke feel. But It's the after getting them pierced pain that hurts the most. Still feeling it and it's been a couple weeks. Everyone is different though, good luck.  #128129; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 03:47:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>If he's from the tent that was all the way up by the monument, they're legit. Had one around 5 and I'm still feeling the effects. Wish I got the name though. :\</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 04:18:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm pretty sure he had some, and then had a few other like chocolate chip and fudge brownie. If it was in a black box that he was carrying around out it's legit.  #128129; #127995;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-29 16:20:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>PM the code for Boston pleaseeeee.  #128557; #128557; #128149;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-19 18:31:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>WHY BOSTON GOTTA BE DIFFICULT.  #129318; #127995; #8205; #9792; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-01 21:24:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>ID on boots though? Love the fit btw.  #128293;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 14:55:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m 5 ft, literally about to camp for the front today because I agree there is room in the back but when you #8217;re smaller all you see is the back of heads and a lot of the tall people swear short people will somehow make their view shitty. :\</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 14:25:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOOKING for: General tent camping for the low. Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 22:43:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Promoters and ambassadors, hit me up about savings please! Looking to buy (2) 3 day wristbands and (2) shuttles from BK!  #128578;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 04:10:02</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128587; #127995; #8205; #9792; #65039; #127881;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Question about Post Office?!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 14:53:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey everyone, so I was looking at the map in the firefly app and found in the center map a  #8220; post office  #8220; tent. It #8217;s right next to the  #8220; lost and found  #8220; tent. My question is are we able to receive mail here? I forgot a vital piece of my site and would have it amazon prime there if I #8217;m able to do so. (I KNOW ITS LAST MINUTE, please don #8217;t be a dick about it when I #8217;m already kicking myself about it. )Thank you, and see you all soon!  #9996; #127996; #127752; #127803; #127774; #128578;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 15:12:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looking for lighting with no electricity source (general camping here) . We got all the camping gear but then realized we #8217;re left in the dark when we didn #8217;t buy any sort of lighting. :\ for whatever reason, anything solar powered here where we are is sold out or too dim that it #8217;s not worth the purchase.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 18:54:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for all the advice everyone! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 22:21:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>THANK YOU FOR THIS, honestly you saved me from overheating right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 03:12:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pay more for Wednesday camp, a lot of the good vibes and parties were there. Camping in row 305 but no one was anywhere near being as lit as the actual 305. Neighbors were rude and did everything possible to avoid contact. Really hate that bad vibe, especially when we #8217;re all there for 5 days. We have our own drinks/food and wanted to share while making new friends but oh well. First year down, many more to go.  #129335; #127995; #8205; #9792; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 05:51:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you.  #128151;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>