<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject2949</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 12:39:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where do you see "gay boy"? it says: "Gay BCv".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 12:49:54</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;A console is just so much easier. I totally COULD build a PC, but I really don't feel like learning how to make one. But you can just look up r/buildapc and see what people are proposing and then order the parts from one shop and many shops will usually offer free assembling. If you don't like flashy shit like me then I'd just post there and ask something without leds because nowadays people are obsessed with this juvenile crap. Although many people have a opinion like you that's why I don't understand the hate on Microsoft for releasing their exclusives on a PC, people don't get that many people only care about consoles and they'll never touch these exlusives on a PC. For me exclusives form a consumer perspective is bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 13:00:31</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Personally I think the last of us. HZD and BB on their own are worth the console ownership, I rarely use mine but I feel like I got the mileage out of it even if I do play almost exclusively on my PC. What's funny is that I bought PS3 because of the hyped exclusives and either there were mediocre for me like Uncharted, Killzone or GoW3 or pretty bad like TLOU and ICO. The only exception was Little Big Planet but that game was kind of forgotten for some reason, I think there's little to none hype for their new Media Molecule IP called "Dreams". That doesn't mean I regret buying a PS3 because I collected most of the exlusives, PS3's best games aren't posted in this sub at all like all the RPG's, 3D Dot Heroes, Yakuza's - it wasn't that popular during PS3 imho like the main PS3 games, actually I didn't see any Yakuza posts here at all even during the launch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 13:04:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Explosions and big shit? most of the games have this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 23:08:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 05:32:15</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Magnuson-Moss Warranty Act  gt;  gt;a federal law governing most consumer purchases in the U.S., or various state laws. ... Even if your written warranty is voided, you may be protected by an implied warranty. We have this in Europe, mandatory warranty regulated by law, not the producer. I thought people in America are on a mercy of companies because I never saw people mentioning this law.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 14:56:59</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I am in Europe and would like to know where I can find this law in case it ever comes up. Thanks! I think each country has individual law but it's a directive from EU which each EU partner has apply in their law.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 14:52:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Therapies don't work anyway, it's just a scam.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 21:10:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, just bought 100k copies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 21:10:35</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Now this I can fap to I fapped 3 time arleady, oh well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 21:11:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey you! stop you criminal cum!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 21:12:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>DAE ENJOYED FALLOUT 4 OR I AM ALONE ON THIS PLANET!?!?!?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 21:23:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Makes me want drop Oysters and buy more VEN but at the same time I believe bear market just started and I'll buy VET cheaper later.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 22:11:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking about something like this in my dreams. Driving a Tesla with hooked up mini PC and Nintendo on the front and on the passenger seats PS4 and Xbox X</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 22:17:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://i.imgur.com/RLfRtFt.jpg Exactly how it works in "Cultures 2", although I couldn't find a photo of repairing. The graphics still look beautiful, the music is gives me chills and the voice acting is awesome at least in my language. The game also is perfect for casuals because the gameplay isn't overcomplicated like most strategy games.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 22:20:44</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; The bear market JUST started? What #8217;s been happening while a lot of cryptos have lost 80-90% between January and now? Like in 2014, Just a warmup, imagine Bitcoin being for 1-3k$ most altcoins selling for much less than now and people posting on crypto subs once every few days. There's still to much traffic in crypto for my taste and people are still to optimistic that bull market is behind the corner, of course anything is possible so we should cost averaging so we won't stuck with a dick in our hand missing the train.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 22:28:13</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Not going to happen again. Crypto is going mainstream. Slowly, but surely. Hopefully not because I think I'm good on my investments and my Oyster might be completely killed by a longer bear but I got some spare cash left just in case we'll get even bigger discounts, I'm prepared for every scenario cost averaging on each huge drop. Also now the bull would help our Vechain because after the Vthor imagine how much spike would Vechain get if the whole market was on buying spree. I could imagine Vechain would be arleady top 5 if they annouced the partnerships during a bull market instead of January bear market.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 22:33:45</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Definitely need that Ledger support, I feel more comfortable when my funds are in an offline wallet. After the swap I'll have to remove any trace of crypto on my computer myself because I feel that every day I play with fire keeping crypto stuff on my daily PC.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 22:36:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>What went wrong?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 22:36:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't remember much actually, maybe because this even didn't work for me so I really never used it or actually I think I used it to play HoMM III only but the client was weird as fuck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:18:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Story of my dick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:20:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Banano*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 23:41:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate USA for all the cool things they have there nowhere to be found in Europe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 01:39:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I made post about this before but I think nobody was interesting so I'll write it here again: If you want use this wallet as a "Desktop" one then you can install an android emulator like "Nox" on PC, I myself couldn't install Vechain app on my phone because for some reason it doesn't run on Kitkat and even the emulators are running on Kitkat but you can upgrade Nox one. I think this way may be even more secure than a real desktop wallet because if you get infected the virus won't simply find your wallet.dat if it's on your virtual machine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>NANO Developer Update: 7/16/18</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 03:29:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 03:38:12</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; That made me think of something, this might be big investors that has not been accepted as one of the 101 authority nodes and just said fuck it and sold everything. But even if that is the case, wouldnt it be more clever to wait and sell at higher prices? Of course but I imagine that there are also very wealthy people like sheiks that wouldn't make a difference for them since they spend that kind of money on a daily basis for stupid shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 03:40:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>[So you're telling me there's a chance](https://i.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/newsfeed/000/840/283/350.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 03:45:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's funny how I'm down a lot with VEN but up 26% with a 350 rank token, I think I'll run to my bank today and I'll just double my stack for a quarter of the price I paid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:00:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>That picture nicely describes the feminist starterpack https://i.imgur.com/HqvXCan.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:02:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>G-force hits my g-spot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:03:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like my dick that wasn't taken out for that long too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:04:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does it smellz?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:04:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>69/69</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 04:07:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You just discovered how media manipulation works, genius!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>NANO Developer Update: 7/16/18</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 12:41:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 13:39:13</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; What's equally interesting is that the buying support is extremely strong. 500k VEN sold, and the price barely moved. There's a lot people that want to get in an it's the top 20 coin so it would be bad if Vechain got destroyed by that transaction because it's arleady very low in comparison to this year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 13:40:47</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I Dont see why advertisement need to be storage decentralized. Look at Torrents. Many people get fucked by copyright lawsuits. Piratebay owner got busted, hence that's why the main PRL dev remains anonymous, when shit hits the fan he won't be arrested, won't be bothered if users gonna upload shady shit there. So far they make progress and the coin almost was heading at ICO price which was 0.06c: https://etherscan.io/token/0x1844b21593262668b7248d0f57a220caaba46ab9#tokenInfo I think this sub needs infos about lower market cap coins with pontential like these because when something hits the front page the coin arleady is rank 100.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 15:25:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dunno, the sub looks pretty stagnant so I'm just chiping in the news I read, you can add something else if you want to keep the sub going.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 15:38:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>If the project will be finished then it's a good alternative for download copyrighted content depending on the download speed it will provide because in some countries you'll get a fine if Internet provider will see that you download illegal content.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 16:00:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't get excited that after the swap you'll double your money because you never know, it all depends mostly what Bitcoin will do, now it pumped a little, might happen it's gonna dive another 1-2k$ down and some people begin the sell offs and we'll end up bellow 1$. I bought in Jan for 4$ and then later averaging at 7$ I was betting that the odds are that shit gonna hit the fan but bought anyway because it might be a flash of a moment and the price might end up much higher. I bought some other coins a week ago at the bottom, gonna buy more if there will be another bottom and I should be good if I didn't invested in the next dot com bubble at the end of its life, but it's good to take a shot at opportunities anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 16:08:28</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Please tell me how is Vechain overvalued when EOS which has nothing at all has 5x Ven's market cap. Or any other top4-1000 coin. Gullible people are more willing to put all their cash in these projects and bring others to it, What Bitconnects market cap rank was? I think it was like the top 20? or something? Marketing and gullible people are the gold mine, most of Vechain investors probably diversify their investments so we won't end up with mega pump to the top 5 and each fail will cost us a rank or 2 in the marketcap like Waltonchain got destroyed for a while because of that fake contest where Tron is still rank 11 after all the fud.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>That coin looks promising, what do you guys think?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 16:26:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 16:27:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will it be on Binance?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 20:18:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure whats the upside using smaller exchanges, Even on Kucoin I waited forever to fill my order on LTC and isnt it the biggest exchange after Binance?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 20:22:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exchanges are the weakest links of crypto, you have to buy crypto somewhere but the fees are eating any pros of investing in it if you want to buy something for it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 21:50:32</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; He #8217;s so proud of himself Not really, he just sneezed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 22:48:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://i.warosu.org/data/biz/img/0077/06/1518799237965.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 01:14:05</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; he actually bought raiblocks right after selling his LTC The same kind of thing I did but during a longer period of time, first I bought LTC back in 2013 then after a long break I bought Vechain and the start of 2018 and a week ago bought xrb. The Vechain investment is more investing in the company than the crypto itself where with nano is investing in the crypto itself. I hold only few bucks in Bitcoin that are leftovers from actually using it to buy stuff after Paypal banned me and stole my money.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>That new institutional money really got out of hand</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 01:24:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 01:29:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Absolutely. But most people aren't doing that.  gt;  gt; I'm always amazed how many portfolios posted here don't even include BTC.  gt;  gt; "My alts can gain so much more than that dinosaur BTC!"  gt;  gt; ....we'll see about that. You really have to invest in risky shit to not being able to profit from alts. From the top 100 even Vechain got out of the sell walls right now that is heavilly manipulated but it's a matter of time when he'll outpace other coins when the swap will be done with. If you want a sure profit then many top 100 that have anything unique to offer shouldn't let you down, the low cap coins should be your smallest investment if you want minimum risk but it's worth to throw a penny or 2 in a promising early project.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can I "upgrade" my Steem reward?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 02:15:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I arleady took the reward but I'm debating to buy Steem so I wonder if I'll be able to "upgrade" my reward, if yes then I just should do the same steps as when getting the reward for the first time?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 02:17:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ripperoni in Bananoni Bitcoinoni.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 02:19:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Goldman Sachs fomoing hard in our Banano. Thanks for the 1.8 million tip, I'll buy a yellow lambo for that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>8999 wins</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 16:04:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hot Busty Girl Creampied</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 16:19:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 18:42:54</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Or sold at $1.9 and fomo back in when it goes to $2 and lose part of track. Trading is soooooo easy in hindsight. There are people that aren't bullish on Vechain and entered only to make quick flip, even if they bought at 1.9$ and the price wouldn't come back for some time then there's minimum risk that the price will never come back so it's a perfect coin for flips.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[nsfw]The girl if you tell her you invested in Banano before it was bellow 69$ in the future.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 19:28:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 19:31:46</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Wall Street : Bitcoin Is The best Bet For Crypto Investors That's good to hear because that means it's the opposite what they're saying. Super bull run incoming on alt coins?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sensual Teen Masturbation</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 19:43:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sensual Teen Masturbation</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 20:10:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 20:14:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Oh man just thinking about that, binance headlining the switch, new 2 cent token... I hope for the best but something tells me they gonna postpone the swap, price will drop like a mohterfucker where other coins gonna pump by 100%.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 23:56:23</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I am pretty sure he is going to FOMO and buy back in later once the prices are high again. Smart traders do the opposite of dumb traders, such is life, we can't fix that. What if now is high?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 00:00:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Vertcoin! lol I can't be the only one holding on to it still? Of course not, there's a fuckton of bagholders of various coins - PRL, PPC, FTC, NMC, NVC and fuckton more, they're forgotten along with the shillers. Buying atlcoins is a risy game, soon new bagholders might be created with their bag of VEN, NANO, BAT, SIA, TRX, ICX, LISK and whatever is heavilly shilled at this moment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 00:04:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vechain.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 18:16:03</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;OCE total valuation will be 15 million VET and the total supply will be 10 billion OCE. 30% of the token will be issued in the Private Round and VeChain Community Round. In the private sale the token price is 1 VET = 800 OCE (There is a 6-months Lockup period) and the VeChain Community Round will be 1 VET = 730 OCE. People are giving you money for free and you segregate them giving your buddies more tokens, nice scam, fuck off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 18:23:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>A tattoo for a short term fad...it's small at least so removing of it won't be a hassle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Biggest Titanic sink in the history of Crypto.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 04:09:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 04:44:04</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I've personally been loading up on bcc. Good choice sir.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 06:52:16</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; what happens if ETF isn't approved?? Buy some lube then.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 14:06:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>You became a meme on 4chan: http://is2.4chan.org/biz/1532052843594.png congratulations.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 14:35:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>My only tip is to invest in known non-shilled cryptos like XMR and you should do good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 15:43:22</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Right now still seems quite early My rule is, if it's on reddit saying "xxx in the top!" then it's arleady too late, so far it checked out with NEO, NANO, kind of Vechain because it stopped growing when it was an ultra shilled on reddit in January but after a month it kept growing again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Vechain inside trading continues.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 16:23:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 19:51:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didn't help, price still all time low this year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>One Year Anniversary and X Node Binding Lottery Event  #8212; Steemit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 19:55:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>BOGGED</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 20:58:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This guy opened my eyes unironically.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 21:19:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 23:56:56</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Just a friendly reminder, never put your life savings into high risk assets. If won't put all my life savings then I'll never gonna make it anon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 00:22:28</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I'm not sure what you are trying to say, That he should just send his tokens from his MEW wallet to Vechain app wallet a.k.a. doing a "manual swap".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 01:40:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>So they force people to use an exchange to take part in lottery?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The China Hustle</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 02:31:13</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 02:36:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bought at 13c, it's my comfiest hold because at this moment Oyster is among the worst scams in cmc rank, just look what coins are before Oyster.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 04:25:12</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Been warning people about this scam since damn well near the top, actually. We'll see how it's a scam when they gonna upgrade the upload size next week, you probably come up with an excuse anyway, if you didn't notice the post was autoremoved so I reuploaded it on my second account elsewhere.  gt;Also, our community should expect to see a significant increase in file upload size by mid next week.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 05:03:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just planning to invest in Monero and the reason why I chose it because as far as I know they use Monero to buy dope on darknet and to do wash trading, in most cases I prefer newer projects but Monero will be my oldest coin because it doesn't matter if it's fast or cheap, all it matters it's proven to be secure to buy illegal stuff. I think it's the Bitcoin as it should be, what's else good that nobody is talking about this coin, nobody is shilling or at least I didn't see and nobody is hating it, I think it's a hidden gem that is the safest hold, privacy wise and value wise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 05:09:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't really bother to argue with you and don't really care "defending" this token on the Internet as I only bought it at 13c for 130 bucks so whatever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 14:24:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's more: [MIA KHALIFA - NERDY FAN GETS TO LOSE HIS VIRGINITY TO THE #1 PORNSTAR](https://www.pornhub.com/view_video.php?viewkey=ph5b2d08f754f78) Go watch and fuck off and get blocked loony.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 14:49:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it will correct to 6000$ then it will be 49800, good deal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 14:52:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm for the money and memes, mostly for the memes because I don't believe in the next bull run at least for the shit I hold.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 15:05:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's the explanation that BCH is on the 4th place in market cap? people are hating it like XRP or EOS but ironically these coins are in the top, it feels like people hate it because they missed the train because I never saw someone shitting on for example a rank 50 coin, somehow the worst coins are the top5 coins.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 15:24:44</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Ever heard of the word HODL? Our lodr and saviour.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I invested 1k$ in VEN and NANO, am I gonna make it reddit?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 15:40:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 16:16:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>This month, NANO at 2.25$ and VEN at 1.86$</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 16:25:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It should be at least 100 MB so at least you can use it for something. If it's 1GB then shit might shake things up but I think that would be a miracle if they made such progress or maybe it's part of the hype and they made 5 MB on purpose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In new month you get deranked by your max rank or current rank?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 22:14:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I got rank 4 but deranked to 5 then will the stars count from my max rank achieved in the next month which is rank 4 or from the current rank 5?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-22 22:16:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 06:02:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait for the bull market and let the magic happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 22:07:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now try point with it at cops, I promise you that nothing bad will happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Guy just added me to talk shit about my deck after a loss LOL</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 00:41:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 00:45:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're an idiot. Don't expect being treated good when you talk shit about other people after adding them LOL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 00:50:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Guy lost like a chump, added me to a friend list and talked shit about me and I'm the idiot? wooow bro, nice joke LOL maybe it was you LOL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 01:02:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Guy knows shit about the meta, wild is so greedy that 30% of the time I just win just by surprise milling these decks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 01:13:31</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; This makes me wonder how people who demonstrate themselves to be so utterly stupid manage to get anywhere on the ladder in this game.  gt; Is it really a case of just netdecking and having so much time on their hands as opposed to actual intelligence and skill?  gt; And yes I'm talking about you. What should I do? pat the next friend add rager and say it's okay to cry? fuck that I'm fed up with these rage idiots arleady.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 01:36:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about buying at 15k, selling at 10k when it dropped to 6k$?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 02:12:37</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; god of war, Bloodborne, uncharted, infamous, horizon zero dawn and many more. There is no "many more" you basically named them all, at least for the casual audience.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 03:21:44</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Persona 5 Not an exlusive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 14:01:44</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; It is also on ps3, so I guess I can't argue with that, but it's still a Sony exclusive. That's not how exclusives work, people also say that Xbox exclusives aren't exclusives because it's on PC.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 16:05:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not adressing anything else because it's not worth commenting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Friend add rager part 2 - Challenge accepted</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 17:23:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 17:29:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm ice cold killa, ice cold, bro.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 17:43:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I ain't fucking around with pussies, some bum in real life pissed me off the other day and I fucked him up, fucked him up good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 18:52:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>You think I give a shit, for me most of you are just pansies, all I care to have like 100 comment karma because otherwise I would be locked out of some subs. It's funny how much of you are butthurt, I bet you do the same shit and rage add people after you lose like a chump and talk shit about someone's playing skills ironically being the same rank as the guy you lost to, pathetic cockroaches.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 18:57:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>QuarkChain, the name reminds me of an old coin "Quarkcoin", long time dead shitcoin, this is how 99% of these coins gonna end up, pretty sad stuff when you enter some of the subreddits and you see posts spammed by some of the left survivors that are still deluded that their coin is going anywhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 19:04:39</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I always thought it was just a meme ;) It...it isn't?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 19:07:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>People say there's something wrong with me, guess what - I passed psych exams for the law enforcement, if I pass the police school then I'm soon to be a cop :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 22:28:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jeez, can MEW be more fucked by hackers than this? it seems it's more dangerous to use MEW than the shittiest of exchanges, sooner or later it seems the site will be gone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 22:34:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>When the Vechain dream went too far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:03:47</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; This is about metamask, not MEW... That is used to connect to MEW....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 23:16:03</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; It can be used without mew and has little to do with MEW... your ledger can be connected to MEW too. It's like blaming MEW for ledger nano S problems In that case ok, I thought it's used mainly for MEW.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dear Sminem...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 01:59:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 08:31:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I came here to laugh, not to feel.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 08:23:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you play the perfection called Witcherino 3 then every other game feels like shit afterwards.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 08:25:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes - I'm a gaymer, no - I'm not gay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 08:26:59</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;It #8217;s what Iwata would have wanted Being imprisoned in looney's basement?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 08:28:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>You mispelled "EA SUX!" on the wall.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 08:31:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>When RGB PC is not enough and you buy RGB teeth implants.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 08:36:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>People don't do that here, there's only OG content in this sub.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 08:38:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; OP is living in the 50s-70s. Retro is popular nowadays.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 08:40:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I'm a gaymer. Yes, I hate EA. No, you can't touch my Switch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 08:44:05</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; This is one of those missions where I'm confused why people fussed so much about it. I felt it was easy compared to say, piloting a certain remote vehicle. I guess some people started playing only since this gen and aren't used to harder games, nowadays many games are just interactive movies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 11:54:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>So with 14k tps it's so far better than NANO? is it even comparable or they aim for something else than xrb?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 11:55:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is the only game you need in your life, in fact it is the only THING you need in life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 12:38:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>It seems like it's reliving it's popularity because I see streamers are playing it on Twitch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 12:39:42</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I watched dsp stream Here lies your problem, who watches that cunt anymore?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 23:10:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cool, get the fuck out tard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 23:14:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not everyone jacks off to power trip like you tard. You got it coming.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 23:36:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wrote it from my head, as much as people joke about the tech it I think I didn't see anyone who might actually saying this in a serious tone like the type of bullshit about shaking out the weak hands etc. The most I see "I'm for the memes" although that's true statement because crypto is a meme goldmine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 23:38:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ice cold bro, I cold. Have an upvote.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 23:42:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Never forgetti. I wanted to put Bitcoinnect quotes but it supposed to be a list about annoying generic shit people here say, Carlos Matos phrases are actually epic, he's my favorite meme, his quotes deserve a separate post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 23:45:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd say it's the sleeping giant but it's more like a giant put into a coma by The Bomber.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 23:47:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or saying about coordinated sell walls so whales can accumulate more of "dem cheap coins".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 01:42:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bro don't worry, I promise you you'll pick up more even at 1$ soon enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 13:11:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ponzi, Ponzi never changes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 13:14:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>They talk shit about these coins but their loved ones like NANO tanked harder than most shitcoins. Most hated coins are in the Top5, coincidence or butthurt that they missed the train?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 13:17:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>You might wait and if Bitcoin drops to 5-3k$ buy some one solid project to get even like XRM for example.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 13:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; God damn it, just when I thought we were approaching bottom you have to come and do this and fuck it all up... It's gonna take several years until all the prophets, HODL moonboys gonna disappear, I don't expect a bullrun anytime sooner where there's a lot of people expecting a bull run anytime now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 13:54:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it's going to happen then I hope you invested all your savings and took a big loan so you'll become a billionaire.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 18:09:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Too soon, it'll drop bellow 1$, screenshot dis.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 18:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe the fact that I've put my real money to ATM the other day and bought something for it instantly on ebay and in case the product wont be delivered I get my cash back no problem? Also each day I can buy the same thing for the exact same price.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 18:28:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Plot twist: They won't and he's a tard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 18:31:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least you can sell this shit when crypto dies, were gonna hold our bags forever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 18:32:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whats your roi? -99% XD rekt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 18:35:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look at mr smartpants, I hope you mortaged yourself for life if youre so sure of the mad bitcoin investment gainz in 100 days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 18:37:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>NANO for the winz, Amirite guyz??? 1000$ EOY, screencap dis.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 18:40:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now it's gonna be around tree fiddy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 12:56:39</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Why even bother coming here if you don't believe in Crypto. Spreading negativity and FUD gt; Just in case I don't wanna miss the train.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 16:12:01</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;nothing happened That's the point, nothing is happening so people are cashing out, these coins are worth shit, it's only a speculation so we need so pump amp;dump news so keep the ponzi going. Btw. the funniest thing is nothing is funny and we crying in a corner overinvested in some vaporware.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 16:22:08</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Read his comments, he had over 1.4M$ in crypto and only bought a 9% of Nano. How do you feel now? xD So now he got rekt even more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 16:24:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>And it is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 16:27:26</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; still is a bubble, needs to pop already. They don't want to hear it, they only want jerk each other because they have heavier bags than their stundent loans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 16:56:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>My fiat didn't crash 99% last year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 18:25:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>That guy from Twitter Christopher Franko is a scammer btw. he made "Franko Coin" and then dumped his stack and ran with the money, now he's with his new hustle called "Expanse Coin", beware of that scum. https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/franko/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 18:45:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish there was an email similar to crypto that you can use via client and save your seed and restore the mail inbox with all the messages whenever you are, there was something similar but you couldn't register with that email name on any site which was useless. I guess it won't happen anytime soon since you can't milk money from ICO on this idea.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 18:51:43</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Classy.. using the obscurity of history to make bogus claims. Get a life man. There was no money to be ran with at FRK. I literally burned about 200 BTC trying to make FRK work. The market just didnt want it.. at the time they wanted shit like dgc and quarkcoin and then darkcoin and doge. They didnt want a no premine, no ico, fairlaunch coin with low inflation. It's just ridiculous anyone would use FRK as project to try and assassinate my character. It's the other way around, you're using the fact that everyone forgot about the old times to push your next con artist scam, people could change their life but instead they invested in your shitcoin scam and lost all their money. It's funny how you cut any links from your previous project if you're in the clear. Whenever you'll appear in social media I'll be following you telling the truth what pos you are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 19:29:14</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Hmm, Looks only slightly sketchier than BitGrail Bitgrail is the ultimate HODL, I heard no one SODL after depositing their nano there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 00:01:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>120k$ market cap? dude it's more dead than Bitconnect, it isn't on any exchange and I doubt it's worth more than three fiddy. You own 60% of premined supply that you dumped on people that trusted this coin and people complain about these mysterious "whales" that try to manipulate the price to scoop up that "cheap" coin but in reality it's their devs dumping hard their own stack on idiots, I don't think I can be jealous of someone that had to steal from someone in the golden times of crypto just like Big Vern and other scumbags, all you had to do is work harder a little or just invest but you prefered to screw people up and cash out immediately, you probably earned less if you just did it legit way and Vern has to hide somewhere in China now. You're the reason what's wrong with many altcoins, most of them are a fast cash grab but fortunately nowadays more people are educated and many of these scams can be spotted immediately.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 02:54:54</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Fundamentals Something something sleeping giants, something something active github, something something great team, something something Asia waking up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 03:00:41</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I held 40,000 binance token from $1.60 , To 60 cents, Now your loss is a small dip in comparison to your nano loss.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 12:46:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>HEY HEY HEYYYY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 12:55:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are you smoking? what few more weeks? did I miss some news? 64gb will NEVER happen, let alone for 0.01$, you people are dellusional, you expect some literal free vaporware, cryptofucks are getting more delusional each dip, do you think they will cast all the free space out of their asses for free with a magic wand?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 12:59:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/92l1ph/shitt_reddit_says/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 18:03:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit I always cringe from these shitty Tinder catch lines. Yes OP you peaked like a beta cuck you are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 18:40:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>What bear?! Bull is around the corner bro!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 20:38:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know some nice underground island myself, it's called a metro station.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 20:55:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like slow unconcious chicks at night.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Boys, tell me that I'm gonna make it, I'm scared.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 23:38:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 23:44:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>LEL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 23:45:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't give a shit bro, coins never should pump because they are listed on some exchange but what they offer, it's like some listing circlejerking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 12:40:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I'm not gonna make it? pls tell me that I'm gonna make it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 12:41:14</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; This 1000x 1000x EOY incoming!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 12:46:08</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Inb4 people show up to go "well where's these businesses using the blockchain?"  gt;  gt; Over $500 Bil worth of companies have already planned to switch over. Several have openly invested a large amount of money (to us, not them) into VeChain. Companies take time to migrate systems. Bright Foods for instance, who will be moving their ENTIRE system over to VeChainThor, said this will take years to complete. Billion dollar empires take time to make major moves. That doesn't mean it's not important to note that VeChain has all the adoption. I'M ALL IN ON VEN, WE'RE GONNA MAKE IT BOYS! I'VE PUT MY ENTIRE SAVINGS INTO THIS PROJECT BECAUSE I BELIEVE!!! VEN GANG! VEN GANG! VEN GANG!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 12:46:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Salty Walty detected.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 12:50:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>STEEM price also barerly moves during this bear although even during the dec bull run it only gained 6x, do you know why? is the STEEM capped somehow and it can't gain too much value?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 12:52:21</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; THIS x1000 THIS x1000 EOY? where I can buy some of THIS? is it on Binance yet?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 12:54:25</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; o 2-3 projects they truly believe in Monero, Vechain, NANO. Am I gonna make it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 12:56:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; But Dtube seems cool to me. It sucks balls, it doesn't accept my compressed videos yet you won't upload few gb's of content and the search bar doesn't even work, a random video porn website is better for hosting videos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 12:59:41</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Look at this guy over here, never heard of VeChain I have 220 VEN, gonna buy 300 more when it drops to 50 cents, am I gonna make it boys?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 13:00:16</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; When you have DNV GL as an authority master node as well as an equity investor, you know the daily users will be here soon. WERE GONNA MAKE IT VEN GANG BOYS, TO DA MUNN!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 21:52:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>LMAO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 21:55:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>2.50 here, then I sold at 10 and bought some shit that got stolen by Cryptsy, I cry vry tim to this day, better its still not to late I HAVE to make it, I dont wanna be a wage cuck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 23:36:37</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Lol looking at vet chart I'm far from salty walty. It's not like WTC dropped harder than the buildings during 9/11, fitting name.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 12:32:46</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Everyone was talking about how we were early adopters, etc, You learned a valuable lesson then: you're a dumbass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 12:34:26</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Only lost 74k once he clicks sell. It #8217;s not materialised yet. Nice coping mechanism, bro.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 12:37:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Damn bro I thought I was bad out about $2500 in and my portfolio this morning was $970 lol Look at mr. moneybags here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 12:40:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shitcoins being washed up properly, bye bye Vechain, NANO, PRL.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 12:41:14</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Accumulating. Sperm in my mouth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 12:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; bullmarket comes around The bull will come right after the wallstreet paychecks, right boys?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 12:47:11</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; A shrinking ALT market is not good It's good, more cheap better technology for us. I feel like I'm stealing at these prices!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 12:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>AHAHAHAHA REKT STELLAR ROCKET BOYS</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 14:35:20</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; When your a student at university $2500 is a lot of money I meant it in a way that some people have much bigger losses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 17:07:11</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I hold some XMR and sadly that's true. :( Why? didn't I hear some bad news about XMR?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 17:12:21</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; yeah, the post is kinda bragging on Monero's role in helping drug traffickers Drugs should be legal though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 17:17:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why Vechain got in then though?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 18:12:17</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; to be completely honest, I moved into crypto because I heard about all the volatility and crazy price movements, its a once in a lifetime opportunity to be in such a market, and people that are not here will miss out forever on the crazy things that happen.  gt;  gt; Of course I care if I loose money, but I just like the entire experience (and the stock market bored me, haha) When I heard about it in 2013 I thought that all you have to do is buy low, wait a day or two and sell high for 2x the price rinse and repeat, how wrong I was LOL In the meantime I was robbed by Cryptsy and I have to hold all over again. Lost like 50k$ from my 300$ initial investment. My advice would be: watch who is your real enemy, it might not be the bear but a faulty wallet app, hacked hardware wallet etc. and you will lose it all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 00:47:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>It dropped by 99,99% in price, it's a worse shitcoin that Bitconnect, literally.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 01:07:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wonder why though it seems everyone is planning buy a car from their crypto savings of all things, why not a chopper or a villa or a house or a business.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 01:34:28</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; It helps that I survived the 2013 - 2016 bear market without capitulating. This is very similar and could take another couple of months to blow over. But some prices are just too good. Which prices, in comparison to 2013 the prices are still overpriced, LTC back then was 50$ then dropped to 2$. Not talking about LTC that is should again drop back to 2$ but for example new coins like NANO was around 0.10$ so in correlation it should still drop around 10 times back to 10 cents.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 03:20:51</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; At least graphics cards price have gone to normal. Around $500 for GTX 1080 on Newegg, probably if not crypto a 2,5 years old card would be for like 400$. Sucks that in my country it's still 600$ which is msrp. I guess at this point I'll wait until Nvidia Volta, no way crypto will get back up by then.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 10:56:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Back in the day the big problem was wallets, when I had like 10 coins I just let it sit on Cryptsy, now many are just erc tokens that you can just keep on one adress on myetherwallet, some have nice website wallets like NANOvault and there are lighweight wallets so an exchange doesn't have to server a purpose as a wallet now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 11:04:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seriously, where I can buy Bitconnect? I'd like to buy some just for the memes. CMC says "Trade Satoshi" but it says there's 0$ volume... Also the question is where I can store it, does it have a wallet?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 11:05:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; What is bitconnect? Bitconnect was true Satoshi's vision.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 11:07:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's popular lately for some reason, I know a person did it for 3 weeks or something, friend of my friend did this too and also I saw randomly a vlog about a guy doing it like 41 days, I guess it's the new thing everyone's doing. I guess we're not trendy anymore with our crypto, gotta step up my game drop crypto and start some starving action.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 11:15:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's too high rank, Anything above top10 is out of interest to me, Monero is the highest rank coin I own, if I was here for steady small gains then I'd invest in something else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Crypto expectations.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 19:01:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Crypto expectation: August.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 19:03:37</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 19:04:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alts are dropping harder so 3k$ would be enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 23:03:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reading posts like these I'm a venture capitalist genius.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 23:25:17</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Yikes. Probably best to get out of those shit coins and into BTC. Bitcoin won't recover his losses, he needs underdogs with lower marketcap rank.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 23:28:00</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Take another loan and buy the fucking dip He'll need mere 9k$ for a Vechain strengh node, at this point 9k$ won't make him a difference.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 23:29:36</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; There are too many patronizing comments here. Remember one thing - had you benefitted from this speculation, all these folks would have been praising you. Good luck. If I couldn't afford it I would take a loan myself although I wouldn't buy right after when crypto went 1000's of %</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 23:32:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember warning some guy on reddit right after NEO starting making GAS to not buy Neo when it went on such bull run and the news arleady were on a front page, right after that it was downhill from there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 23:35:45</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; The retards who do stuff like this always do this at the top. Because at the beginning they always say it's too late, until the third time where it really might be too late.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 23:37:14</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; At least you're young enough to recover. If you decide to try it once more, don't buy Kwatts. Good luck I dunno, I'd prefer to be old enough to not give a shit about debts anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 23:39:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>4chan arleady are laughing their ass off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to secure seeds on your computer</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 13:53:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://truecrypt.ch - make sure the mid5 checks out and don't use TC 7.2 it's a hacked by CIA version. 1. After installing go to Volumes. 2. Create a container. 3. Standard. 4. Select location. 5. AES/Whirpool encryption should be enough. 6. Choose how heavy is your crypto stuff. 7. Choose a complex password . 8. Do as the TC says. 9. Make multiple copies on a USB stick, phone and whatever you like. There are other programs that are constantly updated like Veracrypt. Personally I used Diskcryptor along Truecrypt but someone told me Diskcryptor isn't safe so I dunno. You can also encrypt your whole disk but without a container it won't be reliable because you'll have to decrypt your disk each time you want to use your computer anyway so a container is important, when you'll get a virus the attacker will need your password for the container to get hands on your seeds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Damn buying Opp</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 15:15:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 15:18:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>You shouldn't open it all the time and the point is that you would probably find out before opening the container that you're infected when a hacker will try to access your social media, antivirus will catch something or your computer will be working funny, I don't think you can't notice your computer is infected.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 15:21:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn buying Opp.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 15:23:23</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; So $2900 could be the new $160. That's great, we found the bottom! DAMN BUYING OPP</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 15:25:05</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Bottom line: no clear winner yet, not even BTC or ETH Vechain and NANO are the underdogs. You heard it here first, screencap dis.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 15:26:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>100 Vechain is 0.90$/100VET, damn buying Opp</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 15:28:13</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; This bear market is about to end. All the signs are there. Just like few months ago, sure bud, just wait for the wallstreet paychecks and Asia waking up right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 15:31:41</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Losing 80% of $1,000 sucks but losing 80% of $50,000 can really fuck up the average retail investor and are in no way the same experience, You hit the nail on the spot, back then people were losing their lunch money, now they aren't losing even their money seeing post of that guy that took 100k$ loan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 15:33:05</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Todays crash was because of overspeculation. You're forgetting about beeeeeeeeeeeeconeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeect that was like in top 15, about Asia, India FUD, about Tether FUD about Bitgrail scam, Binance had some issues on top of that and they went offline for a week. I shit even myself at the start of 2018 and I seen some shit before, I didn't know if I should tether up that might go out of business any moment or should I hold my bags, I ran from Kuckcoin because it lagged like shit and funds were disappearing right to Binance that was attacked or something and was offline week after I migrated, shit was tense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 15:40:09</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Back in the really early days Bitcoin had the stink of the dark web and hackers and hitmen. Good ol' days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 15:41:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Not if you were DCA #8217;ing Transfering additional cash as we speak to buy that dumping VET.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 15:42:41</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; That's pretty naive to be honest, but you do you. I was never hacked in my life, I often check my running processes in task manager, use ESET and scan computer with antimalware when I stumble upon weird software or sites. On top of that first you need a specific virus that is meant to steal your crypto seeds, most of them are just fucking up your system. Right now the most dangerous stuff are shady airdrops, swapped wallets in google store, hijacked wallet domains like MEW etc. than being robbed by a trojan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 15:49:14</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Agreed. But also alcohol. And video games, gotta play something when sitting in a bunker(my basement).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 15:50:33</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; "Damn I just lost 40% of my retirement/stock investments, better throw the remainder into a highly volatile magic internet money asset class!" said no one ever Might as well high roll on some shitcoin and get even.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 15:52:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exchanges come and go although I guess few bucks wouldn't hurt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 15:53:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Weeeee don't neeeeed no education.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 15:54:15</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; No, he's just an attention whore. He's also correct, but even a blind pig finds the occasional truffle. Wasn't it him who invented "Mega Coin" that was in the top in 2013 and now it's in the shitter?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>HODLD</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 23:59:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Where I can buy and store Bitconnect? [serious]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 14:09:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bitconnect is a big part of crypto history and I'd like to hold few Bitconnects just for shits and giggles, is there a safe non-malware wallet that I can put them on or they were only storable on their site or something? is there an exchange that I buy it on? CMC says it's on Trade Satoshi but the volume is 0$.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 17:03:03</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Pretty sure the chain is dead, who would keep it alive? It's not: https://chainz.cryptoid.info/bcc/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 17:09:57</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Haha look at that, 134 peers. Well, good luck in getting a few. That means the transaction will take forever?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 23:42:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Redmi Note 5 Pro has Snapdragon 636 and it costs 200 bucks. Comparing a closed system of course is pointless because they can optimize it to the fullest but it's a cool indicator how far phones have went.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:50:55</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Nobody wants to take profits because they might lose those theoretical extra profits. What profits? you're only in profit if you bought yesterday and you're like -50% if you bought a month ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:52:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>VET. Ayy lmao the China Hustle continues.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:55:06</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Alright genius tell me what I need to buy now?! Vechain and NANO. VET will be 1$ in a few years and NANO 100$. Buy half of this and half of this for few thousands $ and you will be a millionaire.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 18:52:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was at my local library the other day, and I saw Sunny Lu. I went up and said hi to him, with my book in hand, and what he said was startling. "WHY YOU READ THERMODYNAMICS BOOK, ROUND EYES? YOU MUST STUDY BLOCKCHAIN TO CONTRIBUTE TO VERESEARCH. WE GLOBAL BLOCKCHAIN RESEARCH TEAM." At this point I'm just thinking, what the fuck, so I try to play it cool and say, "Blockchain's pretty cool, but engineering is my passion." At this point I could tell he was not happy. He looked straight into my eyes, and immediately did a fierce karate kick into my genitals. So I'm sitting on the floor, rolling around in pain, and the dude starts removing books from the library shelves. He literally rips the barcodes off each one, and starts throwing them at me, repeating for each one: "NOT SECURED BY A GLOBAL LEDGER. NOT SECURED BY A GLOBAL LEDGER." I finally start to get up to run away, and he spits in my face and walks away laughing at the top of his lungs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 18:53:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was at my local library the other day, and I saw Sunny Lu. I went up and said hi to him, with my book in hand, and what he said was startling. "WHY YOU READ THERMODYNAMICS BOOK, ROUND EYES? YOU MUST STUDY BLOCKCHAIN TO CONTRIBUTE TO VERESEARCH. WE GLOBAL BLOCKCHAIN RESEARCH TEAM." At this point I'm just thinking, what the fuck, so I try to play it cool and say, "Blockchain's pretty cool, but engineering is my passion." At this point I could tell he was not happy. He looked straight into my eyes, and immediately did a fierce karate kick into my genitals. So I'm sitting on the floor, rolling around in pain, and the dude starts removing books from the library shelves. He literally rips the barcodes off each one, and starts throwing them at me, repeating for each one: "NOT SECURED BY A GLOBAL LEDGER. NOT SECURED BY A GLOBAL LEDGER." I finally start to get up to run away, and he spits in my face and walks away laughing at the top of his lungs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 18:54:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It will below your mind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 00:12:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's the battery life on Redmi Note 5 Pro on stock Lineage? I heard it's like 2 hours lower, if that's the case are there programs that would make the battery life the same? also how's the compatibility with all the features, is it all good?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 00:14:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Xiaomi became the Chinese Samsung, I think Samsung is even making own cars in their mother country.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 00:28:23</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Just install a custom MIUI ROM Would just removing some apps work?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 00:42:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.banggood.com/Xiaomi-Mi-A2-Global-Version-5_99-inch-4GB-RAM-32GB-ROM-Snapdragon-660-Octa-core-4G-Smartphone-p-1325248.html?p=HY14154030419201603X amp;zf=4030419 There's a 209$ offer with a coupon "8BGA243211" if someone wants to buy that phone. I ordered Note 5 Pro 2 days ago myself and I'm mad before finding out about A2 that is 10$ more expensive and much better with stock android and upgraded processor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 00:43:53</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Just exchanged my Galaxy s8 for a Mi A2 and I have to say that it's equal parts amazing and embarrassing how I don't even feel like it's a downgrade when it comes to speed and snappiness with usual usage. Really? and why did you downgrade anyway? It's interesting, isn't S8 like 2x faster than A2? definitely there should be difference in build quality, S8 is very well finished, probably one of the best quality phones out there along with S9 that has the best display on the market. I saw a crash test and the phone passed it very well and and it was drowned in water and still worked flawlessly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 00:49:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have one of the first Xiaomi phones with Kitkat MIUI 7 and turns out after these years MIUI still has problems with music stopping. How's the LineageOS in comparison to stock Android, are there any hardware problems? can the battery last as long as on MIUI?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 03:57:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>AYY LAMO THE EARLY ADOPTION CIRCLEJERK MEME XD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 03:58:52</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; WHATAMIGONNADO?! THEN I PUT 10 THOUSAND VECHAINTHOR ON THE TABLE -YEYEYE THAT'S REAL!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 04:01:00</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Someone already beat you to it. https://whitepaper.koinster.com/ There should be rule 34 for crypto: If it exists there's a erc-20 token for it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 04:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I call it speculation I call it circlejerk meme.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 13:29:55</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; when WiFi is enabled. Otherwise it should be fine. So people actually keep Wifi on? I still have the first phone Xiaomi ever made with 2k MAH battery and I have to turn it off every time I don't use it or the phone dies withing a day and within ~3 hours if used.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why fingerprint sensors are so popular if you can bypass them?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 17:49:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>If someone steals your phone all you need is to plug it to a PC and you'll have access to all the files, so what's the catch?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 19:12:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>So you can't bypass it with any program? Maybe it's stupid question but I have low budget phone that is 4 years old.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 16:08:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I ordered 4 days ago the phone will I be able to upgrade to LineageOS 15.1 without worry?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:46:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>THE JAIL IS NOT ANYMORE AS IT USED TO BE! NO NO NO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:48:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't, it's a reasonable thing to do and don't listen the life coachers, the only thing you should remember to diversify in promising projects like Vechain, NANO, Monero etc. The market is down a ton right now, even if it drops furthermore it should bounce back again and then you're gonna retire, if not then in the worst case you're gonna wage slave for 2-3 years. It was definitely for people taking loans and buying ATH but right now we are faaar from ATH's.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:53:48</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Counter example: I took out a $50k portfolio margin loan at 2% and invested that money in Netflix shares a few years ago. I was aware of the risks, didn't overextend myself, and it turned out quite well.  gt;  gt; OP seems quite aware of the risks of taking out debt -- he clearly states he can repay the money within the year. So the "true" cost of the debt is the interest rate he's paying for a year. I think there are times when loans are justified reasonable risk, we're in the shitter right now, it might drop more, we might have years of bear ahead of us but even then at this moment the market is down enough that further drops shouldn't destroy your portfolio that much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:55:13</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Why don't you buy monthly with your savings? Bullrun is not necessarily starting any time soon, you are invested and got a lot less risk to begin with. If the bull starts it might be the last bull before the dotcom bubble burst.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 01:34:29</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; But there are also multiple projects that currently do the same thing, so it's kinda betting which one will succeed. I basically have one of each type. Supply chain: Vechain. DAG: NANO. Cloud service: Oyster. Privacy: Monero.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 13:59:47</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; The SE will not last you 5 years. You can #8217;t expect a 2016 phone with 2015 specs to last you until 2023. It doesn #8217;t work that way. A low budget phone "Xiaomi Hongmi 1S" lasted me 4 years and I still where during premiere it was arleady a slow crap, I'd still use it if not that headphone jack started losing the connection. How come an Iphone won't last me longer than a chinese beater? Is the battery much more degradable or something like that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 13:59:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>A low budget phone "Xiaomi Hongmi 1S" lasted me 4 years and I still where during premiere it was arleady a slow crap, I'd still use it if not that headphone jack started losing the connection. How come an Iphone won't last me longer than a chinese beater? Is the battery much more degradable or something like that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 14:01:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>The feedback is flawless but I'm asking just in case, I'm not really familiar with the used/refurbrished phone business so I don't know what prices should I expect especially that I'm not from US and I don't know how much locally you can get them for etc. 170$ seems crazy cheap even if it's 2 years old phone but the specs are still much greater, maybe the small display is really not wanted where for me it's the biggest plus. A low budget phone "Xiaomi Hongmi 1S" lasted me 4 years and I still where during premiere it was arleady a slow crap, I'd still use it if not that headphone jack started losing the connection. How come an Iphone won't last me longer than a chinese beater? Is the battery much more degradable or something like that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 14:08:18</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I work with a guy who still uses a 4. I use Xiaomi Hongmi 1S since 2014 and would use another year if not the fact that head phone jack slot is arleady reaaaaly worn off, people think that I will be expecting god knows what after these 5 years, running some simple apps and browsing web will be enough after that and I think even refurb SE will be much better than a chinese brand new 200$ crap. The only question is how the Apple's battery degradation because my old Xiaomi although is dying like after 3-4 hours of web browsing with only 2k mah battery is still usable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 14:15:06</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; If you #8217;re one of those people it might last, but it #8217;s hard to say. The se is already a few years old. I #8217;d say you would have a better experience on a 7 or 8, but that obviously jacks up the price. No one knows how limited the se will be in the future due to its processor and only 2gb of ram. You should easily get 2-3 years from it, but no idea how iOS 14 and beyond will do on it. Well shit, I'm still using Kitkat android on my Xiaomi which is version 4.4.4. I was thinking about the RAM myself since 2GB seems like nothing but I wonder if an Android 4GB RAM phone will be any much more efficient with an inefficient android not to mention that in geekbench Redmi note 5 Pro is 2x slower than Iphone SE.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 14:16:48</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; You can pick up a brand new 32GB iPhone SE at any Best Buy or Walmart right now for $130 from their prepaid phone section. It needs to be unlocked since I'm from Europe, I need an European prepaid carrier, right now I'm using "Play" and 64GB is a must nowadays.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 14:21:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyway, 5 years is ideal I'm not that poor and wouldn't mind switch after 2 years but definitely for me 200$ for a stupid phone is just a maximum although I might be able to replace that battery myself, mostly I want to know if 170$ a refurbrished 64GB is a good deal, if someone bought something like this and there was no surprises.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 20:42:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, it's tested and in case of privacy coins I think it's the most important thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 21:48:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; see the Piracy Megathread. Also check the r/Piracy Wiki for our FAQ and Tools sections. But you only have info for Android, you rules suck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Vechain's promo video.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 21:53:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Vechain's promo video.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 21:54:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Question] Were you ever hacked because of jailbreak and installing unauthorized apps?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 21:57:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm debating of jailbreaking my SE to see if it's gonna suit me since I still have a chance being on 11.2 OS. Is it easy to get screwed and get your passwords stolen, card info etc? which sites are "safe" or fairly safe?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Carrying two phones at once: How to make it work seamlessly</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 22:09:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 01:44:07</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Yeah, SE is the only iP which looks great for me (and is cheap when not being outdated yet at the same time). This might be the last chance to jump on the Iphone classics ship and have up to date experience because they might never come back to the original design, that's why I also personally chose to buy SE until it's still relevant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 01:47:39</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Most people text me on my google voice number and I get the text on every device, even my computer when I'm at my desk. LOL that must look funny</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 11:30:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I also got ninja perma banned in this sub without reason in the ban message, probably for my name despite it saying "Niger"(country) and not "Nig*er"(black person).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 16:59:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>The investigation was on internal affairs level lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>BANANO YOU A BUSTA!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 19:24:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 19:26:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.reddit.com/r/bananocoin/comments/9ah8r1/banano_you_a_busta/ Straight busta.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can I block these annoying Hindi tech videos?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 00:22:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whenever I want to look up some phone reviews I get a fuckton of results with Hindi guys that have english titles but then they talk with their gibberish language, that should be bannable to clickbait international viewers into their shitty videos. Can I filter them somehow?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 01:18:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why they don't remove the notch completely? and just put the camera on the display surface? I guess because then the display would blind the camera but then you can solve it with the software and just turn off part of the camera surrounding. I wonder how much outrage would make if they removed front camera completely, I think I used front camera couple of times during 4 years of usage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 01:28:20</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I love Apple and I have an iPhone X but I #8217;ll be the first to say that, hands down, notifications are FAR better implemented and more useful in Android. I'm using Iphone couple days now and I thought that I just couldn't configure my phone right, but it seems it's just worse there. What I miss from android is a small led blink when the phone is locked when I get a message or a notification or shows charging state for each having a different color. Each notification is showed also after scrolling the notification bar, IOS also has the notification centre but it doesn't seem showing notifications from downloading apps or some other things like new mails.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 17:24:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tether gonna pump it or at least the print news gonna pump it and then crypto gonna dump.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 17:26:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is the Ven number 1077 the amount you hold or its karma in the sub?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 17:40:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will be there a reason to buy redmi note 6 over this? I know Poco is a bit more expensive but with Poco chip and ram you wont have to switch for a veeery long time so youll save in the long term. Why doesn't it have stock android btw? It's because it's too cheap and they want to earn money from MIUI services?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When we will have desktop abilities in our phones?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 17:49:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not talking about display port but about plugging your phone to a monitor and it switches to a special mode with new desktop friendly UI? I think Ubuntu was planning doing something similar. Do you think it will be even a thing with android and it will be popular or it's rather a pointless feature?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 17:52:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm really surprised that so many people complain about that NFC in midrange Xiaomis, it seems like 50% of people are using it, for me it doesnt seem that convenient because its not like credit cards are that big to be a hassle to bring them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 19:50:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mi8 has stock android? If yes then it has advantge over Poco since it has miui and lacks other features.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 19:54:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I bought global Redmi Note 5 Pro 4/64gb for 200$ black version from Gearbest, it was cheaper than from Goldway on official Xiaomi store on Ali.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 19:58:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just blind and in many comparisons I just cant tell which is better, in one comparison I even thought that Iphone 2g shot better photo than Iphone 7.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 20:07:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Europe isnt a target, yes they will sell it there but most Europeans can afford iPhones or Samsungs or other more efficient phones.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 20:10:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>But most people are like this bro.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 20:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Android users are more biased about brands than anyone else, you just need to check some Iphone videos on youtube and see the sewer blowing up, can't believe many of these guys are probably adult.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 20:15:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which one? Samsung?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 22:10:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice, I hope that Google is working on something similar for Android so any phone running Android will be able to do this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 22:12:09</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Rn6 is out? No but it will have SD636 so we know arleady it won't compete with Pocophone so Pocophone is twice as fast than RN6 will be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 00:55:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remade the meme because I made the bilboard crack shitty quality, here's a reupload with the fixed version: https://i.imgur.com/fajX77g.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 02:57:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually India sites are talking about SD630 so even worse than in RN5P. Snapdragon tech progress is very slow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 03:10:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The stainless steel finish is worth the price, if you'll resell the phone then you might get overall more money back than with the 8.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 03:15:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I doubt they'll ever use 4" again, they only did it with SE because they had leftovers so they didnt have to spend resources on new design. next SE 2 probably will use Iphone 8 or 7 look if it will come this year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 15:27:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely, the performance is twice as fast according to benchmarks, even if I didn't have the additional 100$ then I would take a loan, you'll save more money in the long term and you can enjoy the maximum performance right away, the phone will last for years if you're looking to save money.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 19:32:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got my RN5P today that I ordered from Gearbest, I listed it for sale right after and guy came 30 minutes later to buy it, I got a small profit from the resell and I'll wait to buy Pocophone if there will be a chance to get it for 300$.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 00:38:02</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; This is why people think we're a cult. It is a cult.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Should I go for the 1080 TI or wait for RTX 2070 benchmarks?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 10:00:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>The reference RTX 2070 that arleady got sold out on Nvidia page will cost 764.58 USD in my country, I can buy on a sale Gigabyte GeForce GTX 1080 Ti Gaming OC 11GB GDDR5X (352 bit) for only 846.50 USD. Should I wait for benchmarks or GTX 1080 TI is way better and will serve me way longer if I don't care for the 100 bucks difference?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 10:10:39</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; at 1080p! 1080p is just a classic, it has the retro feeling to it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 10:40:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know how long the promotion will last, there's also Ryzen 1700x on sale for 231$</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 17:29:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>that's like 5 times better, SONY IS THE BEST!!!!!!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 17:30:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>shadows alter everything you see bro.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 17:31:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meme tracing, traces memes per second.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 00:02:45</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I understand why it is very interesting but not why so much people are considering it as the best one ever. If the price matters and you want to buy something in the midrange price then there's no point buying things like RN5P.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 00:13:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have no idea why people care so much about jacks, nfc or notches. I use headphones all the time and I rarely used both, usually when I'm charging with my power bank then I unplug my headphones because it's uncomfortable to have a charging cable hanging out from my backpack when I'm walking, notch is a small visual and can't speak for nfc because I only use my debit cards via Internet but using cards in shops instead of your phone doesn't seem like a hassle, I don't know if I would use it anyway since you can get a virus and have your money stolen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 01:22:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>how often are you using it while charging?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 02:48:20</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Indians are scary online. I didn't know they were that active on youtube until I looked up for some Xiaomi reviews, I couldn't find anything besides Indian reviews, now Google thinks I'm Indian because I get a lot of Indian video suggestions, fuck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 02:53:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>In which model?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 03:31:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not much of a dark age, it's still up from previous year, people should hurry up before crypto fuckers will purge the market again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 15:11:43</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Not sure why that matters lol Because I was surprised that you had to charge your phone that often during the day but I see the phone doesn't have huge battery so it checks out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Select all images with China Hustlers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 16:58:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 02:26:37</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Let #8217;s see how it looks in a week or two. "+1(800)273-8255 - U.S. National Suicide Hotline"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 02:32:36</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; It's a fool's rally. Don't you guys understand how bear markets work?  gt;  gt; We've still got a sizeable cool off period remaining until sustained growth can begin again. FUCK YOU MAN!!!!! IT'S A RALLY FOR REAL ALLRIGHT!?!?!?! I WANT MY MOON MOMMY!!! I WANT MY MOOOOON!!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Select all images with China Hustlers</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 15:41:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 08:59:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>In the next batch of images.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 08:59:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>In the next batch of images.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 10:46:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>HEY HEY HEEEEY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>