<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject505</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 07:38:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think it's absurd at all. We've seen another character suffers from their inferiority complex with Kurisu. And that character almost single-handedly cause the beta worldline. *Both* experiences break people. It's a wonder Maho didn't become Nakabachi 2.0</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 07:49:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most likely yes. The "uneventful" episodes gives you hindsight on things. Like the party on episode 3 makes the recent knowledge that Okarin avoided the lab feels more harsh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 08:07:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aside from Blu Ray volumes, buying official merchandise could also help the studio if I recalled correctly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 08:18:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a majestic bathing that would be</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 09:26:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because the first D-mail was a divergence point. The act of sending D-mail is the one that leads to a chain of events that ends with Mayuri being killed (with or without SERN intervention). And the FGL taken by SERN so they have monopoly on time travel technology. As long as they're still in Alpha attractor field, Mayuri will be dead. And that's why they need to undo the D-mail. Merely deleting the data would only mean Mayuri isn't killed by SERN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 11:55:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not in the main one. But there's an instance in S;G 0. Also the Gamma worldline drama CD</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 07:43:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love Mr Braun's reaction.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 07:50:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good good. Let the feel flow through you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 08:01:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Take it. Just take my wallet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 08:09:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cash problem perhaps? Have they won any race in the last years?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 08:27:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not happy with just a mention. After reading it on a wiki I want it to be animated. Next season I guess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 08:34:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>"He made us........ into f*cking killers"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 12:01:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's intentional one. Over and Over again like you said. I think at that point he's simply tired. And had come to a dangerous thoughts like "If she died I could just time leaped backwards and try again and again." or "This is the time where she died. Time to try again on the next loop." Whereas the moment he met Kurisu in Amadeus, he had already given up on saving Kurisu, already destroyed the PhoneWave so he can't time leaped. So that one caught him by surprise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 13:04:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you got the hour wrong</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 23:01:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>No way they're Rounders. FB could just attack Suzuha before she even leave the building. But yeah. Even Stormtroopers are laughing at their aim</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 23:06:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>NO! NO! NO! NOOO! They did not just put a cliffhanger there. NO! Having seen VN spoilers, oh man. oh man. We're going to hear "Re-Awake" soon are we? Can someone put me on one week comma?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 23:10:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rounders aimed better than those guys</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 23:15:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stormtrooper laughs at their terrible aiming</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 23:23:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let's wait before we make assumptions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 23:34:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>One walks the other Runs?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 07:59:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>So "My watch stopped......." Is Steins;Gate equivalent of Haruhi's "Kyon-kun denwa.."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 08:05:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Marlboro and Lucky Strike. The old times when cigarettes companies could sponsor sports</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 20:40:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, the only difference is that both Okabe and us are aware of "My watch just stopped." Whereas we're the only ones tortured by "Kyon-kun denwa."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 09:48:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. Unless it's reserved. A number can be used again after 2 years of the last time they were on the grid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 10:24:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly that I think. It's his homeland and he f\*\*ked it up. In front a lot of fans. So the pressure not to f\*\*k it up was high</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 10:28:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can click on the image on the list. On it's own page, they give you larger resolution Example: [https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/bakemonogatari1645/images/0/08/Nisemonogatari\_Episode\_7\_Endcard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20150930013217](https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/bakemonogatari1645/images/0/08/Nisemonogatari_Episode_7_Endcard.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20150930013217) Which is about 1440 x 810 pixels if the description is to be believed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 11:45:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure which one you're talking about. But here's a playlist: [https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IAEKFiiD3K0 amp;list=PLhFw0ftuwhqvdm5e8wkSOdqQvRY9tHcXL](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IAEKFiiD3K0 amp;list=PLhFw0ftuwhqvdm5e8wkSOdqQvRY9tHcXL) And in case it's a recycled soundtrack from earlier seasons (They do that, the one where Kaiki monologue was a Bakemonogatari OST): [https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TSu1FNulrrY amp;list=PLhFw0ftuwhqutXgKGvXLpik1JI4-E29UY](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TSu1FNulrrY amp;list=PLhFw0ftuwhqutXgKGvXLpik1JI4-E29UY)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 23:33:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>F\*cking Gonorrhea chapter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 23:36:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>HataSaibou Black was even worse. At least this one doesn't have Cholesterol on veins and Tar-ed lungs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 21:14:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The bacteria is different, and the bugs are also different. If you have plans to visit Triassic or Jurassic era treat it like a trip to mars and bring a spacesuit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 21:17:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everyone appeared again in Zoku. But be patient if you want to see Hitagi though, she got Tsukimonogatari treatment again</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 23:48:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>ERASED. The breakfast scene</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 21:31:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not Possible, while there are several worldlines They're not parallel with each other. So only ONE of them are active at any given time. Memories of timeline, a person existence, all changed accordingly when the timeline shifted. By reaching Steins; Gate worldline. Everyone could have a happy life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>