<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject8769</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 20:26:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Will download, try it out these next couple of days and get back to you.  #128522;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-21 22:21:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just downloaded it and was messing with it before I go to my delivery shift in 3 hrs from now. When searching for an address, is it supposed to provide navigation to the location? Not sure. I'm in USA by the way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 09:46:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>4 years, never paid for parking. I used to park at the industrial area until they made it 2hr parking. Then I parked at Ralph's. Finished off parking up by the condos near Corte Bella, find the trail that takes you around back into Lot C and you're golden. It's only a 10-min walk to campus.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 10:30:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen someone deliver in a Hummer H2. Like bruh, you're losing money every time you turn your car on..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Best delivery plus tip.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 10:55:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Normal day of work at Dominos about a year ago, I took a delivery where a couple of moms were sitting out on the drive way on lawn chairs, kids were playing on the grass and sidewalks, dad's were fixing up a trailer that was on the side of the road. Bunch of stuff going on. The receipt had a females name so I approach the ladies and start handing them their order. When one of them says "Do you want to ride a go-kart?" I politely say "no, thank you. I must get back to work." I then look over and the dads are adding fuel to this cool-looking go cart. She then says "Are you sure? I'll give you a $15 tip if you do." I right away said "alright, I'll do it." So I rode the go-kart up and down the street for about 3 minutes and sure enough got my $15. Pretty cool huh?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Comment your randomest tips (not money)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 18:50:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a couple: tequila shot, wine bottles, bong hits, a milkshake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 19:23:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol you're right that intro could have taken this a whole different way..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 20:38:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol the mom's were not smoking hot, but they were attractive in there own way. To each their own definition of "hot."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 20:39:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha wtf? That's the strangest thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-22 20:43:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get $2/run, San Diego area.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-23 10:19:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I'm sure that might come in handy..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-02 10:25:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>But you only drink jarritos...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-06 01:00:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not familiar with the split wage, but I get paid $10/hr + $2/delivery + tips.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New to the Prius family</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-08 18:53:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just purchased my first hybrid, a 2016 Prius C Three. I'm still in the process of learning how to pulse and glide to improve mileage. Will give more tips as I get familiarized. Happy gliding.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-08 19:05:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is in San Diego area, plus I drive a Prius. Long story short, OP should take into consideration (1) the delivery range (2) average customer tips and (3) car mpg. Make comparisons towards other local shops. For example, the local Domin #243;s pays only about $1.20 / delivery. So I'm profitting $0.8 / delivery by working at a local pizza joint, as opposed to a large corporate company. Cheers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>California window tint laws.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 02:24:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just bought a Prius and hate the small front window by the side mirror. I want to tint it as dark as possible. Anyone know if this is legal in California? I know the laws about the main front windows, but curious about these.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 05:03:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's good to know! By the way, do you happen to have a picture of your small window with limo tint? That would be very helpful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-10 10:17:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow your girlfriend is perfectly thick.  #128525;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 18:50:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>However your biweekly paycheck will be taxes based on your total hourly wages + credit card tips. If you wish to report cash tips, that will get taxed as well. Your gas mileage does not get taxed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hiking peaks or nature treasures</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-20 22:32:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've done a lot of nature walking and hiking around north county. Was wondering what your local and favorite spots are. Not including double peak, I run that trail from the lake up quite often. Show me what you got!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-21 10:39:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ladies between 25-40 message me directly. Willing to swap pictures first and see where it goes. No strings attached, just mutual kinky fun for those who are attracted to young fit males.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dealer to change interest, 2 weeks after signing?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 05:28:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I need advice on a new car purchase I made 2 weeks ago. Bought a 2016 Toyota Prius @ 1.99% interest and the dealership called to say they weren't able to finance it at that rate. They say they want to raise it to 2.49% interest, which will raise my monthly payment by $8/month for 72 months. They have proceeded to send me new paper work to sign and return. Question is, are they allowed to do this? I only agreed to purchase the car because of the price I was offered right then and there. Your thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 06:08:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was just going through that subreddit! Thanks, I will look further into this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 06:08:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm, I need to check my agreement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-26 06:21:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks so much. I just read the spot delivery FAQ.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-06 17:10:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Subreddit for see through leggings?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 18:45:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ozium is a good choice, I personally use the Black Ice little trees spray. It's what drug traffickers use to hide drug smell from dogs, works for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 09:46:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm planning on attending Unc for grad school as well and need to find places to live as well. I also want to visit the campus in the next couple of weeks. Roommates perhaps? Which program?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Customer drops pizza..</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-09 09:17:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Order: XL Pep  amp; Sausage, 20 Wings. Early 40's lady greets me at the door and I hand her the order. Wings stacked on top of pizza box. She then sets it aside on top of some cardboard boxes. Seems as if they were doing some packing/unpacking of boxes, not sure if moving. I then kindly ask her to authorize her credit card payment on the slip and hand her the pen, and then it happened. She did not balance the food properly and it fell over. The wings were intact in their container/box. However the pizza box landed vertical between two boxes. I was left speechless.. I mean I delivered the order properly, not my fault. She tipped me $7. Has anyone experienced something similar? How have you responded to this? Any other thoughts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-09 18:26:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seen this more than once Hahaha  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Should I drive for Uber or Lyft?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-09 18:33:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is more profitable per ride here in North County? I only want to do this weekends on spare time. I don't know much about the fares and/or commission that Uber or Lyft keeps; however, I have heard Uber made some cuts recently. Can someone with experience educate me a little? Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-14 09:32:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did the same. I wouldn't risk it at Ralph's.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 07:35:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Give me more info on other places to live, if you don't mind. I'm coming to UNC for my masters in the fall as well! On campus vs off campus?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Visiting UNCo.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 07:42:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kind of a late post, but I'm staying in Denver tonight and going to visit UNCo tomorrow morning. Going to meet some faculty and tour some laboratories. Any current students want to meet up and tell me a bit more about the school? That would be great! DM me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 08:07:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>That calf tho.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 09:30:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>UberSubmarine works too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Christmas Light Displays</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 07:29:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's that time of the year for Christmas lights. Does anyone have a link to a list of communities that are organizing light displays? Maybe those where you tune in on the radio. Thanks much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Christmas Light displays</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 07:43:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's that time of year again for Christmas lights. Does anyone have a link to where I can find more information about community organized light displays? Like those where you tune in on the radio! Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 06:53:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>You've never seen this. Rancho Penasquitos /Poway in San Diego have something like this. Xmas music plays on a radio station and the community's Xmas light go on and off to the rhythm of the music.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Grad Student Financing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 21:09:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm 23 y/o and currently in grad school. I only manage to make about 16k part-time. I have a 6k loan at 6% interest of which I have been paying off the accumulated interest each month and making minimal deductions towards the principal amount. I have about 12k left to pay for the next school year as well. I was recently gifted 10k by a family member for education costs. I immediately transferred it to my savings account with a 1.5% yearly interest. MY QUESTION :Should I pay off my current loan with the 10k now? Or what should I do with the 10k at this point? Sorry I'm not Reddit not Finance fluent..</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 21:20:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>My emergency fund is only $2k.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 21:49:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>~$800-$1k / month.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 21:54:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fair enough, thanks for your input.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 03:59:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, the 12K has not been dispersed, but will be in the Fall. And both loans will have a 6%, you assummed correctly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Airport parking 2018</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 12:04:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello. I need suggestions on airport parking, I saw some lots go for $10/day,is there anything cheaper? I plan on being in Denver for 5 days, so cheaper than ~$50. I don't live anywhere close where I can Uber here. However what are other alternatives under $50 for those 5 days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 06:56:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did that for 2-3 semesters, used the trail outback that takes you to parking lot C, I believe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 06:52:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a meat view.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Took a sip of my beer and the foam spelled RIP.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:29:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 06:32:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a raspberry sour beer!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>