<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject1885</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stills From A Short I DP'd - Some Feedback?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-27 20:11:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-27 22:12:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah it is intentionally dark, which I like, but the amount of light we had access to kind of dictated the level of fill we used. The blue light comes from the doorway in shot 10 which acts as a portal into different dimensions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-27 22:54:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheers! We shot on a BMCC with Nikon and Samyang lenses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-27 23:30:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah it is but most of the look was achieved in camera so it's really only had curve adjustments and sharpening done to it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-27 23:39:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks man!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-28 00:10:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the feedback! I would agree with that about the first two but they are stills from handheld tracking shots and they feel a bit less 2D when in motion. As for the other shots though I think there is definite tonal and spacial separation between the planes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-28 00:12:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah will do man, my brother is just trying to find the time to start cutting the film but should be done early 2015. Cheers!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-28 00:21:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, appreciate that!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Stills From A BMCC Shoot</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-28 14:22:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-28 14:23:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I've posted it in there and subscribed!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-28 14:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>If your going to shoot two-shots then you could compose them on a wide lens to make the characters appear distanced and less comfortable with each other. You could also shoot your singles relatively wide, almost like mid-shots, to not allow the audience to feel too comfortable with them. Some context would help though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-28 23:40:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>As in you prefer it to shooting 35mm stills?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-29 02:01:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I agree, I went from using a 5D to the BMCC and I definitely prefer the images you get out of the CC. The only thing about image quality I miss is the latitude you get in the shadows but if you give this camera enough light then you can still achieve really clean blacks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-29 04:23:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha yeah I agree about the near duplicates, I just couldn't decide which one I liked best! Thanks for the feedback, I really appreciate getting other peoples opinions on my stuff, I think in context (character deciding whether or not to go through the 'portal doorway') shot 12 needed that bright blue wash (which comes from the strong light that the door emits) because it's almost like it's beckoning him in. Also shot 9 is the character walking up some stairs but I probably chose a poor still to demonstrate that! Cheers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-30 02:00:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dictating exactly how he should shoot these frames is completely counter productive. This is his interpretation of the script and he has visualised that in the way he sees fit and in a style which he feels suits the narrative and is in keeping with his own style (obviously I haven't seen the film but from what I've read it would appear that he is successful). How a cinematographer composes a powerful character or lights an isolated character is completely subjective and simply can't be taught or dictated. There's no problem giving him advice on the technical side of cinematography (which can be taught) but your trying to force your style on him and tell him why his compositions don't work. This is especially futile considering you haven't even seen these shots in motion, let alone the film as a whole. The second still for example, I would imagine that as the elevator reaches it's peak the character will actually rise above camera, creating a sense of power and demonstrating his vulnerable nature turning to menace. Your technical advice is clearly pretty useless as well. You describe the second shot as flat when it is anything but. The character is separated from background through tone and colour, the use of leading lines all running into the distance is an age old technique to add depth *and* there are foreground, midground and background elements in play within the composition - thus utilizing all dimensional planes. Not to mention the tonal separation across the whole frame with the highlights of the elevator to the blacks of the railings and his top. *My* advice to you NiatsahcYrneh is to not bother listening to people like me and highbrowalcoholic and shoot things the way you want to and the way you think tells the story best and if it doesn't work then you'll have learnt for the next project you shoot. Overall I am very impressed that a 17 year old can produce images like this (I'm sure there are very few that can) and I wish you the best for the rest of the production! As for you highbrowalcoholic, stop trying to tell people they've done anything right or wrong because, as I said, it's all subjective and if your not going to be constructive then your more likely to discourage people than make them better cinemtographers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-31 15:23:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>The saturation most certainly is not 'out of this world' *or* 'way too vibrant'. Watch anything shot by chris doyle or emmanuel lubezki and you'll see that vibrant colours can be a great tool in telling a story. Either your watching this on a dodgy monitor or your talking out of your arse and giving fruitless advice. It may be a tad too colourful for your taste but that doesn't mean it's wrong, that's just your style and preference.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-07 00:24:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice! Keep up the good work, when was this taken?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-08 23:13:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've bought my first couple of rolls of film and was wandering what aspect ratio 35mm is? If it's not 16:9 is there anything I can do to compose photos on a Pentax ME to make sure I don't lose anything important when it comes to cropping down to 1.77?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-09 03:14:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great, cheers for the help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-10 03:02:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks again haha!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-11 23:11:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which Kodak B+W stock is the best in terms of sharpness and latitude? Are there any websites that do comparisons for things like this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-24 15:29:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are some of the sharpest lenses for 35mm photography?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-24 18:03:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've got a Pentax ME so Pentax K-mount. Oh really, so are 35mm films generally quite soft then? For a sharper look would you recommend using roll film or something?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-24 18:47:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah ok, Thanks for reply there's lots of useful info there! I've actually got an old Zeiss 80mm so I might find an adapter and get some Velvia as well, see how it turns out. Cheers!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-27 23:30:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheers man!Unfortunately we ran into some issues and were unable to finish the project. We may reboot and reshoot the whole thing at some point though and I'll post it on here we do!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-15 21:44:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great, cheers Michael! I love the high-contrast music video look you've got going on, the expressionistic lighting really creates a surreal atmosphere when I look at these. When is the film going to be available for viewing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-15 22:53:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I look forward to seeing it, be sure to post a comment with a link in when it's ready!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New cinematography based subreddit similar to r/CineShots but for YOUR short films, music videos and commercials - PLEASE READ</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-15 23:11:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello, I have recently created a new subreddit called [r/ShortCineShots] (http://www.reddit.com/r/ShortCineShots/). This subreddit is designed to be a place to post stills of your work as a Cinematographer or Director on short films, music videos, commercials or other personal projects so you can receive feedback on your work from other like-minded people without feeling like you are 'showing off'. I appreciate some people already do this on /r/cinematography but I feel like having a dedicated subreddit specifically for this would work much better and would encourage more people to post stills of their work and give and receive feedback. Cheers!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New cinematography based subreddit similar to r/CineShots but for YOUR short films, music videos and commercials - PLEASE READ</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-15 23:16:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello, I have recently created a new subreddit called [/r/ShortCineShots] (http://www.reddit.com/r/ShortCineShots/) . This subreddit is designed to be a place to post stills of your work as a Cinematographer or Director on short films, music videos, commercials or other personal projects so you can receive feedback on your work from other like-minded people without feeling like you are 'showing off'. I appreciate some people already do this on /r/cinematography but I feel like having a dedicated subreddit specifically for this would work much better and would encourage more people to post stills of their work and give and receive feedback. Cheers!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>'Solace' (2015) DP - Will Edwick</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-16 00:00:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-16 00:01:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>These stills are from an experimental film I recently directed and DP'd titled 'Solace'. I shot this film on a Blackmagic Cinema Camera in 2.5k RAW with Samyang, Nikon and vintage Zeiss lenses (along with the Metabone Speedbooster). We travelled to various locations in north-east England and shot timelapses, portraits and video of the people and places we encountered. Everything we shot was done with available light so the Speedbooster and various strengths of ND filter we had were essential and gave us flexibility in uncontrollable lighting situations. We also travelled as light as possible, usually just carrying the camera, lenses, tripod and around 12ft of track.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New Cinematography Based Subreddit To Showcase YOUR Work Going Strong But Need More Subscribers!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-17 18:21:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New Cinematography Based Subreddit To Showcase YOUR Work Is Going Strong But Needs More Subscribers!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-18 01:06:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-18 14:09:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice one, looks great! Were most of these shots "lit" or did you mainly use natural light?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-18 14:50:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, you did a good job of keeping it looking consistent throughout! Did you shoot with compact primes?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-18 23:48:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha cool, is there anywhere we can see this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-19 21:44:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really want to know what this is about, it has a really creepy tone to it. When's the release?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-19 21:47:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah some of the blacks seem a bit unnaturally strong but on the whole it looks really good. What picture profile etc. did you use?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-19 21:49:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can I ask why you chose to shoot on a Handycam?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-19 22:00:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice one, make sure you post a comment with the link in when it's released! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-19 22:36:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok, well drop a comment to remind me haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-19 22:37:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice, have you tried colouring in Resolve? Really upped my game once I learnt my way around it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-19 22:52:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha yeah I sat down to try learn it and subsequently gave up due to being overwhelmed at least 4 or 5 times before I finally started getting to grips with it. Steep learning curve but it really is worth it in the end!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-19 23:44:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ooh what's your feature about? (Without giving too much away haha)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-20 00:00:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shit man that sucks, although I'm glad your getting to make a documentary about it! I've donated to your initial funding (although I didn't have an awful lot to give :p) and I hope you manage to secure further funding in the future :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-20 01:11:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>No worries!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-21 14:04:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you change the title so it is similar to the other ones? Thanks...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-22 18:39:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>What camera and lenses?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-26 18:58:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh wow that was proper sinister haha, nice one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-28 04:59:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go post these over at http://www.reddit.com/r/ShortCineShots/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-07 17:51:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I didn't realise they were slightly off centre, thanks for pointing that out! As I mentioned, we were shooting with 100% available light so one or two shots had to be pushed a couple of stops in post and were still a tad too dark in the end but that kind of adds to the look and feel of the film I think. Cheers for the feedback!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-08 18:06:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which falls under the responsibility of the director *and* the cinematographer...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-08 19:43:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cinematography, in it's 'purest' form, is all things to do with the image and this includes camera placement and blocking. Especially since this is a TV show (presumably with multiple directors and one cinematographer per series) then I'd expect the DP would have a lot more control over this than on a feature</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-08 21:32:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Back when cinema was first being experimented with the cinematographer would be the one in charge of the camera and creating images hence 'Director of Photography' and someone else, usually one of the actors, would be in charge of directing the actors. It wasn't until later that people began to do both, creating the 'Director'. By 'purest' I just mean everything you would be expected to do as a cinematographer should you be working with a first time director for example who has a background in writing not filmmaking. I agree though that some directors will have full control over camera and actor blocking, others will leave it completely to their cinematographer and some will do something inbetween. Look at Woody Allen, he would allow Gordon Willis to have control whereas someone like Tarantino will be almost completely in control of everything except lighting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-09 01:37:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah agreed! I like the retro feel some of these images have, often people over do it to the point where it looks like something from instagram but it appears quite subtle here. Please do elaborate about lenses and lighting etc. though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-09 01:53:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>What lenses did you shoot with?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-09 22:12:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha I'm sure your up to it ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-09 22:16:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow! Blown away by the clarity of these images, could you talk about what camera, lenses and lighting you used to capture these? Also, did you use an additional eye-light in some of these shots or did you bring out the eyes in post?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-09 22:45:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>These aren't photographs are they? Can't get round the fact that these are so sharp when you were using a kit lens haha. Are you using Magic Lantern to shoot RAW?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-09 23:17:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow pretty impressive!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-14 19:18:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>What balance is the stock your going to be using, daylight or tungsten? And are you after a warm look or a natural, white is white look?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-14 20:15:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It really depends what your trying to do with the scene, if you want some lights cool and some warm or natural then balancing with gels is the only way to do it but if your wanting white, neutral colours throughout the image then balancing your camera or stock is good because you don't cut light by using gels. Using halogen bulbs on tungsten film stock should give you pretty much what your after because it's balanced to around 3200 wherea the lights are about 3000 so should be fairly neutral with a slight warm tint.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-15 21:06:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>This feedback is truly wonderful and sums up exactly why I started this subreddit, so people could get genuine and honest feedback on their work. Glad you agreed to judge and I hope that you will be up for doing so again in the future, cheers!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-15 21:13:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll also get the flair's sorted asap</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-24 18:51:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great composition!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-30 00:53:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah they're the same lenses just branded differently, currently ordering a set of them myself after using the 16mm photography version and loving it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-04 21:10:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blade Runner the tyrell corporation scene would be up there</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-05 15:32:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah you really could! One of the best shot films of all time in my opinion</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-23 18:12:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amen, I see hundreds of these videos each week and they never get any better</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-27 19:15:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please provide camera, lens and lighting information :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-09 14:55:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It does not look awesome before colour correction...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-09 15:00:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>These all look flat and a bit dull</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-09 20:12:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's shot flat so that our monitors can display the full dynamic range of the camera, it's not designed to be left like that. None of the best DPs in the world would leave their digitally shot images looking like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-09 20:17:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>They don't look that different to be honest, people underestimate how much contrast they should be putting back into these images</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-10 16:06:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I find unless you use a film emulating LUT you end up chickening out on contrast because you compare the shot before and after and it always looks better but then when you come back to it you find it actually still looks quite flat. Knowing your shooting to a high contrast LUT you can then do stuff with the lighting to make sure it's not too dark and the blacks aren't too deep if your going for a natural look</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-10 16:08:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>It depends how you design your gamma curve and how contrasty you've lit the scene. Simply pulling down the blacks and pushing the whites is going to give that horribly digital look but if you design your curve carefully/make sure you not shooting with high contrast lighting then you can make your images pop without it looking over done</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-10 16:10:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>And for me none of these images really pop</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-16 13:34:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like your making a whole load of excuses for poor work</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-16 19:08:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you were anything other than amateur then you would have known the colour temperature of your lights and balanced your camera well before you got there. Your whole work on that piece is atrocious as well which, as /u/sonofaresiii says, is fine we were all there at some point. Just don't insult people who are trying to help you fix your shitty work</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-17 00:37:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Solid stuff man! There are a few bits in there that feel a bit flat and poorly composed, but the stuff with the Asian actor I really liked, very nicely lit. There were 3 or 4 exceptional compositions as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-17 15:34:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was mainly the shots at the start/end, I've seen much much worse but they did just leave a little bit to be desired in my opinion. Everything in the middle was very nice though and it's one of the first good reels I've seen on here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-18 13:10:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would beg to differ on your point about vignettes http://imgur.com/zUV6h6r, had a budget of around $25m</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-19 01:31:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>50mm isn't what the eye sees at all, on a super 35 sensor that's too long, try somewhere between 24-32mm for that</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-19 01:35:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's no formula, you need to test out all these different focal lengths with different shot sizes and see what you like/don't and what effect it can have on an image and how you can use it to tell the story.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-19 20:03:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah there's a lot of confusion about it because people hear that from photographers (who generally shoot full-frame) but even then I think it's too long</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-20 23:10:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, great film with great cinematography! I generally feel the same way about vignettes (although I tend to use subtle ones on most of my work) but it definitely works in this case because it adds to the imperfect and dirty look the film has</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-20 23:21:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can spot a film Roger Deakins shot from a mile away regardless of who he's working with... Not to say that he's a one trick pony, just his style comes through in nearly everything I've seen of his</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-20 23:24:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Plus, when you 'see' Cronenweth your generally just seeing Dave Fincher</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-28 13:30:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's like cinestyle except Log is a colour space, not a picture profile. It was designed so that the full range of your camera's latitude could be displayed on the camera's screen and on your monitors in post, which generally don't have a lot of dynamic range. The benefit of this is that you can design your own gamma curves instead of using the shitty one's that camera manufacturers design. In the future when high dymanic range monitors, projectors and codecs are available you will be able to retain all the dynamic range your camera has when you add contrast in post</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL That Steven Spielberg and George Lucas used to take out newspaper/magazine adverts when the other director's film became the bigger hit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-30 14:51:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-05 19:24:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Directors in TV tend to have a lot less overall control than they do in Film, they get hired to work within the stylistic parameters of the show and would be fired if they tried to make radical changes. Nic Pizzolatto will be making many of the decisions typically associated with Film Directing so the show shouldn't change too much from episode to episode. I also *think* the same Cinematographer is shooting all 8 episodes, if so he'll be keeping the visual style consitent, but I may be wrong about this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-05 19:28:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I assume he means 'pace'</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-09 20:34:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>A clutch that you'll never let go of because you won't have made the mistake to learn from</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-22 18:47:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's nothing about cinematography a high-end camera will teach you that a cheaper camera won't. If your looking at getting on bigger productions then there is a higher chance they'll be renting cameras and won't require you to own one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How should England line up in the UAE?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-24 13:09:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Personally, my team would be: 1. Cook 2. Hales 3. Root 4. Morgan 5. Bairstow 6. Stokes 7. Buttler 8. Ali 9. Rashid 10. Broad 11. Finn Although there is a good chance this won't be the team that lines up in the first test, my justification is: **2:** Obviously we need to keep testing out partners for Cook until we find one that is good enough, Hales being the next option. I understand that Moeen Ali could probably do a job at the top of the order on the subcontinent but it's not a long term solution because he clearly isn't good enough to open against pace in swinging conditions. **3:** Root is our best player and seems destined for the number three slot. He has also proven he can bat well early in an innings, having come in at 40-odd for 3 on numerous occasions and taken us to a competitive total. **4:** This one is more in the advent of Bells retirement (which he has hinted at; and now would seem like a good time before he potentially does a Michael Clarke). Taylor may be the better option but I would like to see Morgan given another chance (dependant on how he performs in the one-dayers) and having another experienced head in the batting order can only be a good thing. **9:** Seemingly the best spin option England have (even if he isn't test-proven) and will surely be given a run of games against Pakistan that could elevate him above Ali as England's no.1 spinner. **11:** Is there any need to take Anderson to the UAE? He doesn't bowl particularly well on flat surfaces and could do with a rest before the SA tour. Finn's extra pace and bounce could be the better option here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-24 14:25:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I think I would agree as well, I hope he stays and goes on to play well but I was thinking more in case he does retire what the options would be. I still think now would be a good time for him though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-24 14:29:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lets face it, *if* Bell retires they're more likely to bring in someone with test experience so either Morgan or Taylor are probably the more likely. Or even move Ali up to four</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-24 14:31:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>What would your middle order look like then if you're worried about Bairstow, Stokes and Buttler? And yeah like I said, they'd probably go with Taylor should Bell retire but I think Morgan has become a better player since he last played test cricket 3 and a half years ago</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-24 16:28:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I would rather see Taylor given a shot than Hildreth, he may be a fine player but looking long-term, Taylor would be my preferred option</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-24 16:39:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree about Buttler, he's a fine batsmen in his own right and will be a good keeper-batsmen for England, just needs to find some form. I would like to see Taylor at some point, maybe for Bairstow if he can't make the step up. Who would your third spinner be then if we only went with two seamers?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-24 16:44:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about Taylor at 5? I'm not sure the selectors view Ballance as a middle-order player</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 03:05:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good point about Ballance bringing solidity to our middle-order I hadn't considered that, almost like the Collingwood role. Plus he does bat at 5 for Yorkshire</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-03 01:45:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd also try to include as little slow-mo stuff as possible, people see right through that shit. Same goes for aerial footage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-03 17:59:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love slow-mo, just seems like everyone's doing it these days just because they can, then throw it into their reel because it's an easy way to make stuff look cinematic. The rest of your reel is good though, not meaning to discourage!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-04 22:09:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is absolutely not the case, anyone who is hiring him will know that they are the same thing. Not that it matters anyway because a DP doesn't just hold a camera</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-08 02:04:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm no scientist but it sounds like bullshit to me. White isn't a colour, it's about how bright or dark something appears; meaning he would have a hard time distinguishing between a bright sky and a dark horizon for example</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-17 19:10:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's because they can light by eye, not by looking at waveform monitors</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-17 19:49:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've read plenty of interviews with Pro's who talk about lighting by eye just like they did when shooting on film</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-08 16:20:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>It refers to the photographic side of filmmaking so things like lighting, composition, camera movement, colour, camera/lenses etc. I guess with scenery/locations it's less about the actual scenery but more about how it was captured because the cinematographer isn't really in control of the landscape, but *is* partly responsible for A) choosing the location in the first place and B) making the most of a location in terms of how it is shot i.e shooting it at the right time of day for the light and pointing the camera in the most interesting direction.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-08 17:41:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't seen the film yet but so I've heard!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-17 01:04:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude your reel sucks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-04 19:40:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>My Pentax 35mm camera has suddenly started making a strange scratchy sound when I pull the film advance lever (which has also become stiffer) and I'm wondering if this is normal or whether my film is catching on something internally? Anyone else had this issue?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-06 21:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pentax ME</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-07 19:29:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah I see, thanks for the help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>House of Cards S1 E2 (2013)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-08 16:03:32</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-18 20:18:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not sure if it's too late to suggest anything but I'd love to see more in-depth write ups about peoples projects with BTS stills of lighting etc. and frame grabs of the final piece, a bit like AC articles. This would satisfy peoples desire to get feedback on their work, whilst still being educational and beneficial to other members of the sub. It'd also be nice (if possible to implement) to have different flairs that let other people know exactly what level they are i.e professional, semi-professional, amatuer, DSLR enthusiast etc. Edit: Additional sentence</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-29 16:14:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's more about making sure that posts are educational as opposed to people just showing off their work (regardless of how good or bad it is)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-03 14:11:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>It'll actually give you slightly choppier motion. If you wanted the same motion blur at 30fps as you'd get at 24fps you just shoot at 180 degree shutter</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-06 23:18:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I'd really like to hear more about this project, really enjoyed it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Bay of Napoli - Pentax ME / 28mm / Portra 400</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-12 14:22:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-12 17:25:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, spent ages waiting for the boat!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-28 22:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm pretty sure that film was shot spherical and it looks like a 35mm maybe, which your 18-55 kit lens would give you on a APS-C sensor</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-01 13:37:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>So everything shot on the Alexa ever makes you feel sick but this very average and flat looking video you love? Seems you have a peculiar taste in imagery but the only thing I can suggest is that these lenses, due to the tendency to flair, give you a lower contrast image when a bright source is in front of the lens. This washed out look may be what your attracted to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-10 19:16:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>no it's not</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-12 02:24:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It just looks insaaanely 'video-like' in the way the images have been acquired/finished. I assume the Sony CineAlta cameras/Digiprime lenses had something to do with it. I imagine the lighting in those scenes would actually look pretty good if they'd shot on film instead</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-12 04:11:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I should have been more specific, the CineAlta F23/F950 cameras are part of the problem. The F65 is a hugely improved camera compared to Sony's early digital cinema cameras. And it isn't digital that's the issue, it's the shitty acquisition method and really poor colour grading; I just used film as an example because it was the obvious alternative at the time. It's actually pretty easy to avoid this sort of look with digital these days, any half-decent camera shot with conventional settings will give you a way better image than those examples</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-12 04:16:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think a large soft source or backlighting would make those scenes look any less amatuer. You may not be a fan of that lighting style (fair enough) but if this had been shot on an Alexa at 180 degrees with a pro colourist doing the grading, I think it would turn out pretty good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Only got paid 50% of my salary this month due to a clerical error, and my employer is now saying I have to wait until next payday (next month) to receive the rest. Is there anything I can do to get my money earlier?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 16:05:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I worked around 150 hours from 7th November until the 4th of December (the cut-off point for Dec 23rd payday) but when I received my payslip on the 23rd, I realised that I'd only been paid for 78 hours worth of work. I called HR on the 23rd and they agreed that I'd been underpaid and said they would sort it out and call me back. I didn't hear anything for a week (it's Christmas so fair enough) so I rang them back and they said that the issue had been passed on to accounting but because it was past the cut-off point for the December payday, I wouldn't receive the rest of my pay until the next payday on January 25th. So I'm basically being punished for a mistake that they've made and now I'm risking missing credit card/finance payments because of this fuck up. For the record, I quit on the 18th of December and me not working there anymore makes it trickier to try and sort out. Is there anything I can do to get paid earlier or will I just have to suck it up and wait?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 18:48:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh sweet, will it make a difference that I am no longer employed by them and not under contract? Also, who is the best person to get in contact with, my old manager, HR or the accounting department?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 20:00:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>What exactly is a BACS payment, and how do I find out my details?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 20:39:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-28 21:14:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheers! Thanks for the advice man, I'll update once I've spoken to the accounting department!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lens flare in this photo looks like Eric Cartman</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 22:38:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Tax] Just received my payslip and my total income and taxable income are the same. Why hasn't my tax free allowance been accounted for?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-28 23:02:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>For the record, I'm a 23 year old car salesman and made  #163;1883.32 last month</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 00:05:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>My tax code was 955L</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 00:07:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I earned  #163;1883.32 and was taxed  #163;217.2 and NI was  #163;144.4 (which equals 19.2% combined)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 00:15:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I get you, thanks a lot!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 00:16:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I have a company car which counts as income</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 18:24:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ex car salesman here, first off I would pick between a polo or a fiesta as they are both incredibly cheap to run and maintain. Personally I would pick the fiesta (ecoboost engine if possible) as you get the best balance between power and economy, usually road tax exempt if registered before April 2017. I would also make sure to go to a main dealer if reliability is a big concern to you as some smaller dealerships will try and sell you cars that aren't in great condition. Since you've got a good credit score and earn a decent salary you will easily qualify for rates around the 3-4% range which is the maximum amount of interest you want to be paying back. Ask the dealership what flat rate (not APR) they offer, and whether they have any admin fees (Evans halshaw is ~ #163;100 and Arnold Clark don't have any for example). To get the best deal from a dealer, try and go towards the end of the month because they might be behind target and prepared to cut a deal. You will also get the best deal if your prepared to make the purchase on the day. Use this when negotiating, don't tell them before getting figures, but say 'if you knock  #163;2-300 off the price or get the interest rate down then I'll buy it today', they will be much more likely to give it to you. Obviously this means doing your research beforehand, but also be prepared to walk away if your not happy with the car/deal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 19:06:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>A car dealership won't take you seriously if you ask if the RAC can come inspect one of their cars. Everyone thinks dealers are desperate to do business but if you start asking daft stuff like that they will probably just tell you to fuck off</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 19:11:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be honest, owning a depreciating asset outright is never a particularly sensible idea. OP should check out good rental deals or even a PCP (google it) so you get a car that can fit in your monthly budget</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 19:19:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>You will never pay any of the fees if you pay on time each month though. The flat rate is how your monthly payment is calculated as well, APR is just a marketing trick by lenders and best ignored</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 19:31:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or keep his savings and spend it on a holiday or invest it into an appreciating asset to make himself more money. Then potentially get a rental which is based on the depreciation of the vehicle so that he doesn't have any negative equity when he comes to swap his car in a couple of years time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 22:42:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Firstly, you won't pay anything other than the flat rate if you pay on time each month. Secondly if OP goes to a main dealer then they won't be using brokers like Advantage, unless he's sub prime, which it doesn't look like he is. Finally, working out what the flat rate is and what the fees are make it much easier to find out what he will be paying, instead of trying to de-code the incredibly complex nature of the APR. There isn't a salesman in the country who can work out how the APR is calculated and how it impacts the monthly payment, it's purely for marketing/legal reasons</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-26 23:51:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never mentioned anything about it being cheaper...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 00:01:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never said it includes late payment fees, just that you will only pay the flat rate if you pay on time. The reason being that late payment interest is usually charged at the APR %. If it's not that complicated, could you show me how to calculate an APR?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 14:47:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>As much as it's getting down voted, it's true. I've worked in this industry and know how it works, no dealer will take you seriously if you ask for that sort of thing, as harsh as it may sound. Most dealerships have they're own service department as well that will have inspected the car when it arrived on sight, and that will be enough, from they're point of view, to prove the condition of the car</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Landlord 'withdrawing' agreement he made with us</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 15:49:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me and a few friends moved down to London last September and our landlord wrote into the contract that it was a fixed 24 month term even though we verbally agreed to a 12 month term. We called him out on this as we were signing the agreement and he said we would be fine to leave after a year as long as we gave two months notice and helped him find replacement tenants. He emailed us the next day confirming this in writing. Fast forward to last week, we sent an email to our landlord explaining that we were unhappy with his conduct as landlord (breached contract by not giving us any notice of building work he was doing, plumbers let themselves in with their own key early in the morning, along with other smaller issues) so we felt we had grounds to try and terminate our tenancy early. We sent him an email stating that we would be leaving in September this year (12 months early), due to his breach of contract. and that we would not be helping find new tenants. He has since emailed us back saying that since we have stated this, even if we withdraw our comments about not finding tenants (which we will withdraw) he has permanently withdrawn the agreement of letting us leave early, even if we do help find tenants. Is there anything we can do and does he have legal grounds to withdraw his offer permanently?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 21:59:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the help! Just to clarify, we are all happy to help find tenants to replace us if we leave in September, as per the original deal. Is our landlord legally allowed to stop us from doing this, even though we have it in writing from him?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 22:04:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the reply, like I said, we have it in writing that he's happy for us to leave if we find replacement tenants, and we're happy to do so now. Surely he has to honour this agreement even though he's now saying he won't?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the legal and proper way to sign a contract on behalf of a client as an agent?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 13:58:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am an agent and have secured some work-for-hire for a client of mine. For the first time since I've been representing him, he is not able to sign the agreement between him and the company hiring him as he is 300 miles away. What is the legal way to sign on behalf of him considering I have his explicit permission to do so?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 14:34:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great, thanks for the advice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>