<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject2974</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 23:19:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>This tactic is called "neighbor spoofing" and it's really common. I get these robocalls in waves, like one week I'll get them several times a day, and the next nothing. The FCC has been catching some of the people doing this, and actually [fined some guy in Miami $120m for making 97 million robocalls](https://gizmodo.com/fcc-accuses-florida-man-of-making-97-million-robocalls-1825376234), yet it still happens. My method for dealing with it has been just to ignore any call coming from the same area code and prefix as my number, since I have a cell phone anyway and I know the calls aren't coming from a neighbor. Apparently there is an app called Robokiller that is pretty popular and effective at blocking it, too, but I'd have to pay for it. Here's their site explaining the neighbor spoof phenomenon: https://www.robokiller.com/blog/local-call/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 00:38:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Republicans would eat shit despite its nasty smell"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 17:15:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I suspect Newsweek is using their site to mine bitcoin because it's become so slow in the past year or so. I can't even read them on my iPhone anymore. Too bad because I like Kurt Eichenwald.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 17:25:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, a fantasy world where Jesus needs to be taught in school, and evolution is a invention of the Devil.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 17:28:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Somebody needs to be the crazy conservative and Scalia ain't around anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 00:39:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tony the Tiger says, "They're greeeeaaaaaat!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 00:40:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Super cereal post</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 05:34:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trump posts in r/legaladvice: "How president can fire special counsel? (Asking for a friend.)"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 15:20:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Christians 2000 years ago: "Crucify us, burn us, exile us, fill us with arrows, feed us to lions... we will still persist because we believe Jesus Christ is the Lord and Savior of all mankind!" Christians today: "OMG people won't say Merry Christmas anymore, I can't be a Christian!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 16:08:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It needs three disembodied wolf heads howling at the moon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 16:21:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're right. Let's also fire everyone who called First Lady Hillary Clinton a "bitch" and chanted "Lock her up." Especially the teachers, because they should never teach their hate again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 16:32:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Romney will win the primary by an extremely high margin. The delegates at the Utah convention blocked him because he criticized Trump, not because of anything he did to support Trump. It was very vindictive. But the delegates aren't very representative of the voters in Utah. The delegates are more extreme and more partisan than the heavily Mormon voters, who are still pretty uncomfortable with Trump's rhetoric.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 00:13:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>FUCK YEAH SPARKLE SPARKLE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 00:16:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>"The Bat CREDIT CARD?!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 19:49:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meanwhile the GOP will do whatever they can to make it harder for poor people to vote. Fewer polling locations in their area, shorter hours, and more stringent ID requirements.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 19:56:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, like Elliott Rodger. On the surface, if you just look at photos of him, he isn't a bad looking guy, at all. He's actually kinda attractive. Then you read about him or listen to him rant on video, and it's clear why he couldn't get a girlfriend. He was a fucking psycho, even before he shot up a sorority.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 18:22:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup, it was the celebration after his first inauguration. Per [Wikipedia](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/First_inauguration_of_Andrew_Jackson) :  gt; The White House was opened to all for a post-inaugural reception, and was filled by the public even before Jackson arrived on horseback. Soon afterward, Jackson left by a window or a side entrance, and proceeded to Gadsby's Hotel in Old Town Alexandria, Virginia. The crowd continued to descend into a drunken mob, only dispersed when bowls of liquor and punch were placed on the front lawn of the White House. "I never saw such a mixture," said Joseph Story, then a justice of the Supreme Court: "The reign of King Mob seemed triumphant." The White House was left a mess, including several thousand dollars worth of broken china.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 18:26:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>According to legend, after all the party-goers were thrown out of the White House, they stayed on the lawn and chanted, "Give us the wine and give us the cheese!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 21:01:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmmm... It's almost as if Russia's involvement in the 2016 election is just the tip of a giant iceberg involving decades of Russia trying to manipulate other nations and decades of Trump running a shady, mob-like international business empire.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 21:23:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Higher density isn't the answer. I've been to Shanghai, and the sea of highrise apartments is dismal. You can drive for an hour and still be surrounded by identical concrete towers and smog. It's so depressing. I would rather have a beautiful city that focuses on excellent public transportation, like Berlin, where greenspaces have been preserved but it's easy for people to travel by train from the suburbs to the city center.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 22:04:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>The same could be said about almost any European metropolis (though, yes, Berlin might have had the worst depopulation due to WWII). But despite the horrible reason that these cities had to rebuild, they do have exemplary public transportation and I would much rather Seattle keep its historical character than let devrlopment run amok like it does it many cities where they don't give a damn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 23:32:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>My point is not to become Shanghai, or any of the other poorly planned megacities in Asia. Just because everybody wants to live in Seattle doesn't mean Seattle should bend over backwards to let them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 01:11:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shanghai has an astounding population of 24 million people. 40% of the population are migrants who don't have residency permits and have very limited access to public facilities like hospitals. The Chinese government is actively trying to limit the population of Shanghai and Beijing, and forcibly removing slums. The pollution in Shanghai is unhealthy and people there will not live as long because of it. It's nothing to make light of. When I went there, I didn't see the sun for two weeks. There were disabled people begging in the street, wearing rags and selling knickknacks made of garbage. They had huge underground markets full of counterfeit goods, where the air stank of car fumes and I could barely breathe. Pudong was cleaner and more orderly, but that's clearly a newer part of the city that China has groomed as the place for Westerners to feel comfortable. So Shanghai did not strike me not a pinnacle of urban planning.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 16:28:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bruce Lee's grave is in a cemetery next to a park I go to all the time. I really should go walk around that cemetery because it looks pretty cool (and kinda creepy).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 17:01:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Old man yells at cloud.](https://imgur.com/gallery/91sn32Q)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 18:08:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a children's book called [King of the Wind](https://www.amazon.com/King-Wind-Story-Godolphin-Arabian/dp/1416927867/ref=nodl_), a fictionalized account of the Godolphin Arabian and his stable boy. I picked it up from the school library when I was young and read the whole thing. Great book!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 20:39:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, it's funny until you have to share your screen with a client. Oops.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-27 20:59:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember a little while back there was a post about Flynn selling his house with a link to the real estate listing. One of the pictures of the house's garage had a couple of child car seats on the wall. I kinda felt bad after that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 04:48:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Without traffic, the drive is about 15 min. During rush hour, Google Maps takes me through a hellish journey through steep residential streets, requiring me to cross four lane arterials and dodge joggers next to Green Lake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 18:30:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is like watching a schizophrenic homeless man yelling on a street corner, word salad and all. Just put him in a bad suit, slick back his hair, and spray paint his face orange.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 16:13:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought Trump made it so we could be politically incorrect again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 17:17:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe our society needs to glorify a more reasonable form of masculinity. Being a "real man" =/= fucking women.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 17:53:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, I enjoy having sex. It's awesome and most humans also enjoy it. I'm not saying men or anyone should stop having sex. I specifically said "fucking women" because the masculinity being glorified by incels isn't even about pleasure anymore, or even companionship. It's about establishing dominance and higher status by penetrating and inseminating a female.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 22:03:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>So political correctness is only bad when it's invoked against conservatives. Got it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 18:07:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bat Boy is Weekly World News, not National Enquirer. Get your bullshit news sources straight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 18:35:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/thathappened</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 19:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 00:41:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>If Trump deserves a Nobel Peace Prize, Hitler should get a posthumous one for unifying and rejuvenating Europe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 01:15:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, this is an important distinction. There's a lot of nuance in the histories of their platforms. Democrats and Republicans switched different positions at different times for many different reasons, in response to major events and the resulting political pressures, like the Great Depression, the World Wars, the Civil Rights Era, the Vietnam War, etc. These switches are ongoing, too. Like Republican Nixon actually created the EPA to fight pollution and promote environmental protections, which today are a big part of the Democratic platform. And the Democrat LBJ dug us deeper into the Vietnam War by invoking the draft in 1969, which Nixon later ended because it was deeply unpopular, yet the deescalation of conflicts is considered a Democratic position these days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 01:58:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you can't tell someone that you love them because they're an ex, or you've never had a relationship with them, or a relationship isn't possible for whatever reason, it's not love; it's a one-way obsession and you need to move on for your own sanity.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 02:12:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah... I was about to defend this person because, as someone who will soon have a second child, I hope he doesn't have severe autism or any debilitating problems. I don't wish that on any parents. But then I read their later comments and realized they actually did think vaccines caused autism. Oof.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 17:16:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I like your edginess, sykotocwit. You're hired!" \- Dan Savage, probably</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 18:35:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, Trump acts like an idiot, but I think his comment about being able to murder someone on 5th Avenue without repercussions reveals he knows he can push his base and the Republicans as far as he wants. They're morally bankrupt at this point but they still have the delusion that they're the righteous ones as long as they oppose LBGTQ rights, gun control, and abortion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 21:57:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I'm doing my part!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 01:07:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>While your argument sounds okay, I'm gonna have to downvote for ending with a blind link to some obscure, no-context YouTube video.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 01:27:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congratulations. Blind links to YouTube videos posted by nobodies are a great way to waste my cellphone data without telling me why I should care about the video.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 03:08:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>This White House drama has gone beyond jumping the shark. It's jumping whales now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 17:23:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Over half of Americans believe abortion should be legal in most cases, with another quarter believing it should be more restricted but legal in very limited cases. Abortion isn't an "alternative" to birth control; it's a backup in case it fails. And if you're hoping the Catholic Church would help pay for contraception, you're very uninformed. They won't even endorse the use of condoms, let alone give them to people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 21:28:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometimes you don't even need to ask the question. Just mention the weather and Trump will go on a tangent about "doing something" about the Justice Department.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 22:09:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>But the National Enquirer said they had a polygraph expert run Trump's recorded voice through a super special machine and it said Trump is 110% truthful. Check and mate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 05:20:34</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Lo0k I see what you did there...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 15:53:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sad thing is I keep seeing people post in the Seattle subreddits that we need to elect a Giuliani to clear out the increasing number of homeless people. Even in such a liberal place, people think getting a tough guy is a cure for a complicated problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 21:54:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apologize to all of America, more like it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 07:14:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck, I feel like we've been repeating the same week over and over again. We're stuck in a time loop of scandal, distraction, propaganda blitz, rinse, repeat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 20:44:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even if he was misinformed or ignorant, who the fuck goes on national TV and spouts off bullshit knowing it's bullshit? The. Best. People.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 23:41:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know Pence wishes he were Chancellor Palpatine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 23:57:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/iamverybadass</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 00:01:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>What if I put the knife on a rifle, like a bayonet? Is it okay then?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 04:34:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Breitbart pandering to their incel audience.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 03:34:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>And Benjamin Harrison won the electoral college because his party was buying off voters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 05:20:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not opposed to getting rid of the EC. The EC actually makes it easier to game the presidential vote because fewer voters need to be swayed (or, in the case of the election of Benjamin Harrison, bought). Because a major perversion of the EC is that the votes in most states is that it's all or nothing, so a candidate just needs one more vote than 50% and they get all the EC votes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 18:43:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup, it's called "neighbor spoofing." I get these in waves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 18:44:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got one of these in the last week. My iPhone said I was calling myself. I picked it up and it claimed to be ATT asking for my SSN.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 06:43:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Funny, I've been calling that one the Popsicle Building because there's [a big popsicle sculpture](https://www.roadsideamerica.com/tip/40106) in front of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 06:46:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember the windshear around this building being really awful, too. Like I couldn't walk down Blanchard past the alley behind it on a really windy day because the wind it channeled broke my umbrella and knocked me over.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 17:53:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rybolovlev has also been involved in shady dealings on the ultra-fine art market. He's been involved with [Yves Bouvier](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Bouvier_Affair), a disgraced Swiss art dealer who's been charged with art-related fraud and theft and money laundering. Rybolovlev has claimed to be a victim of Bouvier, though he has greatly profited from their ventures, including Rybolovlev's recent sale of Leonardo da Vinci's *Salvador Mundi* for a record-breaking $450m to the Dubai Louvre.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 18:18:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>"This person is unelectable, please don't elect them." You know, I hear this about progressive candidates all the time, and now that the argument is used on a conservative it really sounds absurd.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 20:20:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Compilation failed due to the following error: ...wut?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 21:03:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>These 80s nostalgia trends are getting way outta hand. What's next? Bring back the savings and loan associations?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Skyscrapers affects street winds by channelling winds downward. The problem is often worse around buildings with sharper corners. When the Flatiron Building was completed in NYC in 1902, it caused a stir because the winds next to it blew women's skirts above their ankles.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 21:21:12</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 23:18:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like he should be given an executive position at the NRA.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-07 23:26:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmmm, reminds me of... [ #8216;No Way To Prevent This, #8217; Says Only Nation Where This Regularly Happens](https://www.theonion.com/no-way-to-prevent-this-says-only-nation-where-this-r-1819576527)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 00:00:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bingo. I'd say "if all you have is a hammer, everything looks like a nail," but that's too kind. These gun nuts know full well that the NRA and the pro-gun conservatives in government are blocking any real efforts to address gun violence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 01:26:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>She has to wake up every morning in a house built by slaves. And she watches her son, a beautiful, intelligent, black young man, playing with his dogs on the White House lawn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 16:55:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>M'podium</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 22:29:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>To isolate the US and make them less relevant to world politics, which improves Russia's international standing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 22:34:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trump is trying to swing his big American hammer, but I don't think he can bring trade with Europe to a halt. He's flailing like the big idiot he is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 16:58:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check out the former Governor of Maryland and Vice President under Nixon, [Spiro Agnew](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spiro_Agnew), the only VP to resign in disgrace. Agnew had been accepting kickbacks in exchange for lucrative government contracts ever since he was a prominent Maryland politician, and he continued doing so as VP. They bribed him more directly back then, by giving him envelopes of money. The US Attorney for Maryland managed to catch him by having one of the bribers testify and bribe Agnew in the White House, among other evidence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 17:41:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>It brought down Vice President Spiro Agnew. https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spiro_Agnew</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 17:44:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL Cooley is also the worst medical school in the nation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 19:46:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had this discussion with a barista at a local coffee shop (not Starbucks). If the latte is made with whole cow's milk, it's exempt. If it's made with a milk substitute like soy or almond milk, it will be taxed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 20:02:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's the FAQ from the city: https://www.seattle.gov/Documents/Departments/FAS/BusinessLicenseTax/SBT-distributor-FAQ.pdf Question 16 details what is excluded, including "Any beverage in which natural milk is the primary ingredient." If I go look up [the actual law](http://clerk.seattle.gov/~scripts/nph-brs.exe?s1=5-953.NUM. amp;l=20 amp;Sect6=HITOFF amp;Sect5=BTXN1 amp;d=BTXN amp;p=1 amp;u=/~finance/btxn1.htm amp;r=1 amp;f=G), it says (emphasis added):  gt;"Milk" means natural fluid milk, regardless of animal sources or butterfat content; natural milk concentrate, whether or not reconstituted, regardless of animal source or butterfat content; or dehydrated natural milk, whether or not reconstituted and regardless of animal source or butterfat content; **and plant-based milk substitutes that are marketed as milk, such as but not limited to, soy milk, coconut milk, rice milk, and almond milk.** So the barista was indeed mistaken.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 20:07:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, let's give the school bully the award for Mr. Congeniality, too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 20:45:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trump is already selling accesss with Mar-a-Lago memberships. So at this point the most surprising part is that they're doing it so brazenly, and that my stupid cellular provider is in on it so they can screw me harder than they already have been.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 20:51:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>DRAIN THAT SWAMP! ... right into Michael Cohen's shell corporation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 21:05:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or move to the liberal oasis of Salt Lake City, where they've been gerrymandered into irrelevance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 21:23:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trump apparently used his father's funeral to announce his latest real estate project.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 23:03:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apparently the Australian version doesn't contain quinine, according to Wikipedia: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Irn-Bru</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 23:16:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's not true unless such statements become a self fulfilling prophecy. The potential insolvency of Social Security is a looming problem due to the retirement of the Baby Boomers, because later generations are smaller and won't be able to pay enough to cover the influx of retirees. But the projected shortfall is around something like 25%, so maybr 75% of benefits would still be available, and it would even out as the Boomers pass away and the rate of retirees goes down. So the problem to be addressed is getting some measure to cover the shortfall in funds in the meantime. (There's also a danger that people try to dismantle or sabotage Social Security instead of fixing it.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 00:27:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I currently use AT amp;T because once upon a time they were the only carrier who supported iPhone. I guess it's time to switch. Are any of the other iPhone carriers not douches?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 00:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought it was because we don't want to confuse her with Bernie Sanders. Not that she's anything like Bernie Sanders, but when she first appeared in headlines I was confused about who this crazy new "Sanders" person was at the White House, until I looked up her bio. Now I rarely see journalists refer to her as just "Sanders."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 01:03:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>"What's your profession?" "Businessman." "But what business?" "Every." "Every what!" "Every business."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 03:29:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you don't go out and shop, the terrorists win, people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 16:07:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is gross, not net. That's how Washington B amp;O tax works. It's always gross revenue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 17:39:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>**G**aslighting **O**bstruction **P**rojection</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 21:54:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literal shills.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 00:47:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your user name is literally [the infamous fascist prime minister of Spain](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Francisco_Franco) who gave support to Axis powers in WWII.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 04:33:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine too, a couple years ago. I laughed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 04:36:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a visual representation of the bishop in *The Princess Bride* saying "Marriage." https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u2m6sHROA3U</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 06:04:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh wow, and look--he has good old Ollie North on next. Can Fox News get any stupider or shittier?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 16:27:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like an argument against the "Okies" from *The Grapes of Wrath.*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 18:53:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>And "the law is the law" apparently doesn't apply when the President or his henchmen break the law.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 18:59:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're talking about ripping actual children away from their parents, not twenty-year-olds living in their parents' basements.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:04:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shit, I read the comment. What do I owe?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 19:07:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there a shell company I can wire it to?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 20:56:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>And the fourth district includes Summit County, home of Park City and the most liberal county in Utah.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 21:28:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Suppressing women's rights? Silencing other religions? Torturing political dissidents? Sounds like he's doing things the Republicans would really love to do in America. Trump must be super jealous.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 23:38:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah it's L** #242; #211;**k</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 23:38:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>L** #242; #211;**k</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 07:01:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>What? You saw a video of a Nazi getting punched by random people near 3rd and Pine? Fake news, I say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 07:05:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uhhhhhhh... I mean, yeah, when she and McCain were roundly defeated by Obama and Biden, that was pretty awesome. I cried that night.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 07:07:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ew, gross, it's Shitbarf.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 16:12:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>They would've used paper back then for wrapping. Plastic (synthetic polymer) was invented in 1907, as bakelite, but it first was used to make rigid things. Polyethylene, a plastic more suitable for bags, was invented in 1933, but the plastic bag didn't become common until the 1960s.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 16:36:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>They should spend it on universal healthcare, with free mental health services for everyone, including the homeless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 16:40:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>California isn't the most populous state because of its nice climate and robust economy; it's because their communist government doesn't allow anyone to leave!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 16:45:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I read it, that's why I mentioned the homeless. I'm from Seattle and we're quite familiar here with other states sending their homeless populations over (including many, many, many from California). Throwing money at just the nebulous "homeless crisis" hasn't helped, but I do believe lack of access to free mental health programs, including drug addiction programs, is a big contributor to homelessness in general.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 17:57:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Food packaging changed a lot in the late 19th Century with industrialization. The paper technology got a lot better and cheaper by the beginning of the 20th Century. They found ways to make less acidic papers, and used waxes like paraffin to make them more suitable for containing food.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-12 20:43:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That "whatever" is like a facility outside of the law, where their detainees can't be charged with any crimes but they have no rights because they're children. Like the girl who was trying to sue for an abortion for a pregnancy due to rape was in their loving "care," and her foster whatever tried to find some way to "reverse" her abortion when she managed to obtain one. Edit: link to the story about this https://www.vox.com/identities/2018/2/2/16957378/scott-lloyd-trump-unaccompanied-minors-abortion-pill-reversal-teenager</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 06:50:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in Seattle, and I gotta say, IMO crab cakes made with blue crab claw meat are the best. Dungeness doesn't taste as good--too briny versus the sweet blue crab meat. (But the absolute best crab I ever had was stone crab in the Bahamas.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 16:46:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>"My coworkers disrespect me because I smell like shit. Instead of taking a shower every day, I'll just keep rolling in shit. I found some guys online who said this will make people respect me."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 17:49:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>How's that Koolaid tasting these days?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 18:38:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where there's smoke, there's fire #8212;and goat blowing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 04:43:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sure if Harry Potterism became a real religion, people would find a way to be shitty to each other in the name of Harry Potter. Organized religion is about power, regardless of the traditions behind it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 05:45:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>And the shitshow due to the US embassy moving to Jerusalem. Yikes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 05:47:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hillary personally went to Pyongyang and left a flaming bag of dog turds on Kim Jong-Un's porch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 01:01:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I was a teenager, I would get anxious if someone spoke a different language in my vicinity, because I thought they could be talking about me. Now that I'm older and more mature, I understand that 99.99999% of conversations aren't about me, regardless of language. But I wonder if these grown up idiots complaining about people who use a different language around them actually think these "foreigners" are making fun of them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 21:43:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, that's the real point of school vouchers #8212;not to give parents more choice, but to create a legal wealth transfer to private schools, most of which are run by churches.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 22:44:37</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Access to successful western democracies is *not* a human right. If that's their motive, that must be why there's a net outflow of undocumented immigrants from the US right now. I mean, I wish it was *my* right as a US citizen to have access to a successful democracy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 23:05:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know when I was looking at condos downtown a couple years ago, there was a condo for sale next to the market that has some sort of special assessment and a temporary construction easement to address how construction was going to affect their building. It was clear how this would affect the condo value, but the condo still sold for way more than asking. Apparently SDOT has been working on these arrangements for a long time: https://www.seattle.gov/Documents/Departments/Council/Issues/Viaduct/Answers_for_Council_Property_Right_Acquisition_Waterfront_Program_May_2014.pdf</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 17:04:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>An abortion doesn't require a hospital stay, unless it's very late in a pregnancy and there are complications. The vast majority are done on an outpatient basis.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 21:59:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, I could eat the Moons Over My Hammy every day for the rest of my life. I want to marry that sandwich.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 23:37:01</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; with [him](http://i.imgur.com/7ANgpfY.jpeg) You posted a picture of a handsome shirtless male fitness model. If there's a video of him following a woman into a bathroom, it's probably a porno. Edit: Okay, so I guess the handsome fitness model is a trans man. I vaguely remember something about him, but I guess I wasn't so triggered by his very existence that I've thought about him every time I dropped trou in the ladies' restroom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 23:54:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>So? I'm not looking at people's junk or getting in their face when I'm in the bathroom. I'm not the genital police. I do my business and get out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-18 23:56:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>He can use whatever bathroom he wants, as long as he flushes the toilet and puts his paper towels in the trash.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 16:18:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uhhhhh... [Kent State](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kent_State_shootings)? The National Guard opened fire on students protesting the Vietnam War? Neil Young [wrote a song about it](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ohio_\(Crosby,_Stills,_Nash_%26_Young_song\))? Nixon hid in Camp David for a few days after 100k protesters descended in Washington DC to protest Kent State? And, yeah, after that Nixon met with some of the Kent State protesters at the Lincoln Memorial, but when they wouldn't agree with him, he labeled them communists and [tried to get the FBI to spy on US citizens through outright burglary](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Huston_Plan). I mean, the Patriot Act and the NSA's spying programs are like the culmination of Nixon's deepests desires.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 23:18:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, "far left" to me kinda circles back to the insanity of the far right. Like anti-vaxxers and some of the shit PETA pulls.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 04:29:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look back further and Dante Alighieri was kind of a creepy stalker obsessed with a woman named Beatrice, whom he met just a few times. But rather than lash out at women, he wrote *The Divine Comedy* and inserted her as a main character. In fact, pining after a woman without expecting anything physical in return was a medieval ideal called "courtly love." Young men were told it was noble and moral by the poets of the time. Still weird, but at least not violent.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 06:34:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course not. It was shittier back then in many, many ways. But I do think it's interesting to look at how expectations of men and masculinity have changed over time. Like these days, our culture (particularly popular culture) implies that men are naturally out-of-control horn dogs who need sex or they go crazy. A lot of guys feel entitled to it because they've learned from the culture that they're not men if they aren't having lots of sex. But if you look at masculinity before the Victorian period, it was more common for women to be labeled sex fiends who couldn't control themselves sexually. Men were encouraged to be more chaste. Often men were told having sex (and ejaculating in particular) wasted their energy or life forces, so they should save themselves for reproduction.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 16:28:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>During one of the later debates, he made a claim that many doctors were performing abortions on full term pregnancies. The idiot doesn't even know how childbirth works, either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 01:11:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reminds me of the [last episode of the first season of Black Adder](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_u8EyRTtOtc), when he gathers the most ruthless bastards in the kingdom to take over England.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 03:56:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just gonna leave this right here... [The Impact of Legalized Abortion on Crime](https://cloudfront.escholarship.org/dist/prd/content/qt00p599hk/qt00p599hk.pdf)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 06:58:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ooo, lucky! I hope to someday afford one of those fancy honeycrisp apples. I'm saving up!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 00:48:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mojito is awesome. I love the *vaca frita*. My only complaint is the service can be slow. It's also a little pricier than Bongos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 00:57:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ethiopian: There are three good ones at Northgate, all within a block of each other: Jebena, Enat, and Ahadu. Hawaiian: Super Six in Columbia City is excellent, though it's more Asian Fusion than straight Hawaiian. Kona Kitchen in Maple Leaf or Kauai Family Kitchen in Georgetown are truer to the cuisine. Indian/Himalayan: Annapurna in Capitol Hill is great for North Indian, Nepalese, and Tibetan cuisine. Malaysian/Indonesian: Try Kedai Makan in Capitol Hill.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 06:19:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't be surprised if the Trump Admin was working on initiatives to club more baby seals, promote shark fin soup, and kill every last polar bear. They're all like Captain Planet villians.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 07:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;$5500 per year Hey, they needed that money to stock the breakroom with Red Bull. How can they overwork their developers like a proper startup if they don't have enough Red Bull?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 16:26:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also healthcare and world peace.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 20:11:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kona Kitchen can be a little bland and greasy for me. They also don't have dobash cake. Kauai Family Kitchen is a bit better and it's next door to Cakes of Paradise (Kona Kitchen serves Cakes of Paradise too), so the dessert selection is better at Kauai. But I don't get to Kauai often because their hours are weird.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 19:30:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>McDonalds is not my top restaurant choice in Ballard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 22:51:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Prius is extremely popular for Uber and Lyft drivers. They're basically driving like a taxi, going as quickly and efficiently as they can by being more aggressive. (Or they're new to Uber and meandering around while trying to figure out their GPS.) BMW's are, well... rich people, I guess. I'm not sure if they're deserving of their bad driver reputation, because I've seen similarly bad drivers in all types of cars.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Netflix Is Now Worth More Than Comcast</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 23:53:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 00:35:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know people are fleeing the liberal holocaust of Seattle in droves, jamming up I-5 and I-90 with caravans of trucks and Uhaul trailers, heading for the conservative promise lands in Spokane, in Boise, in Billings. It's becoming a ghost town, I say. A ghost town! (In all seriousness, though, people do begrudgingly leave because they're pushed out by the housing prices.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 01:10:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>True. Per the article, Netflix has been worth more than Comcast before, briefly. Comcast is also a way more diverse company with lots of divisions and assets. Also, Comcast owns 30% of Hulu. The other owners are: Disney (30%), Fox (30%), and Time Warner (10%). Right now [Comcast is trying to outbid Disney to buy to the non-news parts of Fox](https://www.recode.net/2018/5/23/17385214/comcast-versus-disney-fox-hulu), including Hulu, which would give Comcast a 60% majority ownership of Hulu.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 06:07:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Serious question: WTF is wrong with Orange County?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 16:27:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>You don't deserve an apology. You just linked to an information hub about crime victimization. I have no idea where you pulled the specific stats you just quoted because there are dozens of links on that page. Even if I try to drill down on 2010, there are dozens of pages of stats. You're gonna have to give more detailed sources and methodology, bud.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 16:50:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, these are the demands of any open minded skeptic. I don't just take "facts" posted on the internet for their face value. You, the one making the outrageous claims, are the one acting entitled to my approval by saying you don't need to provide decent statistics and a real methodology.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 03:15:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's real: http://www.epicmra.com/team.htm  gt; Bernie Porn is a partner and President of EPIC #9642;MRA. Drawing on over three decades of research and communication experience, Mr. Porn's primary role with the firm involves the writing and analysis of the survey research conducted for EPIC #9642;MRA 's clients. He is also looked to by members of the media, academia and others for commentary on the wide spectrum of topics researched by the firm.  gt;Mr. Porn is a graduate of Aquinas College in Grand Rapids, majoring in urban affairs and schooled in statistics. He was a staff member in the Michigan House of Representatives for nineteen years, serving as the Director of Communications from 1990 to 1992. He worked extensively on the 1981 and 1991 Michigan legislative and congressional redistricting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 03:19:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Remember that time Hillary Clinton endorsed Sarah Palin for VP just cuz they both had lady parts? Yeah, I don't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 05:48:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>We should at least treat guns like automobiles. You know, require people to take a test to get a license to use it, and require them to renew every so often. And require they get insurance, and pay for that insurance themselves. If you use it recklessly, you're liable for the damages. If you're found carrying a gun while drunk or high, you get the gun equivalent of a DUI. And if you allow your unlicensed minor to take it out unsupervised, you get charged with a crime.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 01:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>In American history, the McCarthy Era and the Hollywood blacklist against suspected communists come to mind. This cast a pretty wide net, though, and included the persecution of a lot of different people, many of whom are regarded highly today. Joseph McCarthy's was exposed as the real baddy in the end.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 16:43:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>So this is actually the trailer for *Weekdays at Bernie's.*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 00:50:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go to Squatters and talk about how the Mormons ruin everything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 07:16:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this classified in Breitbart's "Black Crime" section?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 06:05:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope the skeeters stayed away, too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 21:13:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Being naked =/= sexual assault The law in Seattle is that public nudity is legal as long as it's not done in a lewd manner #8212;even if a kid is around #8212;so the hippie was probably reported for doing something worse than just been naked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 23:31:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, my newborn son had a UTI that had barely spread to the blood by the time he got to the ER. His only symptom was a fever, and tests found white blood cells in his urine. They started IV antibiotics and hospitalization immediately, before the blood culture came back as sepsis. They even did a blood draw twice because it's extremely hard to get a good specimen from a newborn. They also had to do two spinal taps to rule out meningitis. It seems aggressive for a little guy, but very necessary at that age. Something like 10% of newborns with fever have sepsis and/or meningitis, and they're deadly diseases. The best day of my life was learning he didn't have meningitis and that we caught the sepsis early enough that there would be no complications.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-29 07:02:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Though for the first few years, the toddler insists on being with you in the bathroom and you keep having to take away the TP and the plunger and anything else in the room.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 17:35:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I gave $50, knowing full well I didn't like Jill Stein and that she would probably piss it away. I just wanted to see some effort for a recount.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 22:23:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Catholic Church is the quintessential example of an organized religion abusing the faithful to extract money and power.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 01:28:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>The transit station tunnel under Macy's/Westlake Center/Nordstrom. is a lifesaver during parades if you need to cross 4th Ave on foot. Like during the Seahawks Super Bowl parade, it was impossible to cross on the surface.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 18:44:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dinesh Fucking D'Souza and Rod "I'll sell Obama's senate seat" Blagojevich, too?! I was already fuming about the ban on German luxury cars, then I just step away to drop the tot off at daycare and now Trump is handing out pardons like he's a Pez dispenser. He's running distraction for something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 21:21:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>These tariffs aren't just fucking over our strawberry jam. It's putting American infrastructure projects in the US in jeopardy. Like the costs on the transit upgrades here in Seattle are already getting too high due to the increased cost of construction materials. We need cheap lumber from Canada, and cheap steel. So much for Trump's grand infrastructure plans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 23:18:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I grew up in Utah suburbs, where the streets are huge yet lead to nowhere, the houses are on quarter acre lots, and you can't go anywhere without a car. No part of Seattle proper feels like true suburbia to me. Once I get into Shoreline or Federal Way, I get the suburban vibe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-31 23:28:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Suburbs still have sidewalks, at least the ones I've been in. Lack of sidewalks feels more rural to me. That said, I live north of 90th in an area without sidewalks, and it's not rural. It's still pretty urban, complete with junkies stealing from our mailbox. I feel like the lack of sidewalks in places like Northgate and Lake City are just a perversion of Seattle. Apparently we're supposed to get sidewalks in connection with the Northgate Light Rail Station, too, but cost overruns are jeopardizing that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 23:27:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>But how dare the mean liberal lady use a big elite word like "feckless."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 03:31:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I know putting arsenic in my bourbon will kill me. But what should I do? NOT put arsenic in my bourbon?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 03:57:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Putin is clearly an alien lizard person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 22:35:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a feeling that if someone mentioned today's good weather, you'd manage to thank Trump for it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 02:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>He'll probably hold it before sundown and serve pork ribs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 07:08:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's been like that for a while. Apparently it belongs to a hoarder who also puts up junk as "protest art". Here's an old Seattle PI article mentioning the house and its owner (from Google Amp so you can get around their dumb survey thing): https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.seattlepi.com/news/amp/Task-force-tries-to-save-those-who-save-too-much-1099672.php EDIT: Also found this article from 2008 with some old Seattle-style whining about the city trying to clean up her yard (caution, site only works on desktop): http://seattlest.com/2008/03/28/the_subversive.php</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-03 16:32:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or a couple of experiments by Dr. Mengele.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 00:44:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bonus, here's a legal case from 2005 where a woman by the same name sued the city of Seattle after the police forcibly detained her for acting crazy near traffic and sent her to Harborview for a mental health evaluation: https://casetext.com/case/thomas-v-city-of-seattle</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 00:53:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hawaii is super Asian and they're actually quite conservative, but the Republican party is pretty much dead there. They used to have some presence, but the current GOP agenda of anti-environmentalism and blatant racism is unacceptable in Hawaii.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-04 23:08:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a Republican talking point that comes up as a solution, but there's not really any proof that allowing people to buy insurance across state lines would significantly lower premiums. If you live in a state with high health care costs, that's due to local factors like regulations, wages, cost of goods etc. Insurers in states with lower health care costs would have to raise their premiums in order to be able to insure someone in a state with higher health care costs, or else they'd just lose money. They would also have to invest in building health care networks in another state so that you could actually use the insurance, which costs the insurer time and money, and the care providers they partner with would also have to upgrade their systems to be able to bill the out-of-state insurer, raising their own administrative costs. In fact, the ACA actually allows states to sell across state lines if they enter into "compacts," and five states have passed laws allowing it, but no insurers have taken up the offer to do so. There are a bunch of other reasons the "across state lines" solution doesn't work, too, detailed here: https://www.factcheck.org/2017/07/selling-insurance-across-state-lines/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-05 00:02:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Green Lake is my favorite. I haven't tried swimming in the lake yet, but it seems popular when it gets warm enough. The community center there has an indoor pool for when it's cool. There's also a playground and a wading pool for the tots. And there are plenty of great restaurants nearby. I like to take a leisurely stroll around the lake, which is about 2.8 miles, then get dinner. Parking is the worst part. Magnuson Park is pretty good, with a swimming beach, playground, walking paths, and wading pool. But not a lot of food options. I see a lot of people take their dogs here because there's an off-leash area. Volunteer Park is gorgeous. No swimming, but great to walk around the old trees. There's a historical conservatory and an old water tower you can climb, as well as a playground and wading pool. (The Asian Art Museum is also here, but it's closed for renovation at the moment, reopening in 2019.) The Lake View Cemetery next door is old and interesting, too. Bruce Lee and Brandon Lee are buried there, as well as a lot of Seattle's founders. I go to Maple Leap Reservoir Park a lot, too, because it's nearby and the playground is great for toddlers. There are a lot of sports fields for baseball, frisbee, soccer, etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 01:13:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have been seeing them in Maple Leaf Reservoir Park a lot. My son likes to search for them now. I don't remember seeing them since I lived in Denver several years ago. There would be swarms of bunnies in the spring. I accidentally ran one over one time when it jumped straight from a roadside bush into my car. Then the coyotes came around in the summer and killed most of them. (I hope the coyotes don't venture into Seattle. One of those bastards jumped a 6 ft fence and killed my old cat.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-08 06:10:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know what you mean. The SLC suburb I grew up in was full of these 70s split-level houses. You're getting some downvotes for pointing it out, but, yes, many people consider the split-level to be dated and kinda ugly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 22:24:46</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Aside from some more progressive churches, the consensus among Christians is that homosexuality is wrong. 70% of Catholics, 66% of mainline (non-evangelical) Protestants, and 62% of Orthodox Christians, and 51% of historically black Protestants believe that homosexuality should be accepted. Only Evangelicals, Mormons, and Jehovah's Witnesses have a majority of their members against it. ([Source: Pew Research Center](http://www.pewforum.org/religious-landscape-study/views-about-homosexuality/)). While the leadership of such organizations might be more anti-LGBTQ (especially Catholics), it's not correct to say it's a policy adopted by Christianity as a whole, or that pro-LGBTQ Christians are too few to be significant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 07:03:16</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;My friend really wants to get married ASAP and always takes her frustration to me (a boy too brown for her) because can't find a boy who suits all this perfectly. This is the sad intersection of r/niceguys and r/nicegirls.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 22:23:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Brigham Young has literally more than 30,000 descendants [by the church's own estimate](https://www.lds.org/church/news/descendants-including-general-authority-observe-brigham-youngs-birthday-at-his-grave-site?lang=eng). I suppose we could ask all of them in a poll, even though none of them actually knew the man, or just read the racist things he did and said.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 22:46:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Back in my day, we just put a big load in the washer on high spin and sat on top.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL Ridley Scott tried to make Gladiator (2000) an authentic representation of Ancient Rome. An early script had Maximus doing a product endorsement for olive oil, which was historically accurate for famous gladiators to do, but the detail was left out in later scripts for being too unbelievable.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 23:38:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 23:55:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not to mention that Maximus never existed and that the real Emperor Commodus ruled 12 years before being murdered in the bath by a wrestler named Narcissus.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 00:13:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>And more freeway overpasses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 01:41:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>The concept of sports sponsorship goes back thousands of years to the Greeks, originally coming from things like the followers of popular gods and wealthy people trying to gain favor with the public. So you'd definitely see cases like "this awesome warrior brought to you by Caesar/Cassius/Apollo." I'm trying to find exact examples of this extended to the products sold by a wealthy sponsor (perhaps a merchant), because some articles mention that ancient Roman graffiti like this has been documented. Edit: [Here's the source a lot of articles point to.](https://books.google.com/books?id=gbFQfkLKFFcC amp;pg=PA220 amp;lpg=PA220 amp;dq=gladiators+product+endorsements amp;source=bl amp;ots=_XheDFrxms amp;sig=Znz_BQNUtCtPJHj9b1Y1rjXMaFs amp;hl=en amp;sa=X amp;ved=2ahUKEwip_tXl6MzbAhUTNX0KHePNCV44ChDoATAHegQIBBAB#v=onepage amp;q=gladiators%20product%20endorsements amp;f=false) The book, [Big Screen Rome](https://www.amazon.com/Screen-Rome-Monica-Silveira-Cyrino/dp/1405116846), is written by a professor at U of New Mexico.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 01:44:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Either it was like his wrestling name, like Ric Flair, or it was his given name, which, given the bombastic reputation of Roman society, doesn't seem out of bounds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 07:10:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just reading the [Wikipedia page for Commodus](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Commodus) left me going: WTF? Like he was obsessed with portraying himself as Hercules. He used to dress as a gladiator in the arena and kill crippled soldiers who were tied to poles and disguised as giants. He really loved killing wild animals, too, and reportedly killed 100 lions in one day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 21:08:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, *Brokeback Mountain* lost Best Picture to *Crash*, a movie that people now consider cringeworthy. 2005 was in the heart of the Bush Era, when society still thought it was okay to call something they didn't like "gay."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 00:36:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>You need to add the sidewalk covered with blackberry thickets and the corners that inexplicably lack ADA-compliant curb cuts (only noticed if you're in a wheelchair or pushing a stroller).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 02:53:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or the meandering group of tourists who walk extremely slow until they completely stop in front of you and block the whole sidewalk while they try to figure out where they are. Most often found in Belltown between the market and the Seattle Center, or in Westlake looking for the monorail.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 03:42:27</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; At long last, Abraham Lincoln is ready to face his greatest enemy: Emperor Komei of Japan. After years of ninja training, will America's greatest president--who also happens to be the Earth's greatest master of the sexual arts--be able to defeat his nemesis and claim the Moon as his own? Find out in the thrilling conclusion of the Presidential Fuck Saga! Sold me on it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 06:12:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also, [sometimes dumpsters](https://www.reddit.com/r/Seattle/comments/5o798z/dumpster_on_green_lake/).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 06:57:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read through the [final text of the initiative](https://sos.wa.gov/_assets/elections/initiatives/finaltext_1531.pdf) and I don't think it's unreasonable. Sounds like it's trying to make stricter enforcement for existing laws like [RCW 9.41.040](http://app.leg.wa.gov/rcw/default.aspx?cite=9.41.040), and make sure whoever obtains a firearm is fully aware of safety practices and aware that having a firearm in the home can be potentially dangerous to those with a history or mental illness and/or suicidal risk. As for Paul Allen's museum pieces, the military is supposed to demil arms before they are sold, and the pieces in museums usually aren't functional. I can't find any sources out there about him owning and displaying a functioning German MG34, but he could legally own that particular firearm as long as he went through process of getting a Class III stamp from the ATF.\*\* This initiative wouldn't prevent anyone from doing the same. And I don't find it at all hypocritical that Paul Allen made the [Flying Heritage  amp; Combat Armor Museum](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flying_Heritage_%26_Combat_Armor_Museum_). TBH, it looks like a pretty cool museum. The history of war is still interesting and important to learn about, even for people who don't own firearms, and I'm glad people can go and see this collection. \*\*Correction: on further research, machine guns have been illegal in Washington state since 1994, but people who obtained them legally with the proper ATF clearance before then can still have them. But this initiative doesn't change that fact in the law, anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 08:10:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>[The NRA has contributed more to Washington state legislators than any other state](https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/politics/wa-has-been-ranking-no-1-for-state-candidate-contributions-from-nra-heres-why/) #8212;more than twice as much the number two state, Texas. People are pretty sick of the NRA and other pro-gun lobbyists throwing full blown toddler tantrums every time there #8217;s even a whiff of gun control gaining popularity. And now the NRA complains about people outspending them? Honestly, the proposed changes in the initiative sound far less cumbersome than getting a driver #8217;s license. And while someone under 21 can get a driver #8217;s license, driving a car is pretty much a necessity for teenagers living in some areas. Carrying a loaded gun around in public should not be a necessity. Plus, [RCW 9.41.042](http://app.leg.wa.gov/RCW/default.aspx?cite=9.41.042), which permits children to use firearms under circumstances like gun ranges and hunting, would remain unchanged (except to raise the age from 18 to 21):  gt;In the case of a person who is a prohibited person on the basis of the person's age, access to the firearm is with the lawful permission of the prohibited person's parent or guardian and supervised by an adult, or is in accordance with RCW 9.41.042</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-13 16:47:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I go to Laura's Alterations in Northgate Mall. It's fairly inexpensive, though judging by the Yelp reviews a lot of people are put off by the tailor's gruff attitude. I don't care about that, as long as the job is done right. If niceness is something you care about, check Yelp and call around for services, pricing, and turnaround times. Some dry cleaners also do tailoring, too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 05:35:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I lived in Salt Lake County, I would always get this uneasy feeling traveling through Utah County, like a Mormon was gonna pop out at any moment and judge me for something stupid like drinking a Coke. The whole place still gives me the creeps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 18:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, no, no... didn't you hear Trump today? He didn't hire Manafort as his campaign manager in order to manage his campaign. Makes total sense!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 18:47:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's going to find the Russian mob faction and kiss their ass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 21:54:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Well, Donald, I'm not sure if Starbucks is the right place to order a Russia USB drive filled with Hillary's hacked emails. Did I read this wrong?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 23:40:31</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Public opinion on the Russia investigation continues to be pretty static, with Trump voters just wanting it to go away. 63% of them want Robert Mueller fired to end the investigation, compared to only 18% who are opposed to firing him. Overall though just 30% of voters think Mueller should be fired with 54% preferring to keep him on. Also...  gt; Last June we found 42% of voters thought the Trump campaign colluded with Russia and 42% didn #8217;t. Now 45% think there was collusion and 43% think there wasn #8217;t. Last June 37% of voters said the Russia story was  #8216;fake news, #8217; and 49% said it wasn #8217;t. Now 39% say the story is  #8216;fake news, #8217; and 46% say it isn #8217;t. **Last June 36% of voters said Trump should continue as President even if collusion was proven, to 54% who said he should resign. Now 35% say Trump should continue as President even if collusion is proven, to 56% who say he should resign.** In other words, the people who approve of Trump apparently don't give a shit if he breaks the law or not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 23:45:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>"So you're saying we need to vote for someone even stupider and even more corrupt than Trump?"  #8211;Farmers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 23:58:00</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;orangest Filet o' Fish Fun fact: The fish now known as [orange roughy](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Orange_roughy) was rebranded in the 1970s because people didn't want to eat a "slimehead," its original name.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 02:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>You laugh, but a study once showed that more expensive placebos work better than cheaper ones: http://psychologyofpain.blogspot.com/2008/10/ig-nobel-prize-for-study-on-placebo.html</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 03:50:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>ballards\_anus\_blood: "Hey, honey, I posted that cool brochure your stepdad found on reddit and got a bunch of karma!" bab's GF: "Oh really? Let me see it. What's your username?" bab: "Uhhhh..."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 06:38:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL... that's the name of one of the albums by the metal band Ministry. I always thought it was a play on the phrase "the land of milk and honey," but apparently it was inspired by a souvenir mug from Tisdale: https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Land_of_Rape_and_Honey</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 23:07:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gee golly, I found it, guys! This is a supreme example of white nationalist garbage propaganda right here in the wild. Let's bag it and tag it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 16:24:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Forcing a woman to carry a child that would likely be stillborn or die in infancy due to its defects is also similar to Nazi crimes. I mean, I like Pope Francis as far as popes go. But I #8217;m over letting a powerful group of only  #8220;celibate #8221; old men dictate reproductive policy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 16:45:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>The SPD police blotter just posted about it: http://spdblotter.seattle.gov/2018/06/17/detectives-investigating-belltown-shooting/ I used to live in the same building as Bathtub Gin. I recall there being quite a few times when someone has been shot at the corner of Blanchard and 1st. I think the alleys and the parking lots back there can be super sketchy, especially on a Saturday night with all the bar activity. It gets worse in the summer. I heard gunshots a few times. I once was crossing the street around there on a Saturday night and someone nearly ran me over in the crosswalk. I gave them a nasty look and kept going. They went all the way around the block to find me again and got out of their car to come after me. They looked pissed and high AF, so I ran into my locked building a fast as I could.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 17:04:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lady Sarah McCorquodale also dated Prince Charles before Diana did. She's bragged before about introducing the royal couple. Later she was also one of Diana's ladies-in-waiting. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lady_Sarah_McCorquodale</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 17:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like they changed the headline to something less confusing:  gt; A Researcher Got Paid $300,000 to Resign After He Said Shooting Wolves Is Bad I found the conclusion of his research interesting:  gt; He found that the rate of wolves preying on livestock actually goes up the more wolves in an area are killed, because it destabilizes the pack #8217;s dynamics. This effect continues until 25 percent of the wolf population has been killed, at which point cattle depredation decreases, but, Wielgus noted, killing a quarter of the population is unsustainable over time. In other words: if wolves are killing your cattle, killing the wolves will only make the problem worse unless you kill a quarter of their population.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 18:49:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not religious, but Proverbs 26 is pretty spot on. It shows that these ass hats aren't anything new and have been around since the dawn of humankind. https://www.biblegateway.com/passage/?search=Proverbs+26 amp;version=NIV  gt; ^4 Do not answer a fool according to his folly, or you yourself will be just like him.  gt; ^11 As a dog returns to its vomit, so fools repeat their folly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 19:37:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sat through a couple of green lights like this, waiting for the bus to be able to turn on Boren.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-18 23:45:20</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; The aunt said what made the call even more painful was that there was nothing she could do. She and her 9-year-old daughter are seeking asylum in the United States after immigrating here two years ago for the exact same reasons and on the exact same route as her sister and her niece. They are from a small town called Armenia, about an hour #8217;s drive northwest of the Salvadoran capital, but well within reach of its crippling crime waves. She said **gangs were everywhere in El Salvador:  #8220;They #8217;re on the buses. They #8217;re in the banks. They #8217;re in schools. They #8217;re in the police. There #8217;s nowhere for normal people to feel safe. #8221;** I really don't buy the argument that these asylum seekers don't qualify because their reasons aren't political enough. These Latin American countries have massive problems with corruption, far worse than the US. If a country isn't taking care of their citizens with a functioning police force, that is a political issue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 00:00:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can barely stand my toddler crying over silly things like the color of his sippy cup or having to wear a shirt he doesn't like. Young children need their guardians in order to feel secure and let them know things will be okay, whether their distress is that they want their favorite toy or they're very sick. Taking this security away from them is the definition of cruelty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 00:16:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish Gov. Inslee would do the same here in Washington. A bunch of the parents are being held by ICE at a detention center near SeaTac. https://splinternews.com/congresswoman-on-immigrants-treatment-at-detention-cent-1826733087</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 20:28:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>She could raise her numbers among conservatives if she just dyed her hair blonde, too. (And I wish I were sarcastic about this, but look at most the female anchors on Fox News.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 22:11:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know. It's like free advertising.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-19 22:16:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seems like most eateries I go to have already switched over to the compostable utensils and straws.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 03:07:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you read the data closer, it's saying females are more likely to attempt suicide or experience suicide ideation, but males are more likely to kill themselves successfully. I've read before this has to do with the fact that suicidal females are more likely to seek help for mental health, and that suicidal males are more likely to use a method that is quick and effective like a gun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 03:12:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just when you thought Paul Manafort had to be Trump's worst campaign manager.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 03:55:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yet the Republicans tried to say having a "taco truck on every corner" would be the horrible consequence of the Democrats' immigration policies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 07:15:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Before a young child first starts daycare, the parents are encouraged to bring the child a few times for visits, so the child understands that they #8217;re in a safe place and their mommy or daddy will come back to pick them up. The parents don #8217;t come back to pick up their kids from Trump Hotels.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 16:33:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I signed the petition outside of a Target. The guy at the table didn't say a word to me except "thank you" afterward.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 22:37:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>What did you expect? They're not grammar Nazis, they're just plain Nazis.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-20 23:38:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pecker doesn't own *Weekly World News* anymore, but he never really owned Batboy, [who endorsed Obama in 2008, protested Prop 8, and is foretold to become President in 2028](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bat_Boy_\(character\)).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 01:43:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only speeding ticket I've gotten in the last decade was on northbound Aurora, just after the bridge. I was going 55+ like everyone else. The motorcycle cop picked me off easily. I don't speed there anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 05:29:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm getting the impression that pro-gun people are attacking the signature gatherers for the gun control initiative because their arguments against the actual initiative are unpopular and don't hold water.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 06:50:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just because something is in public doesn't mean it's in the public domain and anybody can use its likeness. Take for instance the Space Needle. It's the most iconic building in the Seattle skyline, but anybody who wants to use it on their products has to pay its owner, the Space Needle Corporation, to do so. Nobody is exempt from this #8212;including non-profits or government. Even the City of Seattle has to pay them to use pictures of it. And the Space Needle Corp. is very aggressive about enforcing their copyright. Apparently if you try to use a photograph of the Seattle skyline that happens to have the Space Needle, you can do that, but many artists and photographers still complain about those images getting removed from Getty Images or other sites for copyright infringement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 06:57:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. You can see an entire list of copyrighted landmarks on Shutterstock's site here (including "the Bean"): https://www.shutterstock.com/blog/contributor-resources/legal/stock-photo-restrictions They won't allow any images with those landmarks on their site unless the copyright owner allows it, else they could get sued.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 07:21:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>But the thing is that copyright law doesn't just cover monetization (AKA commercial usage). The copyright owner also reserves the right to control *how* their intellectual property is presented to the public. So the copyright owner does have a case if they say they didn't want the work associated with the NRA or the NRA's message in the video. And, yes, the NRA can argue "fair use," but fair use is such a nebulous thing that even the US Copyright Office says that fair use can only be defined on a case-by-case basis through a court ruling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 07:27:52</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;He is unlikely to win in court. Honestly, the artist and the NRA will probably just settle it out of court for an undisclosed amount of money.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 16:18:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Aurora is the dividing line between Greenwood and Licton Springs, Greenwood being considered the "nicer" neighborhood. Though Licton Springs has also seen a lot of price appreciation and home sales recently and has become popular, Greenwood has a lot more "culture" and things to do, especially around Greenwood Ave. There has been an increase in "sketch" in Aurora around this area because of a homeless encampment, so I've seen more homeless milling about and more reports of crime. Mostly the crime is property, like mail theft or people messing with your vehicle and yard. I would check actual crime statistics for the specific area you're thinking of before passing judgment. But that encampment may not be there forever and crime statistics could improve. I'd be very worried about is how close the house is to Aurora. If you can hear significant road noise from the house, this will decrease its resale value, and the road noise will never get better. 2. My friend who lived in Licton Springs took the E line to downtown every day. He had one incident of coming across a dazed homeless man with a bloody face. My friend wasn't attacked, though. Homeless incidents are on the uptick all over, too. 3. I haven't lived in South Seattle before, so I can't comment much on the places down there. That friend who lived in Licton Springs bought a house in Leschi because it's less expensive than North Seattle. I hear good things about Columbia City and have been to the restaurants down there a few times (they're pretty good). For us, we decided to go with North Seattle instead of South because the schools are rated better, which may or may not be an issue for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 18:58:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Their incompetence knows no bounds. It's like hiring a bunch of idiots to remodel your house. I know in a couple years all the plumbing will be leaking and the electrical shorting out, the drywall sagging and the flooring coming up. We're just going to have to rip out all their work and have real professionals fix it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 19:08:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds like they just want some time to make the baby cages nicer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 23:10:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good to know. My toddler just became interested in the zoo and loves elephants despite never ever seeing a real one. So it was a little disappointing to find out the zoo had no elephants.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 17:37:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be fair, someone just told her the jacket had a quote from a Michelle Obama speech on it. /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 21:44:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>"So... what do you do for a living?" "I... um... proofread press releases for the Trump administration. Hey, wait, where are you going?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 21:45:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've heard incels argue that sex should be redistributed like wealth gets redistributed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 21:49:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>["Work Sets You Free"](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arbeit_macht_frei)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 02:15:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe adopt a motif with like lightning bolts and put skulls on their uniform.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:21:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have a lot of Eritreans here in Seattle. It's a country next to Ethiopia that broke away from Ethiopia in 1991. I didn't know much else about it, so I looked it up on Wikipedia after encountering a huge Eritrean festival at a local park one day. I was surprised how awful a government it had, and yet I'd never heard of the problems there before. One party runs the country, they haven't held elections since its inception, and all media is state-owned. All Eritreans 18-40 are required to be in the military, with no limit on when their service ends. A lot of people leave for that reason alone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 07:45:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gharials have those weird buggy eyes and the long pokey snoot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 17:10:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even if absolutely nothing is done to fix the current insolvency crisis of social security, you'd still get 3/4 of what you paid into it back. Quit saying you're never going to see any of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 18:47:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Article XII](https://www.snopes.com/news/2016/07/24/donald-trump-article-xii/) of the Constitution says he can do it. Edit: /s I'm joking, people. Article XII doesn't exist, but that didn't stop Trump from telling other Republicans it was one of his favorite parts of the Constitution. The link is to a Snopes article about his statement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 18:49:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, [Article XII](https://www.snopes.com/news/2016/07/24/donald-trump-article-xii/) says he can do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 19:18:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Article XII doesn't exist. I was referring to an incident where Trump told Republican congresspeople his favorite articles were Article I and Article XII, and numerous Republicans seemed shocked that Trump didn't know the Constitution. The story is at that link. https://www.snopes.com/news/2016/07/24/donald-trump-article-xii/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 00:49:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was in pretty much the same situation last year, where the baby died around 8 weeks and my body didn't recognize it for a couple weeks. I was in pain and the doctor gave three options: wait for the miscarriage, which could take weeks; take drugs to induce miscarriage faster; or get a procedure to clear it. I opted for surgery because I wanted to get it over with. It feels absolutely awful to have a dead fetus in you. But it's a pretty expensive procedure if you don't have insurance and the drugs are cheaper. If I had chosen the drugs and the pharmacist denied me, I would've screamed at them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 16:59:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I saw that right over Maple Leaf yesterday while walking down 8th Ave. Pretty cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 18:01:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Justice Boner engaged.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 18:06:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>But lying is apparently part of the Evangelical religion now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 01:12:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>My Spanish textbook back in the 1990s had a lesson in it where you had to match a picture of people to the Spanish demonym. The picture for "Americanos" was a couple of fat tourists wearing tacky clothes with cash falling out of the pockets. All the demonym pictures were dumb stereotypes, but this one actually made me, the American, laugh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 01:31:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>My father is a Vietnam vet who started seeking care at the VA because the private medical insurance he gets from his employer isn't enough. He's past retirement age and soon won't be able to afford anything but what Medicare and the VA can offer him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 02:11:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's another weird building over in Belltown, [2101 2nd Ave](https://www.pnwarchitecture.com/Building/5120/CenturyLinkBuilding.php), called the CenturyLink Building. It looks like a fortress with not a lot of windows and I'm not even sure how people get inside. I always figured it was full of their network hardware.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 07:40:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; #8220;The time is now for our Congress to step up and confront the biggest challenge to our society, #8221; said House Budget Chairman Rep. Steve Womack (R-Ark.).  #8220;There is not a bigger enemy on the domestic side than the debt and deficits. #8221; You #8217;re the ones who blew up the debt with your party #8217;s stupid tax cuts, Steve. Maybe undo those if debt is the worst thing ever.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 16:00:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>She also didn't try to sell herself enough to me. She was too careful with her words and she didn't personally come to my house to read through the hundreds of pages about her extensive platform readily available on her website.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 02:57:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I might get some hate for saying so, but I frequent P. F. Changs on 4th and Pine. Yes, it's a huge chain, but you can't get more American Chinese than this. My favorites are the Chang's spicy chicken and Hokkien street noodles. But if you want a local restaurant instead, Red Lantern in the ID is pretty good, too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 06:32:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whoever wrote is probably 100% aware that people who don't support Trumps and his spineless Republicans think "thoughts and prayers" is a vapid response to mass shootings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 18:37:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>While surgical abortion is more dangerous, it's a relatively safe procedure as far as surgeries go. It's usually done with something called a dilation and curettage (D amp;C), aided with vacuum aspiration, which reduces risk of complications. In fact, D amp;C is used for a lot of other medical conditions like prolonged miscarriages or even as a diagnosis procedure when a doctor needs to biopsy parts of the reproductive system. It's a very common procedure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 19:02:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's $80 for five years. Most people in Seattle spend $80 a week on coffee.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 19:11:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty sure a lot of male slaves were made into eunuchs, too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-29 23:49:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>The ones I've been in have a doorman and concierge, a mailroom to secure packages, fancy elevators, huge windows with views, parking in the building, nice common rooms with balconies, rentable event spaces, a gym, a dog area, theatre room, conference room, occasional parties for the residents. The units themselves have AC, huge windows with a view (varies on the location in the building), open kitchen and living space, walk in closets, every room wired for high speed internet (often gigabit), thick walls and ceilings so you don't hear your neighbors. Nicer units have fancy European appliances and gas stoves, but standard ones have stainless steel LG/Samsung/GE appliances with electric stoves. The finishes aren't super luxury materials like marble and hardwood, but they use modern materials like quartz countertops and vinyl floor planks #8212;materials that look nice enough and are easier to maintain in a rental. Whether all this is actual luxury depends on what luxury means to you. It's definitely more luxurious than cheaper apartments, but it doesn't match the luxury condos at, say, the Four Seasons. And in a couple decades, these luxury apartments will be old and the management will have fewer amenities, letting them become the cheaper apartments of tomorrow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 00:08:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because a US citizen would never have the last name "Gonzales," and Hispanic gangs are totally known for beheading women with Japanese swords? /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Dr. Bob Sears (who is known for publishing parenting advice along with his father Dr. William Sears) has had his medical license put on probation in California for exempting a 2-year-old from vaccines for illegitimate reasond</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 01:02:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 03:12:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm going to reply to you by posting a few dozen links to hours upon hours of Jordan Peterson's Youtube videos, which I expect you to watch thoroughly so you can join my cult. If you don't, I'm proven right, libtard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 06:38:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>His dad, William Sears, is the guy who invented [attachment parenting](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Attachment_parenting), which is a the batshit crazy parenting philosophy that makes some online parents so insufferable. After I had my son a few years ago, I was reading the internet for help on caring for my infant, and his articles kept coming up at the top of Google. It took me a few months of miserable "co-sleeping" with a wiggly baby before I wised up that Dr. Sears' methods were all about guilting new mothers into a toxic perfectionism that ignored a lot of the real science behind child-rearing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 07:35:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd ask what QAnon is, but I'm getting really sick of having to care about the dumb shit teenagers come up with on 4chan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 16:41:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've noticed that about a lot of the breastfeeding/baby-wearing websites, where they post these pictures from all these non-white cultures with women carrying their babies. I can tell it's crunchy white people making these sites, though, because there's this weird fetishization of it, like "look at this beautiful mother constantly with her baby," when it's like a peasant woman in Bolivia working the fields with her infant strapped to her. I mean, come on, this Bolivian woman probably has to farm from dusk to dawn just to eat, probably hurts all over from the work, probably gets parasitic worms and other diseases we never have to worry about in the US. She probably has a large extended family who are also constantly working, and has no access to formula so she has to carry the infant around or else it would die. The women fetishizing this "natural" lifestyle aren't really willing to live like women do in undeveloped countries, just because they're breastfeeding in the park and wearing their baby to get a $5 latte at the coffee shop. Like critics of attachment parenting have noted, this over-mothering behavior is about the parents themselves needing to make child-rearing some sort of competition, not about what's actually best for their children.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 16:55:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Totally agree. I had some PPD with my son, even though I was narrowly able to avoid C-section and I could breastfeed. But reading all these articles and mothering forums, it's never enough. "Oh, you've only breastfed for a year? I'm still breastfeeding my 3-year-old twins!" "Oh, you're sleep training your child? That's abuse because letting your baby cry for even two minutes will give them brain damage!" "Oh, your baby doesn't want to be carried in a sling constantly and cries and squirms the whole time? You must be doing it wrong and you need to take a baby-wearing class!" I mean, FFS... mothers aren't even allowed to be full human beings in their world. Do what they say, and never make time for just yourself, or else you're a selfish, horrible mother who hates her children.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 17:01:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>That stupid flag Trump held up looks like Eric Trump took a Sharpie to a rainbow flag. No respectable LGBT person would've made a flag that shitty to give to someone they admired.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 17:08:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then they'd go after access to contraceptives and STI treatments (as they already have been), because the anti-abortion movement isn't about stopping "baby murdering." It's about stopping people (particularly women) from controlling when and with whom they have sex. They want sex to have as dire of consequences as possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 23:32:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, the people in that sub are pretty right wing. You'll regularly see upvoted posts for race-baiting and Muslim-bashing stories. My best post in there was a story about some Mexicans disliking NAFTA. If I try to post any stories with pro-immigration, pro-Muslim, or pro-woman bias, it gets downvoted into oblivion. I stopped going there after I posted a story about skyrocketing infant and maternal deaths in Venezuela and it got inundated with "what about the men" comments.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-30 23:42:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm surprised the Trump Administration isn't just releasing scenes from *Breaking Bad* or *Sicario* and claiming they're real footage of MS-13.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 00:25:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>"We learned this one from the British during the Opium Wars."  #8211; China Edit: Thanks for the gold, but you limey bastards are still only allowed to trade through the port of Canton.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 07:27:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was more about the backlash against Trump, like Mexicans hated Trump so they hated NAFTA. Reddit comments were about it being a "win" for Trump because he's so smart. Here's a link to the article (unfortunately Bloomberg seems to lock down its old articles): https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2017-01-31/outraged-mexicans-to-trump-tear-up-nafta-we-re-sick-of-it-too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 17:45:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, the strip club isn't is a historic landmark, but the property next to it is (the Larned Hotel). It's currently owned by Capitol Hill Housing, a nonprofit affordable housing company, and they don't pay property taxes on most of it because it's used for low income apartments. (I used to frequent the art gallery in the commercial space of that building before CHH raised the rent and forced them to move.) I think the strip club won't sell because their triangle of land can't be developed much unless CHH also gives up their larger property. I'm not sure is the Larned Hotel is protected for being historical because it may not have been officially added to the historical registry yet (its status seems to be just "eligible"). https://web6.seattle.gov/DPD/HistoricalSite/QueryResult.aspx?ID=-1753090004</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 18:50:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because wasteful spending only benefits poor people. /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 22:52:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>When a doctor "rips the baby out of the womb of the mother just prior to birth," that's called a birth. This is one of the stupidest things Trump has ever said. Nobody is aborting viable babies past 24 weeks, which is the late second trimester (37 weeks is full term). That's the gestation age at which the baby is sent to the NICU and doctors do everything to keep it alive. If a mother's life is in danger at that point, she gives birth (often via c-section). Even with unviable babies (such as babies that are missing vital organs and can't live on their own), past 24 weeks the mother has to give birth to the baby to have it physically removed from her body.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 16:32:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, wow, it's not like North Korea to lie about things. How could this have happened?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 16:33:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>There was a handshake!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 19:07:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also his music is complete ass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 19:26:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>That original one is pretty stupid, too. Diversity = Commies destroying America?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 19:38:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, that context makes more sense.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 19:54:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Trump Foundation: Our charitable mission is to make sure fewer of Donald J. Trump's children make it into the world, because he's fucking it up enough already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-02 20:40:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Says the political movement that seems to be 90% white male. Hmmmm...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 00:01:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>We can understand the opposing side and firmly disagree, because conservatives have been dishonestly distorting the facts and trying to erase any nuance by shouting about "baby murder." They disseminate propaganda about women's clinics profiting off the procedure, when a very small percentage of their services are abortion and they don't make money off selling "baby parts." They imply that abortions after the first trimester are a routine thing, when the vast majority happen before 13 weeks (and 66% before 8 weeks), and abortions in the second trimester happen because women are delayed in receiving the procedure, or women who actually wanted the child have to get one because of reasons outside of their control. They cry that feminists and liberals love abortion and want everybody to get them all the time, when that's absolutely not the case and liberals are trying to increase access to contraception and reproductive healthcare, and educate everyone about sex so people can avoid the procedure in the first place. And they keep trying to remove funding for reproductive health clinics and prevent people from getting reliable contraception, despite the fact that increased access to these things and sex education has reduced the abortion rate. The conservatives are the unreasonable ones, and we're sick of arguing with them. They have no real solutions except failed policies that have historically increased unwanted pregnancies, increased STI transmission, and increased maternal death and infant mortality rates. And they have no genuine intentions to make the situation better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 00:24:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>White nationalists are pushing the race narrative. The media is reporting on them because their stupid "identity politics" put an asshat in the White House who's now trying to blow up the world.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 00:56:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>"And remember, if you and your family try to escape your shithole country by crossing the US-Mexican border, we'll arrest you, rip your kids from you, detain you indefinitely, and make you pay a ransom to get your kids back."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 01:05:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blaming Marx for what communists later created is like blaming Nietzsche for what the Nazis did. Marx was a philosopher who died long before Bolshevism was even conceived.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 07:03:13</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Mel Gibson in "The Patriot," a film about a giant disembodied head on the horizon that pensively stares off into the distance. Funny article. I love how it ends with the *Rocky IV* training montage. But, alas, it's not explicitly about something happening right now in US politics, and humor pieces are also disallowed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 07:14:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>How come libertarians want to get rid of all regulations on everything #8212;from driving to food safety to businesses #8212;but they're totally fine with regulating women's reproductive options?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 16:24:42</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;We are kept awake at night by the cries of starving children. The sentence (at least the English translation of it here) uses passive voice, which linguistically is a way to shift emphasis from who or what did the action to who or what the action was done to, or the "victim." The Nazis developed this type of thinking, where they came to believe the regret or empathy they felt for their victims was an infliction that jeopardized their mission if they acted on it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 18:38:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Must be like fucking magnets or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 21:31:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Utah would be such a beautiful place if not for the Mormons and the Republicans they insist on putting in power. I lived there 27 years, and I'll never live there again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 04:31:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Obligatory reference to *The Bell Curve*"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 05:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just hold up your secret ring and shout, "Crisis actors, UNITE!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 06:57:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL men actually suffer from more heart disease because they're Chads.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 15:45:56</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Gov. David Ige on Tuesday signed Senate Bill 2571, which will prohibit the sale or distribution of any sunscreen that contains the chemicals oxybenzone and/or octinoxate in Hawaii to anyone without a prescription from a licensed health care provider. I've found that my skin doesn't react well to these ingredients, anyway. I get a rash instead of a sunburn. I prefer sunscreen that uses zinc oxide and/or titanium oxide.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 16:25:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also see Exhibit B: the Men's Bathroom vs the Women's Bathroom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 16:54:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>[TRIGGERED](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/the-fix/wp/2017/07/05/some-trump-supporters-thought-npr-tweeted-propaganda-it-was-the-declaration-of-independence/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 19:32:17</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Hates women who go to church and are self righteous  gt;Wants to date spiritual god-fearing women</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 23:08:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, everyone agrees that homelessness is a big problem, but this video is just mean-spirited and pointless. It's like yelling "get a job" at a panhandler #8212;like they've never heard that before? r/thanksimcured</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 01:43:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Puget Sound belongs to several counties and none of is unclaimed by a county. You can see the county lines on the sound in this WSDOT map (they're the dot-dash lines): http://www.wsdot.wa.gov/mapsdata/products/maps_pdf/MilepostMapPugetSoundInset2016.pdf The county firework laws only apply to unincorporated areas (areas not within any city) and to cities that don't have any specific firework laws of their own. Also be aware that city limits can extend beyond the coast in the sound. Seattle's city limits on the sound pretty much extend all the way to the county line between King and Kitsap counties: https://www.maptechnica.com/city-map/Seattle/WA/5363000</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 02:20:45</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; The greatest thing in the world is to know how to belong to oneself.  #8211;Michel de Montaigne</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 02:52:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's just not funny. The needles on the street, the tents next to the highway, the EMTs resuscitating OD'd homeless people #8212;most people don't think those things are humorous.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 03:13:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe if the House Republicans had integrity and actual values, we'd believe their laments over Trump betraying such things.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 06:40:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like all the supermodels are too tall to date. Sucks to be them. Victoria's Secret should just pack it in and put out a catalog of their models wearing banana hammocks instead.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 22:03:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah, Trump is somehow going to resurrect a 1920s era coal baron and let that zombie corpse run the EPA.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-05 22:32:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure if he's the most corrupt, but he's definitely been the most stupidly corrupt. I'm sure there are plenty of people just as corrupt who just aren't showboating about it like this asshat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 00:09:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, at the time of writing, the Founding Fathers were unaware of the existence of grizzly bears. They just knew about lesser ursines until Lewis and Clark learned of grizzlies in the early 19th century. Had they known about such monsters, they might not have made such a blanket statement about the right to bear arms.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 19:16:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm curious about the spike in Northgate, which according to this report now has the 9th highest crime rate Seattle, due to an uptick in violent crime. The area included in the map contains Northgate Mall, Haller Lake, Licton Springs, Pinehurst, and Maple Leaf. I live in Maple Leaf and it still seems as sleepy as ever, other than someone stealing a couple of my lawn ornaments. Is the violent crime coming from the tiny home village on Aurora around 90th? I've heard a lot of complaints about that, but that doesn't seem like quite enough to justify the higher crime rate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 06:56:00</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Russian president Vladimir Putin says that Western governments are enslaving humanity through vaccines, Funny how batshit crazy people just start stirring everything together to make batshit conspiracy stew.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 17:02:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not a fan of teriyaki in general, but Cafe Banh Mi has great sandwiches for weekday lunch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 22:47:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whenever I hear this complaint, I think of the excuse people made for fascists, that "At least Mussolini made the trains run on time."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 03:25:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is what his mother posted earlier today on Nextdoor:  gt; I #8217;m posting this because my son has gone missing. He was last seen on the evening of 4th of July in his kayak on Green Lake. He was watching the fire works. The next morning his kayak was found capsized and we are desperately looking for answers.  gt;His boat was found on the north west side of the lake (the cove) somewhere between the black bowie and the grating. I #8217;m searching for anyone who may have a security camera in their yard that may overlook that part of the lake or if anyone who may have seen or heard him. No info is too little so please, reach out if you have anything.  gt;https://mobile.twitter.com/seattlepd/status/1015414981477535745?ref_src=twcamp%5Eshare%7Ctwsrc%5Eios%7Ctwgr%5Ecom.apple.UIKit.activity.Message%7Ctwcon%5E7100%7Ctwterm%5E0  gt;I have reported this information to the police.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 16:40:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I went out snorkeling on the Great Barrier Reef once and the group encountered a bunch of these. A bunch of people got stung, one woman across the face. I got out unstung, but almost drowned because I forgot a life jacket and thought I could tough it out. I don't fuck with the ocean anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 18:23:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I come from Utah, a very arid place where the biggest body of water is a shallow, swampy lake so salty that only sea monkeys and algae live in it. The ocean kicked my ass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 19:12:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I would put this squarely on baby formula marketers. Evangelicals don't actually hate breastfeeding, which is actually pretty labor and time intensive for mothers. Excessive breastfeeding (like doing it beyond infancy) goes in hand with things like homeschooling and anti-vaxxers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 21:51:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>The WHO often defines infants as children under 24 months of age. It's not a term with a definite age limit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 22:10:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look, I'm a woman who breastfed my son until he was 20 months (when he didn't care to do it anymore), so don't momsplain to me about how this works.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 23:30:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>11. Marshawn Lynch</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 00:36:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have Marshawn Lynch on there two times, already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 06:43:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought of the crab metaphor, too. It's such a great analogy for the many ways social pressure keeps people in bad situations. Getting away from shitty people does so much to improve your life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 16:45:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought it was the other way around, that her father thought she starred in an entire movie but it was actually Cillian Murphy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 18:57:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>He'd probably have his food spit on at "all-American" fast food joints, too. They pay such shit wages, most the kitchen staff is poor minorities and immigrants.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 19:02:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Obama wasn't perfect on immigration, but he wasn't responsible for the family separation policy. He also tried to do more compassionate immigration reforms but was repeatedly blocked by the Republicans in Congress. The whole shit show has belonged to them even before Trump.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 19:07:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ditto. It's been way more reliable than the Condo Internet gigabit service through Wave I had downtown. Their customer service hasn't been too awful, either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 20:08:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Tat's Truck, of course. http://www.tatstruck.com</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 23:51:00</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; England acknowledged that there might be  #8220;isolated incidents #8221; when asking passengers to remove food from their bags might slow things down, though he pointed out that, nationally, 96 percent of standard passengers have a wait that is 20 minutes or less. Last October in the Salt Lake City airport, the TSA decided they needed to screen everybody for food, with no posted notices or anything. They were pulling pretty much everybody out of line after the X rays detected their snacks. It took us over an hour to get through a line that should've taken 15 minutes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 17:50:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The argument may be unusual in the courts, but it doesn't sound unreasonable for him to get some sort of compensation for it. In medical research, it's expected that patients who participate in studies get compensation, often beyond free medical care. Getting the patent is a bridge too far, though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 19:28:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's normal for doctors to take parts that have "malfunctioned" to check for reasons why the patient got sick, like infection or other problems. It's important for diagnosing the root cause. The gray area seems to be what they do with the samples afterward. I'm unsure if a hospital includes a "right to do whatever we want with the medical waste" clause in all the paperwork they make patients sign on admission. I wouldn't be surprised if that was in the fine print. But even then, a patient could possibly claim the contract was signed under duress, particularly if they were admitted for an emergency medical issue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 20:07:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's fair to criticize the greater issue of money in politics, but not to attack the voting public as "ignorant" just because you disagree with an initiative. Despite its flaws, the initiative process in WA is a better form of direct democracy than a lot of states have. I mean, without it WA probably would not have legal marijuana. The conservative congresspeople from Eastern WA would've blocked those things. And legislators are way easier for lobbyists to buy than the general public.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 22:12:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Portland has [entire blocks devoted to food cart pods](https://www.travelportland.com/article/food-cart-pods/). It's awesome and it's one of the reasons Seattle lags behind Portland as a food destination.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 07:25:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not saying this guy isn't a douche for writing his rightwing crap, but I can't find info saying he beat his wives. Source?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 16:46:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry I'm making current and historical discourse so uncivilized by calling people who malign and persecute other races "racists," calling people who make up facts based on political convenience "liars," and calling people who admire Hitler and want to eradicate Jews "Nazis." My bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 16:49:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look out Trump, McCain is going to furrow his brow and shake his head.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 22:46:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>There have been six presidents in my lifetime, which I'll rank best to worst: 1. Obama 2. Clinton 3. Bush the Elder 4. Reagan 5. Trump 6. Bush the Younger While I believe Trump could be worse than Bush II if his presidency continues, I think people really underestimate how much Bush II fucked things up with starting two unwinnable wars, the Great Recession, the Patriot Act, No Child Left Behind, and his emboldening of Evangelicals in politics.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 22:54:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Be sure to include Matthew 25:31-46:  gt;The Sheep and the Goats  gt;31  #8220;When the Son of Man comes in his glory, and all the angels with him, he will sit on his glorious throne. 32 All the nations will be gathered before him, and he will separate the people one from another as a shepherd separates the sheep from the goats. 33 He will put the sheep on his right and the goats on his left.  gt;34  #8220;Then the King will say to those on his right,  #8216;Come, you who are blessed by my Father; take your inheritance, the kingdom prepared for you since the creation of the world. 35 For I was hungry and you gave me something to eat, I was thirsty and you gave me something to drink, I was a stranger and you invited me in, 36 I needed clothes and you clothed me, I was sick and you looked after me, I was in prison and you came to visit me. #8217;  gt;37  #8220;Then the righteous will answer him,  #8216;Lord, when did we see you hungry and feed you, or thirsty and give you something to drink? 38 When did we see you a stranger and invite you in, or needing clothes and clothe you? 39 When did we see you sick or in prison and go to visit you? #8217;  gt;40  #8220;The King will reply,  #8216;Truly I tell you, whatever you did for one of the least of these brothers and sisters of mine, you did for me. #8217;  gt;41  #8220;Then he will say to those on his left,  #8216;Depart from me, you who are cursed, into the eternal fire prepared for the devil and his angels. 42 For I was hungry and you gave me nothing to eat, I was thirsty and you gave me nothing to drink, 43 I was a stranger and you did not invite me in, I needed clothes and you did not clothe me, I was sick and in prison and you did not look after me. #8217;  gt;44  #8220;They also will answer,  #8216;Lord, when did we see you hungry or thirsty or a stranger or needing clothes or sick or in prison, and did not help you? #8217;  gt;45  #8220;He will reply,  #8216;Truly I tell you, whatever you did not do for one of the least of these, you did not do for me. #8217;  gt;46  #8220;Then they will go away to eternal punishment, but the righteous to eternal life. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-11 23:37:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sadly, I looked into what evangelical scholars think the parable means, and they've already decided that Jesus only wants you to be nice to Christians. Apparently he's totally okay with Christians ignoring the non-Christians in need.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 16:21:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>And yet calling someone an "asshole" never seems to lose its power, even though nobody is literally a giant sphincter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 18:03:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, my brother in law uses legal marijuana (in WA state) for anxiety and he has plenty of guns, plus a concealed carry permit. I don't think there's a ban.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 02:37:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Traffic has been shitty all day. Took me 30 min to get from Northgate to Downtown at 1pm. There weren't any closures or accidents; I-5 was just packed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 03:22:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>He kinda looks drunk, TBH.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 05:40:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It needs a [fake Renoir painting](https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2017/10/donald-trumps-fake-renoir).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 06:03:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>And it's Ronny Jackson, the same guy Trump tried to make Secretary of Veteran Affairs until accusations of misconduct made him withdraw.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 21:49:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check out the Seattle Arts and Culture Office for information on grants, events, opportunities, etc.: http://www.seattle.gov/arts If you want to connect with people, I recommend getting out to the monthly artwalks and chatting with the people you find at the galleries. Each neighborhood that has an art walk is organized differently. Here's a site linking to more info: http://www.seattle.gov/arts/experience/art-walks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 04:00:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now I need to find a story about apples or some other fruit and post it to r/SeattleWA.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 16:34:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a good start to talk to the dealer first. It's a pretty embarrassing mistake for them to make, if it was a mistake. A quick Google search shows it should be Victoria on an 1897 sovereign. If they refuse to refund you, say you'll take them to small claims court, file a complaint with the FTC and Better Business Bureau, leave bad reviews on Yelp and Google, etc. I'm not sure if SPD could do anything, either, but I know they recently busted [a coin dealership in North Seattle for selling stolen goods.](http://spdblotter.seattle.gov/2018/05/21/north-seattle-coin-shop-busted-for-selling-stolen-goods/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 16:51:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't know anyone who's been busted for DUIs involving marijuana, but here's the actual law DUI (RCW 46.61.502): http://app.leg.wa.gov/rcw/default.aspx?cite=46.61.502  gt; (b) The person has, within two hours after driving, a THC concentration of 5.00 or higher as shown by analysis of the person's blood made under RCW 46.61.506 And the law pertaining to actual testing (RCW 46.61.506): http://app.leg.wa.gov/RCW/default.aspx?cite=46.61.506  gt; (b) The blood analysis of the person's THC concentration shall be based upon nanograms per milliliter of whole blood.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 20:01:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's been acting like a petulant child during earnings calls when investors call him out on Tesla's production delays. During a recent one, he switched from listening to the investors and pulled up some rando fanboy off of Youtube who proceeded to gush about Elon's awesomeness.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 20:20:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I carry a few around for my toddler. Some restaurants are kind enough to have plastic cups for kids with reusable straws, but it's not the norm.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 16:11:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It sounds like Sasha Baron Cohen's fake persona.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 16:16:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Borat (2006) was great during the Bush Era. Bruno (2009) less so at the start of the Obama Era. The Dictator (2012) was absolutely forgettable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 16:21:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>According to Google, Larry Pratt is a gun lobbyists. I doubt this old man inserted hip hop stars into a pseudoscience blurb himself. That's something Cohen would've written. Hence why it sounds like him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 21:20:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like to think he's wearing a trenchcoat and about to bust out a 6 ft long sword, but the Tories aren't known for cosplay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 23:35:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like they're attacking the Democrats in Congress for demanding Ecuador extradite Assange. Oh, and it's still all Debbie Wasserman Schultz's fault somehow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 01:33:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know... we'll take all the money from social security, Medicare, and Medicaid, and give it to the richest 0.01% in America. Then we'll ask them kindly to give it back to their workers, on the honor code. This totally can't fail!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 02:10:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Top Pot is super popular in the morning on weekdays. They even have this picture of Obama visiting them several years back. I think that location is also a bakery that sends out their donuts to grocery stores and such.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 00:10:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Subjunctive time: If Rohrbacher were to eat shit, we'd all be happier!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 00:42:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>He knows what's going on. He's just angry that Trump fucked up on obfuscating the entire sham that is the GOP.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 00:48:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like she's a modern [Cassandra](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cassandra). So infuriating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 01:26:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rand Paul is like a toddler who claims he didn't steal a cookie when he has chocolate chips smeared all over his face and crumbs on his shirt. How stupid does he think we are?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 05:36:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like the detail where they're on Fifth Avenue #8212;the place where Trump bragged he could literally kill someone and his supporters still wouldn't care.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 05:48:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>She beat Sanders in the 2016 primary by a far larger margin than Obama beat her in 2008. Quit repeating these divisive lies that Sanders was somehow robbed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 06:25:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I saw these guys on my herb garden today. Like others said, it's a great golden digger wasp, *sphex ichneumoneus*. They're scary looking, but apparently they're not aggressive to humans and help your garden by pollinating flowers and killing other bugs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 22:26:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Let's investigate all the other 7 billion people in the world before we assume it was a Russian."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 23:50:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I moved here from Denver several years ago, and before that lived in Utah. One of my favorite things about Seattle is the weather, because it's very dry in the Rocky Mountains. 1. Everybody blames Californians wherever you go. People were blaming Californians for traffic problems in Utah back in the 80s and 90s, and it's still going on. I haven't heard a lot of griping about Texans, though. 2. Depends on the type of card/pass you get. Orca cards usually just have a set amount of money that you spend on fares, like a debit card for transit, and you refill the account to keep using it. But there are also passes and such available. Ask your work for more details on what they're giving you. 5. Bike theft is a big problem. Make sure your home and your work has a secure place to keep bikes, like a locker inside the garage. 6. I personally do carry an umbrella because I like to wear wool blend coats in the winter and I don't like hoods. Maybe that's because I'm a transplant from a dry place, or because I'm a woman. REI has good, fashionable raincoats, though. Other: My brother-in-law loves to bike to work 10+ miles a day, and he strongly recommends getting an e-bike motor with a good battery because the hills in Seattle can be very tiring. (When I moved here, I was surprised by the hills, and I had to change from a manual transmission car to an automatic because it was ruining my clutch.) I don't live in West Seattle, but I've heard the bus commute from there to downtown can be atrocious due to traffic on the West Seattle bridge and around the I-5/I-90 interchange. One guy I know prefers to use the water taxi and just walk to and from the harbor. If you can, get some sort of A/C during the summer. A/C is everywhere in the Rocky Mountains, so I was appalled that very few apartments had it. You may be able to get away with no A/C in a basement apartment, but anything on the top levels becomes an oven. If your apartment doesn't have A/C, consider getting a portable unit or something in the window. The homeless population has been exploding here. When I first came, I would cheerfully give change to the panhandlers or anyone asking for "bus fare," but I stopped after I realized they just wanted money for drugs. Once, in a bar in the International District, my date and I were chatted up by a friendly guy talking about some baseball game, then he stole my date's jacket and wallet. In other words, be careful, especially in downtown after dark. And don't stress too much about being a "good transplant." Just be you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 00:00:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>And the 2nd is now Tillerson calling Trump a "fucking moron."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 01:03:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's peak season in Seattle, where the summers are beautiful and the cruise ships come daily. I know that Honolulu has $400+ per night rates in December, during its peak season. My relatives usually stay in hotels in North Seattle or Shoreline, where you can find cheaper rates and be close to I-5 or Aurora. AirBnB should have some cheap offerings, too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 02:15:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let's all hope he gets [Borked](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Bork).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 04:27:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>When it gets icy, nobody drives, even if you know how to drive in ice and snow and have a car that can handle it. Ice doesn't happen often here, maybe once or twice per year, so they don't really salt the roads and there aren't many snow plows. And inevitably there are a few cars that get piled up at the bottom of icy hills because they learn too late their brakes are useless.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 04:48:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>As someone who regularly confuses right and left, this sign makes perfect sense to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 05:59:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't know that before, but here's some [quotes from Tom Morello I just found](http://articles.latimes.com/2012/aug/17/entertainment/la-et-ms-tom-morello-rips-into-rage-against-the-machine-fan-paul-ryan-20120817) about Paul Ryan being a "fan":  gt; "I wonder what Ryan's favorite Rage song is? Is it the one where we condemn the genocide of Native Americans? The one lambasting American imperialism? Our cover of "F- the Police"? Or is it the one where we call on the people to seize the means of production? So many excellent choices to jam out to at Young Republican meetings!"  gt;"I clearly see that Ryan has a whole lotta 'rage' in him: A rage against women, a rage against immigrants, a rage against workers, a rage against gays, a rage against the poor, a rage against the environment. Basically the only thing he's not raging against is the privileged elite he's groveling in front of for campaign contributions."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 06:06:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>And also in tweet quoted in the article...  gt; Wilson ... was nearly killed in his bed by a man who broke into his home, wanted to kill him. Wilson was able to shoot with a loaded gun he kept under his bed. Why the fuck do people keep trying to kill him in his sleep?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 06:52:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Because Missouri loves company.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 19:07:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's like... a douchey version of Kevin from *The Office.*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 19:23:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just open your local paper to the obituaries page. All those people, even the ones who died of cancer or old age, crossed the Clintons.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 19:27:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jimmy Carter just loves to meddle by going to foreign countries and reviewing their democratic elections for instances of fraud, intimidation, and disenfranchisement. Then he gives them recommendations on how to improve their democracy so everyone can have their voices heard! The nerve of that man... /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 23:53:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I've seen them shut down the comments on all sorts of articles. The comment section has become melodramatic garbage on any article from a major news source.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 00:29:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>How dare I place such importance on my ability to control when and if I create new human beings. Soooo selfish of me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 02:48:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>How come when the religious right talks about who is the Antichrist, they never think of Trump?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 16:14:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, they buy plenty of it for when liberal comedians dare to call Sarah Huckabee Sanders a liar. Or for when they're told that the things Trump does are fascist or similar to what Nazis did. Or when kids who had a gunman shoot up their school have the audacity to say America has a problem with gun violence.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 16:18:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think he's saying if you're stuck in gridlock on Aurora and you want to quickly text your friend that you'll be late, you can do that safely as long as you're completely stopped and still paying attention. I don't think anybody can text safely while they're actually moving.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 20:19:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's all about money. They have friends who want to use some land to make money, but some snail or bird is keeping them from that fat cash.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 20:25:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>May you never have a peaceful dining experience in any restaurant ever again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 21:19:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, it's declined since the 1990s. Gun violence itself peaked in 1993. But there are a lot of factors contributing to that, including things like economic improvements, education, improved security technology, and fewer children born into poverty. Yet these gun organizations like to highlight whatever crimes still happen and tell people they need to pack heat to stay safe, even though the drop in gun violence doesn't correlate with an increase in gun ownership. Gun ownership has actually dropped since the 1990s. And even though the gun violence rate has dropped, and the violent crime rate is lower than many other countries, the rate of violent deaths is extremely high in the US compared to other countries. That's because guns make it very easy to kill other people, or yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 22:16:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>But ANDORRA... we better watch those mountain-dwelling bastards. They could take Spain and France at any minute. /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 22:49:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Americans like to give the French a hard time for surrendering in WWII. We can't be so smug anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 23:12:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>No need to get defensive.... unless Maria Butina has personally visited you and every other gun owner in Washington. I mean, she got around, but not to that degree.... I hope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 23:20:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Russians don't care about the Second Amendment, or the First or Third or any others. They're intentionally provoking anger in Americans by destroying all nuance in our political discourse, thereby dividing and weakening the nation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 05:58:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fun fact: they used to make heart pacemakers that ran off a tiny bit of plutonium. As of 2003, it was estimated 50-100 living people still had them. If a coroner found one, they were supposed to return it to Los Alamos. https://www.mdtmag.com/blog/2016/01/medtech-memoirs-plutonium-powered-pacemaker</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL in the 60s and 70s nuclear-powered cardiac pacemakers were used, containing a tiny amount of plutonium encased in epoxy and titanium to resist gunshots or cremation. In 2003, over 50 living people still had them. If a coroner finds one, they're supposed to return it to Los Alamos for disposal.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 06:23:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 07:14:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think they were more worried about the medical staff or coroners accidentally handling plutonium if it got out of the pacemaker.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 18:22:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>The spouse is getting less exposure. mrem = millirem, which is one thousandth of a rem. The person with the pacemaker gets .1 rem, or 100 mrem, which is much more than the 7.5 mrem the spouse gets.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 03:14:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Solanine exists in both potato and tomato plants. It's mostly in the leaves, stems, and sprouts, or in unripe tomatoes or green potatoes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In Yellow Submarine (1968) when Ringo is exploring the psychedelic submarine, he pulls a random lever against the wishes of the captain, Old Fred. Ringo explains, "Can't help it, I'm a born Lever-puller." This is a pun on Liverpool, the Beatles' home town.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 07:49:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 07:27:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>He got past the primary for port commissioner last year! Then lost in the general election, but still.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 16:15:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>These are the qualifications required to be in the House of Representatives per the Constitution:  gt;Each representative must: (1) be at least twenty-five years old; (2) have been a citizen of the United States for the past seven years; and (3) be (at the time of the election) an inhabitant of the state he or she represents. The Constitution does not allow further qualifications to be established than that, because doing so would disenfranchise people based on arbitrary standards and be undemocratic. (The only additional disqualification stated is under the Fourteenth Amendment, which says a federal or state officer who takes the requisite oath to support the Constitution, but later engages in rebellion or aids the enemies of the United States, is disqualified from becoming a representative. This post #8211;Civil War provision was intended to prevent those who sided with the Confederacy from serving. However, disqualified individuals may serve if they gain the consent of two-thirds of both houses of Congress.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-24 16:25:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember a while back when Francis was elected Pope after a contentious series of votes. He wasn't a very big name yet and info on him was sparse, but once the news got out of his election, I remember going to Wikipedia to try to read about him. Every refresh the page changed to add or remove some weird tidbits, and it took maybe weeks for it to stabilize.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 03:08:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah... the Hawaiian Republicans lament about the Democrats having a supermajority in the state, but white people are the minority there and the Republicans have enthusiastically become the party of white grievances. They should stop associating with the mainland Republicans and make their own party if they want to be relevant.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:09:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, when I first visited DC eight years ago, I was walking near the National Mall, half lost, and suddenly noticed the White House was right in front of me. Maybe it was the giant fenced lot around it, but the White House looked pretty small compared to everything else I'd seen that day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 00:40:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ballotpedia has some good Wikipedia-like info about this year's elections: https://ballotpedia.org/Washington Also look for the Voters' Pamplet that the state mails out around the time they send a ballot. (You can order it in other languages, too.) https://www.sos.wa.gov/elections/free-voting-materials.aspx This pamplet only contains statements submitted by the candidates themselves, which aren't changed in any way, so you can decide if a candidate makes sense, or if they're a crazy person who can't spell correctly or hire a proofreader. The local newspapers have endorsements, but they tend to be biased. *The Seattle Times* is supposed to have moderate/centrist endorsements, while *The Stranger* is more liberal (with added edgy commentary that can be really petty, but somewhat entertaining to read).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 02:58:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like the guy who comes in at the end to mock the anti-vaxxer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 03:27:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Vaccine injuries," AKA serious side effects from vaccines, can happen, and to address this in the US, Congress created the [National Childhood Vaccine Injury Act](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/National_Childhood_Vaccine_Injury_Act) in 1986. This established a federal fund to compensate victims of severe vaccine side effects, and established a special process for people to file a claim called the Vaccine Injury Compensation Program. Compensation for claims of a vaccine injury comes from the Vaccine Trust Fund, which is administered by the US Treasury and funded by an excise tax paid by the vaccine makers. This was in reaction to some "bad" vaccines that had more than the usual reports of side effects, specifically the pertussis vaccine. As a result, people sued the vaccine makers, and some vaccine makers threatened to go out of business because they couldn't get liability insurance anymore, thus limiting the supply of needed vaccines. The new law shielded vaccine makers from liabilty by mandating less expensive arbitration instead of the usual court process, so vaccine makers could still operate and provide the needed vaccines. You can see how this would seem like a conspiracy between the US government and drug companies to sell more vaccines, if you were inclined to distrust the government and drug companies. But it's really too transparent to be a conspiracy, and it is in the interest of the government to administer or "sell" more vaccines so that the citizens can be healthy. Anti-vaxxers don't want to accept that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 16:11:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>We get the point; that commenter's flair "If you're a female I hate you" sums it up perfectly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 18:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like the original post got deleted for exactly that reason.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 18:13:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love the name "Dow Constantine." Anyway, I hope the historical preservation board allows the Showbox to be designated a landmark. Having people like Constantine support that could help get that pushed through. That way, the developers would have to preserve it somehow in order to proceed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 18:19:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're sure getting us dumb libs good. I'll be sure to offer more respect to the next Trump supporter I talk to. "Great prank destroying the environment! High five, bro!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 18:26:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, the old "national security" defense abused by the GOP. Separating babies from their immigrant parents? It's for national security. Banning refugees and travelers from majority Muslim countries? It's for national security. Allowing the destruction of the habitat of little prairie chickens and bugs? It's for national security.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 20:04:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really imagine him more as the lead in a TV series about an attorney who, after being fired in disgrace from his high-powered Wall Street lawyer job, redeems himself by practicing law in the hard-knock streets of South Seattle, fighting for the under-privileged against drug dealers, corrupt corporations, dirty cops, and (in special episodes) the infamous crime boss who controls "The Jungle."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 20:25:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>There might be some juggalos who like Trump, but last I checked most of them didn't like him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-26 23:33:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, chill... I just find his name epically funny. And last I checked, there isn't any Kshama Sawant fanfic out there... though, I could write her into the "Dow Constantine" series as the clueless "frenemy" councilwoman who butts heads with him in a number of episodes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 04:44:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would add McConnell to that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 07:07:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd gladly have mayo on my sandwich instead of rancid cat puke, thank you very much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 18:09:15</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; 78 degrees As a pregnant woman who feels faint when the temperature is over 74, I would not be happy about this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 19:41:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>As I female programmer, I would put these guys in the libertarian category, which has become this weird, self-centered mix of conservative and liberal. A lot of them are white guys who have developed a bad attitude toward women and minorities. They think they are the smartest human beings to ever live or something, and that they are experts on everything. Often they have bad social skills and don't care to change that. If they get criticism, they'd rather blame someone else for it instead of improving themselves. And they think just because I'm a woman I can show up to any interview and get a million job offers thrown at me. (Newsflash: I struggle to find jobs as much as anyone else, and have to network because the application process is a joke.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 20:36:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right now, I only go outside to walk to my car, where I turn the AC on full blast. This weather is hell for pregnant women.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-27 21:34:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, I hadn't read that one yet. It's all pretty familiar, unfortunately. This behavior is the norm, and women get punished for calling it out. I'm surprised I haven't been told off by a random redditor yet about how there's no gender discrimination, complete with a link to that tired James Damore "manifesto." But the day is young.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 00:28:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Huh... TIL that the "conservative majority" is made up of fake social media accounts that spread disinformation and hate speech for political gain. \#AllBotsMatter</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 00:57:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>In the business news I've read, the most probable source of a tech bubble are the so-called "Unicorns," which are private "startup" companies worth a billion or more. Uber and Lyft are in this category, but the extended list is pretty big, including Slack, Pinterest, WeWork, AirBnB, and a bunch more: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_unicorn_startup_companies People in finance are often questioning the valuations of these companies, because there isn't very much transparency behind them and it's alleged many of the companies resist going public because it will devalue them (see Blue Apron and Square). [It's been estimated that the average unicorn is overvalued by 48%.](https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2955455) This is happening because these companies have no problem getting capital right now. And because of [the JOBS Act of 2012](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jumpstart_Our_Business_Startups_Act), private companies can raise more capital and have more investors without having to disclose their finances. So there is a growing concern that investors have been throwing money into startups that are making up their valuations #8212;securities fraud, essentially #8212;and a reckoning may be imminent when capital stops flowing so freely and investors want their money back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 01:44:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate to recommend Facebook, but there is a fairly active group for Seattle WoC to talk about haircare: https://facebook.com/groups/seattlenaturals It's a public group, so you can at least see the posts without having a FB account.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 02:09:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Requiring a pregnancy test for every woman is pretty invasive. Most women are fully aware if they could be pregnant or not. The doctor could just ask before giving the prescription, like they do for any other drug that's contraindicated in pregnancy. Here in Washington State where weed is outright legal, my OB/GYN just gave me a pamplet about the risks of marijuana use during my pregnancy, similar to the literature for alcohol, tobacco, and other potentially harmful drugs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 20:19:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Onni is the developer who also bought the old Seattle Times building on Fairview. The let homeless people squat there until the city got fed up. Now that they're finally developing it, the building is completely gutted except for the old Seattle Times facade.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 21:37:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's been years since I saw razor clams on a menu. I last had them at Sky City in the Space Needle in 2012. Seems like harvesting them has been more tightly controlled since then: https://www.dnr.wa.gov/programs-and-services/aquatics/shellfish/razor-clams</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 23:35:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a great place to take my toddler when it's too hot or cold or rainy to take him to the playground. I hope they still have a covered play area for tots.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-28 23:50:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're willing to venture up to Everett, the AFK Tavern has exactly what you're looking for. http://www.afktavern.com</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 04:20:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>From my understanding, it's not legal to discriminate against tenants who have service animals or emotional support animals, but there is a growing trend for some tenants to pretend they are disabled and their pets are service animals or emotional support animals in order to get around landlords' "no pets" rules. If you haven't already, you may need to present this landlord with proof of your disability and proof that your animal assists with this disability. If you need further assistance, find an attorney. You can also try the Seattle Tenants' Union for better guidance. https://tenantsunion.org</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL about Blue Babe, a 36,000 year old mummified steppe bison found in Alaska in 1979. After scientists painstakingly dug up the specimen and prepared it for display in the University of Alaska Museum, they decided to celebrate by taking a piece of meat from its neck, stewing it, and eating it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 07:51:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 16:57:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cathy McMorris Rodgers has accepted $673,530 in campaign donations from the telecom industry and voted against net neutrality.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 17:15:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just stop going to work! You can get rid of your car, stop paying for gas or bus fair, get rid of your work clothes, stop taking showers. Think of all that money you'll save. Genius!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 22:46:59</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Trump Derangement Syndrome I last saw that on Facebook from my idiot cousin, just before I closed my account. Trump is eating the bullshit memes his supporters created like a they're all a human centipede ouroboros.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-29 23:52:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well... the potato came from *South* America, from Andean cultures like the Inca. The Spanish brought it to Europe in the Sixteenth Century where it became very popular. It came to North America from the Brits, where the colonists considered it the "Irish potato."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 01:16:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah... Green Lake in particular attracts a wide range of pedestrians #8212;joggers, elderly folks, people on dates, dog walkers, parents pushing strollers, etc. They go slow for a variety of reasons, like to take in the scenery or talk or whatever. And it's really crowded on nice days. I've never tried biking there, but I imagine it would be like biking through Pike Place Market or SeaTac airport. Don't expect everyone to be able to get out of your way at a moment's notice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 01:55:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think this flag is particularly nautical. (Perhaps there's technically a nautical flag in this design, but nautical flags have a lot of designs that overlap with other fields.) To me, more organic, wavy lines invoke the sea. I also associate Seattle and the PNW with [Salish motifs](https://www.google.com/search?q=salish+design+motifs amp;client=safari amp;hl=en-us amp;prmd=isnv amp;source=lnms amp;tbm=isch amp;sa=X amp;ved=0ahUKEwin76bAwMXcAhUsHDQIHQ-GD9UQ_AUIESgB amp;biw=375 amp;bih=553). I think the seal of Seattle itself is inspired by Salish design (though I also think it could use some updating itself), so it sort of clashes with more geometric designs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 02:07:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I second Bremerton. The ferry ride to Bremerton is very relaxing and has gorgeous scenery of the Puget Sound. You can get to it from a ferry terminal on the Seattle waterfront. Bremerton itself is a pretty small town and you don't really need a car to explore it. https://www.wsdot.com/ferries/schedule/scheduledetailbyroute.aspx?route=sea-br</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 02:23:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like that other redditor said, construction costs are going up, and not just on materials for handywork. A lot of large infrastructure projects are having to scale back or get more money from taxpayers because the tariffs are driving up the cost of lumber, steel, concrete, and anything made from those materials.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 17:28:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>They just unjokingly referred to the "motherland" in their title. I think we can assume this is a Russian troll.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 19:33:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>With many, many, many unpresidented typos and misspellings.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I joined Nextdoor a while ago because people on this subreddit said it's ridiculous. I have not been disappointed.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 23:12:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 04:47:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I buy TP from Costco, which is already union-friendly and where they pay and treat their workers well for retail.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 20:41:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, definitely a mistake was made here. The Property Report shows it was last sold in 2015 for $531,000. Redfin has the incorrect sale, but Zillow and Trulia don't. http://blue.kingcounty.com/Assessor/eRealProperty/Detail.aspx?ParcelNbr=2920700235</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 21:12:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apparently the people in those states would rather have private industries ignore them than having the big ole commie gubermint come get up in their bidness. I swear, the whole anti-government sentiment is pathological in red states.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 21:17:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I recall correctly, Assange once claimed that he had RNC emails but he refused to leak them because they weren't interesting or some bullshit like that. Edit: I can't finda record of Assange saying that, but looking back it seems the US intelligence agencies did say the Russians hacked the Republicans but that info never got leaked. Also Assange apparently got some dirt on the Kremlin and declined to publish it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 21:52:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I recall seeing a bunch of spam emails in the DNC leaks, too, like straight up "Nigerian prince asking for a cash advance" type of spam and selling boner pills for cheap. Like, what's the point of leaking this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 22:00:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I knew I'd heard this somewhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 22:08:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not familiar with that site and it's possible it's scraping Redfin. I know Zillow and Trulia have their own data gathering processes separate from Redfin. Zillow actually has records of the property being advertised for rent last year, but no recent sales. Redfin is claiming the sale is from "Public Record," but searches in the public records like the King County Recorder's Office aren't bringing up any recent sales for the parcel. It seems like some data has gotten messed up on Redfin's side. I know when I bought my house a couple years ago, Redfin had two entries for it until we emailed them to correct it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-31 22:45:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mnuchin and his wife remind me of the main henchmen for a Bond villian.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 01:40:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>.... are you serious?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 02:54:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most grocery stores don't ask everyone for ID to buy alcohol or tobacco. It's a hassle for them to card people who are clearly past retirement age. Like Indiana tried to pass a law in 2010 that required they card everyone, and the uproar was so big they changed it to require carding everyone who didn't look more than 40.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Two r/SeattleWA mods are called out for bad behavior on Discord. Commenters lament that r/SeattleWA is now as bad as r/Seattle, and make a third subreddit called r/SeaWA in reaction.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 06:42:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-02 23:58:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>They'd rather believe someone's "out to get them" than know that nobody really gives a fuck what they're thinking or doing. The world's apathy is too frightening to face.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 00:47:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>As an elderly woman behind the counter in a small town, I'm glad they could do the evolution. I didn't want to sleep in Satan's bed in the ID before making a last exit out of seattle. Why go home if there's no way to get back across the oceans to your porch?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 02:14:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>WTF are you on about? Robert Byrd very vocally regreted the associations he had with the KKK when he was younger, and opposed racism and segregation. He also died in 2010, when Americans were still evenly split on the approval/disapproval of gay marriage.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 02:35:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm pretty sure you can't kill me with these low-effort shitposts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 06:25:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only reason T_D idiots obsess about smearing Byrd is because they think he was a "race traitor." The rest of us applaud that he turned away from white supremacy in his later years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 18:34:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Downtown Seattle is full of signs like this. Most of it isn't political and is just silly phrases or weird stickers for local bands or other obscure things. They don't get removed unless it's dangerous, like someone painted over an electric freeway exit sign and interstate maintenance cleaned it up right away. But last I checked, the "One Way" sign near my old apartment still said "One Love." It's part of the weirdness of Seattle, I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 19:14:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's distributed by a subsidiary of Pure Flix, which creates films where Christians are persecuted by over-the-top strawmen atheists and liberals. These are basically propaganda films created for evangelicals, and everyone else finds them transparently stupid and/or downright offensive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 19:24:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, if it wasn't for the Cinema Snob, I wouldn't know about these atrocious films.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 21:31:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Pacific Northwest has a long history with white supremacy. Outside of the liberal centers of Seattle and Portland, it gets pretty damn red state. The Aryan Nation used to have its headquarters in Northern Idaho; they have wanted to create [an all white nation in the PNW since the 80s](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Northwest_Territorial_Imperative). Now we have white supremacist dipshits like Patriot Prayer, Identity Europa, and the Proud Boys starting shit because Trump emboldens them. Joey Gibson, founder of Patriot Prayer, is running for US Senate in WA state. And every time I look at the Seattle subreddits, it's getting brigaded by pro-gun, anti-liberal conservatives trying to politically capitalize on the homeless problem here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 23:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds like they're specifically "dependent" on the finance sector, which is centered in New York. NY State got some important banks and insurance companies to cut off ties with them. Funny how the marijuana industry manages to keep growing without being allowed to use banks, but the NRA can't live without access to finance.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 00:08:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seattle here. Insulting Portland is like insulting our little brother. Don't do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 02:04:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I, for one, think it should be used in infant formula and on powdered donuts."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 02:42:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's like a pile of shit blaming others for saying it smells bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>All y'all are watermeloning wrong</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 04:37:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 22:25:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>It amazes me that in other countries there are riots if the government tries to cut pensions, but here in the US so many people are just complacent about possible cuts to social security. The GOP wants to do it to balance the budget mess they put us in, and still people vote for them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 01:04:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The people organizing these "conservative rallies" know full well they're kicking at beehives. They want to be stung. The vast majority of the counter protesters don't fall for it, either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 01:18:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's not the police. Those are anti-fascist counter protesters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 01:27:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most of the counter protesters aren't violent at all. A small number of them intersect with the anarchist types who show up and start shit at any protest, like on May Day every year. The conservative media seems hellbent on painting all the counter protesters like this, and the dipshits in Patriot Prayer are actively seeking out the anarchist types to engage with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 05:23:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will start shopping at Fred Meyer even more now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 05:28:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reminds me of L. Ron Hubbard. I'm still not sure if a scifi writer started Scientology as a joke or if he really believed it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 07:21:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ravenna is a great neighborhood. Check out Wayward Coffeehouse on 65th and Roosevelt if you're into geeky things and tasty beverages. And if you cross over I-5 you'll get to Greenlake, which is another wonderful area for food and recreation. Light rail will also be coming to Ravenna, though it's still a few years out. The station will be near Roosevelt and 65th.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 07:32:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>No escape from reality.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 07:41:47</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Transportation Secretary Elaine L. Chao said the proposal  #8220;will promote a healthy economy by bringing newer, safer, cleaner and more fuel-efficient vehicles to U.S. roads and we look forward to receiving input from the public. #8221; She's just as full of shit as [her husband](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mitch_McConnell).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 16:29:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sure the Obamas will have a splendid holiday party.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 17:01:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm currently pregnant and not immune to rubella, despite being vaccinated. I wasn't immune during my previous pregnancy with my son either, and they gave me an MMR shot right after giving birth a few years ago. Some vaccines don't work for a small number of people. It's yet another reason herd immunity is important.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-05 23:52:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>It depends on how well the building was made. Older buildings tend to be noisier, but that also depends on the materials. Like I once lived in Belltown in a century-old brick building and only heard my neighbors through open windows or if they were moving heavy furniture above. The bass from the music in the clubs or somebody's stereo could also get through. But I never heard my neighbors arguing. A lot of smaller apartments such as the 4- or 8-plexes seem pretty cheaply made with paper-thin drywall. Or if the place used to be a cheap motel, it's probably not going to be very quiet. The quietest apartment I lived was a brand new building many floors up. The builders made it with concrete floors and generous air gaps between the apartments. I never heard my neighbors, and they never heard my crying newborn (I hope). But that place was also very expensive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 01:55:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great story I'd never heard before. Just one irk about it, though... they seem to be confusing measles with "German measles" (rubella) sometimes. Measles can be a deadly disease for anyone who gets it, while rubella is pretty mild for children and adults but very harmful for unborn babies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 02:15:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maple Leaf Is it Seattle? Is it a suburb? Half of it has sidewalks, half doesn't. It's full of old craftsman houses, with cozy neighborhood cafes on tree-lined Roosevelt Way. Very chill, but don't expect much of a nightlife.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 02:18:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, Kobach was appointed to a sham commission by a white nationalist, so...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 17:11:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>WW2 was won by the Allies, who were a lot more than just the US. Saying that America alone won WW2 is like saying the Burj Khalifa is the tallest building in the world just because of its top 700 ft. It wouldn't be so tall without the other 2,000 ft below it. Also, anti-fascists pre-date WW2. They have been there a very long time, fighting the Nazis, Franco, Mussolini. Though they didn't initially stop the rise of those governments, they fought against a greater evil and many lost their lives, and ultimately they won as the Allies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 20:24:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stop the anti-vaxxers first. Flat-earthers are harmless by comparison.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 23:16:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is going to make a great buddy comedy movie someday.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 00:38:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>... scarlet fever never disappeared. It's a complication of an untreated strep infection, like strep throat. There's no vaccine, but antibiotics prevent it from causing life-threatening complications like heart or kidney failure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 03:30:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, at least we'll get more pictures for r/beholdthemasterrace.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 06:04:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Poorly-designed Seattle intersection #438.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 16:26:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are vaccine trials that fail, such as [one for an HIV vaccine that made some people more susceptible](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC2234358/). But vaccines that are released to the general population are considered safe, unless you're allergic to a component of the vaccine or something. The US government also has [an official program for addressing any "vaccine injury" claims](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vaccine_court) that come up, so they acknowledge the risk isn't zero, but the program itself was established to protect vaccine production from litigious people so everyone can continue to get the benefits of widespread vaccination.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 23:44:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now you can choose to get BOTH black lung and mesothelioma. That's what liberty is all about!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 00:15:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe there's PCP in that pipe he's smoking, because this is downright insane.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 19:04:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yep. The anarchists are the same who show up every May Day and start shit in Seattle and Portland. They aren't an organization, because anarchy is the antithesis of an organization. Yet the conservatives keep conflating them with "antifa" boogeymen and saying the liberals who come to counter-protest are violent, when the vast majority are non-violent and are linked to actual community organizations who advocate for tolerance and compassion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 00:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty sure if a company smears an applicant or an ex-employee all over the internet, they're opening themselves up to being sued. Most companies go out of their way to avoid drama when they reject a candidate, or if they fire or layoff an employee. Often they'll give a good reference so an employee can get rehired, even if that person was totally a bumbling fool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 00:41:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I for one think we should start using whale oil lamps again. Find me Moby Dick!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 00:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ooolala, look at this fancy guy with his ability to refine ores into metal. Rubbing sticks together is where it's at. Make America Stone Age Again!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 00:55:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oog ugh aaaagh libruls. Me fist bash!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 02:28:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like this guy is a T_D troll who is posting US news on r/worldnews instead of r/news because he was banned there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 06:34:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>My son's pediatrician said she doesn't do shots because another pediatrician she knew, who did the shots herself, would get recognized in public by her patients. Like she'd be at the mall and a kid would freak out because he saw the lady who gave him shots. Funny story, I guess, but what about if kids freak out at the poor nurses?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 06:39:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I took my toddler to a petting zoo recently and they had very conspicuous handwashing stations, not to mention that the attendant wouldn't let you in the pen unless you washed your hands. Then they told you again to wash your hands after leaving.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 06:54:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, my son had a 105 temp around age two. We freaked out, took him to urgent care. They looked at him... no ear infection, no lethargy, no rash, no red flags. We had just given him ibuprofen and the fever had gone down significantly. He actually pulled a cereal bar from our baby bag in the doctor's office and started eating it. The doctor sent us home, just saying that it was a random virus and he'd be probably be just fine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 06:59:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gosh that's a lot of big sciency words. NARF!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 15:09:06</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Cathy I hope the Dems use this fundraiser against Cathy McMorris Rodgers. She's been losing ground in Eastern Washington and could lose reelection. http://www.spokesman.com/stories/2018/aug/07/brown-tops-mcmorris-rodgers-in-early-returns/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 15:29:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>And how dare the Democrats use "identity politics" to appeal to voters. /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>From Spokane to Seattle, Democrats #8217; strong primary showings a warning to Republicans</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 15:40:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 15:51:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>... so you're saying I could eat a taco naked anywhere before I drive thru the mosque for my Sharia forced abortion?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 16:35:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Titanium dioxide is in almost everything these days. If you have something that is painted or manufactured to be bright white, it most likely has titanium dioxide, because it's the safest and best white pigment out there. It's even used in cosmetics and food. The only way titanium dioxide is found to possibly cause cancer in humans is breathing the pigment in dust form, which would only happen for people in manufacturing. Zinc oxide is similar. It's safe enough to use in food, but breathing it can make people sick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 17:04:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't find much about it causing birth defects except for a study in mice. Specifically the nanoparticle version of zinc oxide (and titanium dioxide) have been studied as potentially harmful, but the stuff used for humans isn't nanoparticle. I'm currently pregnant and use zinc oxide sunscreen all the time. Also, my prenatal vitamins actually contain zinc oxide because that's what they use to fortify food with zinc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 17:54:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been trying out Nextdoor for Seattle, which is supposed to be a Facebook for neighborhoods. Sign up required extra verification of your address, so one would think they don't have fake accounts. But there was this person yesterday I swear was some sort of foreign troll. The OP was complaining about how they found Nextdoor to be full of nastiness and hate. This commenter decided to prove OP right by repeatedly spouting misspelled, anti-liberal vitriol no matter how much others told them to shut up. They claimed to be an immigrant spouse from Germany, but I swear they sounded like pure uneducated Murican. After they used "\#WalkAway" with the hash to tell people to stop voting Democrat, someone else called them a Russian troll because hashtags aren't supported on Nextdoor and that hashtag is apparently popular with known Russian bots. I reported the account to Nextdoor, but, yeah, I felt disillusioned and despondent. It's like social media companies are making no effort to get rid of the problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 20:32:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tabloids aren't harmless either. Remember that Rupert Murdoch first made his fortune off tabloids in Australia and the UK, and used that to grow into News Corporation and Fox News. He pushed for more sensationalism in journalism. The British tabloids advocated for Brexit and are often credited as the reason so many Brits foolishly voted to leave the EU.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 20:54:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've also read before that the Texas Board of Education has an oversized influence on how textbooks are written for other states, since Texas has so many kids and textbook makers have to focus on making content that Texas approves. And of course the Board of Education is full of religious nuts who want creationism taught next to evolution. They also get pro-Islam content removed, including legitimate facts about the breakthroughs made by medieval Islamic scientists and doctors, and try to gloss over the the history of slavery and the American Civil War.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 21:18:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, that's much better. It was annoying me that the people in r/kerning don't seem to know what kerning is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 21:55:01</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; In fact, in a new poll released by the group today, Trump #8217;s approval rating among blacks has reached 21 percent, more than double what it was in an April Reuters poll. You can't compare a poll done by Reuters to a poll done by someone else and say the difference is representative of anything. The methodologies and results are going to be very different when it's not done by the same pollsters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 23:16:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then Dick Cheney's friend has a press conference to apologize for letting his face get in the way of Dick Cheney's gun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 02:05:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nobody needs to be a nuclear physicist to understand that nuclear weapons are dangerous to humanity and need to be limited. It's obvious from their aftermath.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 02:17:04</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Twitter doesn't have the resources to investigate every possible terms violation. Every internet platform that lets users generate content starts with this excuse, that they are just a venue and not responsible for what their users do. The truth is that they don't want to reduce their profits by investing in better content screening methods. But once they start getting lawsuits, fines, disengaged users, and a need to hire expensive legal teams, they suddenly have enough resources to invest in cleaning up their content.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 02:25:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Criminals get guns by breaking into your house and stealing the guns you bought to protect yourself from break ins. Kinda like how the Soviet Union stole nuclear secrets to make their own, then the nuclear arms race expanded to the point that we have enough of them ready to destroy humanity a thousand times over. The Cold War didn't make anybody safer, and carrying around a gun doesn't make you any safer. It just breeds fear and makes killing people easier.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 02:45:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I know exactly how this is handled at other companies because I've worked with these systems before. The way other tech companies do this is by creating filters that detect suspicious behavior, which may include certain words or phrases, suspicious IPs, changes in activity frequency or active times, etc. Then they refer anything that gets flagged for further review, usually a manual review (by an actual person). Depending on how the filter is prioritized, the content may be removed from view until it's reviewed. If a user reports a content violation, that usually goes to manual review. If a pattern of reports comes up pointing to a new problem not being identified by the filters, like an influx of scam content or other problematic user behavior, new filters are implemented to catch those. It's a game of cat and mouse, and no tech company is just hiring live people to review everything that users do. Most of it is automated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 03:14:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's an incredibly rare possibility, as rare as getting struck by lightning. And if such a thing became common enough for me to worry about, I'd probably be living in a post-apocalyptic hellhole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 16:58:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dinesh D'Souza?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 21:39:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm guessung that graphic showed the deficit from early in Obama's presidency, from when he was cleaning up the crisis Bush II caused. That's the usual pattern, Republicans muck things up and Democrats get blamed for the extra spending needed to make it better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 00:04:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>*Wah wah wah wah clunk clunk beep screeeeeeeeeech bonk buh bonk buh screeee....*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 00:09:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>He looks like a young [General Zod](http://superman.wikia.com/wiki/General_Zod?file=General_Zod_Man_of_Steel.jpg).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 01:20:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vaccine injuries do happen and are actually reported to the US government via a special program called the Vaccine Injury Compensation Program (VICP). The have a claims process and separate court system for validating petitions of vaccine injury, and victims are compensated from a tax that the vaccine makers pay. You can find statistics on vaccine injury claims here: https://www.hrsa.gov/vaccine-compensation/data/index.html An interesting tidbit from that site shows how rare vaccine injuries actually are:  gt; According to the CDC, from 2006 to 2016 over 3.1 billion doses of covered vaccines were distributed in the U.S. For petitions filed in this time period, 5,517 petitions were adjudicated by the Court, and of those 3,737 were compensated. This means for every 1 million doses of vaccine that were distributed, 1 individual was compensated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 01:50:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Uhhh... what? While most soybeans are used for livestock food, the same can be said for other major crops like corn. Soy is also used to make oil and "real" foods like tofu, which is a great source of protein. Feeding livestock also produces more "real" food in the form of meats, dairy, and eggs. Because it's a legume, soybeans also have the added bonus of improving the soil through nitrogen fixation. Rotating soybean crops with other crops reduces the need for fertilizers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 02:01:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>But what about free speech? We all know the Founding Fathers fully intended that any and every citizen could go to their local printing press and demand the owner immediately produce #8212;and distribute #8212;a thousand pamphlets of their longwinded tirades about how Benedict Arnold wasn't a bad fellow or about how Martha Washington was cuckolding her husband. It's right there in the First Amendment!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 04:42:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Japan, the biggest consumer of soy in the world, also has the best life expectancy because of their very healthy diet. They eat soy with every meal. It baffles me that you would call soybeans garbage food and blame them for fat, unhealthy Americans.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 04:52:10</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;Durandy I was gonna say, I've met that guy in the middle, Andy Golub. He used to exhibit some of his memorabilia at local galleries. He seems to eat, breathe, and sleep all things Duran Duran.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 05:02:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same thing as Roger Stone does on Twitter!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 17:02:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, back in the day printing pamphlets was pretty expensive and the presses expected to profit from it, just like they do today. Like Thomas Paine's *Common Sense* pamphlet was printed to be sold and the publisher almost dropped it because it didn't sell well at first. People assume that because you can use Twitter for free, publishing content comes at no cost to Twitter. While Twitter's cost of posting a tweet is almost nothing, it's not zero, and Twitter expects to make money off the content through ad revenue. Like any publisher, they can drop someone for losing them revenue (and still keep around a toxic user like Trump because he's a cash cow).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 17:20:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sex determination works very differently in amphibians than mammals. Some frogs actually have the ability to switch sexes completely when needed, like if there aren't any males for reproduction. (This was a plot point in *Jurassic Park*, where the scientists filled in missing DNA in the dinosaurs with frog DNA and accidentally allowed the all female population to generate males and start reproducing.) So atrazine is interfering with amphibians by hijacking something already in their biology. The effects of atrazine on humans are much different. It's not "feminizing," but has been noted to increase birth defects.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-11 20:58:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok.... so does that mean if I turn away the Jehovah Witnesses for trying to preach their BS at my door, I'm violating the First Amendment?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 01:21:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hormones are a complicated thing, especially in more complicated organisms like humans and other mammals. Mammals have relatively rigid states of being after they're born, in that they can't do things like regenerate body parts. Like with the frogs changing sex, they can do that because their body can dissolve their reproductive organs and regenerate new ones. So changes in humans tend to be more subtle, like how sex hormones can increase or decrease the size of reproductive organs or change the inclination for different sexual behaviors. Hormones are not going make a human penis turn into a vagina, and there isn't a whole lot of evidence that they'll make someone change their sexual orientation. They may influence the development of fetuses in the womb, though research has yet to find any specific thing that will definitely make a child "gay." IMHO, there's just a very common obsession in human culture about men becoming feminine. It's sort of like the ancient fear of castration. Males are conditioned to have angst over anything that could make them less manly, physically or mentally. So when encountering men who are outside the normal gender role, they feel a need to figure out what went "wrong" so they can avoid it at all costs. Cue the scapegoating of soy products, or overly-protective mothers, or playing with girl toys, or whatever. This angst, coupled with the inability to find any specific environmental causes of "abnormal" gender, makes me think human sexuality is a lot more nature than nurture. Anyway, I think studying other organisms and how sex/gender works for them is pretty fascinating. I'd recommend this book for a fun read about it: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dr_Tatiana's_Sex_Advice_to_All_Creation</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 07:11:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I lived in Belltown, there was this homeless guy who would panhandle next to the Aurora on ramp on Battery St. He had a normal sign like "NEED FOOD GOD BLESS" or something like that. But if a woman such as myself was driving by, he'd flip over the sign to say "NEED A SUGAR MAMA" and make a lewd smile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 07:59:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Probably just some rich guy we don't know, but, hey, TIL today is the birthday of Ian McDiarmid (Emperor Palpatine) and Steve Wozniak. Thanks, Internet!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 17:47:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Very true. Considering that poll workers tend to be elderly volunteers, they could be the weakest part of the security.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 20:02:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Flight noise is pretty bad lately in Northeast Seattle, like Maple Leaf/Ravenna/U District. There seem to be a lot more flights coming over this area. Even in Capitol Hill around Volunteer Park, there are constant planes. It's probably not as bad as Burien, though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 21:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're not coming from there. They're larger jets approaching for landing from the north.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 21:18:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not in Burien often enough for comparison, but I'm sure it's worse around there. Some of the neighbors have been complaining about it more lately. Someone claimed they measured with a decibel meter and it's exceeding the allowed noise levels. At the moment, it seems like typical North Seattle whining. I have to admit when I was walking through Maple Leaf yesterday there were constant jets flying overheard, all approaching for landing from the north. I heard fewer today so it may just be dependent on weather.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 22:09:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just add some "Elder" name badges and they're the same.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 23:28:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're kinda the one who brought up they weren't white, as if that makes their abhorrent opinions any better?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 00:41:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>A homeless guy got on a crowded D line bus, brandishing a golf club. He sat in the middle, waving it from his crotch and trying to start conversations with everybody around him. Everyone tried to ignore him. Luckily he ran off the bus around Leary Way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 07:10:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's like a Dunning-Krueger fractal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 00:39:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>The fact that the kid in this post was placed in foster care tells me there's a lot more going on than the kid falling off a couch. Of course the parents would never admit it on social media. I know some parents who had their kid taken away because of Munchausen-by-proxy (unnecessary and harmful medical treatments because the parents wanted attention on social media for their sick child), but I only learned of the truth because the actual abuse was reported in the local newspaper. On social media, the parents claimed CPS were unfairly persecuting them and they posted shit from conspiracy sites as "evidence."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 00:40:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>The general rule is that a child falling from more than two times their height is more likely to hurt themselves. They could still hurt themselves at lower heights, depending on how they land and on what. Infants are also more at risk from fall. But, as the parent of a very rambunctious and stubborn toddler, I can say that he's fallen off a lot of furniture and only had bruises so far (knock on wood).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 02:10:58</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; The Trump administration called the contamination  #8220;a potential public relations nightmare #8221; earlier this year after federal toxicology studies found that some of the compounds are more hazardous than previously acknowledged. Translation: "The Trump Administration will see to it that the EPA stops all future toxicology studies so nobody ever learns more this kind of thing."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 02:46:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>The logic with some people is that if she voted on some bipartisan legislation the Republicans put forth, she's pretty much a Republican. Never mind that the rest of her voting record is incredibly progressive. Also, she may not have swooned over a certain Senator from Vermont, therefore she's pretty much a Republican I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 02:53:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's going to be an entire bookshelf in Barnes  amp; Noble called "Trump Tell-All Books," if it isn't there already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 02:56:47</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Seattle #8217;s Lynnwood Light Rail extension Yup. We're pretty annoyed about this is Seattle. Add to this that Trump's dumb tariffs are the reason construction costs are going up. I hope we sue the Trump Admin if they won't send the promised funds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 03:00:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most are, but some are in red or swing states: * Albuquerque, NM Central Avenue BRT * Dallas, TX DART Red  amp; Blue Line Platform Extensions * El Paso, TX BRT Extension * Jacksonville, FL Southwest BRT * Los Angeles, CA Purple Line Extension (LRT), Section 3 * Minneapolis, MN Blue Line (LRT) Extension * Minneapolis, MN Green Line (LRT) Extension * Minneapolis, MN Orange Line BRT * New York City, NY Canarsie (L) Line Improvements * Orange County, CA Streetcar * Reno, NV Virginia Street BRT * Sacramento, CA Riverfront Streetcar * Seattle, WA Lynnwood LRT extension * Seattle, WA Madison Street BRT * South Shore (IN/IL) Commuter Rail Double Tracking * St. Petersburg, FL Central Avenue BRT * Tempe, AZ Streetcar</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 15:51:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Goldwater failed because he didn't take up the mantle of Evangelicals and actually despised the influence of the religious right, because he actually didn't like how they sought to restrict liberties for others. (Though, like many of the libertarian policies of today, many of the liberties he championed like "states' rights" were essentially the liberty to exercise intolerance and perpetuate inequality.) But Reagan gladly cherrypicked parts of Goldwater's libertarian philosophy and also pandered to evangelical grievances like fear of abortion and women's rights, to great political success. Now Trump is pretty much Shitty Reagan.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 16:29:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Children don't get the MMR (measles, mumps, rubella) until they're a year old. Being that Seattle has so many crunchy anti-vaxxers, I kept my son away from suspiciously sick kids before then.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 23:12:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get steelhead salmon sushi all the time here in Seattle. It's cheap grocery store sushi, but it's pretty good for the price and it's clearly steelhead. It's not the premium salmon you'd get at a proper sushi place, but I can't buy that every day. Or if I want a nice salmon for dinner, the grocery store has king salmon right now, too. You can't get away with mislabeling salmon in Seattle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 15:44:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not many. Here's an article about the use of immigrant farm workers in NC. The farmers have to recruit locally before they can hire Mexican guest workers, and according to the article, for 6500 jobs posted in 2011 in an area with 10% unemployment, 268 US natives applied, 264 were hired (they would hire pretty much anyone and paid well above minimum wage), 163 actually showed up, half left after a month, and only 7 made it to the end of the growing season. https://www.newsobserver.com/news/business/article160086719.html</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 16:51:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I voted for Clinton over Bernie, but this is water under the bridge. Let's focus on the real threat of the GOP.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 17:32:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is a historical irony with black people using the N-word. That irony doesn't exist when other people use it, particularly if white people use it, because the origin of the word is that white people used it to denigrate and oppress black people. This historical context has not disappeared. It's entirely possible for a black person to use it offensively, too, but it depends on social context. I mean, all language is contextual, and all cultures have taboos. Maybe it's unfair that white people can't use the N-word, but in the grand spectrum of unfairness I'm far more concerned that black people die more from treatable illnesses and have higher unemployment. And why would I, a white person, care to use the N-word in the first place, when I understand it's so hurtful and there's literally no situation in which I would find it necessary?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 18:22:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>The "irony" with black people using the N-word is specifically [reappropriation](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Reappropriation), where a group of people start using a slur against them in order to give it less power and turn the animosity of it back on the ones trying to degrade them. This happens a lot, like with the words "queer," bitch," etc. A recent example is the word "deplorable," where Trump supporters took a word used by Hillary Clinton to proudly describe themselves, or where Clinton supporters adopted "nasty woman." Using these terms is an act of defiance by the people they were used against, and in this context it's seen as "acceptable." But I think where people have a problem is that it's also confrontational and not diplomatic. That's why you see people like black rappers using the N-word, because they mean to provoke (which may or may not be making a legitimate point, again depending on the context). But you're not going to see Obama or other black politicians use it because they usually don't want to be divisive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 19:58:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't you feel them trickling down?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 20:46:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm imagining Freddy Mercury singing "Fat Bottom Boys."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 20:49:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, mass vaccination is basically the Holocaust. /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 22:50:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Can't find a better man." - GOP, on Trump</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 23:01:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I once figured out the northernmost place I've been while not in an airplane, and was surprised it was Berlin. It's further north than Vancouver or London.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 00:39:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reminds me of this: [An Abortion Doctor So Sexual That Your Daughter Gets Horny For A Third-Term Procedure? Believe It. His Name Is Ahmed.](https://patriothole.clickhole.com/an-abortion-doctor-so-sexual-that-your-daughter-gets-ho-1825123394)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:07:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Next they'll actually do something about all the robocalls we keep getting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:22:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Now why is there a hole in the ceiling?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:35:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's pretty damn tasteless. Not sure why so many people are upvoting it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:42:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>The artist is Bobby Draws Skulls. He can't be criticized for false advertising.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 01:56:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen thali at other places, usually the restaurants with South Indian cuisine. There isn't a lot of South Indian in Seattle, but you see it more on the eastside. I did go to a North Indian restaurant recently that had thali style lunch. Check out Mani's Kitchen in Pinehurst.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 02:04:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kauai Family Kitchen in Georgetown is uniquely Hawaiian. It's a hole-in-the-wall place with odd hours and old, mismatching furniture, just like the restaurants in Hawaii. They also serve Hawaiian food that's hard to find anywhere else, like poi and lomi lomi salmon. As an added bonus, there's a Hawaiian bakery right next door where you can rarities like chantilly cake or dobash cake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 02:23:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>After this guy dies and goes to the Pearly Gates, he must think Saint Peter is gonna be like, "Well, you were a good Christian and all, but you baked some cakes for those gay people. Guess it's off to Hell with you."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 04:03:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, God, the health insurance scam ones will actually leave me voicemails. I hate those the most.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 06:31:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, this twisted logic was Trump's defense in the Trump University trial. Because the judge was Mexican and Trump said bad things about Mexicans, Trump argued the judge would be biased against him. So just be publicly racist against the judge and you're covered!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 06:53:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup, I'm reminded of Germany, too. I used to work for an international tech company that had an office in Germany. They had a "works council" that they had to consult with to approve changes for the employees. Us Americans would mock them for not being able to do overtime on the fly unless the works council approved it. But you know what? They have a much better work-life balance in Germany, with things like parental leave and protections against being fired for no reason. Us Americans are too eager to be exploited.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 15:54:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cue a reminder that Ayn Rand collected Social Security and Medicare in her later years: https://www.snopes.com/fact-check/ayn-rand-social-security/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 17:46:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Peter Thiel: proof there are gay fascists.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 18:01:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Mr. Chairman, are you, in fact, literally a shit pie?" "Why, yes. It offends me that you find anything wrong with that."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 18:03:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>The DMV believes in equal suffering for all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 18:14:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trump: "I'd like to nominate Zombie Osama Bin Laden to the Supreme Court." *Evangelicals clap.*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 18:49:36</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Patriot Prayer leader Joey Gibson, who is seeking a U.S. Senate seat in Washington state He didn't get past the primary this month, though it's disheartening to see 29,160 people actually voted for him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 19:11:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what the dialogue was back in the 90s. The Clintons said they wanted to keep abortion "safe, legal, and rare," and Republicans like John McCain understood that while he found abortion to be a moral problem, criminalizing it would just lead to illegal abortions and more maternal deaths. The hyper-partisan political environment isn't allowing for any middle ground, but I see more irrationality on abortion from conservatives than liberals. There are right wing organizations making up lies about reproductive health, many with a religious agenda of just stopping (or punishing) extramarital sex. They ignore the evidence that comprehensive sex education, free access to reproductive health clinics, and access to reliable contraception actually reduce abortions. Instead they want to defund programs that do this and advocate for "abstinence-only" programs that aren't proven to work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 19:22:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hate groups always find forums to gather. Before the internet, they handed out pamphlets or novels like *The Turner Diaries*, or they put on their white bed sheets and held rallies. It's not impossible to regulate these people. If they commit actual crimes, they're a lot more likely to go to jail for them these days than back in the heyday of the KKK. It's easier to see what they're doing on the internet, and easier to call it out, shame them, and sue them if necessary.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 19:44:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Most importantly, he doesn't like abortion!"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-16 23:43:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stop trying to sell your tasteless t-shirts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 00:05:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, there was a thread on r/SeattleWA yesterday where a bunch of people were itching to buy this. I hope they were all shills, or else some people need to contact their credit card company.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 00:30:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>So Pai should've said there was an active investigation and he couldn't yet comment on the matter. Instead he lied.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 06:36:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know who keeps upvoting these unfunny edgelord shitposts. FFS, a man died.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 07:00:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Found at the bottom of that BS article:  gt; Disclaimer: This article is not intended to provide medical advice, diagnosis or treatment. Apparently all this anti-vaxxer talk is for entertainment purposes only!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 07:09:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>It also causes some throat, anal, and penis cancers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 17:58:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks like he had a full swastika and got a cut or something that left scar tissue. Maybe someone tried to rip it off his face.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 18:43:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Arabic language and cultural studies are very common in the military these days. My husband's uncle was in the Airforce and the NSA, and during his training, they told him he needs to specialize in one of three languages: Arabic, Russian, or Chinese. The ROTC program also puts a lot of emphasis on those three. It's pretty obvious why.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 06:22:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trump's new Airforce One jets are gonna cost $3.9 billion, and that's for only two 747s.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 16:35:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>They come to West Coast liberal cities like Portland and Berkeley specifically to start shit with the protesters that show up. Like they try to provoke anarchists and anti-fascists who might retaliate with violence so they can get footage of being attacked and claim the liberals are the violent side.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 16:43:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>He knew about it. He's just covering his ass and pretending he never heard of it because it got leaked. He's just as corrupt as everyone else in the Trump Administration.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 16:56:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a very popular initiative in Washington State, and the NRA and the Second Amendment Foundation have been fighting it in court because they know it'll pass on the ballot. Sidenote: Here's a story about the Second Amendment Foundation, featuring a picture of its founder with Maria Butina, the Russian spy connected to the NRA: https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/politics/arrest-of-alleged-russian-agent-maria-butina-puts-spotlight-on-bellevues-second-amendment-foundation/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 01:18:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's real. It's called "Junges Europa" and was made by Arno Breker. https://www.liveauctioneers.com/item/33932048_-junges-europa-by-arno-breker</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 01:24:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>This statue is called "Junges Europa" and was made by Arno Breker, a sculptor best known for his nude statues made for Nazi Germany. (This work was made in the 1970s, though.) https://www.liveauctioneers.com/item/33932048_-junges-europa-by-arno-breker</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 01:46:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>It isn't exactly Nazi art, though, so the description in the picture is kinda fake. It was made by an ex-Nazi in the 1970s and it's evocative of the art he did make for Nazi Germany, but it isn't his actual Nazi Germany art.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 06:36:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope those 43 replies are all "What the fuck is wrong with you, you ignorant bastard?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 06:39:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>They need to rename the Dunning-Krueger effect after anti-vaxxers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 16:58:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lots of commercial flights go over the North Pole. They might not go over the exact pole because it can really mess with older navigation systems (modern GPS can handle it), but I can't find any info saying they're barred from that area by NATO or otherwise. Like I went from Chicago to Shanghai and that went very close to the pole. A lot of major flights from the US to Asia seem to go that way, the closest being within 60 miles of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When you're halfway through reading an article and this pops up.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 17:09:06</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 19:12:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty cool, though it's a little light on places in the Northeast. Some are obvious (Maple Leaf, Lake City, View Ridge), but there's also Pinehurst, Matthew's Beach, Meadowbrook, Victory Heights, Roosevelt, etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 20:43:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>So Congress still hasn't learned much since Ted Stevens' ["series of tubes"](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Series_of_tubes) speech.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 22:54:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>He needs footage for [Triumph of the Will](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Triumph_of_the_Will) Part Two.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-19 23:45:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>"I don't like shit, I just like to smear shit all over myself and walk around in public."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Elon Musk #8217;s Boring Co. Asks Trump Administration for Tariff Relief</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 19:42:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 20:44:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>"If he worked for the Bush Administration, he can't be all bad." \- My mother-in-law</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 20:59:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>So... are they gonna let credit card companies take away your kids if you don't pay the bill? Debtors' baby jails, here we come!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 00:36:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Tommy Wiseau of government: writer, director, producer, and lead actor.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 00:56:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sucks. I just got the TDaP for my pregnancy a few weeks ago. It's standard in the US and there have been outbreaks of whooping cough in my area. You can't insist they give you the vaccine (or talk to another doctor)?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 16:57:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's the "promotion" where they give you more responsibilities and maybe even a new title, but your compensation doesn't change because your boss says there's no money in the budget or HR is being stupid. I call this one the "bullshit promotion."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 18:03:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, the problem with the Boomers getting so much power is too complicated to fix by just barring older people from politics. They are a larger generation by shear numbers and they grew up in a time of great growth. Older people just vote more, and are more likely to have the free time and extra wealth it takes to be in politics. If we want more young politicians in office, in addition to other disadvantaged groups, we need to not only create more openings by having term limits, but more importantly reform how campaigns are financed and create public incentives for people who aren't wealthy to be able to run for office. Because your average 20-30 year old is too busy paying their bills to leave their job and run for office, even if they really wanted to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 18:53:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>A poo gas cloud.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 21:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's just a coffee attorney!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 21:22:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now it's "My Attorney Got Arrested"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 21:23:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Soo.... still calling it a witch hunt on Fox News?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 21:56:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ummmm... get an attorney and fight the charges? (That's much easier if you're also innocent.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:00:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>You laugh, but Trump is totally gonna have all his old photos edited to remove Cohen, just like Stalin did, and pretend they're 100% real.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:04:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Somewhere in the White House, John Kelly has Trump locked in the closet so he can't tweet on his phone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:07:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Scooby Doo gang is gonna pop out at any moment and pull off Michael Cohen's mask, revealing he's actually been Hillary all this time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:12:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>He would have photos manipulated to remove people who were once his close allies after that person crossed him and went to prison or was executed. This article has more: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Censorship_of_images_in_the_Soviet_Union</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:21:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't tease</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:41:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is just the first trial for Manafort. He's scheduled to go on trial in September on charges including conspiracy to defraud the United States, failing to register as a foreign agent, money laundering, witness tampering and making false statements.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:44:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>This only the first trial. He's scheduled to go on trial in September on more charges including conspiracy to defraud the United States, failing to register as a foreign agent, money laundering, witness tampering and making false statements.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:49:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please, my justice boner is going to give me a heart attack!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:50:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>J U S T I C E</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:51:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was Mike Pence, guys!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:52:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Clearly he meant Hillary Clinton, guys!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:52:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nooooooooooooo!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 22:55:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok Vlad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 23:04:52</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;fresh air Not in Seattle. It's too smokey outside, so I'm watching this dumpster fire indoors.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 23:09:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but it is Civil War material.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 23:11:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone call him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 23:15:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Guilty isn't guilty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 23:20:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Needs more ANTIFA.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 23:22:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haven't you heard? She's the candidate who directed him to pay hush money!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 23:30:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>ZOMG an illegal immigrant is suspected to have killed a pretty white girl? Trump is gonna rant about this for six straight hours at his rally tonight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 23:37:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>He didn't write that. Not enough typos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 23:43:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>"If you strike me down, I shall become more powerful than you can possibly imagine." \- Obi-Wan Trump</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 23:44:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>A huge orange turd?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 23:48:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>You ask this like you just dropped your sandwich in a pile of dog poop. No, you can't just brush the sandwich off and it'll be fine to eat, and, no, you can't just brush this shit off Trump and say he's an acceptable POTUS.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 01:06:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't understand why so many people who don't care take the time to post about how much they don't care.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"Individual-1" could literally be anyone</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 03:02:03</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 03:24:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>"INDIVIDUAL-1" COULD LITERALLY BE ANYONE</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 03:32:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>My money is on Millard Fillmore. I think he faked his death in 1874.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 07:07:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chaffetz is such a fucking tool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 07:12:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Friess looks like the crazy rich Texan from The Simpsons. I imagine he acts like him, too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 17:15:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think he's just a useful idiot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 20:17:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>"It was just a joke!" seems to be the go-to excuse for racists and douchebags alike.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 21:54:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah... Jeff "Take Away the Babies of Asylum Seekers" Sessions will never be a hero.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 22:41:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh man, if I could see what happens on 8/25/18... with the pace of things now, the White House might have mysteriously burnt down, Rand Paul might be named Prime Minister of Russia, and Michael Cohen might have been assassinated by Jack Ruby's great grandson.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 23:20:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Orrin Hatch is a bright sunny day compared to Mike Lee.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 23:29:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>She reminds me of Miss Trunchbull from *Matilda.*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 23:31:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Half of them are already in Russia, so it won't be too hard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 23:34:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a pinned mod post saying that they're flairing some posts "Conservative Only" and you can only comment if they grant you a "Conservative" flair. Muh free speech.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 23:52:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nixon infamously said, "When the President does it, that means that it is not illegal." It was shocking then, and it should still be shocking now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 00:02:57</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;cancer I see him more as AIDS, because he's infecting all the institutions meant to protect against disease and making them allow more diseases to enter, like how AIDS infects white blood cells.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 00:46:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a guy in Colorado arrested this week for allegedly strangling his pregnant wife and two daughters then dumping their bodies at his work, after he had a fight with his wife over his own infidelity. Why isn't the GOP calling for better protections against domestic abuse? Because that guy in Colorado was a white US citizen and all they care about is fearmongering against brown immigrants.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 01:19:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Avast! The fabled [Northwest Passage](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Northwest_Passage) has been discovered, and Europe can enjoy the spoils of the Orient. Inform King George III so we can collect our award, posthaste.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 01:39:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>u ok?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 02:22:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, this reeks of David Pecker and the *National Enquirer*, especially because the feds have searched for info in connection with that: https://www.nytimes.com/2018/04/11/us/politics/trump-national-enquirer-american-media.html</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 04:16:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Grab 'em by the front hole." \- An unindicted co-conspirator</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 04:20:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>If Trump had to face the same justice system a poor man did, he would have died young from a shanking during a riot at Attica.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 04:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Okay.](https://m.huffpost.com/us/entry/11983400)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 05:44:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mean, he had to see if the players took a knee during the anthem so he could make unhinged rants about it on Twitter or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 06:06:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I think people are misreading this. She's a Trump supporter, yes, but she wasn't the holdout.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 17:51:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>A few days ago, an article about white South Africans having their farms taken away was on r/worldnews.... it had over 10K upvotes and only 9 comments because the mods locked commenting. It was... weird. This story keeps popping up over there, but that sub seems to be rife with racebaiting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 19:06:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Batboy is a true patriot. I bet he's undercover in Russia right now, hiding in Putin's chimney.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 19:46:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>So... they're totally cool with child labor. Why need immigrants when poor 6-year-olds can do it for peanuts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 19:58:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not only that, Trump is actively fucking up infrastructure projects. Like there are 17 big infrastructure projects for which Congress has promised $1.4 billion, and the Trump Administration is refusing to issue the funds with no explanation whatsoever. Also, construction costs are skyrocketing on these projects because Trump's tariffs are increasing the cost of materials. https://www.citylab.com/transportation/2018/08/the-14-billion-transit-fund-the-government-wont-release/567467/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 22:43:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>He looks like an even schmuckier David Schwimmer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 20:31:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>The delusion is strong with Trump supporters. They'd demand he get the Nobel Prize for wiping his own ass.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 20:35:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>He'll probably just have a fake Nobel Prize medal made up and have his own award ceremony for it, complete with clapping sycophantic interns.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 20:55:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>To quote [the old Randy Newman song](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Short_People), "I don't want no short people round here."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 22:26:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nobody has ever been so excited to see tax return forms as we are now. Show me the deductions!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 22:36:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>And on the other side of the crazy spectrum... incels?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 03:42:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Plus the fact that Amazon was selling them by the pound.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 03:55:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>The right's hatred of Bill Clinton started long before his affair. They will demonize anything the Democrats do, even if they're scandal-free like Obama and just have a Muslim-sounding middle name or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 04:56:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some once [did a study](https://poseidon01.ssrn.com/delivery.php?ID=777119081090114115125007123078072029117046025068004010066117108028006102104102125119029035055009008044005104103118121028001122106071060023014125076107069105081077066011054101120070115102016104022099070085106116125064096021028091071083075003091084020 amp;EXT=pdf) that found couples who spent more on weddings and engagement rings were more likely to divorce.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 05:25:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let's resurrect the political slogan used against Grover Cleveland for his alleged love child: ["Ma, ma, where's my pa?"](https://www.smithsonianmag.com/history/president-clevelands-problem-child-100800/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 05:31:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hawaii may be going through quite a hurricane, but for the rest of us we've got a category 5 shitstorm, and it ain't losing strength.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 07:04:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>The *Wall Street Journal*, which is also a News Corp company falling under Rupert Murdoch's shadow, has been breaking a lot of the Trump stories this week.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 17:35:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>He has so many rats around him we should call him Willard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 20:25:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That never happened. Palin was called out for being an inexperienced idiot, but neither her nor McCain were ever called a Nazi by the Democrats.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 20:44:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I saw a lot of frustration and even shame in McCain's reaction here, in hindsight. He knew there was this bigoted side to the Republican base, shown here in this woman's fear of "Arabs" #8212;an ignorant way to refer to Muslims. He wanted to tamp it down and keep it civil, whereas Trump came in and pandered to their hatred.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 21:30:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's nothing in current law that says the POTUS can or can't be indicted while in office. Several legal scholars have tried to answer the question during times when the question came up, like with Nixon and Bill Clinton, but with Nixon he resigned before the question could be tested, and with Bill Clinton he was impeached but never convicted by Congress, and he was never indicted for criminal matters, only sued for civil matters. So with Trump, it's not that he can't be indicted, it's that there first needs to be an organization to indict him, which the Justice Department has declined to do. State crimes would be another matter entirely. And if Trump was indicted, the question would probably go to the Supreme Court to finally answer whether it's possible or not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 00:41:33</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; Trump has helped expose those GOPers who were working to line their pockets with cheap labor. Including himself, who has used undocumented immigrants for construction projects and has his cheap clothing manufactured in China?  gt; But yeah Trump fucked a porn star this one time, so we should totally ignore this problem. More than once, more than one porn star, and while he was married. Oh, and he illegally paid hush money to them and lied about it repeatedly. Also, Trump is a conman who makes promises he can't keep. Quit deluding yourself, and quit trying to delude others. Nobody outside of his base believes anything Trump says anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 02:03:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>This post is going to be removed because it's not politics and it's not the article's exact title, but I don't think there's a D/R divide in being pro- or anti-zipper merge. Zipper merging is the best way to go, and this can be proven with engineering models and live tests, but neither the drivers in the reddest states nor the drivers in the bluest states do it. The hell that is traffic transcends politics.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 02:28:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's true. An illegal immigrant murdered me yesterday, and a few months ago, too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 02:35:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2018/08/14/liz-prez-gop-charges-warren-has-white-house-ambitions/qBc47qi5qrGPsTeaxJF1uM/story.html Looks like that was John Kingston, attacking her for presidential ambitions.  gt;  #8220;Like too many Massachusetts politicians, she #8217;d rather skip the Fenway franks and instead eat Iowa corn dogs." Lame.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 02:37:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>And this conservative newsrag thinks that's a bad thing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 03:00:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just report them and downvote them. They deserve no replies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 03:10:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, but we're not going to spit on his grave, let alone his still-warm corpse. Have some decency.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 03:11:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 17:06:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ha! This song is the weirdest thing. It came from the sequel to Willard, *Ben*, which was just a mediocre B movie, but the song won the Golden Globe for Best Song that year, was nominated for an Academy Award, and was Michael Jackson's first #1 hit as a solo artist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 17:22:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>SPOILER ALERT. He is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 17:43:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I pulled myself up by my bootstraps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 18:36:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trump should be impeached for the smug ass smile alone. But, you know, repeatedly telling his lackeys to commit crimes for him is a pretty damn legitimate reason, too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 22:07:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fricking AR-15s. Every gun debate lately devolves into some pedantic pro-gun person attacking the concept of an assault weapon and saying people who support gun control just don't understand how an AR-15 works.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 22:24:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Democrats don't need to fight right-wing authoritarians by being left-wing authoritarians.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 22:33:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not known yet. People claim to have seen a red laser sight on the Twitch stream.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 23:24:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm pretty sure there aren't any guns in the Bible #8212;or the Torah or the Quran or most any holy book. But I'm also sure Jesus wouldn't have been packing heat in old Judah if he could. Maybe Simon the Zealot would've, but Jesus told him to chill.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 23:28:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's either a troll or a devoted Infowars listener.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-26 23:49:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no... you mean the administration that couldn't seem to backfill their staff after firing all of Obama's people can't use their small army of white nationalist interns recruited off T_D to handle all this legal stuff?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 00:01:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really? The Daily Mirror? What is with the Trumps and reading tabloid trash?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 00:09:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>He has a GoFundMe page for his legal fund (I'd link it but the automod will remove my comment if I do).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 01:17:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dubya is a good eugooglizer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 01:21:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is happening on every McCain article today. Seems to be a mixture of Russian bots stirring up shit, dumb teenagers trying to be edgy, and just plain tasteless adults who can't wait until the man is in his grave to dance on it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 01:40:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is really hard to "leave" the Mormon church, even for those not in attendance. They baptize at age 8 and will continue to keep people on their roles indefinitely unless someone jumps through their hoops to be removed. Ex-mormons have even created a website to facilitate their removal through legal help because the LDS church makes it so difficult: https://quitmormon.com</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 02:06:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Even for people who aren't ostracized, actually getting their names out of the Mormon roles is tough. They add you as soon as you're baptized at age 8, and they'll keep you on the role until they know you died, and even then they keep records of dead Mormons. To be removed, you have to request it and do some interview with a bishop. It's such a hassle, I haven't done it myself, despite leaving over twenty years ago. Though I just tried QuitMormon.com and am waiting to see if that works.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 02:49:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Mormons are pretty aggressive about outreach to inactive members. I moved to another state, but they still contact my parents about me. They also found my email online and tried to contact me that way. I resist replying because if they find out where I live they'll send over missionaries or other local Mormons to knock on my door. I also don't like being included in their numbers, which they use to advertise what a huge, growing religion they are. I have a lot of problems with their ideology, which is the reason I left, and they're pretending people like me still support their agenda.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 03:06:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>They are to this day very against women's rights and LGBT rights, and continue to excommunicate women who agitate for leadership roles and gay people who refuse to act straight. And they use their money and members to push that agenda beyond their church into US politics, especially in states where they have a lot of members.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 03:30:38</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;we believe in sex for procreation purposes This is the crux of the Mormon church's agenda. Men and women are not equal in marriage, not in a real world, meaningful way. The church will give lip service to women saying in the eyes of God that the man's role of being a leader for his community and family is the same importance as a woman's role of bearing and raising children. But the strict gender roles give Mormon women significantly less power than men. The Mormon agenda is to make more members, full stop. Without that, their numbers and their tithing income would be far less. That's why they had polygamy back in the day. That's why they compel their young members to go on missions and convert poor people in desperate communities. That's why they compel their members to have as much children as possible and keep women from breaking free of that role. That's why they ban homosexual activities.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 05:08:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. Satan is at the center of the Ninth Circle of Hell, and in his three mouths he chews on Judas, Brutus, and Cassius, who were the three most infamous traitors in Dante's time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 05:31:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nixon was a much smarter man than Trump, and the investigations started by Woodward and Bernstein brought him down. I'm not sure Junior even knows that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 17:36:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't used Facebook in over a year, but I remember repeatedly getting notices to reconnect with friends who had died.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 17:55:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://www.npr.org/2018/08/27/642199524/student-loan-watchdog-quits-blames-trump-administration</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 18:01:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>He was also the last in a string of crappy presidents who did little to prevent the animosity leading up to the Civil War. Abraham Lincoln came directly after him, and he's considered the best president, or at least one of the best alongside Washington and FDR.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 18:31:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's an orange shitgibbon, or *Homo stupidus mendax*. Get your facts straight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 18:39:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey Florida! Quit voting for Republicans!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 19:08:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go, go, Godzilla!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 20:14:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>This sounds like a great way for GOP donors to make money off humiliating immigrants with ankle bracelet monitoring.  gt; Visa fraud is the biggest contributor to crime Hard to believe that when immigrants, whether legal or not, commit crimes at a rate less than US citizens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 20:18:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>A very thin majority of white women supported him. They tend to be older, married, more religious, and more rural.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 20:24:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>You say this as a joke, but this is something unions actually do. They lobby Congress and local legislators in order to help their members.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 20:59:22</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I have spent literally millions of dollars trying to do talks, speeches, events, rallies and protests, to say nothing of all the stuff I do behind the scenes I can never tell you about. A lot of that money was my own wealth, from before I even started in journalism. But most of that money came from the Mercers. Did that well finally dry up?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 22:59:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember in the 90s how the Republicans kept calling Bill Clinton a flip flopper. I never understood their criticism because he was doing what reasonable people do: change their minds when they get more information, and compromise to get things done. But Trump's version of flip flopping is never reasonable. Either he double downs and adds even more bullshit to his reasoning, or he caves in to criticism and does the most half-ass, passive aggressive job to "correct" it, often by saying he'll fix it then just letting it drop out of the news.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-27 23:03:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Role modeling"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 05:09:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's cute that you think McCain, Nixon and the Republican party actually exist and aren't part of a Grand Old Projection made by the lizard people directly into our brains.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 15:48:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a feeling things aren't going to go as well for Trump when Lopez Obrador takes power.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 18:21:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm an ex-Mormon woman from Utah (one of the states in this case) who left the LDS church specifically because of their backwards treatment of gender issues. Their hatred of LGBT people all comes down to procreative gender roles dictated by their religion and that's why it's being put forth as a matter of "religious freedom." With Christian churchs like the Mormons, they sustain their numbers and their power by making their members marry young so they can pop out a lot of children (AKA future church members). So women are compelled to be housewives and both sexes are told anything but procreative, heterosexual, marital sex is sinful. LGBT behavior challenge this, and thus the churches ban it and persecute LGBT people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 18:27:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>No....  gt; anything but procreative, heterosexual, marital sex in sinful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 18:41:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>1930s: The Dust Bowl decimates farmers in the United States, prompting FDR's liberal government to improve land management and promote better farming practices, along with issuing affected people assistance through the New Deal. Conservatives balk at the efforts as too much spending. 2018: The Donald decimates farmers in the United States by being a vindictive dumb fuck who doesn't understand basic economics. His administration gives farmers billions in welfare to make up for it. Conservatives stand around and pick their noses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 16:09:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>The *Honolulu Star-Advertiser* is actually a legitimate newspaper and the largest newspaper in Hawaii, despite it having the word "advertiser" in the title. It has a funny name, left over from a merger between the *Honolulu Advertiser* and the *Honolulu Star-Bulletin*. https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Honolulu_Star-Advertiser This pic might be from before 2010 when the merger took place, because honoluluadvertiser.com now redirects to staradvertiser.com.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 19:04:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>They'll just say something dumb like political correctness is worse than the Holocaust.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 19:16:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Quick, get Dinesh D'Souza to remake *Reefer Madness*.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-29 22:20:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I had to learn Adobe Illustrator and Quark Xpress using that stupid mouse. I can probably blame it for my carpal tunnel syndrome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 05:02:21</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; And Border Patrol head Harlon B. Carter #8212;a convicted murderer who killed a Latino as a teenager in 1931 and who later headed the National Rifle Association (NRA) #8212;was frustrated by the sheer numbers of Mexican immigrants, both legal and undocumented, in the United States. He convinced President Eisenhower to ramp up immigration enforcement efforts. TIL the man who radicalized the NRA was a complete and total piece of shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 16:21:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can have it in Utah. It's not very special.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 17:53:27</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt;watching tucker carlson What are you, a masochist?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 18:01:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I recall that in the first round, it was increments of $100 (up to $500), and the second round it was increments of $200 (up to $1000). I haven't seen an episode in a few years though. Edit: Wikipedia says it changed in 2001. I'm old.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 05:53:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know I always read the full email headers on every single email I get.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 06:15:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have advanced text of it:  gt; NO U</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 18:33:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>National Alliance was founded by the author of *The Turner Diaries,* the novel about starting a race war that inspired Timothy McVeigh to do the Oklahoma City bombing. Fuck these people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 21:08:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>So it's possible Trump is so unpopular that dead black people are saying they don't like him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 21:10:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Breitbart and other shit places were claiming something like a 12% approval in one poll was a massive surge in black support.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 23:40:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>When the South Park Movie had the US start a war with Canada, that was literally the most absurd country for us to attack. Then Trump came along and killed satire.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 00:12:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Utah was the third state to allow women to vote, after Wyoming and Colorado. (It was actually the second territory to do it, after Wyoming, because both gave women voting rights before they were even states.) Western states were more progressive about women's suffrage back in the day, though their motives aren't clear. The frontier states didn't have a lot of women (there was a 6-to-1 sex ratio) and they wanted to attract more women to increase their population, plus pioneer women had to be a bit pluckier to endure the lifestyle. So I guess they wanted those "uppity" progressive women to come out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 00:16:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think they're more like AIDS, where they've destroyed the immune system of the US and allowed a multitude of cancers and infections to attack every facet of society.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 02:07:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>There was a strange story making the rounds on BS "natural" sites a couple years ago, claiming Putin had accused Western nations of making their citizens stupider with vaccines and GMOs. Snopes concluded it was some sort of Russian propaganda targeting anti-vaxxers because Putin himself doesn't actually have a problem with vaccines or GMOs. https://www.snopes.com/fact-check/putin-gmo-evolution/  gt; The alleged Putin statement described the average Westerner as an  #8220;intensively vaccinated borderline autistic fat man slumped in front of a screen battling a high-fructose corn syrup comedown. #8221;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 05:02:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>This really offered my exposure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-01 22:16:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>He was more useless than the turn signal on a BMW.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 20:26:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is weird to me because Paul Allen also gave $1 million this year to push a gun control initiative in WA state.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 01:01:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, more frequent intercourse doesn't necessarily correlate to an increase in impregnation because it depends on if a woman is fertile or not. A guy could have sex with a woman hundreds of times but if it's not when she's fertile (around when she's ovulating), she's not going to get pregnant. If a guy increases the lovemaking on the times when she's fertile, then perhaps the chances of accidental pregnancy increase, assuming any contraception used fails.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL that even though daddy-long-leg spiders don't have powerful enough venom to harm humans, they hunt and kill larger spiders that can kill humans, like the redback spider. They use their long legs to quickly wrap other spiders with webbing, immobilizing them before biting and eating them.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 01:17:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:03:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>The redback spider is related to the black widow and has been known to kill people in Australia, though this is very very rare these days with proper medical care. Both spiders can cause [latrodectism](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Latrodectism) which has very nasty symptoms that can last for weeks after the bite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 02:25:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>The thing is that even during a woman's fertile period, more frequent sex doesn't necessarily mean more likelihood of pregnancy. Yes, sex has to happen more than 0 times, but only during the few days before she ovulates. The point of having more frequent sex around that time is to make sure you don't miss the ovulation window. Even then the sperm sticks around in the uterus for a long time, like up to a week, while it swims around looking for the egg. So one good ejaculation in enough. But that's if you're trying to get pregnant. If you're not, and you're using a condom, then it's dependent on if the condom fails, which is more likely to happen the more sex you have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:41:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most of the sperm doesn't travel past the vagina because the cervix only opens very slightly to allow it in during a woman's fertile time. Successful sperm has to swim from the vagina, through the uterus, and up the fallopian tube to meet the egg after ovulation. So it's not really about the quantity of the sperm, but the quality.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>