<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject8726</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-12 05:43:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I disagree. The mount seems like a cool fun new aspect for me. It makes it different then LoL.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-17 13:08:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cassie's arrows have no drop. I was confused af the first time I played her.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-19 02:50:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel the bots sorta have an aimbot cuz they are controlled my computers... And the computer know EXACTLY where a player is at all times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-02 00:27:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just think of something I don't want to happen or some thing I fear (SAD NOT SCARY). It usually shuts me up but can leave u feeling sad afterwards.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 15:58:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once u hit level 13 u stop gaining exp from bot matches</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 15:59:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have been blocked from many kills cuz sha lin sinks down a bit when he uses planted and then it blocks my view of the enemy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-14 00:45:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>675</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-15 03:33:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was lvl 13 for me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-22 04:29:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-28 00:12:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bomb king should roll in on a carpet made of small rolling bombs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-30 05:42:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have u thought of adding champion specific mounts? (I think there is a reddit post floating around somewhere with good ideas.) Also why did u remove the old siege game mode and are u gonna ever bring it back. (I really like it and it is more interesting then the two game modes we have now.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Crashes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-07 21:12:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is paladins not working for anyone else rn?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-11 17:02:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree. When I was new to the game makoa always looked like a bird to. E with gigantic beak thing he is on is champ icon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-11 17:11:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>5 pips 5 grohks. Mad heals 5 fernansoa</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-12 04:43:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Get gold by logging on daily and just playing matches. First three wins of the day give u bonus gold. Kinessa is hard to play cuz any decent flanker can take u out unless u are a pro. There a an ok number of free champs to play. But if U want to try some one new, go to the shooting range and try them out. Buy them from the champions tab in the main screen. U buy champs with gold. Should be around 5k for most of them. Pm me if u have any questions. I will be happy to help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-14 04:15:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>The point of learning 12 champs is that u can help your team once you reach competitive, u would know all roles, not just damage. Me and my friends were considering sharing accounts and getting our "mains" up on someone else's account. Boy am I glad we did not do that. I have reached a point in paladins on which I can play any role. My weakest is frontliner and my strongest is support or flank. I have preferences but can help my team in every competitive match.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-15 04:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pip cuz when I first learned about paladins over a year ago (the game was way better back then) I saw him played and he locked fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I need your help!!! Level 5 or below players</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-20 01:24:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>hey guys, me and my friends just started playing heros of the storm. Unfortunately, i learned about the recruit a friend tooo late. Can people level 5 or below please log in at the link, https://battle.net/recruit/8HT9SQ2BJZ. Thank you!!!!!! P.S. if u want me to log in to your link just pm me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A piece of common knowledge is this not have the same username and password, but what if you made them the same. No one would expect it because it is "bad security".</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 04:43:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry for bad wording.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 04:52:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>True</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-27 04:55:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>So which one is the password to ur account? Lol jk. But that is true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-07 15:35:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>We should just measure birthdays in a universal time zone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-11 01:55:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>so where could i find these matches? If u could post a link that would be awesome</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-12 12:51:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Didi anyone else think of mean girls when they read this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-13 05:44:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Paladins guru has builds I think. Also when u are creating a deck u can import decks from other people. Just click the purple import button while building your deck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-14 13:07:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>The rangers apprentice series by john Flanagan. I have ready many books but that is definitely the best series's of all time. I highly encourage anyone to try it out. Also the Harry Potter series wouldn't be bad either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The only time I will probably really need to use the Spanish I learned in school is when I have to communicate with foreign players in game.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-14 13:21:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 03:15:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great idea!! This would be an interesting champion. But how fast would he be able to run exactly and how far does the healing beam latch from. I don't think hi tez would take the passive though since no other champions have one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>HELP STUCK AND NEED ADVICE! Plz help</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 22:20:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I was taking my new bike for a spin but the steering wasn't completely on point. What ended up happening is I am 30 min away from home by walking with my bike. The steering just doesn't work anymore. Can anyone help me try to fix the steering (has something loosened or something?) I am desperate and really need help. Thank you Edit: I got my bike fixed and am all well now. Thank you to anyone to have advice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 22:35:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't have a tool. I think I am going to wait it out next to my local library till my friends can come and pick me up. Thank you for the advice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 22:36:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't have a tool. I could walk home but then I would have to leave my bike and it would probably be stolen and as it is brand new that would suck. I am just going to wait it out till help can arrive. Thank you though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 22:51:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-16 02:11:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha. I myself am going to run for OA this spring. I will keep this story ok mind as I go through the ordeals. So what are the ordeals and different levels anyways?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-16 02:12:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boy Scouts is not lame. You have some really fun experiences with your friends away from parents. OP just messed up by not making a shelter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-16 02:32:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey what's ur Skype maybe us and 2 of my friends could play sometime. We are looking for 2 more people as well for tournaments and stuff</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-16 20:04:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea, i am on mac and i got in the game but is dced me and now it says player disconnected</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-17 01:03:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>More than pip. Bomb king. Is grumpy and poppy bombs are great but don't show up. What other movement ability can easily kill an entire team. (Throw them off the cliff)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-18 02:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tried to type it with my right hand. Was confused for a full minute thinking "this isn't that ez"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-28 16:39:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do u mean by CC Germany?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-28 16:44:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>What does he mean? I don't get it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 00:56:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok thx</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Any cool easy fun civ 5 mods</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-29 06:01:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I bought the game during New Years but couldn't get the the DLC at the time. (Gonna buy them next sale). So anyways like the title, is there any mods u guys recommend for simply making life a bit easier in game. Bit anything super game chasing though as I am still new to the game. Thx! Edit: What are community patches? Are they any good?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>BNW or GNK</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 04:27:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Title. Basically which pack is better and what are some pros and cons of each one?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 13:14:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ur not alone. My first game I ever played of civ 5 I was alone on continent with only 2 city states. I had to research all the way to ATRONOMY in order to get in contact with other civs. I also went west instead of east which lead to the long way around the world. But I think this shouldn't happen in general tooo many times for you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-30 13:15:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Him and me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-01 23:44:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Back in 5th grade we got a new bus driver who missed a major turn. So we continued on an out of the way road for like 20 min before he could find a place to make a U turn. We were abt 1 hour late to school that day. It was the best.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 04:53:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>OMG SAME!!!!! U had like sooooo much gold tooo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Question: About how long does it take to switch from windows to Mac?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-05 06:45:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Title, I am going to try to hookup up boot camp tomorrow to play some games. I just want to know how long it will take to go from my windows to my Mac OS.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-05 15:36:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Placeholder</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-05 16:50:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I completely agree. My 13th birthday was complete shit. I was sick the entire day so I couldn't go out for dinner like my family normally does. I also couldn't hang out with friends I wanted to see all cuz I was sick. And then none of my "friends" wished me even though I know for a fact some of them knew it was my b day. One of them even called me but didn't wish me. I still remember it till this day. It feels pretty bad when no one remembers ur birthday</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-06 03:57:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is one called deseat.io</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 06:21:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can we also get PTS for mac, i was really excited when i found out abt PTS just to be dissapointed that it wont work for my mac</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Feels Akwardish</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 06:33:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>So after coming from games like LoL, the facts that you use ur left hand to move around and dodge attacks (WASD) while trying to use the same 3 fingers to attack and use abilities seems akwards to me. Like it is hard to move in the direction u want while using an ability. Does anyone else feel this way? Or is it just me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 08:20:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want to get Into doing that. I just need to find a good software that will let me remind stuff to my extra mouse buttons. In smite rn all of them just show up as mouse button 3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 08:22:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think u misunderstood me. I love using WASD to play games. But in smite 3 fingers are on WASD to move ur god around AND those same 3 fingers have to hit number 1-4 on your keyboard to activate ur abilities. So u can't easily be moving and diving the way u want to while hitting ur abilities accurately. In other MOBAS u move with ur mouse and ur left hand is entirely used for abilities. Seems a lot more smooth that way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-07 23:50:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok. I can still use my left hand for abilities like in paladins. Just a bit more of a reach to the number keys in smite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-08 21:44:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn I literally sprinted to my computer after reading the title</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-09 06:25:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>How did u get a mammoth to drop?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-11 06:35:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>YOUR KING APPRECIATED YOUR SUPPORT!! Let's get the bomb to top guys!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 00:41:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's ur paladins username. I need to check this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-12 00:42:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bot match ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-13 14:54:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same I woke up this morning and my mom yelled at me to get out of bed. I changed my clothes and quickly dragged myself downstairs for breakfast. (I thought school would start in 20 min) then my moms like u have a delayed opening fml</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 03:23:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>most schools have school wide laminators/printers/copiers. Its odd that ur school requiers you to use your own!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 04:13:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>The problem is that I got the Spanish packet on Friday (my first day back) and didn't really have spare time to do anything other that finish it. I had a weeks worth of catch up from 5 other subjects to also do so I didn't really spend much time on it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 04:34:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>You misunderstood me. I WAS absent the day of the test. Everyone took it last week and my teacher is insisting I take it tomorrow and is not lettin me take it on Wednesday instead</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 04:37:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>In my Spanish class kids sometimes give wrong answers and my Spanish teacher never catches them. So someone else always has to point it out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 05:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>This one girl in class back in middle school was wearing a tank top thing almost an undershirt I think, but basically not something u can show in public for 12 year old. She did have a jacket shirt in over it but u could still see the sides of her chest cuz the jacket thing was kinda falling off. She was talking to the teacher from her seat (she was right next to me) and the teacher just awkwardly said "put ur shirt on plz." And everyone started cracking up. He was a male teacher Edit: typos</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 05:11:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>After a few good lashes, you all will se it my way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-14 20:47:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did check the google classrooms. (4/6 of my teachers have one) and when I was well enough to do work I was working on all my assignments. This teacher posted none of the work on GC however</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Used to be smart, Now almost failing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-16 00:38:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>So when I was younger I was insanely smart and didn't need to study at all for tests and still ace them. Now as I grow older I don't put enough time into studying and can't change my ways. Does anyone here have advice on how to start focusing on studying for tests more. (I get distracted by /r/teenagers too much :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New Event</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 01:12:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I started playing this game after a long time and there is the new flower event. I saw a post on here about something called a milestone egg? Anyways, is this event still going or did I start playing again just when the event ended? Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 04:18:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Today was my first day back ok the game. Just to be clear, these daily rewards aren't part of the event. They are just a new feature right? Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-17 23:30:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok thank you. Today my daily reward was a rayen (I think). I'm really happy cuz it is a galaxy dragon. Thank you though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-18 02:25:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We're leaking to /r/AskReddit</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-21 23:26:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-21 23:30:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>20 million Zimbabwe dollars</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is Nidalee still good?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-23 19:31:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I have gotten back into playing league after a while. I just want to know if nidalee is still good as a kinglet. She was my favorite and I want to see if she is still worth. Sorry if this is not the right sub for these kinda questions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-24 05:39:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Half my friends play robocraft but I quit after the update.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mac</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-25 06:51:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does gigantic have any plans to release on Mac?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-25 16:11:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>If gigantic doesn't release on Mac, I will just run it off of boot camp. But I would prefer if there was a Mac version.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sale on steam</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-25 18:11:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone know how long the sale will last?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Transcendence</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 03:58:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>What happened to trans in S4. I cant find this item in joust anymore!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 05:42:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh! Ok thx I was trying to use to get some more mana for AP gods</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 05:46:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea... about retaining that knowledge.....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 18:46:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok thx. Isn't it a starter item or nah?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Steam Authorization Fail</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 23:35:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>SO when I joined a lobby it said steam authorization failed and brought me back to the loading screen for the main menu. Has this happened to anyone else?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-26 23:37:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a nice idea. Works well with communication and ordering people around.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 04:55:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically nuke everyone in sight (Civ reference CHECK)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 21:23:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>OMG thank you. I actually went to the control yesterday to remap some stuf but figured I couldn't yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 21:28:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>What model do u have? I can run it on my mid 2013 Mac book air</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 23:44:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do u filter out full servers? I knelt see an option for empty servers?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-01 02:55:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ramming is pretty effective. One time I was in charge of a hoy and we were closing in on a sinking galleon. One of my crew mates suggested we grapple but in response I just rammed the enemy ship. (I know it was wrong of me to not let me crew know we were ramming). I hunch was correct. Since the ship was already sinking. When I rammed them 4 new holes were created and the ship sank within seconds. Sometimes ramming can just be a quicker way to shrink an enemy ship if u don't have the man power to fight</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-01 02:56:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would be kinda unrealistic to start from where u left off but I really like you idea of 4 stages. Nice thoughts!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-01 04:18:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>It would be unrealistic in the sense that if your loading rod was halfway out of the sheath thing when u put ur musket away and when u take it out it manages to be back in the same place automatically. But your 4 stages system works perfectly</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 05:13:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>RemindMe!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 05:39:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can confirm. This was me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 05:46:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is me. Even when I got the top score in my grade (100ish students) in SS (my worst subject) my dad still asked "why didn't you get 100%?" He says it like he is joking about but it really feels bad</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-03 13:21:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>My new Spanish teacher just takes all his wksts and power points from the other Spanish teachers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-04 02:27:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your right click I'm pretty sure</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-04 17:23:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Remind Me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Refund on DLC bundles?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-06 05:49:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I have civ 5 but I was to poor to get the DLC when the game was on sale. I don't mind waiting till the next sale but if I buy a bundle which contains civ 5 plus DLC what will happen to the copy of civ 5 I just bought. Can I refund it for money or will it just sit there?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-06 13:16:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-06 22:17:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg the same exact thing happened to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-06 22:20:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>My parents aren't tech savvy and I just don't share my location with them. When my mom insisted one time on me letting them see my location I just turned it off a few days later and claimed it was a glitch. Edit: words</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hibernation</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-08 04:44:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do u guys decide which dragons go in the hibernation cave. I have reached a point where I have started to put a few dragons in the cave. Also Timmy understanding, dragons in the hibernation cave can not be selected for quests and breeding, correct? Thanks in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-08 12:37:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't have two of any dragon. Is it possible to have all the dragons with just habitats?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-08 12:38:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it possible to have 1 of every dragon on display? Without a hibernation cave?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-08 13:00:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-09 04:35:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey do U mind telling me which habitats j have and their sizes? I'm the type of guy that goes for optimal planning from the start.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-09 04:44:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>In elementary schools this happened cuz kids that age couldn't possibly be expected to switch classes and stuff. Also, in elementary school kids got a six understanding of concepts so he teacher could manage it alll. In middle school and high school students go more in depth so they get specific teachers who know a lot about one specific subject.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-10 03:40:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thx</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Twin Dragons</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 20:38:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do twin dragons look different when u hatch them. Or just the eggs? Edit: I meant that do twin dragons look different than regular dragons?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 22:07:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>So.....</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 22:16:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh I meant that do twin dragons look different from regular dragons.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-13 23:18:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Or thx.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 04:33:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do this. Also add VVGL and VVGF</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Steam Authorization Fail</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-15 22:16:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>So in all my games today i got the "steam Authorization fail" message whenever i i joined a server Edit: I do own the game on steam.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-16 19:44:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea it seems like that. But I do own the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-20 22:37:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dad made me watch Argo in 2nd grade.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-21 20:48:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Up vote for ATLA reference</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-21 21:38:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>"say something to him" FTFY knackneverlack is a girl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anyone know what this is? Or its purpose?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 04:12:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-24 22:59:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Repost from a day ago. Just wow</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Kukulkan Counter</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 01:57:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I am kinda new to the game and I recently played against some Kukulkans. His 3 seems really op, like a steady amount of damage that always almost kills me. So basically does anyone have a good counter, just for his 3, or for Kukulkan himself? Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 07:05:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok thx sooo much. Sorry for the late reply, for some reason none of the comments showed up in my inbox.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 07:44:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. I am really hoping Ganesh or hanuman get implemented too. They could do something cool with hanuman carrying a mountain.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-30 01:12:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nike and isis. I got the new isis skin for free from some site plus isis. Nike is more of a damage warrior so I like her a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I have a question</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 03:25:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I just found this subreddit and was wondering if u guys have these small gray things that U randomly see sometimes and they always move away from ur eyes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 22:45:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>How are u making sooo much gold???!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 01:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am a giant volcanic turtle with a hook, and cannon that shoots fireballs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-11 03:08:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>This literally happened to my friend today. And it wasn't a sub. She also got a detention but she skipped it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 16:14:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gourd and net are direct I'm pretty sure. With blast damage u can hurt urself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Timed Guard Deployment</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 19:35:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I am kinda new to PA and was wondering exactly how the guard schedules worked. I want it so there are guard in the showers during shower time and not all day. If someone could link a guide/video or explain it, I would greatly appreciate it. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-14 20:57:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!! This really clarified things up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-16 16:02:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree. When I was younger (10) we went to my cousins house for Easter. I didn't always get up early enough on Easter so my two cousins would find all the eggs, but they left some of the easier ones to find for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 05:29:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>It still is a repost. Different backstory though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-20 00:19:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>U can save a bit of money by only placing a drain below the shower.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>More Wardens Mod?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 01:37:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I was checking out the ps4 version (i play on pc) and they had a huge variety of wardens that made the game easier or harder. Does anyone know of a mod for pc that adds more unique wardens?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 03:51:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>How would I do that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-22 03:56:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Make sure they have a meal before their programs. That helps too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 01:06:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have this same exact guy. His name is Easter "Zombie" Egg. Right? Anyway what I do is, he has his own cell with an attached canteen. He is basically always in solitary. If he is not in solitary, he is fighting guards. Having 4 guards with takers works for me. Any less and he might kill them all (I've tried). I will post a screenshot when I am at my computer too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Unconscious guard!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 01:10:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>So in a fight one of my guards fell unconscious. The problem is, I can't heal him. He has just been in a medical bed for days now. I have tried everything from paramedics to having a prisoner try to kill him. (And then he can be moved to a hearse) but nothing works. Any ideas? Edit: He can't be fired either.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 20:37:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Be careful. He should have his own area. He shd not be in a solitary cell near other prisoners. He is ex prison guard so other prisoners will automatically target him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 20:39:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not protective custody. He will kill the other prisoners easily when he goes off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 02:18:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ikr.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Badges not received</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 20:36:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I used to play awesomenauts a few years ago (late 2014/early 2015) and just redownloaded the game when I heard about the new update. I just got back in but it doesnt seem to appear that I got my founder medal. Do I have to reach a certain profile lvl first? thanks! *meant to write medal in title</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 21:10:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>so I do technically have it, but i just need to be level 6 to equip it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Unlock Upgrades</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 21:49:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I used to play the game a few years ago, I got to lvl 30 something. As I recall, at most level you got additional upgrades for certain nauts. With update 4.0 what happens to these upgrades?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Allowing applications to connect to internet</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-29 22:06:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I have a MacBook air and recently when I launch games, I always need to allow them to connect to the internet, each and every time. This can get annoying so is there a way to automatically allow them? I already looked in system preferences - gt; network</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 01:51:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it possible that I kept my old upgrades. With some characters I automatically have all the upgrades</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 04:15:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>yea, in there all the connections are allowed but it still asks me each time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 04:16:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>what could I aim to do with Automator in this scenario?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Speed boost stacking</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-01 03:56:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone here know if two of admiral swiggens speed boosts stack. One time give him an extra 15% movement. (That standard boots) and another item gives him an extra ~17% movement when he is not holding homebot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-04 04:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>This literally went through my school today. We use an email provided through google and everyone got this. It spread through group chats like crazy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Multiplayer Games</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-07 16:37:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I started my first multiplayer game with a couple of friends yesterday. Unfortunately I had to leave before the others. How does the ai play out in comparison to what I was planning. Could this potentially screw me over?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Skin for max level Naut</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 02:29:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I was thinking that it would be a cool idea that if you reach the max level for a naut, you would have the option to buy a cool skin with awesomepoints. This could really show your skill at this naut.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 12:45:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well the idea is that as u play a character, u get better with them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-12 12:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's kinda what I was thinking but I feel like the devs don't want to give out too many free skins just yet cuz they still need to make money and want the game to go f2p.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-14 16:49:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>44 thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ELI5: What are U.S. Territories?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 23:14:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>What exactly are the U.S. Territories and how do they work?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 12:36:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>This one guy in mg school that basically said follow for a follow in his bio. Then he started going to the list of people he followed/followed him and started sending them follow requests. He could gain like 100 followers per day just by doing this. Pretty stupid though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-16 12:42:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>576</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-19 23:27:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>3,333</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[QUESTION] Does anyone know where I can find a guitar arrangement for the song Baba Yetu?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 00:45:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I play the classical guitar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-24 22:52:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mac? It's the same version for Mac and windows.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 00:20:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea. I think the devs posted one a while ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Rigged Elections</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 01:58:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I got elected into the OA. I haven't gone to my ordeal yet and I'm pretty sure I was only elected because of my Scoutmaster. Last year he made it very clear that we should vote for everyone. This year there was an OA representative here so he was a bit more discreet but still was getting the message across. Does this happen in anyone else's troop? This scoutmaster is new and has only been here for a few years. The previous Scoutmaster was great and I'm sad he stepped down. Edit: When words are hard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 02:47:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>16</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 05:00:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't my troop would hold their own elections. So I'm assuming there might had been a representative 2 years ago. But maybe he just didn't make a strong precedence. 2 years ago our troop oa representative was gold the election.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-30 12:40:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know!!! Lupine was really freaky as a werewolf. His entire body has no hair.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 19:16:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>128</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Adding mods?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 01:46:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it possible to add mods to already existing mod packs. I started mage quest and wanted to add some other mods to make it more fun. Edit: how would I go about doing this? Would I just download the mod and put it in some mod folder I can find?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How dangerous is warp?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 01:57:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just learned about warp and have a small amount from getting research mastery. Is it plausible for me to get all the research in the thaumonomicon even with the warp limitirations?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Map reset?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 02:15:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I have this one world with a mini map mod. I started a new world real quick to test something out in creative. And it used the same map as my previous world. I thought it was strange but whatever. I deleted the new world and when I went back to my original world the map was reset and all my waypoints were deleted. Edit: the minimap mod is journey map unlimited in the mage quest mod pack.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Which version of Thaumcraft?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 02:49:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone know which version of thaumcraft the mage quest mod pack on the FTb launcher uses? I tried looking around but didn't get much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 03:24:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm pretty sure it's journey map. I can double check when I get back to my computer. Just wondering, how would deleting the \minecraft folder within the mod pack help?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 03:27:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The curse launcher is the same as the twitch launcher right? It said they merged or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Make it easier to see unread notifications.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 03:29:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like the new inbox but it's kind of hard to see which notifications are read and unread. Maybe add a red circle or something next to the name of unread messages.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-14 20:52:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>DLC ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-14 22:21:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ohh. What are these rewards?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Alpha continues to early acces?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-17 05:26:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I have an alpha key and can play the game right now. My question is that will I be able to continue playing the game after July 25th when it goes into early access without having to buy the early access package?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-17 21:37:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>People with alpha don't get a free founders pack</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Extremely downvoted posts should also be on the front page.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-17 21:38:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>So people can see what others extremely hate and add their own hate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-21 01:10:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do u understand the joke?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Lack of Motivation</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-25 03:01:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I have played civ through a couple of games and have started to find myself lacking motivation to continue playing. What are some ways to keep the game interesting?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Would r/worldnews count for the citizenship in the nation requirement where you need to read a top newspaper for 5 days in a row?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 06:46:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 21:07:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>u/ironnhead</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-29 01:12:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>And why is that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Challenges</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 02:00:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just saw a post where a guy is attempting to keep intake to max and see what happens. So what are some other challenges like this to make the game more interesting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can prisoners go into staff only zones if being escorted by guards?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 02:11:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like if they are going to solitary and have to pass a staff only zone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 06:37:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Volkswagen? Like reinvent the way your ride/drive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 06:46:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. I can search more tomorrow. It could also be a honda commercial. But definitely a car commercial.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 06:54:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fake it until you make it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 07:35:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>My legendary has his own super cell with a permanent station of 4 guards. Most of the times their 4 tazers can bring him down easily, otherwise we have some deaths. Edit:4 tazers</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 07:38:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>My min sec dorms always had tunnels so I decided to do some fancy scheduling work and have dogs in the dorms all night searching for tunnels. Seems to have worked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 18:54:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://everythingistakenlikehonestly.tumblr.com/post/162555255484/this-is-my-super-max-wing-just-a-large the top is my small PC wing. for the gang leader problem, a way to end punishments on one person is to assign them a permanent punishment, then cancel it. That removes an earlier punishment of the same type (lockdown/sollitary)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 08:19:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>RemindMe! 12 next Part of awesome magic story</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>National wonders V.S. World wonders</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 08:46:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is the difference? And where can I find a list of national wonders and world wonders?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 17:42:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't help with design much but you should know that you can't build all that with your starting money. You will have to find a way to build a small prison and that can be expanded upon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 18:27:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>In my school we lock the doors and pull a blind over the windows so an attackers can't look in. But a flaw in logic is couldn't an attacker know which rooms have kids from which rooms are locked and blinded.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 01:55:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. Blinds can only be closed from the inside. So if the door is locked and blinds are closed any attacker can deduce that there are people inside.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 06:12:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>My female friend has this rule. And one time she told her mom she was going jogging but she was secretly hanging out with our group of friends. We almost ran into her mom on the way for ice cream but we managed to get away without being seen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What are these yellow flags I keep seeing on the ground outside?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 06:26:36</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 08:05:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's a full tunnel search?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 08:27:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ohhh. U mean shakedown.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 19:34:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I play the on pc and have never seen it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 20:21:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>RemindMe! 12 hours</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 23:47:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>RemindMe! 25 hours</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-06 00:23:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Set up the canteen right next to the Mac sec cell. And have multiple guards stationed with him permanently. I have four legendary prisoners and they share a max sec dorm with 6 perm guards. No armed cuz I don't want them to die.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-06 06:39:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm pretty sure the range is at least 50 blocks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anyway to get Psych Ward on PC</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-06 06:47:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-06 07:41:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I learned how to play civ V from quill's civ C tutorial. I was surprised how the first part took half an hour and only explained the first turn and seemed to go by really quick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-06 15:56:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>In any case. Get used to a lot of attacks on guards with these guys.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-07 05:44:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>93 ty!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 05:51:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Civ 5. It is soo vast and is turn based so I can leave at a moments notice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 16:23:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Simple planes please!!! I like my eggs nice and boiled.  #128527;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-08 23:48:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>This looks really interesting and I love to try it out. Anymore keys left? Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-09 03:50:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>How did U put games on an excel sheet?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-09 03:54:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do u mean delete the steamapi.dll file.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-09 04:52:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where can u find this file?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-09 05:34:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-09 06:44:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-09 09:11:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Quill18 has a good civ 5 tutorial. He taught me how to play when I had 0 experience in civ or other games like it. Edit: words are hard</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 23:29:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>In school we had to spend months on Helen Keller cuz we read a book about her. So I can't get them mixed up anymore. The book was miracle worker.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Some feedback.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 05:05:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. In your list of subscribed subreddits, why was the alphabet on the right shrunken down to not include every letter and only some? I personally like the old version better. 2. The new view options are nice, but I sometimes get really far down my home page or the popular page and want to switch. Perhaps we could scroll up a bit and the option to change views come back up? Kinda like on the safari app where a bunch of options appear if u scroll up a bit but disappear when u scroll down so u can see the full screen. What do you guys think of this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 09:19:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same here. We aren't poor by any standards but compared to a lot of the population in my town. We kinda are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-11 09:29:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm feeling the same way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 05:27:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do U mean the median house price is over 1 mil. In ur town?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 05:54:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>If u go the FAQ there are links</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 06:28:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait what do u mean that all security levels pay the same? Like u get the same amount of money for max, med, and min sec? When is this update coming out?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 00:12:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ohh. Has this update already come out? That must be why my max sec prison is making a lot less than it was before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 05:59:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not every gang member. Just leaders imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 06:02:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks op!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 16:52:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>But where's the fun in that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 23:34:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never payed much attention to why trifles showed a hog but when I showed the game to my friend and he constantly asked about them. We decided to look it up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Idea] Change how deployment hours work</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 04:31:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>So the current deployment scedule that allows you to assign different hours different patrols is really confusing. I think there should be a rework. In the rework, Each possible schedule (8 currently) should get its own tab that is different from the other schedules. With this different schedules can overlap and the idea is one for meal times, one for lockups, etc. What do you guys think? Edit: So it's it could be like different "shifts".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 16:42:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks op.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 17:50:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>But often the pc inmates will be dead after fights.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-15 17:53:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is also a snitch sorter mod which I find really helpful. It's basically an object you unlock after researching something. It takes any inmate within 20 blocks and switches them to pc if they are snitches, ex cops, etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 01:12:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. It makes it easiest to organize and keep track of "shifts".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 04:13:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Civ V. Ita really fun and I like how you can just get up and go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 04:15:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>574 Terraria My friends really like it and I want to see what the fuss is about. And j already have dst and haven't head of starbound. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-02 19:42:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Instead of fiddling around with patrol timings (I believe the system shd be reworked, see my other post) I just assigned a bunch of guards to my max sec canteens so if there is a fight they are there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 17:46:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have one of those. Is the name Easter "Zombie" Egg?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 17:47:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Recently I use a snitch sorter which I place in my reception.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-04 18:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea. By sambot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-05 15:26:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Having my little cousin (5) ask me to go to park with him when I can't say no. It's super boring and I hate going, but I can't say no. Every day for the past two weeks I've had to go except for the times I can get out of the house with my sister in the evening.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is anyone else finding it hard to keep track of the two timelines in season 1?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-05 19:32:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pls no spoilers I'm only on s1 ep16</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-07 23:20:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sad song by elaina king</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-11 00:49:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who's your daddy plz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 05:15:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Town of Salem plz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Game Freezing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 15:10:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have only played for around 4 hours and while exploring the dry reef past the overgrowth my game has frozen forcing me to restart multiple times. Can anyone help?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-12 18:21:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>In my case the screen didn't go black and I couldn't hear music. The screen just froze as it was. I reinstalled slime rancher and that seemed to have fixed he problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Hunger levels for slimes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 11:35:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I noticed that slimes smile or frown depending on how hungry they are. Has anyone studied this and made a table?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why is my plort market crashing?!?!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 11:53:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 12:17:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>The thing is, I have only sold honey and boom plorts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 12:27:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would disagree with you on this point. I think 13 is a good age for new resistors providing they can control themselves. I know some kids who are in their early teens and still Reddit. It really depends on what type of teen it is and if they can or can not restrain themselves from delving into dark Reddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 12:28:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea I have been. I hoarded up 300 honey and boom plorts each. Now I'm trying to get 20 rad crystal largos for more of a variety.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 18:53:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I need these for the gordos... right?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-13 23:27:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 03:29:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm mostly saving these up for the hunter Gordo in the moss blanket.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 05:23:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are market and refinery links? And when do I get them?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 05:26:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>To keep phosphors in corrals u need a solar shield.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 07:52:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good luck to all who entered!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do gordo snares work?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-14 20:53:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>More specifically, how long do they take and when can you start unlocking the further tiers higher that novice?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 00:34:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Slime keys?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So what's new?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 05:09:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I took a pretty long break from the game. (I stopped just after Willo came out). And I plan to get back into it. What are some major thing I should take note of? Edit: Words are hard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 18:32:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unless it's a toddler/young girl.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 18:35:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well.. I've sold over 250 of at least 4 different plorts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 19:01:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>It runs fine on Mac.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 19:03:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like what?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 19:04:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is true and all but he was talking abt chicken coops.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 19:08:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Their called Gordo's btw</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anyone know what the fruit on the right is? when i try to suck it up it just disintegrates</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 20:41:08</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-17 08:06:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually if u see the great fire lion turtle he can give u the gift of firebending. They explain during LoK when u learn abt the first avatar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-17 08:10:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hack_me2 plz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-17 08:19:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>When my name was Apple two games in a row and I got escort both times. In my second game there were three people from my first game in it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anyone know the BPM of Baba Yetu?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 01:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 06:47:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't know for sure but sounds like patronage. I know it has some city state stuff in there but I never went too deep into it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 22:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the song.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What happens if the game ends with an escort and a gf?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 00:57:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>The escort can infinitely block the gf every night.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 03:48:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 03:56:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why doesn't escort win?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 04:00:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Won't mafioso become gf?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 05:59:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my friend Ganesha. It's a children's movie about the Indian diety Ganesha. It was the only video/movie we had when I moved America at a young age. His the only thing I would watch because I could not understand English. I've watched it over 20 times.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 06:00:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>That they are forced to obey my every command.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 05:21:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>RemindMe! 7 hours</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 05:25:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine had one that was run by a few kids. But it was deleted in a week.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 15:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ur account is only 18 days old</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-26 22:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>This would be nice. Like during a riot just a squadron of guards to control would help out a lot. Riot guards aren't the best cuz they don't have a tazers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-27 03:33:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>No you don't. IIRC you only need to be the last person in control of your on capital.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-29 14:46:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can click on the microphone (below the chat box) if u want to hide the chat box. I know it bothered me when I played with my friends.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-30 14:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just keep exploring. The slime keys open up slime doors which lead to new areas of the map. It also sounds like you have too many gardens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 04:45:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm kinda in the same boat. I assume (like me) op needs friends and can't easily make new ones. So we have to stick with the friends we have made over time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 14:02:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>As a kid it's worse if there are a ton of rich kids in your school too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 15:19:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Over cooked pls</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-02 16:04:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like the idea of scanning gates and Gordon's so u can mark them on ur map.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Teachers should give extra credit on tests and quizzes if they give it back later then they said they would.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 02:56:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Teacher take off points when we hand in assignments late or give straight zeros. So they should give us points back when they hand back assignments after they said they would. We can both see through the other party's excuses so why should the teaachers be able to get away with it?? Edit: The giving back of points is something more suited to r/crazyideas, but I want this to be a discussion about teachers who repeatedly fail to give assessments back. On a lighter note, praise the teacher who can grade accurately and quickly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 03:00:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not whining. The teacher should take as long as they need to, but if they say like "I will hand back your tests on Monday". And when Monday comes around they're like "I'm sorry, you will get them back tomorrow". Sometimes this goes on and on. It gets really infuriating.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 05:12:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>What am I failing at exactly?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ELI5: How do memory foam pillows work?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 05:17:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>On another note, what about those memory foam cooking pillows?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 05:21:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>My post wasn't meant to be about handing in late work (it is completely understandable to get points deducted for late work), but more so on the side of why it's ok for teachers to go back on their word when handing back assessments. Just say the accurate date the first time. Better than repeatedly saying "tomorrow"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 04:40:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Steamworld Heist Puzzle agent Lethal league My favorite movie is Oh My God, a Hindi movie about a man who take god/temples to court over an Insurance company policy. Hilarious. Thanks so much!!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 12:48:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wouldn't it be nice if we could stop having reposts?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 06:20:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Story?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-15 06:29:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love games!!!! games4life</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Everytime I have a conversation with my dad, I end up regretting it.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 02:22:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>He really just yells at me and tells me how I am lacking in life. I feel bad cause he is my dad and cares for me, but his social interactions with me and my sister really come off as rude and he makes the entire family mad/unhappy sometimes depending on what he says Edit: Asian Family</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-18 14:12:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've tried talking to him about this with and without my sister. It's just the fact that every conversation with him has to be about studies. And he can't have a proper conversation, it's really just him talking. Most of the time when he seems really happy is when he is drunk. Thank you for the advice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-24 18:19:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>72 thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 01:24:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Always</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 01:38:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Playing With friends is really fun. I often try to set up games with some friends and play through those. It's easier on diplomacy too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 12:51:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>This happened twice in a row in my game last njght!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Turn Reminder Mod?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-06 02:44:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you guys know of any good mods that make a customizable alert/reminder appear on a certain turn?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-07 06:35:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was jail or like this once. Three maf jails in a row. Each person claimed doc. Executed each one of them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-07 22:39:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want something that shows a notification after a certain amount of turns. So I can remind myself to change a certain production or something</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do I tell my Parents?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-09 21:33:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>So today I got my first bad grade in a serious test. It was a social studies test I thought I prepared well enough for, but I ended up doubting myself and made a few mistakes. Our teacher is making us get it signed so I have to show my parents. I know this might seem a bit whiny for some. But my parents are hardcore Asians and I have gotten into every honors class except for Spanish. My dad expects 110% on everything, but my mom is a bit more understanding. So I'm basically looking for any tips you guys might have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 01:22:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I find it annoying too. So I play with hybrid. Basically it's simultaneous during normal gameplay, but turn based during wars. I also don't use turn timers. But I play with my friends in voice chat so...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-10 20:49:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does it? In normal games the order is randomly chosen in the beginning. So during hybrid the highest scorer goes first in wars? I didn't know that. Seems kind of unfair to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>LPT: Holding Shift-Option while changing volume on Mac increase or decrease your volume by a quarter of the normal change</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 01:50:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 12:59:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Transparency</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 13:00:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>My parents</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What exactly are theming bonuses?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 03:46:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen them mentioned in the civilopedia but don't really know how they occur or what they are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-13 12:55:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are some examples of these combinations?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 13:07:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favorite color is forest green</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-23 05:02:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>76 super hot plz!! Thanks for the giveaway!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-24 04:33:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>POK #201;MON!!! I can finally achieve my goal of catching them all!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 05:47:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Foxtato foxtato, what a wonderful phrase</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>TIL: The generic character names are all real people who played a part in the Salem witch trials</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 05:50:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I started learning about the Salem witch trials today in school and when my teacher started mentioning people like Giles Corey and John Williams I was super surprised. Like I actually know who she is talking about for once.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 21:52:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would totally do this, but my teacher is like super strict and I would get in so much trouble. If this was in an other class though...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>In an essay, can I use past tense when referring to events taken place in a book?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 23:57:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>So in an essay where we are discussing whether a certain action should or should not have taken place, is it ok to use past tense when talking about what rights a person had? Like he did not have the right to do the action. Or should the word does be used? I'm new to this sub and I hope I'm not breaking any rules. Thank you!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My father is the only person can make me super pissed off, so I try to avoid talking to him</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 22:43:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've started to avoid talking to my father because he gets me triggered almost every time I talk to him. He is the type of person who never admits he is wrong and continues conversations/arguments for so long that I start to get bored and just want to stop. Just the other day we were arguing about which time slot I should go to for an event. I wanted to go the second time but he wanted me to go to the first time. I had more valid points, but he just steers the discussion away from them by saying how "All you do is come up with reasons". We argued for soo long that by the time we finished it was too late for me to even go to the first time slot. My mom and sister feel the same way but we can't do anything about it. I know I should treat him with kindness and respect since he is my father and has done so much for me, but at the same time, it's as if he tries to get me mad. It's hard for me to remember any good memories with him. I just don't know how to interact with him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 04:01:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Randomly kill people's secluded gardens/farms. Leaving them confused as fuck on what happened</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 04:02:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can I have alchemy land plz?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are Old Game Files compatible with the new update?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-30 02:32:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm trying to load up my old game file, I started before the new update and the game keeps freezing during the loading screen. The only way to get out is to force quit the game. Mac BTW.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-30 23:34:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do flat-earthers fear the most... Sphere itself Hands of fate please!! Thanks for the giveaway and putting links to the games</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 04:43:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>753 I'm not doing soo great, lots of wrk and poor time management. Thanks though!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-03 12:21:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>384</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Learning more champions</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-05 18:48:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I've reached a point in the game where I want to learn more champions. Their strengths and weaknesses, how to play against or with them. Is there any guide, video or written, that you guys would recommend. Nothing too specific, just like their abilities and what to watch out for when playing against them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why is the client recommending that I reroll or disenchant any shards I don't want?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-07 23:35:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just got a Janna shard from an honor capsule and I'm not sure if I want to disenchant it just yet, I don't have enough BE to upgrade it but I will when the turn IP into BE.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What's the difference between preseason and the actual season?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-08 05:01:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I read somewhere that preseason starts tomorrow but the actual season starts in January. I'm assuming that the preseason is a time when the changes are implemented so people can try them out. Then during the actual season, you start the ranking process. Can someone just confirm or deny this? Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 02:38:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>This would mainly work with little kids only. I know as I grew older I became better at lying and how to make it sound more natural.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mod for Map Pins?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 16:41:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I started watching some Civ 6 and noticed that they had map pins for planning purposes. This seems it could really useful in civ 5 too, does anyone happen to know a mod for this? I imagine there would be one. I bought Civ 5 through the steam client BTW.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The New Rewards System is Insane!!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-09 22:33:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just leveled from 20 to 21 and all I got was a capsule for 600 BE, considering this is the only way to get BE now is absurd. They might as well remove buying champions through BE altogether. Riot should bring the currency to what it was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 05:23:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>trashbotisup!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-10 05:30:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can buy an additional page for 6300 BE, the equivalent of a full priced champion. I don't think it's worth, just make presets before and screenshot them. Then quickly switch during champ select.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 00:55:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I learned through quill18's tutorial. While he may not make the best decision on harder difficulties his tutorial series was great.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 00:59:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like going a random civ. Them working with that. England was a fun one though, long bowman op</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Best Ancient Runes Upgrade</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 05:24:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>IMO one of the best things to get from ancient runes is upgrading a scout to an archer. This allows the archer to keep the scout promotions and ignore rough terrain. Especially good cuz I'm Babylon in my current game and my scout upgraded to my UU the bowman even before I got archery.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 08:22:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh also, I'm slightly triggered cuz when I was a turn away from finishing writing I got it from an ancient ruin. lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 17:32:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's smart, I only have 100 hours so I'm kinda new.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 00:33:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Place your votes now! Which ever comment gets more upvotes wins.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 00:41:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Trashbot</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 00:42:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like this one</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mods are bugging out game</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 00:43:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I tried playing with mods but in my last two games around 100 turns in I can't choose production for my cities any more. I'm using Info addict Faster aircraft animations Diplomatic values And some more, does anyone know what's going on?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Read Posts Bug</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 00:46:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>For some reason some posts don't turn gray (from black) after I read them. And also some posts turn gray (read) before I even open them. I'm iOS and using Alien blue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 07:32:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>A correction to the domination victory, you need to be the last civ in control of your own capital, not necessarily have everyone else's capital too. However, if going for a domination win you will probably end up controlling all the capitals anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 07:33:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Quill18's civ V tutorial taught me a lot. Just go to his channel - gt; playlists - gt; command F civ V till u find the tutorial playlist.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Great Prophets with the Mausoleum at Halicarnassus</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 22:42:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>So when you spread religion with a Great Prophet, you can do it four times. Does each time grant you 100 gold if you have the Mausoleum at Halicarnassus? Or just the final time?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-12 23:25:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't get your hopes up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 06:50:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree, though I don't see this much in LoL; back when I played Thanatos in Smite it would constantly bug me when people killed he minions i needed to lifesteal off of to survive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Manufactory Placement</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 04:22:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it better to place a Manufactory in my best production city (not my capital) to improve it or place it in my capital (second best) to make sure it has good production too?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 06:05:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>? There is no screenshot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-15 05:24:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a repost, I've seen it before. But why am I not surprised.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 02:53:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always turn time victory off. The only time I might ever use it is if it's for an achievement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 02:54:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try to get info you wouldn't be able to otherwise get. Like how many turns are you from the great library? Or what are you rushing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-16 20:58:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>563 Super hot or simple plains please!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 04:22:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would say fill out tradition/liberty first. Than rush to rationalism. As for your ideology, if you have easily accessible coal then can be improved quickly I would say so that, then build 3 factories. If coal isn't really a viable thing to get, especially with building up the rest of your infrastructure first might as well start researching.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 04:26:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Vanilla is fine just the DLC is worth which is why everyone's telling you to get it. I like to use interface mods like EUI and info addict , so I can't really recommend any gameplay changing mods. I heard Vox Populi (the community patch) is really fun, almost like another DLC but I'm yet to try it out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 07:18:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not that I know of.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 22:33:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a bug with high sierra. Lucky for that I'm to lazy to update my devices so I haven't had this problem but my friend has. If you really want to play I'm pretty sure you can revert back your OS version.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-18 22:06:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hackzack please My favorite song is Baba Yetu by Christopher Tin, featured in Civ IV Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 07:28:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sims 3 please!! https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=qBbpFGGAkmo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 07:32:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dungeon defenders Spacechem Mini metro 258 743 Thanks soo much!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 07:33:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>836 Thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-20 05:48:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Machinarium please This is right up my alley, an adventure/puzzle game invoking technology!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 02:25:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Black guards And Euro truck simulator 2 Thanks for the giveaway!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 02:25:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>World war Z thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 02:27:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rocket league is a really fun game I've only got to play a friends houses. I really want it so I can play with my friends!! Thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Bug] Download Bar off center</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-23 16:01:45</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 02:38:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>386</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 02:38:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>135</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 21:22:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Magicka 2 246</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-24 23:18:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's macro?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What to do with Project Tokens?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 05:47:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I'm wondering how to spend my project tokens, I'll end up having a total of 96 from the quests. The borders are out of question cuz I won't be getting the skins. What is the best use of them basically, I'm leaning towards the champion orbs?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 18:46:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hero siege 487</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-25 18:47:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 13:35:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>7053</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-27 13:35:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>753</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 00:10:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>483 Stardew Valley If taken then minecraft story mode My favorite tv show is criminal minds. I don't know why I love scaring myself or making myself paranoid but yea. I think I really like just the thrill of connecting the dots in time to save the next victim. Thanks for the giveaway!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-28 00:13:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Helloworld</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-29 07:13:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do this called in the key bind menu? My f is bound to something else and this sounds really useful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 23:53:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://steamcommunity.com/id/ganlas324/ Thanks for the giveaway!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-30 23:53:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>436 Thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 05:35:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rust Thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 05:36:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>2 Thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 05:37:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>24 Thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-02 05:38:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>742</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-03 19:15:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Undertale Thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 01:01:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you using high sierra? I think there is a known bug that civ V doesn't work with high sierra. I heard the devs are working on a solution, my friend has the same issue. The only way to fix it at the moment is to revert OS versions.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 13:16:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Town of Salem Train simulator 2017 Borderlands My favorite steam game is civilization V. As for beating it... that's a long way off. Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 00:15:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>500 Amazon Coins Please! The joke's bad but it's the quickest one I could come up with off the top of my head and not going over to r/Jokes and taking something from there. What do you call a cow with no legs... Ground Beef . What do you call a cow with 1 leg... Lean Beef . What do you call a cow with 2 legs... Your Mom!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 00:25:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>[SteamID](http://steamcommunity.com/id/ganlas324/) The only online shopping I do is from Amazon. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 00:27:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>[SteamID](http://steamcommunity.com/id/ganlas324/) This game has always been on my radar, for a couple years now. It just seems fun, and I want another action-packed type game to keep me busy. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-07 00:29:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Passpartout: The Starving Artist Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-08 03:55:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>734</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>$650 Max Budget Build</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 02:51:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Have you read the sidebar and [rules](http://www.reddit.com/r/buildapc/wiki/rules)? (Please do)** Yes I have. **What is your intended use for this build? The more details the better.** I want to use this build for gaming. Lol/CSGO/Rocket League. **If gaming, what kind of performance are you looking for? (Screen resolution, framerate, game settings)** I'm fine running these games without ultra-high quality. Around 30 fps is good. **What is your budget (ballpark is okay)?** $650 **In what country are you purchasing your parts?** U.S.A **Post a draft of your potential build here (specific parts please).** https://pcpartpicker.com/list/fWBywV **Provide any additional details you wish below.** This is my first build ever, so I'm not completely sure if all the specs check out. I don't really want to get into overclocking. Also, is this build upgradable down the line? I read that future-proofing builds isn't really a thing but, would it be possible to upgrade this build relatively easily in the future? And if so, what would need to be upgraded. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-09 03:12:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why would I want to change my motherboard to a micro? Like what would be some pros/cons.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 09:40:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks op!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What reason is there to live?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 02:13:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some days like today I just feel really depressed, like what's to stop me from killing myself. Why should I be happy, why should I stay alive?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-11 02:17:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>this is soo me right now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-12 06:56:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>A thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 00:46:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>144 Thanks op!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Leaver Buster</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-16 20:54:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I recently got hit with leaver buster, 20 min queue for 5 games after I had to leave an ai game. I'm down to my last game with the queue, and I was wondering about my profile after I finish the 5 game in the low priority queue. So after I finish my 5 games, is my leaverbuster record reset like from fresh? Or if have to leave a game will I get hit with the penalty again? Basically, does the game remember that I had the queue penalty before and is it more likely to punish me since I already was in low priority queue? Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 00:46:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>1468</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 00:46:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>4619</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 00:47:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>mistletoe Thanks op!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 00:48:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks OP!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The next comment button is no longer transparent.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-19 05:56:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I just deleted and redownloaded Reddit to clear my cache. After redownloading I noticed the next comment is now a solid white instead of the transparent gray it was before. Before i barely noticed it while residing but now it blocks my sight. Did the devs change this permanently? It can I change it back?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 07:53:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>724 Thanks OP!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 07:53:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>485 Thanks OP!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 07:55:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks OP!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 00:42:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>629 Thanks OP!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 00:43:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>486 Gary's mod please Thanks OP!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 00:44:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>368 Thanks OP!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 00:46:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi Thanks OP!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 00:46:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi Thanks OP!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-24 00:48:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi Thanks OP!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 07:47:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can I have csgo please? I game on a MacBook Pro that my parents gave a while back. I hope to build me own PC this summer [steam ID](http://steamcommunity.com/id/ganlas324) Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 07:49:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Steam ID](http://steamcommunity.com/id/ganlas324) Can I have stardew valley please?? So here's my story (I'm no writer BTW) Me, my dad, and my aunt were hiking down a mountain. We aren't serious hikers but we like to be adventurous on family vacations. So my aunt slips on some moss and hits her head. It starts bleeding and blood gets all over the place, her hair, her jacket, her bag. Of course being the smart capable people we are we packed no bandages or any first aid supplies and all we had was a role of paper towels. We sat down for a good 10 minutes letting my aunt rest, thinking how we were gonna help her get down. We had no water or food because it was with my cousins and uncle further up ahead. Thanks to the generosity of some strangers who gave us food and water we managed to help my aunt back to the cars. Luckily no one got badly hurt and my aunt was relatively find in a couple days.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 07:56:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Steam ID](http://steamcommunity.com/id/ganlas324) Can I have nidhog? Thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 07:57:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks OP!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 07:57:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>So true</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 07:59:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Having my own money But with great money, comes great taxes and bills Fml</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 08:00:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Eat the pumpkin pie that's sitting right next to me. But then I'll become even more fat and I'm trying to lose weight. Plus I need to share it with my family.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 08:00:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>White collar</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 00:50:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>4854 Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 15:00:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd love a key! Congratulations on making your own game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-02 01:52:50</DATE>
    <TEXT> #128514; this is easily the most used emoji</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-07 03:23:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Plague inc plz Thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-10 05:28:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't forget coconuts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Why don't SWAT teams bring an ambulance with them when responding to an emergency?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 22:33:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It feels like a lot of deaths could be averted if there was an ambulance ready to take victims to the hospital. This is only of course if the local town has ambulances to spare at the moment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 23:20:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>And what if a civilian get caught in the cross fire.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 21:21:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Click the x on the top right</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 21:22:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>The area where it leads you to click is covered by an ad or something. This ad takes you to the steam store. You can click an X on the top right to go the actually button. You do need an account for this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What are the two symbols on the top right? I see this when hovering over a friend's name from my friends list.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-14 02:05:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What do the two symbols on the top right mean?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-15 23:41:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 21:02:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friend (she plays the piano) has a shirt that has a fermata and he words hold me underneath it. I always wondered what type of reactions she era with it. A fermata is a musical symbol that basically means play until the conductor tell you to stop ignoring what's written on the page.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do the new honor rewards work?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 00:11:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>So when I logged in yesterday I got placed in honor level 5, but I didn't get any rewards. Does this mean after getting some honors I reach the checkpoint and that's it or will I be receiving the rewards later? How does this work?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-17 00:32:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't really think it means anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>People who say they're not looking for any trouble almost always find trouble</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-21 06:35:04</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 06:38:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Strangers, but most of them were cool about it. There was only this one guy who raged super hard. It's always the Yi's...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 20:42:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nami It's a close team fight and I'm spamming my W so no one dies, then it jumps to an enemy and kills them. I'm not trying to steal kills just save my team. It's either that or my ult. I often use my ult when the enemy tries to disengage, cuz it's great at stopping them. But then it kills someone who's low and I feel bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-22 23:27:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nami</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 00:59:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>3268 Steam gift card. Thanks op!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-23 05:49:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>The thing is I main nami support and my W involves healing allies while damaging enemies. And it does a surprising amount of damage. So I spam my W trying to keep my team alive so we can work together on a good push or baron lategame. A death would really hurt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-25 02:35:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just keep typing. When I was younger I was hopeless at typing and didn't even really work on it. As I grew older and typed more frequently while doing homework, chatting with friends, or playing games. I just learned the keyboard. But I don't use all my fingers or the stupid home position thing that tried to teach us in school. Mainly my middle and ring fingers on my left land and my pointer, ring, and index finger on my right hand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-28 07:12:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't' know if I should, we have soo many mutual friends who I like and it would just make things super awkward. Especially since we see talk in school everyday. I think I'm just gonna not play league alone with him and just ignore him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 06:24:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Summiners rift</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What does this mean? My download bar is stuck at this and the time remaining keeps fluctuating.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-29 22:34:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-03 23:44:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks op</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 02:28:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why are the lines of text not lined up??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-05 04:35:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>And civ V</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 23:08:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's the scoreboard for the game. It stays the entire time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 23:10:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's the difference between the game clock and the play clock?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-06 23:13:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok. Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 04:26:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would use this to buy Stardew valley or Ravenfield. Thanks op!!!! [Steam ID](http://steamcommunity.com/id/ganlas324/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-07 04:42:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>1665 Thanks op!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I downplay my birthday and pretend it's not a big deal because I don't want to let my parents know that I'm always depressed around my birthdays</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 03:13:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've just had bad experiences during my birthdays for the past few years. From none of my "friends" remembering my birthday even if spent the entire day with them and I reminded them the day before to being super sick and wishing I could die. This year no one remembered again and my parents took me out to some Korean place I didn't even like. I only agreed cuz I know my dad really wanted to go and would argue like crazy if I said no. The presents aren't as big of a deal to me, I know anything a really want my dad would never agree to. So lately I've listed started saying my birthdays no big deal, even if it matters to me. It's easier this way than for me to feel sad for myself or have other people possibly feel sad for me. I also have extreme self doubt so I don't even know if my birthday should be something I rally care about. I just don't know anymore.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-11 01:15:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's exactly how I feel</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-12 02:28:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>When me and my friends started playing my friend got this on his first night and we were super confused what happened as he tried to describe it over discord.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ELI5: What is graph theory?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 04:49:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>My parents are making me take a Combinatorics and Graph Theory course this summer, but I have no idea what it is. I tried searching but the other posts didn't really explain it. I get combinatorics but what is graph theory? Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 08:04:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree, I don't even think my parents know what it is. They just saw a math course and signed me up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Do you still get a chest if someone on your team gets an S?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 00:54:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know in season 7 if someone on your team got an S and you owned the champion you played, you would also get a chest. Does it still work that way? I own Master Yi and while playing him, multiple people on my team have gotten S's in multiple games but I have still not gotten a chest. I have not earned a chest with him this season (or ever).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 01:11:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ohh ok, thank you. I always played with my friends last season but not so much recently. I guess I got it mixed up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-19 16:00:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/morbidquestions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-20 00:27:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm confused, what am I not seeing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Season 5 Episode 8: Outfoxed</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 02:54:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am only on S5E10 so no spoilers, please. While watching outfoxed it never made sense to me how long it took Rossi and Jennifer to run upstairs and help Morgan. From the first gunshot and sounds of fighting, there were 25-30 seconds where Morgan was facing the unsub alone. It shouldn't have taken the others more than 10 seconds to run upstairs. Am I the only one who feels this way?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do I go about attacking this city? I have more units coming, but Heliopolis can one-shot my cannons with an archer. I already tried attacking, this is loaded from an autosave.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 04:44:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 06:20:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry I wasn't very clear about the arrows. I'll just wait till I research dynamite and get artillery.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 14:25:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you suggest I increase my science? Im starting to build public schools in all my cities now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The only thing stopping me from killing myself is knowing how devastated my sister, cousins, as grandparents would be.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 05:20:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 16:15:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>How were they arrested?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 16:57:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>..., a very way to phrase my question would be how did the police figure out it was him?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-28 05:30:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's so annoying, especially if your reading a long story from r/writingprompts or a sub like r/pettyrevenge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 20:41:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I personally watched quill18's civ V beginners guide. After. First episode I started exploring on my own.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Have two types of prisons; one for dangerous criminals who need to be off the streets, and one for people who made mistakes and got caught.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 22:03:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Live photos was a cool idea but now when someone texts me a live photo its just the camera shaking a bunch and then settling on the subject.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-13 22:06:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 00:16:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most people don't even realize they have Live Photos and everyone's too lazy to take proper life photos when the recipient doesn't even care if it's a live photo or not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 00:26:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>It plays automatically. You can't stop it Edit: in my experience it has always played automatically. I don't get live photos often so I never bothered looking into how to turn it off.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 01:49:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe it only plays automatically if you're viewing it from a laptop. That's what happened to me before I made this post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 03:37:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Remember the time he put the self destruct button on the bottom of the robot army's feet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I finally understand how people can stay up all night texting</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-14 04:35:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never had the type of friends who I would text often or chat with late at night over text (only voice if we were playing a game or something). But recently I became friends with this girl in school, we don't really share much in common other than school but I recently I could be texting with her for like half an hour and not even realize times passing by.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What to do while fields grow?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 19:38:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey guys I recently bought farming simulator 17 and I'm a couple hours in on easy difficulty. I just planted my first batch of crops on my 3 fields but I don't know what to do while they grow. I've been spending my time completing missions but there must be something else to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-18 20:48:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Which should I go for first? I haven't invested into any of that yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-19 00:25:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tried the logging tutorial and got the life of me hated trying to pickup and move logs with the claw. It was worse than those arcade claw machines.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My grandmother died and I feel nothing</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-26 03:52:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I got the call I felt sad but it wasn't overbearing. I have no problems functioning and whenever someone expresses his or her condolences I just say thank you but feel it is totally unnecessary. Sometimes it feels like they are sadder than I am. And all my family members are offering support of I need it but I really don't. Is this normal?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 12:49:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me and my friends love doing this if he's on the free rotation. We call it Mundo Ball</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 20:35:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think so, but we would rather spend our BE on people we would play more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 01:14:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>does it? the comment you responded to was deleted</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-28 13:03:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can I have mini metro please? I would recommend Slime Rancher if you're into peaceful farming sims with the occasional bit of action. In the game you manage a ranch full of slimes and in order to get new slimes you have to go into the wilderness and capture them. The games adorable and the slimes are really cute. I would really recommend it if you're ever feeling sad, it helped me. Thank you!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is skipping bronze normal?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-29 06:36:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just finished my provisional games yesterday and placed silver 4. I've never played ranked before season 8 but I completely skipped bronze. This seems weird to me because some of my friends who are better than me and have played ranked in previous season got placed in bronze. I also only won 4of my provisional matches. Is this normal or did I just get really lucky with my placements?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 06:55:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>638 Mini metro please!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Alt Tabbing out of Farming Simulator 17</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 02:30:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there a way to alt tab out of this game? I don't like playing in windowed mode, but I also want access to the rest of my programs while playing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 06:25:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>God I miss this show so much</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-01 07:08:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>154 Would you rather be able to breathe fire or breathe water/mist spray? Thanks!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 02:21:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>418 Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 06:54:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>528 Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[SPOILER] Season 6 Episode 18 "Lauren"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 03:20:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>**This post contains spoilers, consider yourself warned.** So I just finished episode 18 and I'm curious [how Emily staged her death](#s). Did anyone pick up on some clues that I didn't, or is it revealed later on in the season? It reminds me a lot of [Neal Caffrey's](#s) death scene from White Collar. (Great show!)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My new thing when people obnoxiously brag</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 06:49:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>So some people always feel the need to have the coolest story in a conversation. Like taking the same exact story as someone just said, changing names, and making it "cooler". These types of people also bring up their achievements all the time during a normal conversation. For example, I play League of Legends with my friends and this one friend always needs to have had the best games, and constantly talk about all the amazing plays he's made. To the point where it gets annoying and kinda sounds fake. So whenever he does this I've now been complementing him and talking about what a great player he is. "Killing them kindness" as some say. I find this to be way more satisfying and better for my health than secretly raging in the inside like I used to do. But I also feel a bit bad doing it cuz I do it like everyday, but he brags and talks like this everyday so it's just my response.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-08 05:35:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you do that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-09 02:35:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>r/summonerschool it's a subreddit dedicated to helping players get better at League of Legends and it's helped me get a lot better. I find that I tend to browse it more than any other sub</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 23:54:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sid Meier's Civilization III Complete Steam CD Key 48 Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 13:24:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a toggle thing, so if you bind spacebar to toggle camera lock if would unlock/lock it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-16 21:21:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>My ego</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 01:42:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is actually a good idea for starting items since Nami has good sustain with her poke. I'm gonna try it next game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Caster vs Engage Supports</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 03:25:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>So me and my friend both like to main support. I main caster supports like Nami, Janna, and Soraka, while she mains engage/tank supports Alistar, Tahm Kench, and Leona. We were discussing this the other day and were wondering, what are the pros and cons of each class and when are they better than the other?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Caster vs Engage Supports</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-17 06:47:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>So me and my friend both like to main support. I main caster supports like Nami, Janna, and Soraka, while she mains engage/tank supports Alistar, Tahm Kench, and Leona. We were discussing this the other day and were wondering, what are the pros and cons of each class and when are they better than the other?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 18:17:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unusable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 18:31:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>What skin are you using?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-22 18:36:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nah b, you need to steal those kills. Snipe with your ult or "heal" your assasin while they're chasing down kills.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 02:51:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not possible to get anymore, right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Serious] College recruiters of Reddit, what do you really look for while selecting an application for college, like how much do grades matter in comparison to other stuff?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 04:30:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm useless</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 00:17:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just feel so useless and don't know why I shouldn't kill myself. The only thing stopping me is I don't have an easy quick way yet, I was thinking pills would be the best. I feel like I get nothing in life, I don't make it onto any teams, I'm socially akward, I'm fat, none of my friends actually like me. My parents are always mad at me because I didn't make it onto the mathcounts team or robotics team or because some of my friends are doing better than me. My mom tells me to stay away from my other friends because of all their faults and they'll just drag me down. Anything I once thought I should be proud of my mom just shutdown and said its nothing great. You probably only won the guitar competition because you were the only one participating. I feel like I will never be able to be happy or content, and if I ever am it will just be shutdown. Life's just pointless and I might as well kill myself to spare me the pain and eternal depression. The rational part of me thinks this is stupid because I am smart, I'm in all honors but I just feel like I won't achieve anything in life or be accepted into any good colleges. Even though I'm smarter than a lot of people in my grade, there are lot of people who are better than me at everything. My school life is getting worse too. I often can't concentrate at home, so I do worse on my homework and tests. Which causes my parents to be pissed again and I just feel like my entire life is a downward spiral. The one thing that makes me happy is playing LoL with my friends but my parents always say its useless and It will get me nothing in life so I shouldn't waste my time on it. And lately I feel all my friends don't want to hang out with me but they do i'm there cuz they might as well. I'm sorry for this rant, I just needed to let it out somewhere.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 17:01:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like using the dart monkey building. The free dart monkeys are really good when U can transform them into supers later in. Also a 3-2 monkey can get you pretty far on its own. (The tri shot, not spike ball. I haven't played in a while.)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Proposed changes to the save icon</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 00:55:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>So when you try to save a post from your feed the save icon already has a check on it, before you even save it. It feels kinda misleading. I think it shouldn't have a check before you save it, only after. So you know if you've saved it or not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 22:06:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try looking at his runes and what lanes he's been ganking. If he's been ganking melee lanes and avoiding fight with ranged enemies, he's probably going for rhaast. If he's doing the opposite he's probably going for shadow assasin. Also Kayns with electrocute/dark harvest are more likely to go shadow assassin. But keep in mind you can never truly know until he changes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 22:06:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you still get the skt t1 nami skin? Edit: all the old championship skins have been brought back for the MSI</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 01:44:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea they brought back all the old championship skins for MSI.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 02:46:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>My friends' face when I tell them scuttled is the hardest camp to clear as fiddle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 13:00:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good job on reaching diamond. Also you can't change the titles of posts, only the body.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 20:35:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't realize what sub this was and since I'm on mobile the full image wasn't visible. I thought the title was referring to something totally different.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm still learning Rakan, but I'm really proud of this play.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 01:25:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 04:54:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>u/silvershape ask and you shall receive</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ULPT: Feel stuck doing boring worksheets for your teachers? Look online, more often than not many teachers get their worksheets and questions from online sources, which sometimes have answers.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-08 23:38:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>For example, my history teacher gets many questions from his teacher's copy of the textbook, but some other teacher who uses the same textbook uploaded the teachers copy to his website for his students to use. It's also conveniently available for anyone else to use too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 19:13:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those are his facebook friends and their high scores for that map. The color medal denotes which difficulty they completed it on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We're leaking into League of Legends' Patch Notes</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 22:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 00:08:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm the exact opposite, I always thought it was a weird cube thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 00:29:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh sorry, i should have probably checked this sub before posting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 03:48:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks OP!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 15:06:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>IIRC I don't think they expected Scott to know that they were on to them, hence them being surprised when they see the pictures.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 23:16:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do you face the constant stream of biter attacks? I'm still kinda new to this game so I don't know what all the map symbols look like but it doesn't look like you have laser guns everywhere. Or maybe you do and I'm just retarded.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 12:45:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>From your regime I'm assuming your min sec population is smaller than all the others. Could you post a link of your canteen and kitchens, it seems like you would need a gigantic kitchen for even a small number of prisoners.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-30 20:47:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-01 13:29:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Their argument is this "stupid immigrant" is raising too much of a ruckus so let's just a give him a bit of the money to shut him up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I just cut myself for the first time...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 03:29:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got into a really heated argument with my Dad, but the thing with him I know its best not to say anything back so I try and contain myself the best I can. Which leaves me so frustrated and angry with my life. It was over some stupid thing about how he doesn't want me asking a friend for help on a homework assignment and one thing just led to another. The minute he left I just burst into tears and I didn't even know why. I think it was something about how I hate him so much and he just causes me so many problems and I have to live with him for a few more years and will have to remain in contact too. (I can't bear the thought of having everyone know I went NC with my dad). In the middle of the tears, I just reached for the scissor on the side of my desk and made a couple cuts. I don't know what drove me to do it, I always thought I would never do it. I'm occasionally depressed and sometimes I want to die but I never feel like I'm ever going to do it. I don't have the courage, means, etc.. I'm sorry for the rant, I just need to vent this out to someone. On another note, my clear mind is now freaking out about the two scars I have on my arm. Ones kinda small and not really noticeable but the other is kinda large and I don't want it to raise any looks. What are some good ways to get rid of scars or at least reduce the discoloration that can be done from home with stuff you would normally find around a house? Edit: It's ironic because my dad was originally talking about how I always get distracted and I shouldn't have my messaging app open (discord) even though I just opened it to message a friend for help. But this whole thing has wasted so much more time than I would have even if I started talking to a friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>