<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject3725</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-06 08:26:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I remember playing as Lannister and getting crushed by Baratheon.PLaying as greyjoy I did ok but not better because of my poor decision making</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Build Help] Virgin PC builder here. I want a PC for gaming. I have a budget of about $1000 (AUD) Give me advice about the parts I have chosen so far</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-06 08:58:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there anything I can change. Better alternatives between hardware. I am switching over to pc gaming for the next generation and ditching consoles. I do not plan on overclocking (hence my decision on choosing a non-k CPU). The main problem is I am planning to build during November and my biggest fear is the release of better alternative hardware. Is there anything I can wait for that would go well with the build? Any advice is appreciated edit: The parts that are "purchased" haven't actually been purchased they are from stores named PC DIY and MSY (The stores aren't on the pc part picker website) [PCPartPicker part list](http://au.pcpartpicker.com/p/1dJMi) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://au.pcpartpicker.com/p/1dJMi/by_merchant/) / [Benchmarks](http://au.pcpartpicker.com/p/1dJMi/benchmarks/) Type|Item|Price :----|:----|:---- **CPU** | [Intel Core i5-3470 3.2GHz Quad-Core Processor](http://au.pcpartpicker.com/part/intel-cpu-bx80637i53470) | Purchased For $209.00 **Motherboard** | [Asus P8Z77-V LX ATX LGA1155 Motherboard](http://au.pcpartpicker.com/part/asus-motherboard-p8z77vlx) | Purchased For $119.00 **Memory** | [Corsair Vengeance 8GB (2 x 4GB) DDR3-1600 Memory](http://au.pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-memory-cml8gx3m2a1600c9) | $85.00 @ Mwave Australia **Storage** | [Samsung 840 Series 120GB 2.5" Solid State Disk](http://au.pcpartpicker.com/part/samsung-internal-hard-drive-mz7td120bw) | Purchased For $105.00 **Storage** | [Seagate Barracuda 2TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive](http://au.pcpartpicker.com/part/seagate-internal-hard-drive-stbd2000101) | Purchased For $94.00 **Video Card** | [Gigabyte Radeon HD 7870 2GB Video Card](http://au.pcpartpicker.com/part/gigabyte-video-card-gvr787oc2gd) | $235.00 @ PCCaseGear **Case** | [Corsair 200R ATX Mid Tower Case](http://au.pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-case-200r) | Purchased For $72.00 **Power Supply** | [Corsair Builder 600W ATX12V Power Supply](http://au.pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-power-supply-cmpsu600cx) | Purchased For $85.00 **Optical Drive** | [LG GH24NS95 DVD/CD Writer](http://au.pcpartpicker.com/part/lg-optical-drive-gh24ns95) | $21.00 @ Mwave Australia **Operating System** | [Microsoft Windows 7 Home Premium SP1 (OEM) (64-bit)](http://au.pcpartpicker.com/part/microsoft-os-gfc02050) | Purchased For $100.00 | | **Total** | Prices include shipping, taxes, and discounts when available. | $1125.00 | Generated by PCPartPicker 2013-07-06 16:50 EST+1000 |</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-06 14:09:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is the extra 16 bucks really worth it? What extra benefit can Haswell give me? Any great H87 motherboards you can recommend?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-07 01:22:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have found a similar Asus board priced the same as the Ivy bridge board I've chosen, the Asus H87 PRO which is about $129. The Asrock in the price range is the Asrock H87 Performance which is $125. Since I have no experience with motherboard manufacturers I don't know what brand is reliable. So an Asrock would be the way to go?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-07 04:40:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for all the help the pc now comes down to a sub total of $987.76 after replacing the products with what you recommended. Also btw is this the Sapphire card you were talking about? http://www.pccasegear.com/index.php?main_page=product_info amp;cPath=193_1372 amp;products_id=22516</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-08 04:10:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>My love for you is like diarrhea. I can't keep it in</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-09 13:46:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bro, I was in the exact same position you were. Loved this game. But there was one far far away mission that was a bitch I can't remember it that well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-09 14:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I personally stopped after MW3. God that game was awful but the survival missions were pretty solid. I did enjoy MW2 though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-14 01:41:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but the coop trophies were a pain. I played them locally with my friend and damn they were difficult for 2 players only. With 3 or 4 player it would've been much easier</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-08-24 05:21:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's it unsubbing till the game comes out</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-01 02:16:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think GRRM said in an interview that both TWOW and ADOS are going to be 1500 pages each. Besides that mid 2015 seems like a good estimate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-01 06:42:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-01 10:56:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what I was going for.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-16 13:29:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>So much chaos in one episode</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-22 15:33:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it is a beta Franklin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-23 16:16:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gambling advertising during sports events</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Spoilers]PLEASE HELP!! I think my main storyline is broken</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-02 09:42:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I'm about half way through my storyline and I'm at a point where I no mission shows up on my radar. After completing the mission 'Blitz play' aka the mask heist I received a Delvin mission and a Solomon Richards mission. I stopped playing for a while at that point. When I got back to my game I noticed something fishy in my radar. Oddly there was no Solomon Richards icon. I continued playing the storyline and completed the cop motorbike mission and the mission where you steal the black car for Delvin. I then completed a Trevor mission after that. I am at the point where Trevor owns the strip club and I also completed the 'Surveying the score' mission where you plan the big heist and you're meant to follow the two security vans with your helicopter. Now I can't see ANY main story missions on my map. All I see are Stranger and freaks missions and the lester assassination missions. I've tried restarting the game nothing seems to work.:/ I am not sure what to do now I'd expect this type of shit in Skyrim but certainly not a gta game</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-02 09:50:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've definitely completed the first assassination mission. The hotel assassination mission right? Should I complete another?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-02 10:16:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah just finished the second assassination mission and can confirm it doesn't do shit. There's nothing also I can do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-02 10:37:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Crap I was able to reload a save just after that Delvin mission where you steal the black car. But guess what. Still no Solomon</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-02 10:48:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I was able to access it but the Solomon mission still wont show up</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-02 11:56:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks I am trying to look for it as well. I haven't found it yet but I do see a few posts stating that the patch may have caused single player issues or gta online may have caused single player issues. Could be related to this? EDIT; I think I've found it: http://www.reddit.com/r/GrandTheftAutoV/comments/1nikcx/glitches_since_the_update_today/ Also there are some very similar posts:http://www.reddit.com/r/GrandTheftAutoV/comments/1nj1pz/spoiler_possible_glitch_no_story_mission_showing/ http://www.reddit.com/r/GrandTheftAutoV/comments/1niyyy/for_those_who_havent_updated_yet_some_info_ps3/ I think that I can come to the conclusion that downloading the update and trying to access GTA:O may have caused this problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-02 12:20:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank god I've found this post. I thought I was the only one. I thought the mission icons disappearing and other single player problems were rare bugs. Having downloaded the update and trying to access GTA:O may have caused my Solomon mission to vanish. I have posted on the Rockstar support page and have yet to hear from them. I am contemplating whether to completely start the game over again or wait for the issue to be addressed and patched</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-03 02:28:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Still haven't heard from them yet. Here it is anyway http://support.rockstargames.com/hc/en-us/requests/1034678 And my post which is almost identical http://www.reddit.com/r/GrandTheftAutoV/comments/1nkjxq/spoilersplease_help_i_think_my_main_storyline_is/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-03 07:22:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I the only one getting single player issues from trying to launch GTA online?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-03 15:19:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel ya. Now mission icons wont show up for me and I can't progress through the main storyline. I don't know whether to start over or wait till the single player issues are finally addressed and solved</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-04 01:00:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>No singleplayer issues being addressed. *sigh*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-10 09:29:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>A fame system. There's been countless times in TES:V where I've been so frustrated because of NPCs not acknowledging me when [Spoiler](#s 'I saved the ENTIRE WORLD FROM ALDUIN')</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Build Help] A few questions on wifi cards</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-03 10:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>With the computer im planning to build I need a wifi card because my ethernet cord can't reach where I'm going to be putting my PC. I've noticed that there are threee types of wifi adapters available. A PCI, PCI E and USB. Are there any main differences between the three?The mother board I'm [getting] (http://www.pccasegear.com/index.php?main_page=product_info amp;cPath=138_1491 amp;products_id=23561) has two PCI and PCI E slots but not the short PCI E slot. This [wifi card](http://www.pccasegear.com/index.php?main_page=product_info amp;cPath=200_328 amp;products_id=19577) looks like it can only fit in the small pcie slots. Can it fit in a normal pci e slot where you plug in a graphics card? I know this [PCI wifi card](http://www.pccasegear.com/index.php?main_page=product_info amp;cPath=200_328 amp;products_id=17622) will fit. This is all confusing to me can you help me out?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-10 09:36:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>*cough**cough* COD: Ghosts *cough* *cough*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Build Help] Quick noob question</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-12 09:43:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm about to build my first pc very soon. I don't have any speakers lying around. Will headphones work just plugging them in the front audio port? Im thinking of buying the tt esport cronos headset.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-06 15:07:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Played Skyrim for a while without realising that after 10 hours of gameplay I had 20 perk points waiting to be spent on skill trees</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-20 23:11:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>My Steam URL http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198116165697/ The games I'm interested in are **Deus Ex:Human revolution** because I like how tthe game in open to different play styles. I already have this on PS3 and being a fairly new Master racer I would like to experience this game on PC **The Witcher 2** looks interesting and I have generally heard good things about it. Finally **Sleeping dogs** I love open world games such as GTA, AC Saints row etc and it looks like a lot of fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-11 12:16:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've knew about this since release. The perks of having a strategy guide handy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Legal Studies assignment help</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-05 12:06:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi there, I have a legal studies media file+in class written response assessment for school and I'm wondering if you guys know of any online news articles concerning either Aboriginal law, the right to appeal and rules of precedent. I've already found articles on the Australian Constitution, international law and procedural fairness. Any help will be greatly appreciated :).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Gus Fring taking care of business with the cartel, as usual</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-06 12:00:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-06 14:36:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>More pics http://imgur.com/a/F8iRu#0</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-06 23:07:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>EXACTLY. There are normal glasses in single player. There is no reason why they shouldn't be in multiplayer</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-14 10:04:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm feeling more hilarity than rage</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-12 08:05:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>relevant https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3Y5SAM91oG4 amp;list=PLuKg-WhduhkmIcFMN7wxfVWYu8qnk0jMN</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-19 16:08:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hows life in the embassy?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-10 07:02:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>#Darksiders #FTL #SpecOps hope I win</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>A Question about order tokens and power tokens</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-28 02:13:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfortunately I don't have a board game or rule book with me at the moment but I think there may have been some misinterpretation of using order tokens in areas controlled by a power token. My friends and I have always assumed that you can use consolidate power order tokens in power token-controlled areas to farm more power tokens (Is this a misinterpretation as well?). However during a 6 player match last night house Greyjoy decided to place a +0 march order from Greyjoy controlled Eyrie and a -1 march order in the power token controlled Blood Gate. He apparently managed to make a chain march through his power token and march into my Tyrell power token occupied Crackclaw Point. We got into a heated argument because of this move because it was a make or break order that determined the victor. I thought it was an illegal move and consulted the rulebook for clarification however it was late at night and I couldn't be bothered to read as I was really exhausted. In short what type of order tokens can be place in power token controlled areas if any? Also any other relevant rules? And can you please specify the page number of the rule book</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-28 02:50:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you very much. Makes me realise how many unbalanced games I've played</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-30 10:59:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does it happen to be a Solomon Richards mission? I've had a very similar problem just after release. I had to start the game all over again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-11 04:50:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>TIL I own the same case as a guy with a sports car</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-01 08:36:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who else thought it was Gus Fring from the thumbnail?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-16 10:23:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the giveaway. Insurgency please. 3442 http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198116165697/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-25 16:43:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Use the down vote button more often.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-25 16:45:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Our lust and desire for dank memes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-25 16:50:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gold</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-29 15:05:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>To reintroduce gang recruitment from GTA:SA. Having Franklin rolling with his homies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-13 03:49:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't afford the game since I spent most my money on my rig and the game itself is really expensive for a game released 2 years ago!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-13 12:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ty much appreciated.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-15 14:30:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>ty much appreciated</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Help] Not having touched the game in months I came back to some horrible graphical issues</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-16 07:19:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I currently have Nexus Mod manager 0.48.1 and the reason I haven't updated is because it is recommended that all my mods are working as they are (which they aren't) and I'm also using SKSE My Specs are : Intel core i5 4570, 8GB ram, Gigabyte B85M D3H, GPU - AMD R9 280x 3GB, Windows 7 Home Premium 64 bit Load order:esp: http://imgur.com/jIW3YoP,SkAsv9c#0 Mod list:http://imgur.com/cbA6FAV,O35PFyc#0 Skyrim prefs ini http://pastebin.com/6aNK3U7i The Enb I have installed is realvision After doing a few Google searches I took the guess that it may have been an issue with RLO but I have a feeling it may be real-vision enb causing this since after running the game several times I saw some weird rainbow contraption shapes. Here's what's happening, it's during a key moment in the DB questline I don't know if that's relevant: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YbYJQDw7w2g amp;feature=youtu.be</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-17 02:07:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know why this was down-voted but I'm still really pissed since I didn't do shit to my game and returned to a broken one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-20 05:52:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you very much and best of luck to everyone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-20 13:22:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you can get it on new gen or PC go for it. If you're getting it on 360 be prepared for horrendously long load times and crashes that online is more prone for. If you only care about single player then the 360 version is just fine. Take this with a grain of salt my experience on the PS3 version has been extremely frustrating online</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-21 07:41:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>4244</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-22 23:25:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>9833</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-06 15:30:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Warhammer #174; 40,000: Dawn of War #174; - Game of the Year Edition please</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When the weeaboo game is strong</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-20 13:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-20 07:29:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>467894</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-29 13:35:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>1131 Corsair k70</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-31 13:05:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>*moind</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-31 13:15:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-19 10:13:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's a suggestion. Create flairs that indicate whether someone is getting a male or female's judgement. It would be cool if sexual orientation would be included as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-09 06:01:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Got the game on my android phone emulator. So much nostalgia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-09 12:44:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks op</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-04 13:26:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Microwaving chicken in what I had thought was a paper bag. I was oblivious to the fact that there was aluminium foil on the inside. After 5 seconds I heard a series of loud pops and saw sparks flying inside. I immediately switched the power and had a fire extinguisher ready shitting myself. Luckily there was only a small flame on top of the bag which slowly died out. The chicken was still intact. Neither the microwave nor the household were damaged thankfully.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-05 10:00:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>At least you made that mistake at 10. I was 18 years old lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-27 15:29:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>3369</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-14 15:32:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheers, good luck everyone</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-22 04:08:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol death march is easy af once you get op weapons and armour and complete quests and defeat monsters within your level range.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What piece of advice that you have applied, completely backfired?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-18 15:34:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-26 07:15:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>The same patriarchy that has 18 year olds used as cannon fodder during war, running out on the beach towards certain death while high on speed?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-02 08:25:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can hate on Islam without hating muslims you know</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-17 07:33:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okeh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-01 15:20:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Had a similar experience. The stripper I was chatting up ordered a drink at the bar then I ordered mine. Turns out the bartender charged both drinks on my debit card even though I saw the stripper give her card. What drink costs $23.50?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-24 08:07:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't want to introduce someone to a future world of global warming, national debt , peak oil etc</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>HTC ONE M8 - Storage issue after fixing error loop</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 05:56:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>After charging my phone after the battery died I kept on getting theses error loops stating that "unfortunately HTC SENSE Home has stopped working" and "Unfortunately com.google.process.gapps has stopped". Luckily the settings app was left open and I was able to fix these by clearing the data for each respective app. However, most of my apps vanished from my phone which meant that I had to download them again from the Play store. However my phone has insufficient storage. Every time I delete something, there is no dent in storage. I even tried this for an app that was listed to be up to 3GB but still nothing. Any ideas?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 06:20:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hmm, I'm not sure what you mean but I tried moving the Spotify App (2.76GB) to my SD and internal storage did not change. Instead the data on for apps decreased and the data in System increased</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-16 16:48:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a lexar 32GBHC and it has 10 on it so I'm assuming it is a class 10?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 01:36:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Raid: Redemption and the Raid 2. Indonesian Action flicks with absolutely exceptional fight choreography. One of the best action movies imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 16:47:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's definitely God. When John yells "damn you" to him he responds "many have".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-28 09:47:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is why I love my current job. People treat you like a saint when you're giving away free samples at supermarkets</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>HELP - HTC ONE M8 acts weird , then even weirder</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 12:58:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey guys I'm left scratching my head as to what's going on with my M8. One time I accidentally dropped the phone from chair level and that sigh of relief of finding nothing shattered quickly turned into worry as the damn thing would not turn on. It was bricked. I tried charging it only to find the red LED flashing subsequently after the battery symbol flashed on repeat. I took it to a phone repairer and $80 later he managed to "fix" it and claimed the issue was the gunk in the charging port. Since it was only at 6% at that point I deiced to charge it home and there was one little problem, the phone charges incredibly slow. It estimates that it will take 23 hours to get to 100% on the factory charger. I should also mention that I was at a music festival recently and it was pissing down rain. A lot of rain landed on the M8 since I urgently needed to contact a friend but I used it under my poncho (even though rain still managed to hit it every now and then). Could this have contributed? Is the battery fucked? Does it need to be replaced? How is the dirty charging port related to this? Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-08 23:49:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>The issue is the exact same when I try to charge it with a micro usb connected to an apple power adapter so there's that. Is it difficult to replace the daughterboard? Where can a buy a replacement? Any special tools I need?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-09 02:11:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I just got back with the phone repairer and they said it will cost in excess of $150 AUD to fix it because of the parts and labour. So it might be best i take it into my own hands. I might just place the daughterboard myself if it changes anything. The repair process looks hard as fuck but Ill give it a shot. Thanks for the heads up about the daughterboard type and all your help so far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-21 11:29:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>As with "abs on a skinny guy are like big tits on a fat chick, doesn't count"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>On the fence with this one. Help a newbie out, PGR or nah?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 14:35:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-18 06:45:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>In a perfect world, politicians like Greg Hunt should resign in disgrace for stating something so nonsensical and erroneous like the gateway theory. I'm sure bikie gang members have at one point rode push bikes. Let criminalise push bikes cos it's a gateway to the comancheros! Correlation != causation fmd</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 03:47:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>the GTAO model is so profitable there's no way they won't borrow some elements from GTAO. However, I don't think they'll just copy and paste the game and add a RDR skin on top</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 16:13:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just as everyone was getting mopey about the lack of news</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 01:25:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well it didn't last for long. Her mum got fired from her real estate job for using the mansions she was selling in these videos</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 02:03:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah true that Instagram following is a tangible wealth creator now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 10:57:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've accepted that I am gonna die before the Winds of Winter comes out though</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-02 04:44:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol at United "you got a loicence for that joke?" Kingdom</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 16:30:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Deadset you just described an experience I had except only my patience was rewarded and got a fire hook up right before 4/20.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-21 10:07:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look how slow we were for same sex marriage. Don't expect anything, medical or recreational for at least 5 years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 14:26:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>$180 for half an o of very high quality dank in Australia</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 14:35:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was either these clowns, or the corrupt ALP. You just can't win</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 15:00:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you'll find this helpful https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d-SUhJT3g1c amp;ab_channel=shooterwilliamson</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 17:01:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Say what you want about the merits/faults of each party's policies but comparing O'Farrell's resignation to Obeid singlehandedly putting his own party into disrepute is naive. I fully support voting third parties.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 23:54:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wasn't that just a legal loophole corrected?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 10:33:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where in Australia? In Sydney $15 is the norm, $20 at most.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 12:17:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Drug free Australia claims that Cannabis causes more harm to society than tobacco and alcohol whereas a professor specialising in anaesthesia, drug sciences and applied chemistry says otherwise. Hmmmmmm who do i believe? /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 09:07:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>PGRS are endemic in Australia and is heavily pushed by organised crime and people still tolerate it and keep the demand high.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>