<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject8770</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The Alice Morgan case. S4E02</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-01 18:52:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just finished watching Season 4 of Luther and I have to say, what a damn pity it's so short but I would love to hear everybody's opinion on just what is going on with Alice Morgan. [Spoilers, naturally] I personally don't think she is dead (and I don't believe Ruth Wilson was too busy to not be able to come back for season 4 (proof: http://www.telegraph.co.uk/culture/tvandradio/11576114/Ruth-Wilson-Im-more-honest-in-acting-than-in-life.html), not seeing her and watching everything unfold builds up the suspense and mystery surrounding her so I don't think the producers made a bad decision to leave her out(previous link also supports this) (they had done it before anyway)) as I don't think Megan had any founded reason to kill her, faking her death would (and was) enough to use Luther as her puppet (in planting the evidence, but I don't understand why she wasn't able to do this herself? In the end, it was an anonymous tip that lead to Stacy Bell being caught, not Luther enforcing it and she was able to easily break into Luther's home to steal his locked away phone and leave undetected which shows she was capable of such act. Maybe it was because Luther had made her the promise that she wanted him to fulfil it and be the one to set Stacy Bell up?). Also, why did Megan have to steal Luther's phone in the first place and did Megan leave the diamonds and the two phones in the safe container (The one being Megan stole from Luther and the other possibly being Alice's) for Luther to find them? As you can see, season 4 gave more questions than answers and do I have so many more questions that have yet to be asked here (hope someone could answer them all). On another note, I enjoy watching Luther but I would have left it like how it ended at the end of season 3 (I thought the ending was good) but season 4 was made so I guess I can't complain watching some more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-01 20:02:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Dark Knight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-02 18:05:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>The snubbing is consistent with all of Christopher Nolan's movies unfortunately.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-03 19:10:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I completely agree with what you have just said. I think one possibility as to why Megan did not carry out planting the evidence herself may have been due to Luther's promise to her that he would solve the Jonathan Black case and catch the true suspect. Maybe Megan wanted Luther to do it so he could fulfil that promise to her. As to why she took Luther's phone in the first place, (which shows she was more than capable of planting the evidence against Bell) confuses me as to what she could have done with it in her possession. You said she can pressurise Luther with it but I don't understand how as it's a burner phone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 05:36:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>If we were to explore all possibilities then Megan, could potentially turn out to be the next 'Alice Morgan' (in other words, an ingenious murderer) who meddles with John Luther and it would certainly explain how she was able to outfox Ruth Wilson's Alice Morgan. On another note, Megan does seem to be pulling a few references from Alice Morgan, one example being from the Roadrunner expression, "Meep meep" (And another very explicit one but can't remember off the top of my head(I will look it up)). However, I don't quite understand how she is able to know all of this and why anyone would extract (or give up in Alice's case) this sort of information if Megan was to have interrogated Alice Morgan which leads me to thinking, maybe Megan and Alice could have an established rapport between each other and be pulling the threads for something else planned (and this references are used to show this connection between the two to Luther (You could argue that Megan does this to prove to John Luther that she has seen Alice Morgan but as I've said before, the references used by Megan are almost impossible to have been known by her unless one of Alice Morgan or John Luther had given it up). This is very skeptical though with how the finale ended up between Megan and Luther in the car scene and their little but not so light-hearted exchanges, but these references derived from Alice Morgan just give me a very funny feeling.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-04 19:35:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>What you have said there is very likely but when I went back to watch episode 2 again, from season 4, I watched the scene between Megan and Luther, where they are sitting together on the bench. Megan admits that she had been listening to Alice and Luther's conversation for a while now and so could indicate how she has come to such knowledge of these references from Alice. However, if this is true, it still doesn't explain why Megan would steal Luther's burner phone when she already has all the insight she requires. As for the other reference that I was talking about (the one where I had said I'll look it up), it was the interrogation scene between Megan and Luther where, Luther discovers Megan's huge insight and knowledge of the Jonathan Black case. At first, Luther thinks the only way she could have gained this knowledge was from Alice, as Luther had only spoken to her about it, but then later discovers that Megan was involved heavily in the case herself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-05 13:52:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it may have been done in maybe the same way one of the suspects in the series (the guy running around with the shotgun, trying to bring justice to those the law had let go of) did it to his brother-in-law (I think he was). The suspect was able to clone his brother-in-law's SIM so whenever he got a call, the suspect was able to easily listen in on it. However, in order for this to work, Megan needed either the SIM of Alice's or Luther's phone, which would not be very easy to do unless there was another, more convenient method to listening in on the phone calls. Going back to my earlier argument, this must be the only way Megan could have gained so much information about Alice as Alice would not have given up anything if she was interrogated. Alice Morgan is extremely loyal to Luther, you only have to watch the finale episode of season 1 where she says that she will "never betray" Luther to understand it. This bond only got stronger as the series carried on, saving each other's skins countless times and finally Luther choosing Alice at the end of the season 3 finale. So my point is, the knowledge Megan has acquired about Alice is only through phone conversations/text messaging but is that all really enough to be able to know much about Alice and even discover her whereabouts. Maybe, maybe not, but I sense there may be another factor at play here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-05 21:58:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, you're right. We can't come to any conclusions with what we've been given at the moment. Only way to resolve this is through more episodes but I fear we won't be getting more anytime soon, hence the reason I made this post. Idris Elba's quote from the interview is quite interesting and it hadn't come to my attention before. I think his belief is supported through the finale of season 4, where Megan pretty much puts across a cryptic message to Luther about Alice Morgan. However, what I thought I understood from season 4 was Luther at first, certainly did not believe Alice Morgan had died but slowly started believe she may have truly died (this is what I felt, at least) but as I said, it's interesting that Idris Elba said Luther doesn't believe Alice Morgan is dead. Is there any chance you could find the interview and send a link for me to also check out. Oh and I almost forgot to mention, at the end of the finale for season 4, a David Bowie song is played when Luther walks out of Megan's car, could this give any indication or clue about anything? (John Luther is also seen taking a glimpse look at Alice Morgan's photograph)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-05 23:49:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for providing the link. I've just skimmed through the interview and saw the bit where he mention's Luther thinks Alice Morgan isn't dead. However, Idris Elba also mentions that "Neil's clever way of putting the Alice story to a close, some way, some how, and have Luther carry that burden" is what I picked out which strikes me. Luther could very well think Alice Morgan is still alive but Idris Elba himself mentions the writer wanted to end Alice's story in Luther and that the show is on Luther, not Luther and Alice, so it maybe wants to shift away from Alice Morgan and more onto Luther. I personally wouldn't understand why someone would want to kill off one of their most iconic character but this could also very well be a method of diverting attention on her death away to not spoil anything for the upcoming season/movie ((which the writer could have very certainly recommended to Idris Elba himself) An example of this would be what happened in the season 5 finale for Game of Thrones). On a side note, I hope Luther stays in London because they literally are recording in my back garden. They used my park as a hospital Alice Morgan was kept prisoner in, during episode 1 for season 2. I enjoy seeing places I recognise :).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-09 18:26:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah yeah, you're right. I just listened to the actual song and it doesn't sound like David Bowie to me anymore but apparently Robert Smith re-recorded the song for the Luther series (he sounds a bit different in this version). The song is called 'A few hours after this'. I can't help but think the lyrics for this song could provide some clue as to what could happen in the future for the Luther series.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-10 01:50:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm guessing John Luther also wanted revenge on Ian Reed for what he had done to his wife, going under police custody would have meant potentially Ian getting away with murder and Luther's wrath, not to mention, the gun with Luther's handprints would have been the final nail in the coffin had he not intercepted Justin's car.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-19 01:38:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just re-watched bits of the first episode of series 4 but I couldn't find a timeline between the finale of series 3 and the beginning of series 4. If I had to guess though, I'd say it's been 4-6 months, maximum a year, (judging by how Luther responds to a question from Theo Bloom, about his relationship between himself and Alice Morgan at the beginning of episode 1, series 4). I think in that amount of time, Luther would have been able to take care of his things and tidy up loose ends while Alice, could derive a plan on how to gain enough money (blue diamonds) to permanently leave the country. As for what you said about Megan, I'm not sure what you mean exactly, but Megan does mention that she saw Alice Morgan as Luther's blindspot, where she can hurt Luther, but the "Perhaps that's why I did it.......but I didn't" that follows is just intended to puzzle Luther (and the audience) about what has happened to Alice Morgan. I don't think they are introducing Megan as the 'Alice Morgan 2.0'. I think Megan's true purpose for her introduction was to finally disrupt the bond between Luther and Alice Morgan, as this had not been done before in the previous series, testing Luther mentally, as Alice Morgan is the only person left in his life (or so it seems).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-25 12:35:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sherlock has even less episodes per season compared to Luther (although longer episodes (extra half an hour on top of Luther's episodes)) but it is still great and feels satisfying.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-25 12:39:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>The intro for Luther is perfect. Sets the tone and theme extremely well for the series.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-31 04:38:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there anything special you can do with that faction?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-10 21:24:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's available on Mac both on the Appstore and Steam.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-14 02:06:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alex DeLarge.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-22 02:04:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there a tutorial for mac?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-24 23:49:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>The last image of Geralt with Ciri reminds me of the artwork made for Hitman 2: Silent Assassin of Agent 47.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-07 11:02:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are correct.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-26 23:25:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>What were you referring to exactly when you mentioned the "animosity and hatred" towards Ruth Wilson's Alice Morgan character?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Surely this shouldn't go unpunished.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 02:46:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-12-29 02:49:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Started ranked with a 4 man party. The random, Pulse, decides it'll be a good idea to nitro cell the whole team and immediately leave the game, leaving us not only a man down but also starting the game a round down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to counter pulse</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-01 03:57:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-23 09:40:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hostage not killed. Fission mailed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-27 02:26:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>This glitch happened to me just tonight with Montagne but I'm pretty sure I never used any gadgets.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-02 22:38:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chalet garage doors issue - The left hand side of the garage door cannot be breached with a thermite charge or Hibana's pellet. Below, I've linked footages of it happening on both patch 2.1.0 and 2.1.1. [2.1.0](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tslwLMzC0IE) [2.1.1](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1nilI-M1puk) Cannot reload gun issue - Don't have footage captured of this one but when I was downed after emptying my MP5 mag, with doc, I revived myself but couldn't reload my MP5 or aim down sights but I could use my pistol just fine. The reload animation would occur (on the MP5) but it would it would still say that I have no bullets in the new mag (this reload animation happened everytime I switched between my primary and secondary.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Panic mode</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-11 16:22:51</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 12:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Godzilla (2014)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 21:00:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been in Glaz's position numerous times but I usually end up killing my teammate along with Caveira.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-30 17:17:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Arrival (2016). I went into this movie having not watched a single bit of trailer but I had heard really good things about it and boy did it impress. I don't want to talk about it much (mostly because I don't want to spoil anything (besides, I'm not even sure how to use spoiler tags, lol) and you could literally write about it all day long. It was such a beautifully constructed movie with a good soundtrack to go with it and would recommend any fans of Sci-Fi to definitely watch this movie. Interstellar was another movie that I thoroughly enjoyed but I have to be honest and say Arrival was the better of the two (although Interstellar is still a marvellous movie also). It was easier to comprehend the complexity of what happens in Arrival than Interstellar (I managed to figure out the reveal before it was shown, so bonus points for me) but that doesn't mean it's easy. If you've got a keen eye for details and whatnot then you could put the pieces together so I really enjoyed this aspect to Arrival where I really had to use my head to figure out what was going on (which Interstellar also had in abundance). All in all, would highly recommend a watch, even if you're not really into Sci-Fi, then you could still really appreciate the psychological aspect of this movie, as I had described earlier on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-03 17:59:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's exactly where I left off and honestly didn't want to play again. Haven't gone back to it so far.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 22:45:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>[--]7</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-01 16:50:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Roberto Soldado.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-12 01:53:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought Kimmich was a midfielder? Guess they gave him the Sergi Roberto route.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-19 01:24:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most likely due to his price tag.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-08 04:20:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blind started his first season at Man Utd playing in midfield under Van Gaal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is Ubisoft's stance on K amp;M users on consoles?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 03:53:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>High rank (platinum-diamond) is becoming increasingly infested with players using K amp;M rather than controllers so I was wondering if anyone knew what Ubisoft's opinion on this is. Personally, it is very difficult to play against opponents who use a mouse for aim as their skill ceiling is much higher than that of controller users, so it is unfair but I also understand that other games (such as paragon (which can also be played PS4-PC cross-platform)) allow K amp;M to be used automatically after plugging in via USB leading me to question whether this the future for console gaming?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 04:22:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry I don't mean it in a rude way but why not switch to playing siege on the computer if thats what you're most comfortable with?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 04:30:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tbh, I can't afford to either otherwise I'd love to play siege on the computer. Atm, I'm just stuck at platinum 2 aswell since dropping from platinum 1 a while back. Just one step forward, two steps back really.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-19 16:12:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Le</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 14:09:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure Rashford's height is updated, he must be growing as he definitely doesn't look 5'11 any longer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-22 18:55:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I call it the Rey Mysterio mask.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-02 14:33:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like your name.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-15 20:48:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just had this glitch happening for me but it was on bank and kafe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 01:36:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try playing terrorist hunt to reach level 20 or grab a few friends for casual. If you don't have any friends who play siege then I'm sure there should be communities, like the ones found on PS4, where you can group up and play together.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 01:38:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Red silk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 01:45:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I personally think ranked is a better platform for learning good positions such as angles, or good spots for example, a mira window. However, you must first learn the maps before this is possible, which terrorist hunt can be very useful for. I find people mess about in casual often so it doesn't help much and you know this from your own personal experience.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 02:02:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>If the problem is gunfights then practice your aim on terrorist hunt. As for the so called stupid mistakes, thats quite vague, so I'm not sure what you're referring to exactly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 02:19:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe because it was a brand new map?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-16 20:14:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you've got access to the computer, then I'm sure you can easily check the specs and share here for others to help you a lot more. Otherwise, I wouldn't pay.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 02:36:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you serious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 02:43:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blitz's shield doesn't extend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 02:45:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Play ranked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-26 02:55:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every trap is visible if you pay attention. As for droning, it basically gives you two extra lives as you can use it to scout defences and enemy positions so I don't understand what you're complaining about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 10:46:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>You sound like you just suck at the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-11 13:15:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't agree with the downgrading but I'd guess to play with his friends.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-13 02:12:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the year one skin was gold.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-25 02:27:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can confirm.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-18 23:46:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>That Fabian round was amazing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-22 11:44:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh boy, I take it you never experienced the Castle glitch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>