<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject0</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-10 23:16:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a little late for this, but I agree. I thought you were saying that BE is bad overall. I was shocked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-15 10:51:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Regular Monster was ruined for me. I was drinking it and a friend of mine said, "Doesn't that taste like diapers?" and I spit it out. I have tried it a few times since then but still can't shake it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-15 11:06:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you elaborate on the prostitution?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-15 12:09:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most free porn sites (Pornhub, Redtube) are owned by the same companies as the pay-sites (Brazzers) and are, as addressed before me, advertisements for the pay-sites. One of the reasons that it's not fruitful to pay people to go take down copyrighted material is because the porn industry is gigantic and as soon as someone puts a copy of a scene online, it can be uploaded repeatedly. So, if they're going to do it anyway, the company (I can't remember the company's name, it's 6AM lol) might as well put out a better version with a link to where you can pay to see the whole thing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-15 12:23:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why? You can not use the site if you feel "exploited" if they ask you if you can donate to keep their free site running. I am laughing about this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-15 12:51:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know if this has been addressed yet, but for a while you could literally enter anything for the second word.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-15 14:51:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>You be a man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-16 00:29:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>You my dawg.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-16 00:31:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hell yeah dawg.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-17 09:53:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Playing Magic (the gathering), making music and hanging out with my friends. Shit's fun, (wo)man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-17 11:47:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>You sure told them! Maybe they would have stopped if you had actually said something to them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-17 22:52:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>If something is right to you, it shouldn't be hard to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-17 23:48:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Actually, most people that pirate software/movies/music are pretty broke people and, in most cases, either couldn't or wouldn't buy what they pirate if for some reason they couldn't do so anymore. You're assuming that 4-5 billion people are in the market for, have the money for, and can justify spending money on a car. The choice isn't "do I pirate this or do I buy it" for most people, it's "do I pirate this or not have it at all."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-17 23:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah but with IRL cards there is packaging, shipping, the need for stores, etc. It's pretty justified, I think. I am not saying that Magic is too expensive by itself, they're just creating data instead of actually making the cards. Granted, it's not a gigantic difference, WotC is printing money either way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-17 23:56:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I said most cases, if you caught that. I guess you didn't, that's fine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-18 15:30:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>What? Your arbitrary number means nothing, it's obviously a case by case basis. Don't be mad because you're wrong, dawg. That's not cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-18 15:35:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You seem to not understand. If you couldn't/wouldn't buy it, they do not lose money. You are not a lost sale. You are simply too poor or uninterested in their product to spend money on it. If you can't buy it because of where you live, as explained earlier, you are not a lost sale. Obviously you don't HAVE to torrent anything and you still choose to do it. I don't get what your angle is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-19 05:24:01</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; And that's why companies that sell those goods are loosing profit not money, they have to make the money to lose them in the first place. Confirmed mental retardation</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-19 06:09:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're making creatures better. MaRo has said that, besides Reserved List concerns, there isn't a creature in Alpha that they couldn't reprint due to power level. Creatures used to suck. That "power creep" is making creatures more viable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-19 06:38:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, shit. Sorry. This is I think the second thing I have ever posted to Reddit. I appreciate you telling me haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-19 06:48:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a very hard card to play. It requires pretty complete knowledge of your deck and a pretty good idea of what you can't handle otherwise to take correctly. It's a good card when played by bad players, it's an amazing card when played by good players. That being said, since nobody else knows what else is in your deck, we can't really make informed decisions. As fa as the information we have goes, I would probably pick the Revelation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-19 07:08:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could agree. I play creature-based decks but after rotation I want to build Izzet control with spellheart chimera and young pyromancer. I feel like it will be a good transition for me. I just don't like when people complain that they can't play creatureless decks anymore. It's whack. Like, people are mad because their style of play isn't as good anymore. I also believe that, all in all, creature decks playing creature decks require way more thought and have way more decisions to make. The advantage is a lot more incremental and one bad move can lead to losing. It's fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-24 17:21:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why? Shit cards don't get played. Out of the 16 cards he's drawn, the only one that's been popular is Mortars (Anger of the Gods should be popular too). If you painted and nobody cared about stuff you did because of something that wasn't under your control, you'd be upset too. I don't mind the "this card sucks but here's the painting" because you actually get to see the high-res image of the art and maybe appreciate a tin street market as something other than something to write on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-24 18:18:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not the same. He is talking about the card being bad, not his art. He has nothing to do with the card. I can see what you mean, but it's not the same as fishing for compliments by saying his art sucks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-24 18:30:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just don't know why you would be upset about that. To each his own. If I were an artist with thousands and thousands of people looking at my art everyday I would try to be as visible as possible. There's no sense not to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-25 05:39:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought it had something to do with his name. I thought "Again?" was referring to the Sum Ting Wong thing that happened a while ago. I have been trying to figure out what innuendo his name was for about 15 minutes. I have brought shame to my family.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-25 06:21:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't even imagine what you go through every day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-25 20:16:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why is there a dichotomy involving rape? Both females and males get raped. I don't think that tackling the issue through making a gender division is a good thing. It's a human issue. Edit: I'm getting downvoted for that? haha alright sexists calm down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-25 20:41:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your landbase is a gigantic deal. As in, the type and amount of mana you have will impact how well your deck runs monumentally. Also, a huge factor in how good a card is is how much mana it costs. That doesn't mean that cards that cost a lot are bad, you just need to make sure that the effect/creature you're getting is worth the 5 mana. I think that Dragons are a good example of this. For 5 mana you could either have a Thundermaw Hellkite or for 1 more mana you could have a Shivan Dragon. Conventional logic for a new player would show that Shivan is better because it costs more, but for that comparison it should be obvious that Thundermaw is a lot better. TL;DR: Your landbase is very important and knowing what effects should cost will save you a lot of trouble.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-25 21:50:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did. This was "in response", it seems, which is the problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-25 22:08:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right? haha I just noticed that the sources and citations weren't the same on the posts and it seems like it was a response. Hopefully it wasn't. Either way, I don't think that splitting it up by gender is the right move. Everyone is susceptible to being raped.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-26 00:54:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, like I said, I know what it's from. Still doesn't answer the question of why there needs to be the dichotomy of gender regarding rape.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-26 01:41:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, there is. One is featuring men, and one is featuring women. Why do they have to be gender specific? Why can't they just be people? Why can't they be "sexual assault survivors" and not "male/female sexual assault survivors"? You certainly wouldn't see "white sexual assault survivors" and "black sexual assault survivors". Boo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-26 02:11:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. Yes there is. Here, on Reddit, there are two separate links with the two genders. I looked at their tumblr, like I told you before. Just because the people who did it aren't doing it, doesn't mean it doesn't happen. I don't know how you can say there isn't a difference to be made between male and female sexual assault survivors when the thread we're on is "27 Female Survivors Of Sexual Assault Quoting The People Who Attacked Them" with another thread made earlier for males.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-30 03:49:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I could agree that it could suck. I love fallout, I just don't like that I can surpass the struggle at a relatively low point. I shouldn't be past the point of worrying about repairing weapons/having supplies at level 15. I love how Dead Money flips the game on its head to where you're excited about finding tin cans. That sounds like a cool playthrough, I might try it out. Thanks a bunch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-30 03:53:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Out of everything you could hate about the gaming culture, it's this? It isn't difficult to not buy into a certain marketing promotion. You vote with your dollar. I do, however, think that your hatred could be pointed in a much more productive direction.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-30 06:19:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the info, I appreciate it. I think that Hardcore Mode adds a lot of tedium and isn't exactly the same type of difficulty increase as, like you mentioned, base health being lowered or having a smaller carry rate. I would totally do this mod if I had it for PC, but I am a 360 toting piece of trash. ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-30 09:39:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's definitely not about the realism factor in a sense of having to eat or drink. It's more realistic to assume that you shouldn't be able to be (basically) immortal after level 20.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-30 09:42:28</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; I disagree. I mean I just finished a very hard survival run of NV and all the DLC's including Dead Money and for the most part I never worried about supplies. That's my point. Do you think that, put in the shoes of the Courier, you would never have to worry about supplies?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-30 10:11:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>The game itself. Difficulty doesn't really matter for the most part.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-30 10:13:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's how I feel about stuff like that. Like I mentioned earlier, I guess there is a fine line between what is needless tedium and what would actually add to a richer experience. It definitely wouldn't be easy to make a full game like Dead Money, but I would definitely play it if it were to happen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-30 10:21:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is exactly it. I don't understand what people don't get. I understand that there are people that play more to explore and collect. There are games for that. When someone said "I think you're looking for a different series" I was slightly shocked. How wouldn't you want a more deep experience with a post-apocalyptic environment rather than an Elder Scrolls game with guns and less colors?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-30 11:30:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Decided to come up with a caption for an ancient picture***</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-30 11:39:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>It solves it more than anything else that's been offered. On my latest playthrough I haven't been focusing on getting as much money and loot as possible (although in the environment that's the instinct). A lot of things are just a little too readily available. Especially once you take a few things into account like giving 3 Doctor's Bags to Markland at Bitter Springs and he says that they will last *a whole refugee camp* weeks. Meanwhile you have 300 stims and 20 more doctor's bags.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-09-30 23:02:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's pretty cool. I really wish I had a PC that can run NV now with everyone talking about sweet mods lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-01 05:48:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think anyone was suggesting that Fallout go survival-horror.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-02 00:50:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>The gameplay in terms of setting and element, yeah. However, I have explained pretty thoroughly (as has everyone else) that what I am talking about is how much more realistic it is when it comes to resource gathering and management. Obviously I wasn't suggesting that there should be a full game like dead money. It's just unrealistic how you can be basically immortal at level 15/20 in NV.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-02 02:01:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>About a decade ago. I was going to the local swimming pool every day during the summer and I would call my mom to come get me. However, this was during the time of those "Bob Wehadababyitsaboy" commercials so I would just spend the payphone money on a snickers and call my mom and state my name as "Mom ineedarideitsyourboy"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-02 02:24:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am not a waiter either, but a prep cook that helps my dad sometimes at a nice restaurant. The place, a restaurant that hosts wedding receptions and birthday parties, is about 15 minutes from the ocean in Florida and we, as most all other restaurants in the area, will still buy frozen scallops, shrimp and fish from Publix. We also advertise some shitty fish (IIRC it's called Smy or something like that, google searches come up with nothing) as grouper (an expensive, high quality fish) and nobody knows the difference because they don't eat grouper enough to know the difference. It's mostly so shitty because the restaurant is part of a yacht club that charged people insane amounts of money for membership. I was just making things always thinking that if I was paying that much for what I was being served, I would be livid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-02 02:32:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>One thing I remember hearing somewhere about the difference between west and east coast (almost perfectly personified by tupac vs biggie) was that west coast rappers make you feel like you're in the limo with them, while east coast rappers make you feel like you're in the ghetto with them. Myself, I like east coast rap. I am not one say "oh this person is bad because they're from Long Beach" or whatever but it happens that most of the hip hop I like is from NYC. East coast rappers seem to have more subject matter related to their everyday lives while west coast rappers use their rap as a statement of fact. For example, I think that the difference between Illmatic by Nas and Doggystyle by Snoop Dogg shows the difference between the two areas very well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-02 03:22:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I write down everything I think of. When I started writing it was sorta the same as having writer's block in the sense that nothing amazing was coming out. I knew I had to write no matter what because writing bad stuff makes it easier for you to get out the good stuff and also helps you know that its good. I hope that that helped.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-02 03:31:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>there is always tappedout.net where you can make and goldfish (playtest by yourself) any deck. As for the actual idea of a deck, I would say just look at cards that get you get excited about and go from there. An example would be that I like Demonheart Chimera. It has the potential to be awesome in a deck built with it in mind. It wants instants and sorceries in the graveyard. Izzet charm is prety versatile in that it does 3 things that Red/Blue wants to do, counter, loot, direct damage. The looting (drawing 2 and discarding 2) is even better considering that it would beef your Chimera. That's in. Quicken puts itself in the graveyard, draws you a card and can make any sorcery an instant (like Mizzium Mortars for example) all for one mana so that's in. Young Pyromancer is amazing with a lot of instants and sorceries. That's in. You just go from there. I hope that that helps.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-02 04:38:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the best answer. OP, if you're actually trying to understand details of the game, this is where you need to look.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-02 05:06:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you serious? If you agreed to talk about it, be a man and do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-02 06:26:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Adding onto u/mombo101's point, you don't want to have too many cards be pieces to one win condition. If you found some way to make your whole deck synergistic it would be better but needing 4 specific cards to do something cute is not good deckbuilding. You would rather have something like Agent of the Fates where you could make the opponent essentially sac a creature every turn, but it's still not good. You have a whole deck of cards for a reason. Something you could so is look into Isochron Scepter. It's a better card (thats subjective I guess but Arcanist is pretty poopy) that allows for those shenanigans at a much higher level.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-03 00:34:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is actually a deck I am building. Here's the list: http://tappedout.net/mtg-decks/b-pota/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-03 11:34:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. I didn't make up my side yet but that's definitely going in. Seems pretty good. Too bad that and hands of binding are the only near playable cipher cards. Cipher is a sweet mechanic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-04 05:45:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't count EDH in the "unplayable" classification. A card has to be Wood Elemental bad to be unplayable in EDH.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-04 14:07:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>How would a business stay afloat if they have people just spending a few bucks? That's obviously what *you* want. That's not what a shop owner wants in terms of spending unless they have, you know, 1000+ people coming in a month.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-05 00:59:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you say "on chips and a booster pack or some dice or something" that's definitely not up for interpretation. That's just a few bucks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-05 12:02:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you know how much a box costs (direct from wizards) and how much you have to sell it for to stay competitive in the sealed product market? You make pennies per pack. For example, one of the shops listed above that did the Q amp;A said that he makes 2 dollars off of a box when he sells them on ebay, which is where most of his sealed product is sold. A pack and some chips isn't going to get a business by by any means. If you go to a place a lot and they provide you with a nice, clean environment to hang out and play magic then you should spend a much more significant amount of money than what you would spend on the things you described.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-05 12:58:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>If they aren't going to do something about it, you should. It's not a waste of a cop's time since that's what taxpayers like myself (and I would assume you, but I don't know) pay for. Someone stole your stuff. It's a matter of principle. If the shop owner will neither tell/show you who it was nor confront them about it then fuck them. The right thing to do would be to have the person replace what they stole and then tell the person never to come back. That's pathetic. I am sorry that that happened to you. I sympathize with your situation. I hope everything ends up okay. TL;DR: That shop owner is a prick and nobody should stand for either the store owner or the thief's behavior. Call the cops. Edit: To the people downvoting me, how do you feel about it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-05 13:05:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>A CASE OF WORLDWAKE LOL WHAT "sorry you got your 200 dollar deck (that I could easily replace as a shop owner) stolen and had to deal with the cops for an hour. Here is $4,000 dollars worth of magic cards for your trouble."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-05 22:49:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>A lot. I like how you're deflecting what I have said because you're wrong. It's hot. I like it. Don't be mad at me, kid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-05 23:23:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Keep telling yourself that. I tried to have a discussion with you and you just keep deflecting what I say. Be mad some more, kid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-05 23:26:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just curious, how is the card frame more flavorful?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-06 08:01:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not aware of the public opinion of this movie but I'm glad other people found it off-putting because of how "done up" it looks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-07 07:38:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Aetherling is probably the best blue control(ish) finishers in standard right now. I don't know if "aggro" is the way to considering that mono blue can control pretty well with cyclonic rift, voyage's end, dissolve, etc. A good curve could be turn 1 do some shit, turn 2 tidebinder mage, tap some shit down. turn 3 thassa turn 4 jace or anything else and thassa has devotion. finish with stuff like Aetherling. Ball out. Edit: Anything else with UU in the mana cost.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-07 07:43:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also something to note is that you can have two or more and activate one plate mail then in response activate the other plate mail's ability so its not even much of a downside.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-07 07:45:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I say kid a lot. It's not an insulting word to me. I don't think that insults would have been constructive. Sorry for using the same word twice. It won't happen again, pal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-07 07:52:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I totally agree that it can't control as well as WU. It just seemed to me that you more wanted to make Thassa work than have an aggro deck. If you want to keep it creature heavy, it looks pretty good. I dig it. Still, like you said, Jace would still be a pretty cool fit. I have a UR deck with SPellheart Chimera, Young Pyromancer and stuff like that and Thassa works pretty well in it. I am excited about it. in fact, here it is: http://tappedout.net/mtg-decks/b-pota/ The reason I am showing you this is to show you that Thassa can work with a more creature heavy deck. I do however think that her scry ability is most useful when you've got spells to use. But, even then, with her you can get risky with what you play cause you can pitch it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-08 01:34:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_Z3cwJrnXzc amp;list=RD02YZOSFsHMSo8</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-09 15:19:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am assuming that it's because Magic just began its third 10-year period.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-25 12:00:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>How could someone take comfort in that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-14 22:50:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>How much did you influence the writing on the album being the first album with you as a guitarist?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-23 09:33:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>How big was this hole? Did you need to fit a football team through it? I am shocked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-11-30 17:12:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a nice image but I'm pretty sure it's exactly that: an image. It doesn't move when you walk.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-05 23:33:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know Devin, their guitarist, and the dude that posted this. They all play, and any of them will play a game with you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-06 05:52:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I live in Columbus. My name is Sid, if you have like seen me on his facebook or something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-06 12:12:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Coincidentally enough, I am opening up a card shop in Columbus. It should be open in February. I am stoked on it. That's pretty cool. The dude who owns comic town is sweet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-19 07:11:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>What an immature way to respond. People don't like you much, do they?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-19 07:35:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-28 20:20:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, it's actually about 1-2 miles from campus. I was thinking of a way to incorporate it as well but I can't really think of anything that bridges the gap of something that would sound cool for both. I am a creative writer (hip-hop) so it's not hard for me to write clever things, it's just a pretty huge decision and I am afraid to name it something terrible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-28 22:41:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's awesome! Perhaps you are familiar with the intersection of High and Hudson, where the Taco Bell is? We'll be right there! I am pretty excited about it. It's going to be awesome, and of course you and your friends will be welcome any time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-28 22:42:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>See, I thought it sounded cool too. Hitting random on the gatherer sounds like a sweet idea. Thanks a bunch!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-30 00:22:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not really. I am not trying to be "that guy" but everyone I know thinks that the soldiery sucks. I know a lot of people that only go because it's close to campus. The guy that owns the place is rude to everyone. I am excited about getting people to start coming to my store because it's closer, nicer and because I will treat them better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-30 00:23:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, that seems like something we would do. I know that Stoneforge isn't copyrighted, and there are shops like Mana Vault and other card names as well. I think that we would split them, in any case.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-30 06:38:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hell yeah. We are excited to have you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-30 18:42:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I remember correctly, you can buy boxes from WoTC for 76.50 and most distributors for ~80. Most card shops make in between 2-10 dollars off of a whole box at a competitive price, depending on shipping costs and other factors. When you buy singles as a dealer, you buy them at 50% cash value usually. Shops mostly have boxes for limited (draft, sealed) and look at them as a very small fraction of the store's income when not linked to FNM/tournament play. I remember the owner of the LGS I go to telling me that he makes more money off of a 10 dollar card (bought at 5) than a whole box. Also, supply and demand is what drives prices for singles and the supply is just fine for stuff like Theros that is in print (more than any other set ever most likely) and isn't a niche product like MM. TL;DR: it has to do with how much boxes cost to buy from WoTC and/or distributors and how the secondary market is different from doing so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-06 08:01:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's pretty dope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-07 03:36:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was really curious about this. I could never find anything about anything he's done recently. Do you have an idea or could you point me in the direction?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-08 10:26:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Book your own in any venue that will have you. I am part of a duo and we played with my friend who plays the fiddle and hits a pad and also played with a DJ. We had a good time and pulled some pretty good money. It was a fun show. Now I can book shows if I wanted to by knowing enough talent with enough draw. I would say that you need to make connections and figure out what you can do for yourself if you can't find anyone else to put you on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-08 17:23:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>For sure. To elaborate, we had around 100 people there for it when we only had 5 songs. There was the DJ and the dude with the fiddle. Charged 5 dollars at the door, about 80 of them paid. Sound dude needs paid 10 a set, venues either let you play for free (they make money through drinks, especially for hip hop since most of the crowd wants to sip and nod) or charge a small amount. In any case, you have 3 acts, you pull in 400 bucks, you pay the sound dude 30, shit, let's say you even have to pay the venue 70 for variety's sake. If you split it evenly (which I perhaps should not have done, but did anyway) you still make 100 bucks. I'd pay 100 bucks to play a fun show, which makes getting paid to do it even better. I spent the money on pizza. First show's earnings (sarcastically deemed "rap money" lol) blown on a dumb whim. Great night.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-11 14:53:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why are you using so many question marks? Nothing you said was a question.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-11 14:55:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, definitely. Either a 4/3 or 4 direct damage is bad, because you wanted them to make the other choice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-11 16:03:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Both of the examples in the second usage are questions. What /u/android47 said weren't even complete sentences. The main reason I even commented on it was because he/she was delivering a snide/condescending response, which in most cases makes people not want to go out to play magic. Being met with a response like this when you don't have a good understanding of card evaluation hurts people and discourages them from trying to participate/learn from more experienced players in the future.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-11 16:33:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, you're witty. ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-12 21:41:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>if that IS your real name.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 15:41:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I notice that a lot of newer players have problems with untap upkeep draw as well. I was trying to come up with a way to remember it more easily but couldn't really come up with anything besides perhaps placing a die or a counter on top of their deck to make sure they remember.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 15:46:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was considering making what would essentially be a preconstructed starter deck, like a mono-green deck because they usually have the most simple creatures and creatures/combat are more engaging to new players (that's my theory, anyway). Plus some stuff like Giant Growth and stuff like that and perhaps some overruns or some big finishing sorcery. By buying bulk, I could reasonably expect to assemble a lot of them and hand them out as part of the class/seminar/a better term for class.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 15:51:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>What would you suggest is a good order for new players to learn the card types in? So far I have the idea of teaching them about card types in this order: lands, creatures, sorceries, enchantments (first normal enchantments, then auras), instants, artifacts and then Planeswalkers. The main reason I would put artifacts so far back on the list right before Planeswalkers is because I feel as though artifacts can emulate every permanent type besides planeswalkers. There are mana rocks, artifacts that are just enchantments without a colored mana cost, or are/can turn into creatures. Plus, artifacts tend to have activated abilities and that can be confusing as well so I would rather teach them about artifacts at a later time. Would you agree? Edit: I forgot instants in my listing. Erebos, forgive me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 15:56:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you :) I know about those little decks. I think they are cool and should be able to get them. I want to have them for anyone to take, but I would prefer to be more engaged and ask them to maybe play a game and get acquainted with the basic rules. I feel like a more personal touch would go a long way in creating a good customer base. Also, my first deck was one of those small decks. It had a vampire nighthawk in it and that's still my favorite magic card.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 16:07:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>What spells do you use? I was thinking about giant growths, perhaps a few overruns and something else that's pretty easy to understand.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 16:17:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. I was bummed about him not being reprinted in M14. Then, I saw what monoblack was doing and completely understood why.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 16:20:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I planned on having a "tutor tuesday" type of thing, where we post something on social media (most likely facebook) where we can be asked any sort of question and the events of the day can be geared towards newer players. I don't know how many people in the community would be willing to help be a "mentor" but if I can find the right type (and amount) of people to do it then I think it's perfectly doable. Thank you for your input!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 16:23:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. That took me a long time to find out as well when I first started. Nobody told me, for some reason. Do you think it would be smart to group things together in the speed in which they can be activated/cast? Mostly just meaning instants and abilities of creatures/enchantments/artifacts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 16:27:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>There is a place on the Short North called Kingmakers, which is a bar that has a huge selection of board games. I am not affiliated with them, I am opening on Hudson street, right off of High, close to jack  amp; benny's, taco bell  amp; goodwill. Edit: Also, I don't drink, but I still highly recommend going there. It's a sweet place and they sell all types of craft beer/soda as well as some sort of gourmet pretzel that is really good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 16:30:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is pretty smart, and definitely something I will consider doing. Thanks a bunch!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 16:32:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. In my opinion, the vast majority of the MTG community is made up of friendly, encouraging people but there are always bad apples and it's definitely disheartening when someone makes fun of you for being bad. We are going to be enforcing a pretty tight policy about that type of stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 16:35:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>do you think that placing a counter or die on the top of their deck to remind them up untap and do upkeep effects (if there are any) before they draw is a good idea?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 16:45:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. That's why I was so excited when I learned what makes Black tick. It was so cool to play sign in blood (even though it's a mediocre card, but that was way before I was introduced to the concept of card advantage) because I was doing something some other color was supposed to be doing. Hell, if your opponent can't kill you, your life is just as much of a resource as mana.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 16:48:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have been working on how to present the color wheel as part of the hook. I think that a lot of people will get pretty excited when they hear about whatever their brain tells them is fun. "Want huge creatures? Green is the color for you", etc.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 16:50:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 16:51:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is so unfortunate :( I plan on having small section of teaching talking about the value of cards and to be informed when trading.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 16:54:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. Coincidentally, stores make exponentially more money off of singles than sealed. For example, you can buy a box from wizards wholesale for around 75 dollars. You can sell that for, depending on the pricing of stores around you/what you would be able to charge, 15-30 dollars. There are stores that sell sealed product online that only make 2 dollars per box shipped through USPS. In most other retail markets, spending 75 dollars to make 2 dollars is absurd. Stores thrive on the sale of singles.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 16:58:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Wanna be ***that guy?***" Here's your very first blue deck! ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 17:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I play a fair amount of blue as well. I just remember when I first started I would see an island and groan. It's still sorta the same way, though. hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 17:23:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Regeneration is ranked among the most difficult abilities to understand. I have been playing for a little over 2 years now and only fully understood it when I first started being interested in how the rules worked. It's pretty clunky. Same thing with protection, really. It isn't intuitive for my Soldier of the Pantheon to die to a Supreme Verdict, just to name one of the odd situations that arise with protection.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 17:35:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>On the corner of High and Hudson, right across the street from the goodwill and next to the gas station. We should be open within a month and should be hosting events almost every day, most of which will be MTG related but we're of course willing to do anything that the community has a demand for. Personally, I have always wanted to get into DND so we might have a DND night as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 17:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I meant to put that in, I will edit it now. Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 17:40:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Schrodinger's cards. That's the best.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 17:42:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I was specifically hoping that artifacts would be in the right place. I feel like they're so close to enchantments that it could get a little bit confusing. It's weird to see myself type the equivalent of "artifacts might be the second hardest card type to have a new player understand", but it's the truth.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 17:44:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you elaborate so I understand why you think this way?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 17:46:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Agreed. A large amount of what gets people hooked is the flavor of being a mage and slingin' spells. I actually want to try out a flavor tournament to where people who win in the coolest ways win some sort of prize or something. There would have to be some planning involved, but I think it would be awesome if it were executed correctly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 17:47:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a good way to look at it and to make it much less hurtful when a new player loses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 21:06:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stoneforge Games. We haven't got the signage up or anything yet, in fact the drywall for the space has just finished getting set up. We should be open within a month. It's on the corner of High and Hudson, right across the street from the Goodwill :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 21:08:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>As far as I know, no there is not. I know there is one farther east called the soldiery, but it's a pretty bad place to go and people are turned away by either the smell, the environment or the terrible attitude of the owner. Most people I talk to who have been there say that they would rather not play magic than go to the soldiery. Not that we went for opening a shop based on those opinions alone, but I do understand that there is a need for players within campus (and even around campus) to have a place to play some magic that is inviting and comfortable to be in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 21:15:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>The reason sealed product is cheap is because of competition. Before online sales (and in some areas) you can sell a box for 120 dollars and get away with it. In Columbus, boxes from an LGS should be ~100 if it's a standard legal set. Prices continue to go down though because a lot of online sellers are selling boxes for cheaper and cheaper. They make money off of the volume. I can't expect someone to want to buy my box for 30 dollars more than they cold buy it for online. Plus, the profit margin on singles is pretty great and labor cost is probably a bunch of friends sitting at a table, drinking soda (or beer) and opening packs or drafting. Most LGS' only even have sealed product to keep you happy and to support draft/prizes. An LGS should make more money off of a 15-20 card than they do a standard-legal box, and that's being conservative.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 21:23:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is really shitty. In an effort to curb that type of behavior in trading, I am going to be actively showing new players apps on their phones that can tell them the prices of cards. I would much rather not hace someone feel like they got ripped off. I know how it feels. I first started playing in Innistrad (played when I was 8 during 8th or 9th edition, all I remember is that I had a white bordered vizzerdrix) and I opened some packs and got a liliana of the veil. I then traded it to the resident shop swindler who traded me a ton of crap for it. I mean, 10 cards for a deck I have, for one card I don't even know how to use? Seemed good at the time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 21:25:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is very helpful information! Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 21:34:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/nocontext</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 21:39:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am glad to have been a part of it. I love the Magic community.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 21:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>May I ask what you didn't like about comic town?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 21:58:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're opening on the corner of High and Hudson, right by the taco bell and rally's. We should be open within a month. I would love it if you stopped by and checked the place out. I promise it will rule.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 22:01:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be awesome :) I am sure we will always be happy to have someone come in and teach some people the game. Yeah, the whole "activation cost" thing is a pretty tricky subject.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 22:04:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>We will be open within the next month. I am very excited about being a part of the local gaming community and I find it awesome that Kingmakers is around. I love me some board games.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-29 22:31:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can definitely do that! I look forward to it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-30 07:04:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am not worried about the Soldiery at all. Not only is the Magic community huge and needs more shops, but I haven't ever heard a good story about that place. I know that it will not be difficult to provide a much better atmosphere than that store.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-30 07:09:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I said wholesale, as in that's what I buy them from WotC for. Distributors are a little more. 85ish being common for the consumer just says how low the profit margin is on boxes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-30 07:14:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry for the late reply. It should be open within the next month!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-30 07:48:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Flavorfully, I side with Boros. I play with every color right now, but black is in almost every deck I have. :) Edit: How about you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-31 03:45:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that calling it "stealing their business" is not a good way to look at it. The Magic community in Columbus is very large and continues to grow every day. I believe that we can both be healthy and succeed in the environment we are in. Not only will we be another great hobby store in Columbus, we will be providing a non-soldiery permanent (eh, eh?) for people on campus to come play as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-31 03:45:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually don't know how to tag people :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-31 04:05:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, there's more to it than that. Mostly, the Magic community in Columbus is pretty huge and I think that from what I have seen at most shops, there is definitely room for more shops in the area. I think that our location in Columbus is special, as well. Being a 5 minute bus ride away, as opposed to a 10/20 minute drive to any specific shop is pretty good. It's not like I have anything against the soldiery, but there are multiple shops (which will soon include mine) that are much better in my opinion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-31 09:30:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>We have a website almost done, just working where we want things to go. It should be up by the time we open. As for the whole FNM thing, I completely understand. I do, however, know that people who only play FNM (myself included) are in the vast minority. Most players would love to have an event with any non-FNM supported format, along with events during the week for Standard/Modern/Limited/etc. I completely understand what you mean. I don't think that it will be an issue that some people won't come because I don't expect to be able to get everyone to come to my store. I do believe that we can get enough people to come to the store though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-03 21:41:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some time ago there was a WWE wrestler named Virgil who achieved an average amount of stardom in the wrestling world. He now attends conventions selling autographed pictures and nobody cares. Sometimes he will even set up outside if he, for some reason, can't get a space inside. There is even a website dedicated to spotting him. http://lonelyvirgil.net/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-05 19:21:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I most likely can't hire anyone right now. Also there are child labor laws that make it so we can't hire people that are too young.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-20 23:02:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go ahead and do that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-26 19:27:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Standard really isn't the format for combos. If you're going super casual, you might as well go modern and do one of the wonky combos there. Maybe deadeye navigator/deceiver exarch/gilded lotus combo. There is a lot more room to do cool stuff. Edit: Either way you go, Modern gives you more access to stuff that will protect your combo as well. If you still want to stay in standard with that combo, I would suggest that your blue is heavy countermagic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I participated in one of the biggest Magic: the Gathering tournaments of all time this weekend. In an effort to document it, I posed for pictures near people with exposed asscracks. I present to you Grand Prix Richmond Crackstyle.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-10 22:13:54</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-10 22:18:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. Show your friends. It's part funny, part social commentary and part PSA.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I went to GP Richmond this weekend and posed for pictures with people with exposed asscracks. Check out GP Richmond Crackstyle. (xpost-funny)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-10 22:24:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-10 22:32:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Whatever makes you happy, I guess.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-10 22:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>As usual, there are bad apples in the bunch but Magic players as a whole (especially ones who pay 40 dollars for an event and travel a lot [8 hours for me] to get there) are normal, perfectly fine smelling people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-10 22:42:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's what's up!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-10 22:58:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I play a lot of black. Black can do a lot of the stuff other colors can do, but at the cost of life. I look at life in magic as a resource. Winning with 1 life is the same, if not better, than winning with more life.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-10 23:19:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something equally unacceptable is having your ass exposed in a convention center with over 4000 people (only counting the main event competitors) in it. I can see where you're coming from but this is more than just about being funny. I hope that people will see this and think "maybe I SHOULD pull my pants up." There is no way (barring some sort of handicap) that they didn't notice this. Not doing anything about it is lazy, gross and bad for the community. Some people won't get into magic because of this type of stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-10 23:23:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I appreciate it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-10 23:26:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd rather spare the person the shame of being confronted in front of other people. Maybe this way they might be able to see themselves and understand that it's disgusting and that they should figure out what they need to do to change their habits.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-10 23:27:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not about being fat. It's about having your ass exposed to thousands of people and not having the courtesy to pull your shirt down or pull your pants up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-10 23:45:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>What would I get ad revenue from? I don't own Imgur.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 00:02:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I rap and also happen to love action bronson.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 00:04:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I couldn't find any. Believe me, I tried. I am a fan of diversifying my bonds.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 00:05:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>make sure to read the bones!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 00:26:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I played BW Tokens. Not the Wescoe list but one with Virtue and Bitterblossom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 00:28:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>freshbreezemovement.bandcamp.com. Supreme irony in the name, I know. Tell me what you think!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 00:39:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>For everyone making the Action Bronson comparisons (as well as a shameless plug), I also rap. Check out freshbreezemovement.bandcamp.com and let me know how much worse I am than him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 01:09:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 01:44:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I appreciate it a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 01:50:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I forgive you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 02:25:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! We have a friend of mine produce the stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 03:45:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's actually two people. I'm usually the lower toned voice and the dude I rap with is the higher toned voice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 04:36:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some context: part-time compared me to Bronson a lot and I posted my latest album on there. I was messaged a few times saying I should post here. I figured it wasn't recent enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 04:56:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's unfortunate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 05:05:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not your fault. I appreciate the kind words.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 07:25:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I've been straightedge for almost 7 years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 07:58:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have beard on my face too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 08:13:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know. I definitely didn't do it. It was deleted. The dude was really cool and I highly doubt that he had it deleted somehow. He thought it was hilarious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 08:20:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why can't you judge me on the content of my character and not by my beard (which clearly occupies my face as well)?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 08:30:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually just did about an hour ago!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 08:33:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I appreciate it a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 08:34:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am not the one talking about drugs in our rap. I am the other one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 08:40:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I'm a pretty cool guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 08:48:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, okay. You were talking about that guy. I thought you were talking about the guy I rap with, who references drug use a lot. I don't do drugs or drink. No offense taken, man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 08:51:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, I have tried. I used to be in the gym 20 hours a week. I got really strong and ran a good amount and lost a little bit of weight, but I never got below a certain weight. I have pretty good eating habits, I think. I don't know if there's something wrong with me but I don't like being the guy that goes "wahhh I have a thyroid problem" or anything like that but I most definitely don't eat considerably more than the average person. I usually eat once a day, and it's usually not really anything unhealthy (besides maybe high in sodium). I appreciate the compliment/motivation a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 08:52:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did this in between rounds. I went 2-4 dropped. It was my first Modern tournament and I didn't really know the meta too much. I played BW tokens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 08:53:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>63rd place out of 4300 people is pretty amazing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 08:54:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually don't know how to do that. I am sorry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 08:55:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I had a sinus infection while I recorded that, it was pretty bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 08:59:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>It doesn't have anything to do with me being fat. Anyone who thinks that this has anything to do with their weight is insane. This is about having the common courtesy of not having your ass exposed when you're sitting down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:00:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>My mom always told me to go outside and come back when the sun comes down.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:00:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>fuck yeah dude. fuck yeah.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:06:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I appreciate it a lot. Making music is fun and it's good to hear that people like it. It's all free to download, too. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:06:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you very much. I am glad that you feel that way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:07:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tattoos.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:07:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! Some nice old lady told me they looked like Lake Michigan recently. I don't know why they specifically look like lake michigan, but at least it wasn't lake huron.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:09:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I appreciate that a lot. A record deal would obviously be pretty cool. hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:10:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know how to feel just now. I appreciate your words hahaha I wish you the best of luck in continuing your exploration of your sexuality.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:12:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish. He steals all of my ideas. He pretty much made it impossible for me to "make it" in hip hop without being called "Action Bronson lite" or 'Diet Bronson" or some shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:17:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did poorly. Went 2-4 drop to watch my friend in a feature match. I played BW tokens with Bitterblossom.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:20:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I said "one of the". I know that GPLV was bigger.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:32:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:34:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's the ocarina of time from the Legend of Zelda.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tight, thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:36:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, we drove almost 8 hours to get there. It was a great time. I like traveling a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:45:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>fucking fashion police?! I don't know what the last guy did but I am not making fun of these people for dressing the way they are. Their asscrack is exposed. That has nothing to do with fashion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:46:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm wearing jeans. Also, like I said before, having your ass exposed has nothing to do with being fat.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:48:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I appreciate it a lot. I expected everyone to talk shit about it, considering the insane amount of downvotes and criticism I am getting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:54:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't really care about what he said. He is not very informed, so I can't expect him to have an informed opinion.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:57:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you very much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:57:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the advice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 09:57:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't wear black to hide my weight. It's pretty clear that I am huge. I like black.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 10:12:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I could somehow transfer it to you, I would. I don't care about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 10:39:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you very much:)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 10:49:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I appreciate that a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 10:57:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did pretty poorly. BW tokens doesn't produce enough threats. Decks like Jund/Pod fuck me up with abrupt decay and maelstrom pulse. Plus a lot of people were running Engineered Explosives in the sideboard. Tokens isn't big, so it couldn't have been tokens. It was my first Modern event too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 10:59:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate that!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 11:02:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ruffles are underrated. I dig it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 11:11:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you mean?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 11:13:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I played BW tokens at this event. Mill is shitty in 9/10 situations. Kill spells and hate are obviously good, and aggro with Xenagod isn't really that powerful of an aggro deck. I'd rather play a lower curve and play better cards.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 11:17:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you very much :) I really appreciate it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 11:24:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well, I've been recognized multiple times already besides only being in the basement of a bar and my house. It's going to be really weird going to events now. hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 11:28:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's wrong with me having knuckle tattoos?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 11:32:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty poorly. I dropped at 2-4 to watch my friend play a feature match. I was goign to play all day, though. I have never played a Modern tournament before that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 11:40:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I find it pretty funny that I am being insulted pretty harshly. It doesn't bother me, but it speaks to the hypocrisy of Reddit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 12:01:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. I don't know why so many people are compelled to ask this, or why it matters, but yes I have. Sex is pretty cool. You know, you just feel some boobs and they just feel like... bags of sand?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 12:02:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hell yeah! That's what's up. Keep it up, dawg.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 12:04:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well then I would suggest you go get another one. I rock this shit, b.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 12:07:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, all funny stuff aside, I think you and I need to have a talk. I am not your fucking guy, pal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 12:44:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm wearing jeans, and my beard clearly occupies my face.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 19:34:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why would you type a P.S. as you're actually typing whatever you're trying to say to me? That seems a little odd.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-11 23:47:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was actually by his request that it was taken down. I didn't even know about it until it was pointed out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-12 07:16:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think that I am a kid. :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-12 07:30:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate it. I think I had cool things to say, too. This whole thing is pretty crazy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-12 08:19:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I don't know why everyone jumps to that conclusion. I am obviously not making fun of fat people. It's also crazy how many insults I am receiving over this. It doesn't bother me (mostly considering that my beard occupies both my neck and face) but it's still pretty crazy to be persecuted for how people perceive what I did, while also being insulted so harshly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-12 08:31:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would like to think that I'm a pretty cool dude as well! Also, that doesn't sound creepy at all. I appreciate it a lot. They're real too :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-12 23:24:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know, right? Thanks for letting me know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-13 03:28:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually live in Columbus. I was just born in Delaware.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-13 04:10:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not yet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-13 07:34:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for telling me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-13 19:14:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I see everything! Thank you very much :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-14 17:16:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you think that if I were banned (as of now I'm not ) that I would have to stop altogether? That's not the case. Competitive magic is 1/10th of the magic I play.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-15 09:49:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is unfortunate for me that I have been banned, but I understand. I also understand why my actions were harmful to the community. However, I do believe that I helped start a dialogue about appearance and hygiene when attending events (and in general) that I believe has strengthened the community. That being said, I do not regret what I did. I will have a great 18 months, and I hope you do too. I really appreciate your approach. I have gotten a lot of pretty harsh messages (including multiple death threats) and I appreciate someone talking to me about this in a mature way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-15 11:12:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know this was 4 days ago, but I wanted to tell you that I believe you're the first person that got what I was doing. You rule.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-15 12:20:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>hahaha y u hatin son? u mad cuz im stylin on u?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-16 02:10:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am convinced that you don't have a sense of humor. I'm sorry, male man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-16 08:22:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha dawg you don't have to be so aggressive. You should learn to take a hint. What you say doesn't bother me. Go do something worthwhile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-16 22:49:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I won't even front: that's some good hardstyle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-16 22:52:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's mostly "I want to put a bullet in your head" stuff. You know, the funny kind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-16 22:54:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Enjoy the front page!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-17 03:20:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's not very nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-20 10:44:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Semi-fame is weird. I can't say I don't think it's funny that people recognize me for something as stupid as this, but at the same time it's odd knowing that somewhere, someone is making my face into coffee art. [coffee game major](https://scontent-b-ord.xx.fbcdn.net/hphotos-frc3/t1.0-9/10001561_714249985292571_1095225850_n.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-22 02:15:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't call the top guy's beard "manly", but I agree that mine could be a lot better. I'm just trying to work with what I have, dawg. Thanks for the laugh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-22 02:21:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>You make me feel like a man among men.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-22 05:46:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's not very nice!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-22 07:41:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's also not very nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-22 09:42:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I go to a lot of shows. My favorite hardcore band is bodycount.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-22 09:53:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, it's pretty bad. Cards just keep going up because of how many people play. I'll say this: you should get back into it. You can make sweet decks for cheap and play with your friends. I'm a pretty frugal dude and this is mostly what I do. Power level is relative to your environment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-23 01:38:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love you too, mysterious internet being!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-24 21:18:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I try not to reply to everyone that mentions me so I don't look weird. hahaha anyway, I appreciate you defending me. That being said, I can't be your dad. I know nothing about adopting/parenting a dragon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-25 00:03:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks a bunch, I am glad you like it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-26 00:27:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't have stems right now but I could get them. PM me the ideas you have.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-26 02:55:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>There were 4300 people. I bet you could find 16 dudes that like it when girls shit on their chest if you felt so inclined. I didn't mean for this to make it seem as though a large amount of people look this way because they don't.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-26 05:09:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahahah my dude</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-26 05:12:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>PM me and let me know what's poppin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-27 20:46:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I walk with my feet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-31 02:52:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>You might!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-01 19:09:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been straight edge for about 7 years. Edit: Typo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-02 00:04:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would advise you not to. I have been involved with straight edge and hardcore for a long time and I know a lot of people that regret them. I am not saying you'll sell out, but if you do you'll have to get them covered or live with them. Both options suck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-09 09:22:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, dawg!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-09 12:04:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would like to share with you something that has helped me in times like this. Someone who impacts your life will never truly be gone as long as you live with the lessons they taught and teach them to others. I offer my condolences and a shoulder to lean on if you need someone to talk to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-10 02:40:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't, sorry. Maybe I should.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-12 04:53:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha whattttt?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-12 04:55:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Indeed it is true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-12 08:02:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you live in Ohio, we can make the arrangement. Where I'm from though we have a tradition of an exchange of dowry. You must supply a few cows or something useful before we can be best friends.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-14 05:20:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You already have one, my child.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-14 05:22:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was going to post this. This shit is gross.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-17 22:18:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kid r u mad cuz I flex on u wit my internet skilz?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-17 22:21:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, this is pretty tight. This justifies drinking so much coffee that I feel like coffee. Now I've actually been coffee.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-17 22:53:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait wait wait people can see what I'm subscribed to? I'm fucked. Hahahahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-17 22:58:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>By the power vested in me by being the subject of this thread, I pronounce this comment to be super shitty. Boooooo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-17 23:03:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Huh? The coffee art is dope. Making fun of someone because of their occupation is not dope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-18 01:08:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's pretty alright. Coffee art is cool but people staring at me all the time when I'm out is weird. But its whatever. To anyone who sees me in real life: just come up to me. I'm a nice dude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-18 04:51:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Show me!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-18 05:01:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have already commented on this thread, yo. I saw this picture like a month ago haha thanks for thinking of me  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-18 09:46:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not looking for the acceptance of anyone who thinks my intentions were to bully or shame players. What I did had negative repercussions that I had not thought of at the time and it's unfortunate that people feel this way, but that doesn't mean that I'm some prick who was making fun of people. I stopped associating myself with the general magic community not because of the smell or how the people look, but because of the sexism, elitism and ignorance that plague it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-18 09:51:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be undeniably the coolest thing of all time. I support terrible decisions. Hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-18 09:54:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn dude you already own a high school? That's way better than being on time.com.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-18 10:38:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I want you to know that this ban doesn't affect me in the slightest. I will never be away from the game unless I become uninterested. I don't understand how it's okay for these people to let their bodies pour out of their clothing, and then claim they're "supposed to be able to feel safe" when it's brought up. That's honestly an absurd argument. I understand your general perspective, but the whole "sacred gaming hall asscrack sanctuary" point is piss poor. How about these people take responsibility for what they were doing instead of blaming me for other people seeing it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-18 11:06:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not trying to make fun of the guy. I'm just trying to explain why I feel like he is wrong about the situation, and also that how he feels about me as a person doesn't matter. I don't know how to say that in a way that doesn't make me sound like a dickhead but that's how I feel. I wish he could channel is hatred for me into something positive. Edit: "make fun", not "mane fun".</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-18 22:32:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha that is so dope. Send some to me and I will sign them if you want.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-19 05:09:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not Shane.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-19 05:10:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I need to set up a P.O. box. I'll do it tomorrow dawg.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-19 16:13:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know, right? What a fucking prick. I can't believe you'd do something like this, OP.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-21 10:09:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sucks that you're the type of person that would/wouldn't do something solely based on other people that do/don't do it. Boo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-21 10:13:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who is your daddy and what does he do?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-21 10:16:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't like hats.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-21 10:17:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love you too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-21 19:20:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>So is this Blake or something</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-22 06:33:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually do rap. freshbreezemovement.bandcamp.com. check it out!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-22 22:29:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could look at it that way, yeah. Although it's not against "drugs", since a drug is just something that affects how your body operates when ingested. It's against alcohol, cigarettes and drug abuse. You can PM me about it if you have any more questions. Edit: didnt finish writing before I sent my comment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-23 10:39:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks dude! I appreciate it a lot. It's all free to download as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-23 11:40:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a sweet show at Carabar on Friday with some heavier bands. One band I am going for is Colors (colorsoh.bandcamp.com) and its free admission and you can be under 21. PM me if you want more info.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-23 22:51:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Love is hard to understand, my friend. I'm just glad you enjoyed them. Stay pimpin, playa.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-25 22:00:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not a Christian. There are more religions on Earth than your own, yo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-26 04:05:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hell yeah it was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-28 00:39:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha this rules</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-28 06:51:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel good. I live on Earth. I have a roof over my head, access to water that won't kill me, access to doctors when I am sick or hurt and people that love me dearly. I'm pretty fucking stoked on life, yo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-28 07:07:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go to your doctor and see if you can get Euphoria injections. *tips fedora*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-28 07:10:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Rapping with action bronson or throwing a huge pizza party. That shit would be dope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-28 09:19:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm just a human being, homie. I'll be a legend once I actually do something to improve the world besides make people laugh (not that isnt also important). Now that the world knows that I'm a comedic genius, it'll be much easier to raise millions of dollars for some dope ass charity or some shit, you feel me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-28 12:38:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Stores have offered to let me do one but I'm not trying to put them in that position just in case some dickhead tells Wizards about it. I can't buy one either. I'm pretty broke right now. But hey, thats life. I'll be able to do one soon and it'll be all good. The new cards are dope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-28 12:51:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have to come to Ohio, but hell yeah you're invited.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-28 13:06:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>See? You get it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-28 15:47:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>What, pizza parties? I'm insulted that you've never invited me. Hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-29 00:03:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't drink, but I'm down to kick it and drink some delicious coca cola and play some magic while you drink beer and play some magic. Haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-29 01:59:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can get to Canada from where I am in only a few hours, if I am not mistaken.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-30 03:36:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yo, I'd like to offer to help. As well as being an emcee, I also play a shitload of games and dabble in writing dialogue. On top of that, I am reddit famous. Not that that means "let me help I'm special", but if something were made of it I am sure it would get a significant amount of exposure it wouldn't have normally gotten.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-30 13:27:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man, this is a good fucking comment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-02 23:59:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Other people's asses.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-03 02:50:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll never have wisdom teeth, which is pretty tight. My dentist told me I'd understand when I was older. Having seen a good friend of mine just get some teeth pulled yesterday because of them, I'm stoked as hell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-08 01:09:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>O u got me, clurt. U got me 2 a T.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-08 16:25:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pizza Joint is my spot. They have good prices and the pizza is pretty par.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-18 08:41:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha thanks. I'm just trying to do dumb shit in a state I don't live in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-21 05:24:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well nobody replied to me, which is some bullshit, but I ended up meeting some people and doing some dumb shit anyway. Just giving you closure since you're the only person that said anything haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-21 20:27:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I'm going to New York this weekend. If I do, do you want to hang out and show me some dumb shit to do? Haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-22 23:06:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know. I just kind of wing it. Hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-25 12:21:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, not all 12 million people that play Magic are morbidly obese. If this was an honest question, you are stupid. If this was an attempt at humor, you are unfunny. I don't know which reality is worse.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-25 12:39:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-25 12:41:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, that is my name. Good contribution.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-25 13:37:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't care either way, it was just a really terrible question. Anyway, thanks for the compliment. It means a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-25 23:58:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks. It is what it is, homie. I'll be able to play again competitively sometime in september 2015 so I guess I have something to look forward to haha Edit: autocorrect</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-26 00:00:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I got banned from playing in tournaments for a year and a half.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-26 00:01:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate the kind words. I'd feel more accomplished about all of this had I actually tried. I do shit like this all the time (and still do it) and never expected people to think it was funny.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-26 00:04:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why wouldn't you believe me? I'm not even the person that brought it up lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-26 00:35:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I'm definitely not bummed about it. I met the vocalist of one of my favorite bands (circa survive, if you care to know) last weekend and he knew who I was so that alone made everything worth it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-26 00:42:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>You made that? Yo this shit is dope. All of my friends had shown me this and I lost it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-26 00:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>The tekken machine at the pizza joint is broken. I would have shown you a Yoshimitsu game no man has ever seen before, so you're lucky. Also, I don't drink but you were in fact pretty plastered. Haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-26 05:10:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in Ohio. I was visiting for the weekend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-26 06:03:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am checking out the dream pipe EP, and man this is some dope stuff. I can't find anything that talks about if you're open to people rapping on your music for non-profit use. I would really like to make some songs with your music.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-26 11:54:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hell yeah. I'll let you know how things are going as I'm progressing. Do you have an email I could keep in touch and send you files with?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-26 11:58:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn. Here I was thinking I was a human being or some shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-30 15:29:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't know when I took them. Note that they're in different places, and the first and third one were taken about 6 hours apart.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-05 05:43:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>No it isn't. I took them 3 months ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-05 10:43:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-07 08:59:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't actually know. I should have a lot, shouldn't I? It doesn't bother me but I was always curious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-07 13:05:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't care about karma. Having the #6 post of all time is all of the validation I could ever need. Now I'm convinced that I'm a comedic genius, invincible and omnipotent. I appreciate your inquiry. I was wondering what was going on as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-08 13:15:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn dude, after the 1000th neckbeard comment, it somehow still manages to be original and hilarious. You'd be wise to expect the opposite, but you'd be wrong! . Recognize my genius and move on, dawg. I'm just out here revolutionizing the way the world views comedy and you're just out here mad because a neckbeard gets way more ass than you. DAE le troll amirite</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-08 13:16:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-10 19:25:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did you see if Deez worked?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-10 19:32:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn dude, you got him good. Next, tell him he has cooties. That will teach him the dangers of looking at funny stuff. I'm just kidding man. You're really lame and stupid for using "gay" as an insult. With all due respect (which is none), go fuck yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-10 22:13:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're not a nice person. That's not cool. You shouldn't be so insulting. Making assumptions about who I am based on how I look is pretty shitty as well. In any case, I still stand by "go fuck yourself" no matter how much better looking you are than me. I can tell you're a loser because you go out of your way to insult people on the internet. I can feel the "someone care about what I say" vibe from you, dawg. Do you think it's unfair that people care about what I say/do even though I'm a "fat sloppy looking virgin" and you have to rely on reactions to anonymous internet insults for validation? You could say, "if you don't care then why did you say all of that?", and that would be a valid response. The truth is that I care about you and I am worried. I hope you find something that makes you happy so that you don't have to lurk reddit and call people gay. Until then, go fuck yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-11 02:40:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha hell yeah, dude!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-11 09:36:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not active on Reddit so this is the only thing I get notifications for. XOXOXO, subject0 Edit: forgot a word.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-14 17:16:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha this is tight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-14 17:20:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry, but your friend is mistaken. I couldn't care less. I was on time.com. It was totally worth it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-14 21:16:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who is your friend? I'm curious about who thought I was bummed out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-15 10:44:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>As I've already mentioned, I am largely inactive on Reddit and this is the only thread I get notifications for. Even if that was not the case, there is no reason for me not to reply to someone if I want to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-15 10:45:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know two micahs. They're both cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-16 02:59:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn. I couldn't find any information about this. I was totally going to go.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-18 06:21:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg thx. A/S/L? I'm 14/f/ca lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-18 07:35:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>O I just moved there 2 ;) :) :p c:</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-18 19:04:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Find the original post. I took these pictures, I am the subject of these pictures and I posted them here first.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-21 01:59:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the kind words!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-21 04:29:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not my issue if you don't understand my intention.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-26 01:44:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Look at the date of the post. It is from 3 months ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-26 01:44:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm the original guy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-06 09:50:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude, I straight up cannot believe this. This is some funny shit. Hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-10 05:18:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's definitely not the original post. You're an idiot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-10 08:15:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>That post is attempting to make fun of me. I don't know how you assume that the post making fun of me came before the original post. You're actually an idiot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-11 00:50:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha alright then. Its definitely not a repost. You could just figure it out but you're not, so it's cool. Fuck it. I'm out here gettin it n u r juz hatin ok cuz im da bes in da intronetz n u r juz a pos bitchboi lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-13 23:58:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I got banned for 18 months, which was 4 months ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-14 06:49:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't do anything else on Reddit. I have an app on my phone so I can respond to people and track my post's progress as it climbs to the highest post of all time. My guess is that it will be there in two weeks. I'm stoked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-14 06:56:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Kind of. I played in a lot of small tournaments in my area but it's not that big of a deal. I still play a lot of magic. A lot of cool shit happened because of this post and I'm happy that people thought it was funny.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-14 10:48:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its labeled NSFW so for a lot of people it doesn't show up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-14 11:01:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I definitely care. I am honored to know that I helped someone in whatever way I could. It's good to feel appreciated. I appreciate you taking the time to talk to me. It means a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-15 09:24:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was removed because that's what he wanted. It's still on my instagram account (@immortalmessiah).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-16 05:03:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit. This means the world. Thank you so much. If you (or anyone else reading this, for that matter) want to, you can PM me and we can talk about whatever is on your mind. I'm honored to have been able to help you in a tough time. I love you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-17 03:56:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's been going up a few hundred upvotes a day.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-17 05:15:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha that's tight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-17 20:11:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>You imagined my asscrack hahaha fuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-24 23:09:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you don't want to czech it out, that's cool too. What's poppin this weekend? I'm going to Boston for another Magic tournament (even though I am banned). I don't plan on playing, but I'm gonna be fuckin around in the area. If you're in town, let's kick it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-24 23:30:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can still go. I have friends that are playing in the event and I plan on playing casually with people I meet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-27 03:37:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's the top post of all time now. SUCK IT LOSER HAHAHA</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-27 03:47:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha yeah it's pretty wild.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-27 03:47:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a great question that I don't have an answer for. Let me look and I'll edit the response.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-27 04:44:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes it is. Uhh xD lol ;p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-27 04:45:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm from Ohio. I went to play in a tournament.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-27 04:46:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>As far as I'm concerned, you and I are friends.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-27 04:48:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's crazy. I was signing people's cards and taking pictures with them in Boston which is around 800 miles from my house. It is pretty surreal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-27 10:19:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was a greatly exaggerated response. I thought the person was being irrationally shitty so I felt it would be funny to respond like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-27 10:22:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hell yeah. This is sweet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-27 15:18:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfortunately, it is true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-27 19:09:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I misread the question. It's an 18 month ban which was 4 months ago. It lifts some time in September of 2015.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-27 22:09:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really? I might consider it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-27 22:17:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, Gary.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-28 19:20:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>You talked me into it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-28 20:21:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>A few people that weren't involved noticed that I was taking a picture/getting one taken of me, but they didn't know what was happening. I think that it was in plain enough sight that nobody thought anything of it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-28 20:43:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not really. I was only near the people for a few seconds at a time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-28 23:03:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know. I never really looked into it. I don't care much, so it's never been a big deal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-28 23:26:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I got banned by the DCI, the governing body of MTG tournaments, for 18 months. It's shitty, but I understand and accept it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 00:30:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was really weird. Basically all of my personal information was found (which I don't care about) and a Verizon.net email account emailed me claiming to be someone in the DCI. It was really sketchy looking and I asked the person to verify their identity and they wouldn't. I had an period of 48 hours initially to explain myself. I spent most of it making sure that the person was even real. I ended up finding the facebook profile for the man that was allegedly emailing me and he confirmed that it was actually him. They didn't go into detail, they just told me that I was banned and that I could appeal it. I appealed twice only asking for the ban to be shortened and got denied. A guy who got caught cheating on camera in a tournament for money only got banned for 6 months and just won money at a tournament. That's what I'm most bummed about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 00:47:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>It hasn't yet. Overall though my life has changed a lot. I get recognized pretty much everywhere I go. It is pretty crazy. I was just in Boston at a MTG tournament (not playing, just hanging out) and was taking pictures and signing cards all day. It was wild. I used to get threats sent from deleted accounts. Now I get messages from people saying I stopped them from committing suicide. It's all just been really crazy. I laugh about it a lot because it's all so absurd. I've learned a good lesson from all of it, which is that everything we do has an effect on the world and that we are very powerful. Any one of us can change the world.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 00:54:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was sweet. It was my first Modern tournament. MTG has different formats (mostly limiting how far back in time you can use cards from, but also with banlists for cards that are too good) and they're all completely different. I drove for I think like 7 or 8 hours to get there and had a blast. Playing magic is a lot of fun. I did poorly, as expected, and dropped from the tournament because a friend of mine was playing a professional player and he wrote an article about how his deck was the most consistent. My friend beat him and we were stoked. Overall it was awesome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 01:08:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't play any online games right now. I've been playing fallout new vegas, clash of clans and pokemon emerald on my phone. I don't have the time to commit to become good at a game. If I did, I would play minecraft. I used to play on a server. It was pretty fun.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 05:27:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's how I feel as well. If I was banned for 18 months for this, someone who was caught cheating for money should have been banned for much longer. They set a disappointing precedence. Bonus reading material! Someone did something slightly related to what I did a while ago: http://legitmtg.com/culture/interview-with-gerald-freas-dr8sides/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 05:32:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>As of now I don't. I don't even think it's that funny. I thought everyone was going to think I was weird, but here we are! Hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 06:41:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not my responsibility to enlighten you. I've gone into detail numerous times over the last 4 momths about how I feel about the expectation of privacy at a highly publicized event that you'd need to sign a media consent waiver form to participate in. I do understand that there is an issue with the pictures but I don't think that I invaded anyone's privacy. As for why Reddit applauds it, I don't know. I don't even think the pictures are that funny.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 09:14:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha it was tight. It was weird that the character was telling me I was lying as if it mattered. People are crazy, yo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 09:14:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha it was tight. It was weird that the character was telling me I was lying as if it mattered. People are crazy, yo.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 09:16:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, you're a unique little snowflake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-29 23:21:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>"hero of time", from Zelda. The "of" is on my thumbs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-30 02:14:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>God damn right.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-30 12:23:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>The only thing I smoke r clownz like U on tha b-ball court. Just kidding. I don't smoke or drink, but I don't have anything against people that do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-30 22:22:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>All of my cards got stolen from me recently. Right now I don't own any valuable cards. I do own a set (4) of foil nyx-fleece ram, which is an okay card illustrated by my favorite artist. Her name is Terese Nielsen, you should check her stuff out if you're interested in things that look cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-31 08:54:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>In standard I just have super shitty decks. I have UB notion thief/whispering madness and I have WR Heroic. As for my collection, I had playsets of snapcasters and Liliana of the veil, some shocklands and a bunch of stuff from Terese Nielsen, my favorite artist. Signed foil enter the infinite, spanish buy a box promo birds of paradise, some other shit. Those aren't particularly valuable, but they meant a lot me. Such is life homie. Shit happens.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-31 21:58:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that's not very nice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-31 22:10:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am glad to have conquered test post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-31 22:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shit, chillin. Gonna go watch guardians tonight. I'm stoked. What about you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-31 22:13:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha thank you very much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-31 22:28:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those I know involved with magic were pleased. They're not people who would have their asscracks hanging out and dislike when others fly in the face of common courtesy by doing so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-31 22:45:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, they're definitely controversial. Haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-31 23:15:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think the guy's name is Andrew Shrout. He wrote an article saying that Storm was the most consistent deck and that there is no reason not to play it. My friend played UWR control and beat him 2-1. It was exciting.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-31 23:17:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, it's pretty sweet. Some guy actually gave me the last one I needed while I was in Boston. I had 3 and he made it 4. The reason 4 is the ideal number is because you can only play 4 copies of any card in a deck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-31 23:23:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I always answer these questions assuming the person knows nothing about magic. The article he wrote was really bold and, iirc, said there wasn't a reason to play any other deck. But he beat Zvi Mowshowitz, then beat Shrout, then lost to Patrick Dickmann playing RUG twin. Patrick was a nice dude.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-31 23:29:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anything that involves spending time with someone I care about. The perfect example would be playing magic, listening to music and enjoying beverages (soda for me). Or it could be going to a hardcore/metal show, getting pizza, setting dumpsters on fire, all types of shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-31 23:31:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>18 months.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-31 23:34:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you ever see me, absolutely haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-31 23:37:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't hold your breath. I most likely won't do this anymore but I think that I'm capable of doing things way funnier than this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-31 23:43:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd be slightly insulted by this if you weren't almost completely illiterate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-31 23:51:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's the only thing about the whole situation I'm bitter about.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-31 23:55:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't make an effort to spell shit correctly. I just do. It's not as if you have to "dress up" to be any good at speaking English. Bub u r dum OK lol wow haha omg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-31 23:57:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Word. I live in Columbus!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 00:02:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yea! She's cool. Do I know you, by chance?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 00:14:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>The bar was set kinda high before this too. Haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 00:31:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll be seeing it at midnight tonight. I'm excited. I've been reading guardians for a long time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 00:45:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did not call them. This is the email I received. https://twitter.com/subject0/status/494977098445246464</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 00:50:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>That guy fucked the story up. He delivered wings to a friend. There was a house show going on (basically a small concert in a house featuring punk/punkish bands) and the delivery guy asked for my friend. I pushed the door open and there were people jumping from couch to couch. It was tight. I then ordered wings from the same place and just walked to get them because the place was 5 minutes away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 00:52:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yup. You got me, totally dude for real</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 01:01:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Richmond, VA.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 01:17:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was visiting a friend at a bar and my friend's car got broken into. I had my decks and trade binder in a bag inside the car.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 01:19:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe that I looked at a real ban list and saw my name. I'll check it all again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 01:22:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.wizards.com/default.asp?x=dci/suspended This is the list on the Wizards site. Unfortunately, my name is on the list.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 01:24:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>My sense of humor is stupid. I do dumb shit like this a lot. I don't play any other tcgs but I don't really know of any others.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 01:26:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I still play. I just can't play in tournaments which was only a small amount of the Magic I play. I'd still rather play tournaments, but it is what it is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 01:28:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's a thin line between fries and shakes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 01:40:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't need any games. I don't play many video games. I'll just do it. PM me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 01:56:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe he has been banned multiple times. I'm actually not too educated on his ban history. I have only gathered information from the conversations I have had with judges about the situation.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 02:01:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha yeah this shit is tight. Is this from a show or anything?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 02:02:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hear it a lot. I also rap. The amount of parallels we have is incredible. I want to rap with him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 02:07:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>freshbreezemovement.bandcamp.com. Check it out! I don't really know how I sound. I'm the deeper voice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 02:46:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Buy Duel of the Planeswalkers on whichever game store you use. It's the best way to learn. Other than that, use decks you think are fun and don't sweat the rules too much. You'll understand them all eventually.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 03:21:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I attended GP Boston last week. It was a good time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 03:46:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I live 12 hours away. I went for the trip mostly. If you went to one you'd probably go to one closer than I did. If you don't have a deck, you will most likely have to spend a lot of money to get one unless you build affinity or something similarly inexpensive. If you have a deck, it costs 40 bucks to play. You get sweet shit for playing though, like an exclusive promo/playmat that you can recoup your losses with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 04:15:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you very much! I'm glad you like it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 05:05:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've had the dream to rap in an old folks home for a while. Just a lot of the ways he thinks as well. All of my friends say that if I were born in Queens I would be Bronson. Nothing against him of course. I just want to rap with him haha Edit: we have a Facebook! .com/freshbreezemovement</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-01 16:03:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you unable to read?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-02 23:03:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think you're the first person to ask me this in all of reddit. I am part of a rap duo called Fresh Breeze Movement. My "rap name" is OB1. My username says OB1 of the fresh breeze movement.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-03 07:29:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you very much! I'm really glad you like it. I don't believe I've heard of either of them. I'll check them out for sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-03 07:30:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been meaning to. I might as well since I can't play magic competitively.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-03 15:13:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The test post is no more. I have dominated the internet. Your puny test post is blackened by the shadow cast from my boot. Test post asked me to open my heart drive and find a mercy file and I spoke three words before ending its reign : File not found.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-04 04:36:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was banned for 18 months.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-07 14:20:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nm, chillin. U</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 11:58:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yo! What's up?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 19:08:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too. It's pretty cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 15:21:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Who are you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 15:26:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can find this picture (as some random loser did) on my instagram at @godofthegame Edit: To clarify, OP is not in this picture. OP is a leech who is using my content for useless internet points. Edit 2: That's a joke. I'm joking.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 15:46:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I cared about karma, i would be pissed. My shit is low for having the top post ever. Fuck it. I'm out here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 16:26:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Body Count is one of my favorite bands. Represent, dawg.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 16:58:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>These are dope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 17:08:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's the fact that someone from where I live (who most likely knows me) has been posting pictures of me on the internet and not telling me. I'm not mad. I'm just explaining the situation because I think it's dishonest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 17:11:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>AY WASSUP DENNY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 18:15:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ayyyyy what's up?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 18:49:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 19:19:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>You get it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-10 04:54:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>There several comments talking about it. I'm not going to go through 6k+ comments to find them, but I screenshotted one. http://instagram.com/p/qfvWJ7lgTd/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-10 05:48:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apparently so.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-10 06:18:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's hard to accept your compliment when you're calling me a neckbeard in the same sentence. Classifying me by how I look is shitty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-10 13:01:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have to bring a lot to the table. I'm the funniest person of all time. Hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-10 18:30:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're attempting to attract me with your cooking skills, it's working.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-10 20:19:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ship one to Ohio. Consider it dowry. Hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-17 02:42:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Create something better.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-17 03:52:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree that it's stupid. If you look at my profile, you'd see that I was largely inactive before this post. I did it because it's funny to me. Internet points don't matter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-20 04:50:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a good question. Right now we're in the middle of writing more music. I don't know when it will be out, unfortunately. However, both of us are also involved with other projects that are coming out soon. I can PM you when I have more information if you'd like.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-23 05:49:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha this is tight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-27 08:00:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mostly, yes. There are shitty people in pretty much every "scene" or culture, including MTG players. I don't really play with them besides in tournaments (which I haven't been doing since being banned) and you just beat them and move on. Overall, I believe that the community is mostly full of sweet people.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-03 11:21:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen coffee art with my face on it, I've seen a comic where Mario is made to look and pose like me, and I've seen a picture of Joel from the last of us posing near a clicker. That's all I've seen so far but I'm really interested in seeing everything people have done because it's dope to see that kind of shit haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-05 03:58:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unsporting conduct - Ballin 2 hard</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-15 09:39:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>She didn't reply to me. I guess we will never know what magic we could have created.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-17 02:35:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>For age? I'm 23.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-27 09:34:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>My instagram is godofthegame. Prepare yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-29 04:05:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha this is tight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-29 06:37:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I still went there to hang out and trade people. I didn't play in the tournament and still can't play for another year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-29 07:08:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Are you a judge? I talked with a few judges as soon as I got there pretty much. I also saw a dude in a full army uniform when I was near the mall. I'm curious as to who you were. In any case, I'm sorry we couldn't talk in person. :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-29 07:16:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>This girl worked at a restaurant I have been going to for a few years. She has since moved. She was really cool. I get noticed all the time. It's pretty wild. I can pretty much go anywhere and someone will come up and ask to take a picture with me, even if it's just something like a convenient store. I appreciate the kind words. Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-29 07:17:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I get to hang out with your dog, I'd consider it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-29 07:46:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's weird that this is what I'm internet famous for. I do a lot of stuff that I think is way funnier. I should probably get to recording it. I'm glad you'd be my friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-29 08:32:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually burnt some of it earlier tonight. I put on corpse paint with some friends and we fought with lit torches. Tomorrow I'm going to survey the damage. Hopefully, some of the beard is able to be salvaged. I love you too man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-29 08:41:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have an instagram. @godofthegame. As for other things I don't really have the means with which to do anything the way I would want to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-30 06:06:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm interested.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-01 13:18:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>People don't really know what to do most of the time. I just tell them to do what feels natural and that I'll do the same. It always comes out perfectly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-03 16:08:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Land destruction is so shitty now. *sigh*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-05 10:46:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so sweet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-07 08:21:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't play anymore. The servers were getting terrible and I got caught up in Magic because the new set came out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-07 13:44:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well executed, OP. You could have done whatever you wanted but stuck with the classic hand-over-fist. I'm proud of you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-08 11:23:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would call it a hardstyle/rap squat hybrid.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-10 12:23:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>This dude I know has some pretty absurd names for cards. He is a pretty wild dude. RTR block had some hits including Electrobutter for [[Azor's Elecutors]] and Black Spatula for [[Sepulchral Primordial]], leading our LGS to refer to all of the Primordials as spatulas. Theros didn't have too many hits besides Xanax and Klonopin for [[Anax and Cymede]] and George Polukis for [[Polukranos, World Eater]] . Khans has Brand Name Aspirin for [[War-Name Aspirant]], Grim Hairy Sex for [[Grim Haruspex]], and Riverbend Aereloa for [[Riverwheel Aerialists]] and a bunch of other stuff. As for me, my friends and I mostly just use real names for cards that sound similar, like Tony Dungy for [[Dungrove Elder]].</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-13 08:46:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Our hair is dark and we both have bad beards. Other than that we look nothing alike. I'm shocked that anyone would actually wonder if we were the same person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-13 09:50:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I resemble another human. That's a damn good joke.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-13 10:14:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I understand that you don't mean any harm. The joke just isn't funny. It's cool though, I don't really expect anything else from r/funny.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-13 10:26:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Its cool dawg. This was my first time seeing the video though, its not bad haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-13 11:12:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell him i said what's up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-28 15:10:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Since he was at 8 life this doesn't matter but after God's willing resolved the hammerhands would have fallen off of favored hoplite. Anyway, that's shitty. In any case, you still won (assuming that the soldier token was from akroan crusader or was otherwise red). The guy either knew what he was trying to do or is not willing to understand the game. In either case it's sad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-29 00:18:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I'm the neckbeard that created and posted the top post of all time. This person is just someone who talks about being affectionate with a cartoon character.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-04 20:58:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hit the Marcus Crosswoods pretty much every Tuesday and catch a movie. It also has free popcorn which is dope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-04 21:33:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been going for around 6 months and it has been in effect since the first time I went. If it were to stop it wouldn't be a deal-breaker but it's sweet that I don't have to spend more on popcorn.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-06 02:39:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>All you have to do is get a card and register it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-10 10:52:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something that I didn't see mentioned was that priority does not get passed when a cost is paid. Adding or removing counters to activate an ability of a planeswalker is considered paying the cost (to be the boss) and cannot be responded to. An opponent can respond when the ability is put onto the stack.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-14 05:07:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha shit, this is dope. I'm amazed at what people put next to my face.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-20 04:15:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Me too, dawg. Me too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-29 19:37:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why was I invited to be a mod of this sub? I don't know what's going on here at all.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-29 19:43:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this subreddit really only about you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-29 19:55:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do I know you? Why would people randomly post on this subreddit?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-01 06:48:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol ya is 4 reel me u can tell bi tha way we look sumwut semaler lol u got me gulpeg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-12 08:14:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>WHAT?! hahaha is this a joke? I can't tell. I only commented because I was confused as to why someone I didn't know invited me to be a mod of a subreddit about them. It didn't make sense and still doesn't make sense. I can't tell if you're fucking with me or not and it's hilarious. You're a funny dude, Joe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-17 23:39:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I realize that I am late to the party here but this is by far the funniest thing I have ever seen on reddit. This should be the top post of all time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-22 04:54:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>How long am I waiting for?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-22 05:02:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>How do I do that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-22 05:08:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're being too pushy. I'll just trade with someone else.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-22 05:11:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's not uncommon andI don't want to trade with someone as unpleasant as you. I hope you find what you're looking for.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-22 05:18:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're being very impatient about me adding you while I'm cooking dinner. A HA torchic is not uncommon and I feel like a 4IV bagon is an unfair trade for it, although I did offer it but mostly it was for people who had both torchic and shuckle. I was and am still willing to post proof of its IVs but it will be to someone who isn't a douchebag.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-22 05:23:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for telling me. I was willing to do it anyway because I want the torchic and shuckle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-22 05:33:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have a heart scale with your name on it. Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-22 05:38:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>That suits me well. I'm adding you right now and then hopping online. Edit: I'm giving it to the 4IV bagon. Thanks for your help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-22 05:52:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's fine, thank you for your help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-24 08:26:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Intentionally withholding a "scene" where the characters find the solution to a major problem for no other reason than to have it be the twist is the easiest way to ruin a movie for me. A good example is Ocean's Eleven. I feel like there is no good reason to leave the fact that they filmed the heist in the fake vault out of the movie until the end other than having it be the twist. If I were following these people trying to figure out how to do it, I would rather see them come to the conclusion and plan it. Another example is Fast Five. I can't really remember too many of the details but they were planning an escape for the big heist and they had an issue with a low bridge. They end up having some sort of system where they take air out of the tires to fit the vehicle through. I should have seen them come to that idea. I think it's lazy writing and it will make me feel like the whole movie was a waste of time even though everything before that could have been incredible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-25 22:57:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>No I'm not. I'm not involved in this at all. You can be whatever you want, I don't care</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-25 23:15:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>You too, Joe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-30 12:45:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you play constructed Magic? Swiftspear is a 4-of in tier 1 modern and legacy decks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-24 19:27:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm late to the thread and similar opinions have been downvoted, but I am in the mood to express myself. The video is cool but I would much rather have their resources put into better stuff. I only watch them one time when they first come out and that's because I'm craving more information about the story. We're getting sweet prerelease events, more GPs, streaming, stores are now getting more FNM promos, all of this sweet stuff (and more) that they're doing for the game because it is so strong. I'd rather have something that will make my game experience better or have a long lasting effect. If you love the lore, they've been beefing up uncharted realms articles recently. Maybe you can check that out sometime; they're awesome. TL;DR: It's unfortunate that we didn't get a trailer but the resources that were put into it are most likely being put into cooler stuff.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-24 20:10:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Your insight is terrible. Prize support is strictly up to your LGS. Wizards even gives your LGS free booster boxes when they get their prerelease boxes. Those prerelease boxes come with a foil promo of a card (which in this set could have been worth up to 45 dollars), 5 packs of cards and the clan pack, which is value at that point alone. You also get a cool die and get to participate in the event activity, which in this set was the ugins fate booster where you got 3 of 26 alternate art promos (which are all valuable and the alternate art ugin is worth over 100 dollars). You then have a chance to place in the tournament and get more free cards. Back when they did textless player rewards, they didn't do nearly as much as they do now for the players. They spend so much money to keep us interested in the game. What other game does that? Don't get me wrong, I want textless promo cards as much as the next guy but it's asinine to think they are doing less for us now than they were in the past.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-24 21:25:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Depending on how much you can get boxes for, you can just buy 3-4 ugins instead of buying a box.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-27 06:02:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was actually just online and was told I needed an admin to change my time played. Whenever you can hop on, let me know so I can hop on and get everything changed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-06 01:13:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd also be interested in the story behind Mardu Shadowspear, but mostly because I'm interested in Mark Poole's future with illustrating Magic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-10 11:19:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there any way I can help with this? I can't go but would love to contribute in any way I could.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-14 20:23:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>They were false at the time, but not now. I have since been banned from playing magic in tournaments for 18 months</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-14 20:24:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>You've always got my love.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-14 20:33:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's over on September 14th. I do not plan on taking more pictures :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-14 20:46:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't do anything else, it just took then time to figure out what to do I guess. I don't know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-15 11:31:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, that's the only thing it affects. I still go to tournaments to hang out and trade cards. Once I travelled from Columbus, OH to Boston, MA to go to a tournament I couldn't play in and ended up leaving the event because the organizer was on some bullshit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-15 11:38:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that they banned me for a valid reason. My intent wasn't to bully or harass anyone, as I've explained in detail multiple times when answering this question.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-15 11:39:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't drink, but I'd love to come down and kick it. If I'm ever in the area I'll message you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-15 12:34:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Say it again somewhere else in the thread, two times wasn't enough. Make sure more people know what your opinion is because it definitely matters.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-15 22:26:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>My opinion matters because I'm the one who did it. Your opinion doesn't matter because you're a random person. There are lots of people who disagree with what I did who aren't posting their opinion multiple times in one thread for attention. I've stated before that what I did was wrong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-16 00:04:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for your input</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-18 10:28:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like even though my intentions weren't to harm the people in the pictures, I did. I thought it was harmless and in good fun, but people were hurt by it and that definitely sucks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-19 18:17:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can't fathom how many times I get asked this every day. I don't know anything about their karma system.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-21 12:05:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel no different. I was on time.com which is a pretty cool accomplishment.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-21 13:52:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gurmag Angler I think seems better in the deck than Tasigur because it makes it easier to cast two creature spells for vengevine. You can delve for it and then be able to cast gravecrawler as a second creature spell if it's in the graveyard. It also favorably blocks 4/5 goyfs, tasigur, siege rhino and whatever else something with 4 power couldn't kill. It's also important to note that its not legendary. I've found that the one extra mana is not relevant in most cases. Source: I also play dredgevine.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-21 13:58:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is probably bad advice, but if you mean "counter" in the biblical sense, there's a black counterspell in modern. [[Dash Hopes]]</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-05 05:16:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone who would actually confuse this dude with me is an idiot. 1/5, poor attempt at low hanging fruit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 08:00:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Having fun" for some people is playing a technically tight game of magic and being rewarded for being on top of everything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 08:02:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does it change anything that rebound is a "may" ability? I read that judge procedure was to assume the player chose not to perform it if the missed trigger was a may ability.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 09:16:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Out of curiosity, what's your interpretation of disruptive?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 09:31:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>They can read the cards just the same as I can read mine. They're still playing incorrectly if they're missing their triggers on their own cards in their own deck. I'm not sure if any good/honest player plays a certain way assuming their opponent will miss an important trigger. I'm playing the devil's advocate mostly to say that the idea "you're here to have fun, let them get their triggers" isn't correct because your fun isn't equal to anyone else's fun and vice versa. You can't expect anyone to get out of magic what you get out of magic. To some, like myself, the fun in the game is knowing the rules, playing the game within the rules and being rewarded for it. If I make a mistake or miss a trigger, I don't call a judge so I can get it. I played poorly and will face the consequences. Ultimately, the rules enforcement level is the deciding factor in any situation like this so what we think about missed trigger etiquette doesn't matter.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-20 09:40:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>You'd let someone put their rebounded [[Artful Maneuver]] targeting the creature not being blocked onto the stack for lethal damage because it was still their turn?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-23 20:57:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wanted to learn how to play Magic before i started so I went to the lgs near where I had grown up. There was a guy there who had just bought 2 boxes of Innistrad. He took all the rares/mythics and gave me all of the commons/uncommons. 3.5 years later I'm still playing. Now whenever I get bulk shit like through boxes/fat packs/drafts I make sure to give it away to a newer player that would use the cards. It's funny to see how when you're new it's almost a blessing to receive them and when you've been playing for a while it's easier to give the bulk away than it is to transport it home.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-30 10:05:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>U my dawg for this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-05 13:27:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some of these answers are no good. [Here is a list of magic slang.]( http://mtg.wikia.com/wiki/Slang) Some of it you'll never hear but most of it is pretty on point. Edit: By no good, I mean they use terms OP wouldn't understand or have explanations that are completely wrong. Since OP doesn't know what aggro means, you can assume he or she doesn't know anything at all. How can a player who doesn't know what aggro means understand what someone means when they say "generate value", "fat threat", "milling", etc.? Someone said midrange decks "can be seen as decks with big dumb dudes". Someone said that blue is commonly found in decks that get big creatures out early. Someone said that burn decks are close to combo decks. These are all irresponsible things to tell a new player because they're untrue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-18 14:06:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>So you believe that a deck you literally built in less than an hour (that pro players/builders have already tried to make viable) is a tier 1.5 deck in modern based on you piloting it to a top 4 finish at your local FNM? [That's a pretty farfetched claim.]( http://img2.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20140810002816/pokemon/images/2/21/083Farfetch'd_Dream.png)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-18 20:29:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you have any meaningful results with the deck beyond your local FNM top 4, or at all? Could you provide anything to convince someone that you're not just another kid that's overzealous about his shitty deck? If you've brewed with hall-of-famers can you explain why you take such a leap of faith when describing it as tier 1.5 without any results besides top 4 at a local FNM? Can you explain why none of your HOF pals never did anything with the card but you seem to have realized it's potential? Are you better than them? Do you deserve to be in the hall of fame? Do you expect people to blindly believe you and start building the deck you made (and boarding against it) in the future just because you said it's as good as you believe it is? Do you think that you're a good player just because how long you've played for? Do you think you're good enough for anyone to give a fuck about you or anything that you do? In short, you seem like an asshole. Your answers here make you seem not like a well-adjusted person who has played magic for 20+ years (and I guess other stuff) but an emotionally immature person that cannot accept criticism or have a meaningful conversation. I feel sorry for the people who have to deal with you in person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-19 12:34:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Awake by Tycho and Minecraft.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-29 21:49:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sup</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-01 00:33:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha this is incredible. Thanks for this, OP. I'm going to post this on my instagram, which is @biblicalfigure if you were curious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-01 00:43:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm always here for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-01 01:03:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>...but why male models?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-01 01:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I listen to Emancipator as well, but my Minecraft playlist is Pelican, Harvard, Tycho and Nujabes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-01 01:53:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>If someone talks to me, I'll respond to them. I originally commented a week ago. Cry about it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-01 10:52:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not anymore lol sucker</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-12 17:12:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a time to be alive. Eternal playable FNM promos the 2 months before I can play tournaments again. hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-31 01:11:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so sick. I'm proud of you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-31 01:12:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a 1/2 for 2 with downside? Unplayable trash.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-31 01:16:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're the best. If you do any more stuff like this, PM me. I always get a kick out of it and usually post stuff onto my Instagram which is @biblicalfigure. Keep on stuntin.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-31 01:17:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ayyy it's all good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-31 09:21:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I appreciate it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-31 09:23:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's cool, I wasn't being serious. Well, I was serious when I said the card sucks, but in a joking manner. I appreciate you taking the time to make the card in any case.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-31 09:24:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Slap a rancor and a daybreak coronet on me and I'm not half bad.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-31 09:26:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's the thought that counts!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-02 06:49:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you ask everyone who they are? Why does it matter if I'm the guy on the right or not?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-02 06:52:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate it. I'd rather have fun and be able to laugh at myself than be shitty all the time. With all the hate mail I get, I'd have a hell of a reason to be shitty. I just read it with my friends and we laugh that some dweeb took the time to try and make me feel bad. It's pretty funny.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-02 12:38:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn, good thing I'm not some worthless piece of shit then, right? You sound like a prick. It's not my responsibility to enlighten you on who I am. If you want to know something about someone should figure it out for yourself instead of pretty much asking them why their opinion matters. Maybe you weren't trying to come off as insulting but tying my significance to my presence in this picture (and others) is pretty lame.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-02 16:32:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's not true. We're both human beings which is enough to be able to do what you want without being questioned.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-02 19:09:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't mind my erect penis.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-04 07:22:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh it's true. It's damn true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-04 10:02:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're playing a sealed prerelease strictly to open value in your box it's probably not going to go well. Why wouldn't you want a better card for the format which would give you a better chance at prize packs?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-04 10:38:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree with you on all of those points. It's probably the best way to do things now the way they are though, all things considered. They switched it to random promos because the promo cycle wasn't balanced. In m15, some promos were much more playable than others. I'd probably rather have it the way it is right now too because I think they're missing the mark on what people want with promos. For example (although not really related), fnm promos have been pretty on and off since they started, from frost walker and encroaching wastes to stoke the flames and path/visions. Ideally we would all be happy but it can't be the case and unfortunately for the casual people, being able to play your promo in the event is going to top all of our concerns about value, monetary or otherwise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-04 10:41:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure. I believe I went over this a bit before when this picture first got put up (9 months ago) but this woman worked at a restaurant I really like. I frequented it and they all know me, so when the internet stuff went off they were all super stoked. Lauren, the girl in the picture, asked me for a picture with her. She asked me what she should do and I said "do whatever you want, I'm sure it will work out just fine" and this is what happened. She said she was moving and I haven't seen her since. She is pretty cool. I wonder if she knows this picture has been posted a billion times lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-04 10:55:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's definitely something they're trying to figure out. I also happen to like promos because I can pick up sets of foil cards that I like for cheap over the weekend. Ideally we'd have eternally playable promos useful outside of the one event but there's no pleasing everyone and this seems like the good way to go. You might open something sweet, you might not. Playing with a good sealed card is probably worth it more to newer players than getting a cool card (best case scenario something like a PW or high profile mythic that will see play, worst case some straight up bullshit) that they can't play. The newer players win that one since they're the one buying all the packs and shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-10 10:14:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't necessarily call it difficult to tell who illustrated a card. You can tell if a card is illustrated by most artists with other cards to compare to. You can tell if something is done by Chan, Hamm, Nielsen, Murai, Swanland, Cearly, McKinnon, Walker, Reynolds, Mohrbacher, Kopinski, etc. if you know their style. Some artists without a track record kind of blend in to a degree but to call magic's art homogenous is pushing it. Once we get more pieces from the new artists we'll be able to notice their art before looking at the artist credit too. As for the mediums in which they illustrate in, khans block had an abnormally large (which will hopefully become normal) number of pieces made with only physical mediums. For some reason there is a stigma around digital painting but the quality of art is at such a high level that it's hard for me to find anything to complain about (besides not liking a few artists). I understand your point but I think that things are pretty good where they're at. I'd rather have mostly everything looking really good and have to really evaluate their style to appreciate it rather than have stuff be all over the place and some of it be shitty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-11 04:55:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>What order so you suggest we play them in? Should we create separate characters or stay with Pash, Oskara, etc.?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-23 00:12:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone had this as a mat? I want to see it too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-23 00:16:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah this was from my Instagram.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-04 05:59:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're all respectable. I can't pick a favorite. Just know that you're all keeping the spirit alive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-05 02:07:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>This looks tight. My friends and I have been trying to find a DM in the Columbus area because we really want to do this. You're the best.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-05 08:17:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're my dawg. This is tight hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-05 09:45:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate the kind words.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-09 03:22:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks pal. I'd like to think that I'm both a cool dude and at least pretty decent at playing magic. Being banned from playing tournaments sucks but it's nothing compared to how my life has changed because of my post. One of the coolest things about it is finding people whose lives I have touched in some weird way, so thank you very much for the kind words.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-31 04:10:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're my dawg for this. I'm glad to have touched the lives of so many hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-31 04:13:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's true. I even drove from Ohio to Boston to go to a GP I couldn't participate in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-01 08:45:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm in Columbus. Come getcho ass whooped.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-02 04:51:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get a lot of messages. When I'm unbanned I will start playing competitively again. The break from tournaments has been refreshing (especially on my wallet) and has sort of rekindled my love for magic as more than something to be competitive in. That being said, I'm ready to go to an FNM with some shitty black deck and do poorly. It's gonna be sick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-10 04:08:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I swipe right until they run out. You denied me. WE COULD HAVE BEEN EACH OTHER'S EVERYTHING.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-10 04:29:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been estranged from most of my family (my brothers included) for almost a decade exactly because of stuff like this. You're really shitty for putting my family's business on the internet and also for grouping me together with them. I've never stolen from you and was never rude to your parents.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-10 04:32:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work security at Ledo's on the weekends.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-10 04:36:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Identity confirmed. That's me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-10 04:46:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm single n redi 2 mingle hmu</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-10 04:48:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not annoyed. It's pretty cool lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-10 05:04:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha you are so mad at me. That's pretty tight. You even said you'd spit on me. I'm gonna tell my dad about this. Edit: Yeah that picture is sick, thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-10 05:31:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I underestimated just how mad you are. You're probably fuming behind your computer screen. You finally got to tell me personally how you feel. That's tight. Too bad your opinion doesn't matter to me. U r just hatin bcuz I am stylin on u n evry way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-10 05:33:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've seen you in my dreams.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-10 05:37:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the kind words.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-10 08:24:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm proud of you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-10 08:30:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could at least take me to a movie first. Hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-10 08:48:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>A friend of mine and I went to LA/SF last July for independence day. A tree fell and knocked out our power so we decided to drive to the east coast. It was pretty sick. I want to be living in LA before the year is over.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-10 08:51:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't drink alcohol but I'd be down to grab a ginger ale or some bullshit like that. Haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-10 08:52:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell your mom to hit me up. I wanna see those pictures.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-10 09:15:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>u c me out here gettin mines</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-11 03:57:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bruh y u hatin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-11 04:02:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>For moms? Yeah.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-11 04:07:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you actually want it I'll pm it to you. I prefer psychological thrillers and romcoms, but I'll watch anything really.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-11 04:07:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you ever had a broccoli pizza? That shit is phenomenal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-11 04:10:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't tell you what the name stands for unless you're in it but it's tight. It's a magic crew.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-11 04:13:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Send a self addressed stamped envelope with some shit in it to Hobby Central in Delaware, Ohio and I'll sign whatever you want.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-11 04:16:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>IGET HOEZ</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-14 07:53:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-16 03:57:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>You all make me so proud.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-22 08:45:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was playing Gatecrash prerelease. I was playing with some dude for top 8. He was playing gruul and I was playing boros. It was game 3. He was at 13 and I was at some amount of life, I can't really remember, it was kinda low. I had a [[boros reckoner]] on board with a [[martial glory]] and [[scorchwalker]] in my hand. The dude had a scorchwalker on board. He attacked with his scorchwalker and I blocked with the reckoner. Before damage I cast martial glory, making his boi an 8/1 and my boi a 3/6. I then bloodrushed my scorchwalker onto his, making his boi a 13/2. Damage went through, reckoner took 13, my opponent took 13. I beat my opponent during his own combat, which is by far the coolest way I will ever win a game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-22 09:52:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're a dawg. This is sick. 10/10 expression. I am proud of you. Thank you for fighting the good fight, brother.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-23 03:50:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, its gonna be sick. I can't wait.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-23 11:19:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll answer any question you want. Well, almost any question.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-23 20:36:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>1: I played it like 15 years ago but stopped when I moved away from the place I played. I randomly had a thought about ~4 years ago to get back into it. Now here I am. 2: I'm into a lot of stuff. Music is big for me. Indie, funk, hip hop, jazz, alt rock, folk, metal, hardcore, etc.. I haven't been really traveling lately but I love doing it. I like stars. When I'm free I hit one of a few spots at night sometimes and kick it and check them out. I like writing. Recently i have been unable to write anything but I normally write a lot of poetry and hip hop. I like animals, pro wrestling, engineering, architecture, getting laid, all types of shit. 3: Right now, Noah Gundersen has been in constant rotation with Nujabes, Tides of Man, Sugar Glyder and Harvard. 4: Creation and achievement inspires me. It's so sick that we can think about pretty much anything and make it, or think of pretty much anything and we can do it. That shit gets me excited.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-24 10:10:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the kind words. I lightly follow WWE and even less so UFC but I've always been a fan of lesnar so I know a bit about the crossover situation. I think his presence brings legitimacy to pro wrestling. That's pretty much all I've got on that. I wish I could help more.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-24 10:17:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't seen villainous wealth putting up any results since this thread so I came back to check on you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-24 23:59:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh hell yeah, this is sick. What's next? I can't wait to see. You all make me proud.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 01:12:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's sick. It's pretty sweet isn't it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 01:27:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fuck yeah. I can't wait either. My ban will be lifted by the time it comes out so it's gonna be a good time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 01:28:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 01:54:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I must not have seen it. I really only get on Reddit when I get mail. I'm sorry. I just checked yours out and it's pretty sick as well. I'm proud of you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 01:55:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. In a year and a half, you're the first person to tell me that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 01:55:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah I got banned but it's up in less than a month.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 02:17:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Where u @ bruh, swang thru n get this work</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 02:47:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jerks don't look as good as I do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 03:06:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a good question. The guy I make the music with and i haven't really been hanging out but I've been trying to find someone to do it with that has similar views on stuff. I don't want to do it alone because most of my enjoyment comes from creating it and that's best when I can share it with someone.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 03:07:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>The stuff that people think about the shop isn't really true, I just haven't wanted to talk about it because I failed. We ran out of money. It had nothing to do with me being banned or anything. Had we not ran out of money we could have made it work.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 03:16:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was being sarcastic. I've been told that I look similar to Jon Snow a million times. However, I never knew who he was before I was told that and I have never seen the show, so I did not intend to do that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 03:26:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're not upset with each other. We still talk from time to time. I just haven't been able to be creative lately so I feel bad. I'd love nothing more than to write music with him but I can't really create anything I'm happy with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 03:28:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm still allowed to go to events but I can't play in them. You should post on r/magictcg and see if there is anyone around you to play with.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 04:46:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree. I love more than just magic so I'm trying to make other stuff work out and it's going pretty well so far I think. Everything will be alright.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 06:14:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>And do what?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 10:35:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I already tried. Right now I'm trying to focus on getting on Twitch but there are some obstacles I have to overcome. I don't have a computer capable of running games but I've got almost everything I need for a nice (well, nice for me) desktop so I can start doing that. If that's successful it can finance the other stuff I want to do, which is a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-03 21:50:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're a dawg for this one. It's going to be a fun time getting a set of these. I can't wait.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-04 12:21:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just under half of your lands enter the battlefield tapped, which isn't ideal for a fast deck. I know since you have 3 colors you need dual lands but it's hard to be aggressive when you're essentially a turn behind if you play any etbt land. If you're trying to maximize damage output, you would ideally have 4 chief of the edge in the deck. Magmatic chasm can be good in the sideboard but it can be dead against some decks. Thopters don't care about it. You would be better off with cards that will always help you win. I would replace grave strength with another threat. If you cast grave strength targeting a creature and your opponent kills it before it hits them, you used two cards and your opponent only used one. You'd rather use cards that will never really give you the opportunity to get blown out like that. The same concept goes for any card in this deck that may have applications in some situations but not others or cards that "put all of your eggs in one basket". I play BW warriors casually. It's fun. Some suggestions I have for the deck include [[Battle brawler]] [[Blood-Chin Rager]] [[Goblin Rabblemaster]] [[Butcher of the Horde]] [[Lightning Strike]] [[Brutal Hordechief]] [[Kolaghan's Command]]</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-07 20:52:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Liliana of the Veil is pretty boring too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-14 08:16:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Right now it says I'm still banned. I'm assuming (and hoping) that it's because it's not midnight on the west coast. Edit: To everyone that looks at my twitter, I view twitter as a complete joke and use it for satire. What I say on it doesn't represent how I feel about anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-14 08:37:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>My twitter is almost 100% satire. I rarely use it meaningfully.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I'm no longer banned from playing in magic tournaments. I have risen from the ashes to defend my honor against the scrubs of Earth. Prepare yourselves.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-14 20:16:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-14 22:01:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tell your sister I said congratulations.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-14 22:32:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>HMU on Instagram: @biblicalfigure also I'll be playing the midnight at Saturday prerelease at Hobby Central in Delaware, OH if anyone wants to come thru and get whooped. Or whoop me. It could go either way but in any case y'all are my dawgs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-14 23:03:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm glad I could help, my friend. If you ever want someone to talk to our whatever, give me a shout.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yo, I'm the crackstyle guy. I got unbanned from playing in magic tournaments today, which is pretty sick. Ask me anything.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-14 23:41:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>A few people asked me to do this so here I am. If you want to follow me on social media, I have an Instagram @biblicalfigure and a twitter @ob1fbm. I'll answer anything that is a) interesting and b) not too personal. Edit: that's a lot of questions. I'll try my best. Edit 2: I have been streaming on Twitch recently. If anyone wants to check me out, my channel is twitch.tv/OB1TV. I'm usually on weekday evenings. Come through and hang out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-14 23:55:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, one dude told me that he became a local celebrity though which is pretty sick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-14 23:56:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>By a few people, yeah. I'm not worried about it. Everything will be alright.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:01:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am not a fan of any specific color but I like combinations, like purple/orange, red/blue, yellow/green, red/purple, stuff like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Every day of my life. It's pretty tight most of the time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:03:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Far and away, my favorite pizza is topped with broccoli.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:04:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>My plans are to travel to tournaments and do poorly but have a great time anyway. I don't plan on taking more pictures.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:07:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like a wide variety of music. Right now I am listening to a lot of Noah Gundersen, Tycho, Tides of Man, Amon Amarth and Bayside. I'm glad you like the game. It's pretty dope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:09:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually have a few. [Check them out.](freshbreezemovement.bandcamp.com)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:10:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll take a picture with you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:10:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>It feels pretty cool, I'd have to say.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:11:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't blame anyone for taking things too seriously. I probably don't take many things seriously enough.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:12:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>All the time. It's pretty funny to watch people get the courage up to ask me. I can totally tell when people are talking about me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:14:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>My first big tournament. I don't really notice it anymore so that's pretty cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:16:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Someone from the dci just asked me for my side of the story before they decided what to do about the situation. The identity of the person messaging me was sketchy at first but i figured out it was legit and emailed them back.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:19:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not ready for babies yet, but soon. But u ain't ready 4 me tho</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:25:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>U feel me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:26:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gangster rap and hardcore music.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:27:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I expected everyone to think I was weird. I had never really used Reddit and didn't understand the culture haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:29:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just did the first one and then the people kept showing up so I kept going. Then I dropped from the tournament and took up my day doing it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:30:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mostly play black but I do enjoy and play every color. Mostly with black. Haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:31:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>My favorite card is probably vampire nighthawk. It's not amazing but he is my dawg.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:32:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do security at bars. As for a real career I don't really know what I want to do.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:33:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh for sure. I like dgd a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:34:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>The ones in the Louvre and the tower of Pisa were sick. I have been wanting to go around the country/world and do the same thing but haven't really been able to afford to travel recently.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:36:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would do it in person. Haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:37:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>My fingers and thumbs say "hero of time" and an ocarina is on my hand, both related to Zelda games.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:37:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was just a length of time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:39:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, it was alright. It was a good 18 months.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:41:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like Nas, older Three 6 mafia, BIG, Snoop, Dre, shit like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:43:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have two tiny leaders decks but nobody plays anymore so I am currently venturing into EDH. I have no idea who I want to use so I am stuck as of right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:43:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't only have my hands tattooed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:44:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work on campus at Ledo's nights over the weekend. Come say hi and we'll chat and stuff. I'm jumping off cliffs during the day next weekend so I am booked.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:46:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is awesome haha you're a dawg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:53:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's sick. I'm glad I could help :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:54:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't drink but angry orchard smells good haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:55:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's kind of junky so far. There are a lot of garbage rares which sucks but full art basic lands is pretty tight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:57:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'd like to think I helped raise awareness. I don't know how much credit to take but even if it's not because of me at all it's pretty damn awesome.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 00:59:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't think about it until a few days later.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 01:00:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gengar or electabuzz. Hawlucha is a close runner-up. If only he evolved.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 01:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do it for my people. Yes, I'm a fan of metal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 01:02:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't smoke any weed, so 0.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 01:05:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish. I'm bad at basketball but I feel like a giant bipedal lizard has to be even worse than me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 01:08:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I failed. :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 01:10:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Come through hobby central on a Friday or Saturday afternoon and I'll be there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 01:13:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm single but Tinder is going pretty well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 01:13:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am 24.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 01:14:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Like, if I could travel through time and make the decision again? Absolutely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 02:23:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope. We ran out of money. Contrary to popular belief, it had nothing to do with me being banned.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 02:25:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't heard it all but I really like the songs I've heard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 02:30:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>1) I've already explained that in the thread 2) I have never had surgery 3) I'll give it a shot. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 02:40:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm playing super Mario maker with some friends right now. I'm excited to go jump off of some cliffs tomorrow so it's gonna be icy. I don't drink so I don't have much to say about my favorite.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 02:45:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do not want to buy your magic cards. Travis Scott isn't bad. I can dig it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 02:49:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>It wasn't that big of a deal. I normally do pretty well in my opinion but in bigger tournaments I never really did too well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 02:49:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm a baller and a shot caller.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 02:54:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I started playing in innistrad which has been my favorite block so far. Return to ravnica was pretty tight too.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 02:57:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>O u kno I feel u</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 02:59:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I'll sign it in person.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 03:07:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amazing. That gets me so excited. What a time to be alive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 03:08:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't want him to get in trouble.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 03:08:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do security at bars. I have plans for the future but I'd rather talk about them when they're happening.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 03:10:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's pretty awesome. I have a good laugh with friends every time I see something that references the post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 03:13:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I'm there every weekend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 03:16:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't really eat Pringles but I would probably like the salt and vinegar the best. I like vinegar.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 05:23:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>That would be a pretty funny story. I'm in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 05:24:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh I'm finna.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 05:25:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Show me a picture when you do it. It will be so sweet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 05:37:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>My dad thinks it's pretty sweet. My mom is indifferent. My brothers aren't impressed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 05:39:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm into everything really, but I don't have any decks together besides casual standard (bw warriors and mono b) and tiny leaders (varolz and yasova).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 05:42:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like the acacia strain. I'm hanging out with their guitarist right now, we're playing super smash brothers. I like born of osiris, those are my dudes. I also like Slayer, Amon Amarth, all types of shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 05:49:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>He is currently unlocking ness with Luigi.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 05:57:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can if you want, I don't mind.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 06:04:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love cholula. I always have a supply on deck ready to roll.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 06:18:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, I ran out of money. I work at Ledo's mostly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 06:18:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>OB1 is my rap name. FBM stands for fresh breeze movement, the name under which my friend and I make music.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 06:48:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm in. I PMed you. This is absurd lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 06:55:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can be whatever you want!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 09:25:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I stand corrected.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 09:36:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not really. I get why they did it. It's all good, no hard feelings. Whoops. Didn't know I already answered.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 09:55:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>On the tour that's coming up? I'll be at every Ohio date.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 10:22:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've never been to an icp concert. What did I say about slivers?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 10:26:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not too many. TUI, Alpha  amp; Omega, and a few others. I'm mostly into local bands and anything else I can see live. I don't really listen to it much when I'm about and about but live shows make me feel alive. Ya boi gets lit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 10:26:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're in the area, sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 10:27:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I appreciate it a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 10:28:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll be playing the battle for zendikar prerelease as my first event.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 10:31:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I played when I was younger and a few years ago just decided to get back into it. I thought to myself, man, it's probably crazy now. So I went to my lgs where I used to play and a dude gave me a bunch of common cards and I started playing from there. The art is sweet and the game is challenging. I'd suggest to get into it. If you need any advice, hit me up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 10:31:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, look at the silver lining. At least a bunch of people pretty much told you that you're hot as fuck.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 10:33:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I would probably consider myself a better tempo player than anything else. My least favorite archetype would probably be aggro.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 10:34:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 10:34:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have no clue.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 10:34:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah probably not. Why wouldn't you just ask him?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 10:36:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually did one when my original post made #1 but I guess they didn't want me there because I am strictly internet famous. For now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 10:38:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, definitely.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 10:47:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not good with names. I heard a song with Snoop on it that was really good. I heard one with Kendrick which was pretty tight as well. I think that's all. I am about to buy it right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 10:50:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I mostly play at hobby central in Delaware.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-15 14:45:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>One of my brothers said (paraphrasing): "the TIME website is okay, but it's not the magazine. People don't read news on the internet. If it's not in the magazine it won't resonate with anyone. Let me know when you're in the magazine."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-16 00:11:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>It a combination of myself, a friend of mine and self timers. It was mostly me setting my phone against my bag and hoping it worked out. There were a lot of outtakes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-16 18:46:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-18 21:11:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure I've ever hung out with anyone who wears a spongebob hat or shirt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-22 01:33:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh shit, this is tight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-22 03:28:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>No matter how internet famous you may or may not be, I'll still love you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-27 23:54:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>No. I logged in a while ago and gave someone all of my stuff and logged off. It wasn't a good fit for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-27 23:56:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did a prerelease at midnight on Saturday. I got a few good cards but no support so I was pretty much forced to play BR with no big winners. I went 3/2 for the night.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-27 23:58:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you very much. Save your money dawg, the kind words are more than enough. I'd way rather you just download it for free if funds are tight. Just enter 0 in the price field and cop that shit, player.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-27 23:59:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why don't you try and figure it out for yourself? It's not hard.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-27 23:59:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>What's good player</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-28 07:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am actually setting up a channel to start streaming. I haven't played much hearthstone so I don't have competitive decks or anything but I figured it would be fun anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-28 07:02:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, it was pretty damn dope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-28 07:03:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know. I've never been there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-28 07:16:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sent you a PM. I have no idea what I'm doing lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-28 10:44:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not trying to be a dick. It says what I'm known for on reddit (by pretty much everyone on this site) in the title of thread. You could have googled my reddit name or the term in the title, or gone to my profile or gather some context in the comments. It's not my responsibility to enlighten you. I feel sorry for you if you feel like you're entitled to that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-28 20:51:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, it *is* pretty clear. If it isn't to you, that's not my problem.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-28 22:35:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's some nice grass. Hahaha this is sick. It's unbelievable how inconsiderate babies are.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-29 07:53:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't really remember how I explained it but I made sure to do so in a way that didn't incriminate anyone else. They mostly wanted to know who was with me and who took pictures and stuff like that. Someone at some point had implied that a few friends of mine were involved and they were not, so my side of the story was mostly "nobody else was involved."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-29 11:25:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>That isn't it at all. It's more along the lines of "figure it out for yourself". It has nothing to do with how many people have heard of me and everything to do with you thinking that you're entitled to me qualifying myself to you because you didn't know who I am. I am not here to hold your hand and be your guide to the internet. I'm not interested in talking about this anymore so I'm not going to continue but if you have something to tell me, feel free to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-07 06:49:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>10/10, I am proud of you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-07 11:07:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh Dave, you know you're my dawg.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-07 13:41:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not a fan of horrorcore in general but stuff like old Triple 6 (mystic stylez) is tight. I'd consider the at least somewhat similar to horrorcore. I probably also only listen to it because I like the three 6 albums that came after so much. Brotha Lynch Hung is skilled in my opinion but it's not something I listen to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-07 15:04:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get notifications from my Reddit app onto my phone. When someone mentions me or messages me with a link I check it out. I sometimes ask people to tag me in these pictures because otherwise I won't see them since I'm rarely on. I make an effort to comment on them to show appreciation because it's tight to have people do this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-18 00:33:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was playing bw tokens. Bitterblossom had just been unbanned and I wanted to play it so I figured that was the best bet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 00:10:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha you people are crazy. This is so sweet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-23 09:39:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Also, her ex (now not ex I guess) is a guy I consider to be my brother.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-26 01:52:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have so many rare pepes that I might fuck around and put them on eBay for like, a couple million.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-26 08:14:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha seeing stuff like this makes my day. I got shopped next to a picture of a starfish. What a time to be alive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-27 03:02:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hell yeah. It was nice meeting you. I'm glad you had a good time! Edit: shameless plug: if any of you want to watch me play video games, [I have a twitch channel. Come check your boy out.](http://twitch.tv/OB1TV) I also have an [Instagram if you want to check that out as well. It's pretty tight.](http://Instagram.com/biblicalfigure)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-27 03:24:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've only played the BFZ prerelease since my ban was lifted. Working on the weekends conflicts with my schedule and makes it so that I can never play FNMs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-27 03:34:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, you can not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-27 03:36:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I plan on doing stuff that is way cooler, you just have to give me time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-27 04:56:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>No, you can not.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-27 05:22:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I played some BR bullshit that didn't have any good cards lol my pool was pretty much complete garbage. I got 9th so it must have not been too bad but you know what I mean.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-27 06:31:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! That means a lot. We have more music on the way.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-27 06:50:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have only played sealed once and haven't drafted personally but it looks pretty cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-27 06:52:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't drink, so I guess that's PJ's by default. I can't wait :) haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-27 07:24:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, I haven't been there in at least 3 years. I think the sandwich I had had chicken fingers, fries and mac n cheese on it. It was immaculate.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-27 07:25:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I just started streaming so I'm not really sure what I'll settle with but the last two times I did it I played rocket league. I'll probably play the shit out of fallout 4 when it comes out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-27 08:16:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just started playing it. It's definitely fun but probably just a placeholder until I find something better. That something better may just be fallout 4.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-27 08:25:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm actually very new to PC gaming as a whole (besides having played Minecraft for like 5 years) and I'm concerned that I'll be garbage at using a keyboard and mouse. I might as well try but I sometimes get intimidated because I know that people that are playing now have years on me and that I won't be good enough to be competitive.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-27 08:29:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>He asked me to take it down. He had a lot more to lose than I did because his livelihood is based on his ability to be involved with competitive magic. I didn't want to be responsible for anyone else getting in trouble.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-27 12:16:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I have a few albums out with a friend of mine with more music coming out soon. Check them out.]( https://freshbreezemovement.bandcamp.com/album/black-holes-blasphemy)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-27 13:19:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have one more that's on my foot, but other than that, yes I only have my hands done haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-27 13:28:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've only done it a few times. I played fallout 3 the first time and have played rocket league since. I am thinking of playing hearthstone but I do plan on playing a lot of fallout 4 when it comes out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-28 23:03:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have my condolences, dawg. I'm glad I could help. Hit me up if you ever need anyone to talk to.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-30 12:56:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so awesome. This shit gets me so excited to see. I wish I could actually go there. Cracks across America. It's genius.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-02 19:13:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha that is fucking amazing. I am honored.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-03 16:32:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah that was me lol that game is pretty alright.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-05 00:39:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahaha this is sick. You are buck wild. I never thought anything like this would happen but here we are. 10/10. Edit: if anyone cares, I am about to start streaming some Rocket League with a friend. [Come chat with your boy.](https://twitch.TV/OB1TV)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-05 00:55:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope that you can find it in your heart to forgive me. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-05 02:32:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol bitch I might be</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-05 06:49:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have! I'm a big fan of the two BG commanders. Also the zombie dragon fucking rules. I'm into it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-05 07:08:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not familiar with twitch at all really. Do they allow that type of thing?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-05 07:37:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh that's sick. I'm gonna light them up tomorrow like there is no tomorrow.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-05 09:35:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>$12.50 is mad money? Shit, I'm not doing as badly with life as I thought I was.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-06 06:46:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I got a gift box and it didn't have 2500 cards in it. What the hell WOTC. Edit: it's sarcasm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-06 07:11:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I should have specified that I'm being sarcastic.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-24 17:31:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't used it at all except the first mission and when I find a frame while exploring and don't want to stop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-06 09:52:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol this is awesome. I'm proud of you. Funny bit of information for you, sometimes I go to comic book/anime conventions (I think maybe 4-6 since the post) and pretty much every time I wear the same outfit I did on that day when I took those pictures. A few people have told me that I don't have the look of the real guy. A few have also told me that my tattoos don't match or that they're poorly drawn on. It's pretty funny. Anyway pal I am happy that you did this. Thanks a bunch.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-09 19:23:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about Baneslayer screams value? Would you rather pay 5 mana for nothing or 5 mana for 5 life and a 3/3 in the worst case scenario?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-09 20:14:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, the downside for Baneslayer is borderline infinitely higher because there is a huge possibility that it will do nothing for you besides cost you 5 mana. I'd rather play a 5/3 vanilla creature that gives me a 3/3 and 5 life if my opponent has any competent removal than a 5/5 with a bunch of abilities that gives me nothing if my opponent has competent removal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-13 12:48:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I work at a bar on the weekends so I have the resources to mess around with stuff. I also don't drink so I've been figuring out the best stuff I can make without alcohol. The bar I work at stocks Gosling's ginger beer (nonalcoholic), which is a spicy ginger ale. I have a 12 oz cup, fill it with ice, squeeze 1/4 orange into it and then fill it with the ginger beer, but any ginger ale will do and orange juice will also be fine. Sprite with the sweetened lime juice is good. Dr pepper and grenadine is good. The important thing is that you're doing a good thing for yourself and nobody should feel like a reject for that. You're there to be social. What matters is that you have a good time. There is no shame in not drinking alcohol or drinking water or whatever else you want. As for the cheapskate aspect, I know that the bartenders at my job appreciate people that don't drink at the bar. However, the work they're doing for you is pretty similar to what they would do for you if you were drinking alcohol, and in some cases more (getting a bottle from a cooler and opening it vs getting a glass, filling it with ice, using the gun for soda, waiting for the fizz to go down, pour, wait, pour) so tipping them is the right thing to do pretty much no matter what you get. TL;DR: ginger ale and orange juice and be a dawg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-24 15:52:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah. Furthermore, pseudo lifelink stacks but actual lifelink doesn't. Say you had a [[souls of the faultless]] enchanted with [[armadillo cloak]] and [[unflinching courage]], it would have two instances of pseudo lifelink (triggering under different conditions of course) and one instance of actual lifelink. Even furthermore, pseudo lifelink is a trigger, which goes on the stack and can be responded to. Lifelink is not a trigger, does not use the stack, and happens simultaneously as damage is dealt.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-28 18:57:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude, hell yeah. 10/10. You got him good, my brother.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-29 15:04:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy shit. This is the best thing I have ever seen. I am deeply honored.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-12-29 15:16:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks pal! You're the best.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-14 04:50:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're the best.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-14 04:53:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a time to be alive. Thanks for carrying on the legacy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 11:11:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Present them pics, player.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 11:12:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol hell yeah. This is tight. 10/10</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I met Rick and Morty this weekend. Rick was wasted.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 13:05:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 13:07:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>/u/TrentSack is one of these people. I don't know who the other one is. They both have sweet costumes. I am proud of them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 13:11:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're a damn animal!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 13:39:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know it broh. Edit: If y'all wanna follow me on IG, check your boy out @biblicalfigure. Prepare yourself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 14:14:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was at Ohayocon over the weekend. I live close by so I go and kick it and try and get into some trouble when it rolls through.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 14:16:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>It feels pretty cool. Say your prayers and eat your vitamins or some shit like that, you know?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 14:34:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not afraid of anything but holding babies.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 14:37:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I went both days and didn't count on Friday but Saturday's count ended in the 190s for pictures.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 14:40:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am actually cleaning up a verse I just wrote about an hour ago for a song on our new album. If anyone is interested, [I rap with a friend of mine. Here is an album. There are three more if you like it and they're all free to download.](https://freshbreezemovement.bandcamp.com/album/black-holes-blasphemy)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 14:56:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>The reaction is mostly positive. I only go to a few stores where most people know me or at least know of me. I have had a few people air their grievances with me but it is what it is. I don't really play in tournaments anymore anyway.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 15:24:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I walked up to them for a picture and they lost their minds, telling me they were looking for me all day. They were the best rick and morty so I had to get a picture. They had to get one as well. As we were taking pictures a whole bunch of people came up and asked for pictures and everyone ended up taking a huge group picture. It was pretty cool. As for the poses, I never really tell anyone what to do. I ask them if we're smiling, if we're kneeling, whatever. It doesn't really matter to me. This specific picture was one for them that my friend caught, I believe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 15:26:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh it's true. It's damn true.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 16:24:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was pretty cool. I was in the rave for a minute and quickly realized that raves aren't my bag, but it was tight to see in any case. I admire the cosplays that people make; creation in any capacity is dope.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 16:26:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not recently, but once our new album is closer we will announce something we have been planning for a while.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 17:14:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do not but I'm sure I could listen to them and write them down sometime soon for you. 2 of our albums are all original, as well as the upcoming one.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 17:45:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>You can use all of Mutated Mechanics and all of Earthbound as much as you want, just credit us and show me the video when you use it. The other stuff you have to use at your own risk, seeing as how not all of it is original. The new album will also be free to use with credit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-20 19:16:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>It is a Nujabes track! Thank you for the kind words :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-21 06:45:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! I've been straight edge for ~8 years.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-21 07:45:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're a dog  #128054; #128054; #128054;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-22 07:34:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are the best, thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-26 11:37:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've recorded a few songs in that studio a few years ago. The computers there only have garageband. It's free to book but you do have to book it in advance, I don't really know how in advance though and we were only able to use the studio for an hour. Also, their microphones weren't the best but all of the information I just gave you most likely has changed since I was there. The dude I make music with mentioned that a lot of people booked the studio to record rap.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-29 13:13:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>This looks pretty cool. Thanks a bunch!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-31 09:08:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-01-31 09:37:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol this is tight, thank you for sharing.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-05 09:26:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so sweet. Thank you so much for taking the time to do this. It will help my group out a lot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-20 17:06:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol you are a damn dog! This is sick.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-22 08:39:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're an animal  #128054;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-26 05:39:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am looking for someone to scratch over some songs for an EP I am putting out with a friend of mine. [Here is something we have done in the past, but what we've got coming up is a lot better. I can show you unmixed recordings of it if you're interested.](https://freshbreezemovement.bandcamp.com/album/black-holes-blasphemy) We can collaborate on ideas to make it sound sweet. Hit me up.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-02 08:49:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm part of a duo looking for someone to collaborate with, involving some scratching on a few songs and make some dope shit. We already have an EP ready to release and ideally I would like to add some scratches before it gets sent out. [Check us out.](http://freshbreezemovement.bandcamp.com/album/black-holes-blasphemy) We would love to contribute to anything you are involved with if you'd like as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-07 15:39:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>When I pick a beat, it's usually me just going through beat tapes on MHH. It's not just the one beat on the tape that does it, it's more of a cohesive feel throughout the production. The project I completed recently is exclusively produced by u/HobbesDuende and I plan on having most projects exclusively produced unless we're explicitly going for a mixtape sound in which case it would be more eclectic. So I just listen to the tape while doing something else and if my head nods throughout the tape I look into it further. As far as determining the subject goes, that's kind of a loaded question. Some emcees go into writing without having a subject. The content of those types of raps are more towards the "introduction, braggadocio (I'm the best, other rappers suck, I've accomplished stuff, etc.), outro" end of the spectrum. If you want to go in with something in mind then it's as simple as deciding what to do. What are you happy about? Upset about? What is going on in your life? With the flows, I listen to the beat on repeat and kind of freestyle with noises and sounds and experimenting with different cadences and all that. I watched a video before I was an emcee and I think it was tech n9ne but maybe I'm wrong. Anyway, he explained how he found his flow on songs and he said that he listens to beats and makes drum sounds and builds his flow and cadence around that. When I listen to music I hear drums over everything so that helped me a lot. The structure may be the part that is most daunting for me. Its hard for me to change the flow structure once I'm locked in and I like to keep rhymes going for as long as I can without it sounding forced. It's hard for me to say, "I should switch up the flow coming in on the 9th bar" or whatever if I like what I'm doing. I'm working on it and getting better at making things different when they need to be but its probably my biggest weak point and something I'm always aware of. Putting together rhyming words is oddly easy for me. It's always the stuff before the rhyme that's the hardest. I finish the first bar with no thought of how to rhyme the next line with what I ended with. For example, let's say I ended my first line with "ended with". Where does that go? Penmanship. Scent of it. Imminent. I never think about rhyming the next line with what I ended with. My goal is to write lines that proceed my shitty penmanship. I make mistakes and raise the eraser, inspired by the scent of it. My success is predetermined, my victory is imminent. (Kinda whack but you get the point) If writing is tedious, you may be experiencing one of a few problems I have dealt with so I'll try to offer my advice on them. You may just be uninspired, which happens to everyone. Read a book or watch some movies about a subject you enjoy. Just consume and become inspired again and get back at it. You may be discouraged by how your writing had been turning out. Even if you think your writing is whack, keep doing it. I'm pretty happy with where I'm at with my ability to write good songs (but obviously trying to improve in all aspects at all times) but before I was I wrote some straight garbage for a few years before even considering picking up a microphone. I showed my friends and they laughed at how shitty it was. Now, they don't laugh. Now, they're excited to read and hear more because I've personally learned what's whack and what isn't. You may be going through some things where you aren't in a mental state to be as creative as you were, want to be or can be. For a few years I wasn't in a place where I could sit down and write something naturally. It came out forced, hamfisted and terrible. I've since gotten over it and am back to being stricken with creativity and inspiration and being able to naturally write. If you are having a life issue that needs worked out, I wish you the best. It really can suck the creative energy from you. Obviously every response in this thread is going to be different and that's fine. Everyone here does things differently, as will you when you come into your own. I hope the responses will steer you in the right direction because making music is incredible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-07 15:47:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>The best quick fix is to turn off monitoring. It's really not going to get to a point where it doesn't affect you negatively to have it on unless you spend money. If you are going to spend money, your microphone will not help decrease the latency. Upgrading your processor (and maybe your RAM iirc) will decrease that to a good point. You could change the buffer rate and a few other things to make a small improvement but it's likely to not be enough. If your computer can't handle processing the signal quickly enough there isn't really a good way to fake it. Source: I record on a shitty laptop with no monitoring</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-09 15:29:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't get why magical wouldn't work. The game isn't called Magical it's centered around you being a wizard. I'll be damned if the spells I sling aren't magical, brother.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-09 16:58:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was a wizard way before I was a planeswalker, jack. I don't know if you had your memory wiped by some nefarious mage but the way I grew up I didn't know about the blind eternities until I could conjure elemental storms that would make your bones rattle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-28 05:47:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sure did.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-30 23:40:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>good lord.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-05 19:35:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lol ayyyyy this is pretty damn funny</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-08 05:16:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man, you people never cease to amaze me. I get juiced whenever someone tags me on Reddit because I know it's gonna be some shit like this. It makes my day every time. 10/10 I'm tryna be in John Wick 2.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-08 05:30:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is it with people trying to see my asscrack? Y'all are wild.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-08 06:05:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I cannot lie... yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-08 06:07:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>You know just how to make me smile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-08 06:15:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a fair trade. I'd do it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-08 08:30:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I grew up around a lot of people. Yes, some of them were black.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-08 09:31:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I get a surprising amount of DMs asking me if stories about people knowing me are true, or if I was really out watching a movie in Kansas or if I was here, there or wherever. I must say that this is the oddest and funniest of this type of question that I have ever gotten. Unfortunately, I have to tell you that you got swindled in the worst way. The good ol' Garage Sale Swindle. Unbelievable. I hope your recovery is swift.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-08 09:49:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Let me know what you think!](freshbreezemovement.bandcamp.com)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-26 09:35:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You get hoes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-26 12:39:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes. Just like my wallet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-14 11:26:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once the creature exiles and returns with the displacer's ability, the game considers it a new object and therefore would not be exiled by the stasis snare.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-16 03:00:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm in.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-01 07:38:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I had a dime for every time I dreamt of something and couldn't figure out how to create it, I'd have ZERO DIMES!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-25 12:01:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not dead, homie. I'm still here. Still standing. Still strong.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-25 12:48:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>holla @ your boi</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-25 14:47:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're waiting on the masters to come back for the new EP and it'll be out. It shouldn't be more than a week or two. [Here is where it will be when it releases.](http://fresh breeze movement.bandcamp.com) Thanks for listening!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-25 14:48:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shit, Morris. You're making me blush.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-14 22:20:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Goodness. It's so weird to play overwatch and then come across pictures like this. 10/10 GG pls dont nerf</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-14 23:03:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seeing as how this is the top post on r/all right now which refers to me I'd say that that was a pretty safe bet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-23 10:50:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-09-28 22:37:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Alex, can I call you Alex? Anyway, listen dawg, don't play the game like this. Don't disrespect the game in such grotesque fashion. You're more than this. You know I believe in you, right? You know we all are rooting for you to bring that 100% uncut supreme content but this isn't the way to do it. Did you think of me when you did this, Al? Did you think of the people? The little children and the old, spent souls. They needed you to come through for them and you failed. You failed me, them and everyone else this time. I still have faith in you, Big A (The Silvanator). Bring the heat next time pal.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-01 06:05:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>You did me proud. I'm thankful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-30 02:40:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>[the shoulder pads were a little small on me but whatever.](http://imgur.com/ZXZw4nx.jpg)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-10-30 23:01:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is correct. I don't really post much but I read pretty much everything on this sub. I've been a fan of wrestling for as long as I can remember. I stopped watching a while ago but still followed it and then came back just like everyone else at some point. Next year I'm going as Vader. You heard it here first. Haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-07 21:11:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn't have gotten through it without you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-13 18:44:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Biggest Magic what? We are dying to know</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-15 21:53:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's the boy right there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-22 08:44:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm thankful. Fantastic shot.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-22 08:44:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-25 05:05:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is tight. I am thankful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-08 09:35:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm new to having an iphone. When I open the video I want to watch there is no way I can find to give me the URL. How do you get that once you press play on the video and it starts to play?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-28 08:45:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Fun fact, [I'm good friends with the hype man for the goal patrol.](http://imgur.com/177BcUy) That was my second game that I've ever gone to and I had a good time. Also this is pretty weird but whatever</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-28 09:09:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>You could stalk me if you wanted.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-01 01:24:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-08 16:42:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>OP I don't think that this is good advice. If people don't want to listen they're not going to listen regardless of how many tracks it is. If they do continue to listen you'll have better stats regarding when people stopped. I don't make beats but I have a few records and one of the most revealing pieces of data IMO is the rate at which the plays drop from song to song. If it's worse, more people will stop listening at that specific song. A natural drop in plays is standard but some people won't feel every single track you put out and not everyone is going to listen to the whole thing to formulate an opinion. As a rapper who looks for beats to use on this sub, individual tracks are much easier for multiple reasons. One track is annoying because if I'm not feeling a specific beat I have to find out where the next one starts, either by reading your annotations or by finding it myself which adds another step either way. Secondly, if you were to in theory agree to collaborate with someone and let them use your beats it would cost extra steps for either them or you to get them separated for use. While not very time consuming, it is still another whole interaction that needs to be done. I worked with u/hobbesduende on here and it was as simple as, "hey, can I use your beats for a tape" "yeah let me know what you come up with" "okay here is the tape thank you" and having to separate them would personally be a hassle. I am currently looking for beats for another tape and honestly don't even bother with full tapes that are one track. It's a nightmare to annotate and a nightmare to keep track of. TL;DR: my opinion as a rapper is that they should be individual tracks because it benefits both the producer and the rapper.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 03:02:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're correct, my friend!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 04:15:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hell no lol this picture was taken from my Instagram and posted on Reddit (with this same caption even) a long time ago.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 08:06:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>What pops out at me the most is the structure of the beats and composition of the patterns with one another. I think the beats are put together very well and lend themselves to both listening standalone or making a track to. I can't offer much advice/feedback from any other perspective besides rapper and listener and from those perspectives I would consider this tape to be pretty tight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 04:46:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good job my friend!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-28 16:06:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you. Is this what most people use?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 23:37:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>She knows what it is! Mine does this too and it always makes me laugh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 23:37:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're a dog! Thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-07 23:40:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate that, my friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-08 18:28:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't hold your breath lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[SPOILER] My view of the spot in the main event!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 06:07:35</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-18 06:31:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely. It was awesome. They brought dudes in hardhats to jack the ring back up afterwards and the event staff were shooing people away.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 02:42:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for the help. The gain really isn't the problem, I should have mentioned that the noise even plays at the same level when the mic isn't plugged in and also when the mic's input levels are at 0.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-23 07:27:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did not know you could use Reaper with OBS. Could you point me in the right direction of how to do that? I see a few conflicting ways and I am pretty confused about it. Thank you very much.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 05:09:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're a G</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-28 10:11:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can't disagree with that last part any more. Stealing? Really? How is it stealing when they provide you both a potential "customer" base (I put it in quotations because a viewer that subscribes to your channel is not your customer, but Twitch's) AND provide your viewer a way to support you and give you money? That has value no matter whether or not you agree with it. Imagine this: you pay some small amount of money to purchase the purplepoloplayer.com domain. You pay someone to design an entire webpage/website for you that can host your live streaming that won't save VODS or have a sidebar chat room or have any of the nice things that twitch provides to most people for free. You pay someone to set up whatever you'll need to facilitate live streaming. You run into lots of problems and pay someone to fix them. You set up a subscription service, more problems. You do all this stuff. OK now what. You stream and nobody watches you because you're not streaming on a website designed through millions of dollars and man-hours to get people to watch your stream because they make money from it. Furthermore, if they took 100% of your sub fee and you agreed to it, they're not outright stealing anything. They could say, "whatever people pay, you have to match out of pocket", and if you agree to it when you partner they're not stealing anything.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 18:12:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol ayyy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-09 16:45:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can you explain how you know for certain that the sole intention of those pictures being posted was for reddit karma?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-10 01:14:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think there was a lot of productive conversation that came from the post. Look at this thread (over 3 years removed from the post itself) and many others for examples of that. Why do you think that the problem has to be presented in only the exact way you approve of for there to be any other intention? I could provide some insight, seeing as how I'm the OP of the post you're referring to. I don't give a fuck about reddit karma. I hardly post anything at all and before i posted those pictures I had only had a handful of posts/comments at all before that post.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 01:38:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>ayyyy let's get it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-25 21:55:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>you get pussy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-26 01:19:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>im kickin it, what about you?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-05 09:04:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>[This is a very good playlist of videos to watch to help you learn about streaming.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F_16JqjRboo amp;list=PLr5MtCgh28M8_6LQzK9Cj5leIQcx7z9fQ) The videos are long but you can just listen while you work or whatever since they're sort of like podcasts. Maybe there are actual podcast versions of it, I am not sure. Anyway, I am very happy for you, my friend. Streaming is very fulfilling. I hope it works out for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-05 09:37:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>in that case, it doesn't have to be street. It could be, hood (in the same context as "street"), goon, criminal, crook, something along those lines. Something that has a clean translation. I have been looking at google translate because I figured that single words can't be translated all that poorly. What would you think?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-05 10:17:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>latro seems nice. So, in that case, "latro ab utero ad tumulum" would translate to "thug from the womb to the tomb"?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-05 10:30:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>you get it in, my friend. thank you very much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-05 10:37:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>actually, one more question. If I was trying to translate "straight edge" (context: meant to resemble the sharpness of the edge of a blade/razor and represents lifelong abstinence from drugs/alcohol and is used as a descriptor, ex: "i am straight edge" or "i have been straight edge for a long time"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-14 01:08:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am getting sound from the virtual output, it works with everything else fine. It just doesn't work with steam or maybe with this specific game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 20:55:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have issues with that game as well, I run my audio through voicemeeter on PC and the voice chat doesn't work with my microphone, I have to use the headset mic and it sucks. I see a lot of people complain about the game too when it comes to voice, so it could be the game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-27 09:45:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>You said it's an XLR mic coming through a mixer right? Is it phantom powered? There is a slight buzzing noise when I use my mixer and it doesn't come up when phantom power isn't running. It's a shot in the dark but it's possible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-28 15:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>While i do agree that the amount an individual is **able** to spend does have a limit, what they're **willing** to spend can increase, considering that the affiliate program does add value to the website and will bring forth more streamers that viewers will want to support. streaming becoming more mainstream, the affiliate program and other factors increase the value of the website. the more channels that reach higher levels of production/content, driven by the affiliate program, the more eyes will be on the streamers, and some of those viewers will be willing to spend money. i think the main issue is that people worked very hard to get their sub buttons and they feel like it's unfair that others don't have to. that's the main complaint I'm seeing anyway. the reality is that, yes, it is going to be very easy to get the sub button now. once i get mine, i will have been streaming for 3 months almost on the dot. a friend of mine streamed for 3 years before they got their button. some people give up after trying to get a button for years. another part of this reality, as i explained earlier, is that a rising tide lifts all boats. if i had to hunt and gather my food for years, and then a market came into my village/town/whatever and people that just moved in were able to obtain food easier than i had been doing it, why would i be mad about that? the more people there are, all the more food will be grown. the more people with high quality content, the more support there will be for them. if the product/service quality increases, the amount of people interested in the content will rise and the amount they're willing to spend will rise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 07:42:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>this is tight. you killed it my bro. i thought i was looking at myself for a second!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 07:42:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks my friend. it's fantastic</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-13 00:24:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>lol we pickin em off out here!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-14 12:28:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>getting nothing from my amazing PC build? i got an amazing PC out of it. I use it every day for gaming, recording music, editing video, browsing the internet, all types of important things for me. if streaming was no longer viable tomorrow id be completely fine with spending a lot on a pc because I'll have it for over a decade. the fair way to make money is to earn it. do well enough with streaming that you can afford beer from what your followers give you. you'll probably end up drinking a lot less because the money most likely won't come for a long time (if at all) unless you focus on becoming a good streamer.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-15 11:57:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>get at me dawg i got you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-24 10:37:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is fucked up. I didn't get banned from playing Magic for this shit.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 22:46:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>i like ankhbot because i dont have to have my browser open to monitor my chat. i can have the game, OBS and ankhbot and you've got everything you need, plus it saves cpu. i think it works very well for what i need.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-06 06:30:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>the pyro budget died for the microphones in this segment</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-08 22:24:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>what a time to be alive. i never thought i would see myself shopped into some presidential shit like this. thank you very much lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 23:00:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jesus Christ. It's worldwide. I mean I know it has been but damn, it still blows my mind to see it. Thanks for keeping my legacy alive, you get hoes! shameless plug edit: i stream on twitch. (@OB1TV) I have an instagram (@biblicalfigure). I have a twitter (@biblical_figure) i fuck with yall heavy. this shit makes me smile all the time when i see something i did bring people happiness. i gotta lot of love for yall edit: i did direct linking to my profile, which is not allowed. My bad yall</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 23:01:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>you get hoes too</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 23:29:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm here for you. i shall rise again once my people need me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 23:31:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>millions (and millions)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 23:31:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>laugh louder. fuck the neighbors</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-09 23:45:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>good thing we dont give a fuck what you think in this thread bitch we partyin havin a good time go get comfortable somewhere else!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 02:49:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>the bot did what the bot had to do. hey bot i fixed the post</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 03:03:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>i think not, dawg. knees at an obtuse angle, too much smile, not enough pain in the eyes. she still looks like she had fun so i am happy for her and for that she gets a pass. thanks for showing me the pic!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 04:44:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>[More like:](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ep2pyvKTiG0)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-19 08:38:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>you could download Audacity (free digital audio workstation if you don't already have one) and import your sound. from there you can turn the volume on the master mix of it all the way to the max and that will make it as loud as it can go. if the wave gets bigger than the area it occupies (you'll know what i mean when you do it) you'll hear a bit of clipping but if it's not the whole thing it won't be noticeable. honestly if you couldn't figure it out i can help you with it. just pm me if you can't figure it out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 01:14:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>sup dawg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 01:06:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>i have the same interface, but the generation before this one. you should absolutely be able to connect your mic to the interface via xlr and connect the interface to your pc via usb with no other connection.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-22 01:45:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah, it should work. if not i can try to help, my friend</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 20:38:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>18 months, my friend.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 22:23:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>bro that brightens my day, thank you for sharing that. I love that shit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-13 23:00:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>i love that, my friend. Magic is a great game.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 04:40:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>every time i go out for the most part lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 04:41:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>they cant keep me locked down forever my bro</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 04:41:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>i can take that heat my friend, if you got some happiness out of it id say it was well worth it haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-14 04:43:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>not soon enough, my friend :( but soon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-19 02:06:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Something I haven't seen get talked about too much is how diverse this event is. It's beautiful how well represented the world is in NXT right now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 00:36:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>youre 100% wrong haha that aint me baby</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 00:36:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks my bro!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 00:37:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>i completely agree. OK we're both fat and have shitty beards lol sick</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 00:50:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah, i'm the guy they're asking about so i'd know if that dude in this picture was me or not lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 00:51:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>is there a "you're tight" tag? /yt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 01:34:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>you can summon me any time my friend</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 01:37:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>i needed that my bro, thank you. you're right. self deprecation aint cool. i got some strengths.  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 01:46:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>i appreciate that, my friend. we gotta get it in out here you know what i mean</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 02:16:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>you used a winky cat emoticon lmao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-04 02:17:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>[absolutely](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k3CR9XshxfM)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-10 03:43:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm thankful</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-22 15:43:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>dont be mad because cant pull some bullshit like this off, my friend. you dont have to bring others down to feel good</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 09:34:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>thanks for showing me this my bro. i appreciate you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-19 07:58:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>-_-</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-08 17:01:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really like it. not having to have my bot on screen to monitor chat, not having to use the streamlabels app for alerts, and things such as the bit cup, alerts etc not having to be browser sources are all big reasons to be excited. thru all of that combined my CPU usage decreased by about 20%, my workspace is way less cluttered, and personally I think it looks less janky than OBS itself but that's not really a factor. this and the streamlabs chatbot integrating with the actual extension as far as currency and stuff goes, in addition to them stating they want to integrate the chatbot in SLOBS, streamlabs is something I feel confident and comfortable going all in on. it's an amazing service imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 07:03:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>left monitor i've got streamlabs OBS open. it shows alerts, chat and a live preview of the stream. before SLOBS, I just had streamlabs open with OBS. middle monitor is where i play the game, then right i usually have my discord and spotify. before SLOBS i had chat and spotify on my right monitor, but since SLOBS gives me all the info that would normally be used in 3 windows, i can have something like my discord on. i have been feeling like i could go down to 2 if i needed to. have SLOBS on one monitor and the game on the other.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-17 10:50:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>yeah, i like it a lot. i had streamlabs, OBS, ankhbot, all separately and then ankhbot became streamlabs chatbot. then streamlabs came out with their own broadcasting software that combines their OBS and streamlabels. it also uses widgets instead of broswer sources for things like your alerts, bit cup, etc so it uses a lot less CPU for me, anywhere from 15-30% less. ive seen people say it uses more, i personally have only seen positive changes but again, thats just what happened with me. anyone elses mileage will vary. SLOBS is only as good as it can get if you're using their other services though, although streamlabs chatbot is currently not integrated with SLOBS, so you could use another. well, you could anyway, but you know what i mean. it wouldnt be as advantageous if you used streamelements for your alerts/etc and nightbot for example. so since i already happened to use the streamlabs stuff, it works great for me and i recommend it. but yeah, with that i can for sure go down to 2 monitors but i already have the third so i just have the luxury of having spotify bigger and having live discord stuff which is cool.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-23 18:32:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you! this is tight.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 18:06:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>of course, my bro</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 18:07:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>thats very nice of you. i'd like to think we'd be friends to. what ive always wanted in life is to throw a 24 hour pizza party for my friends and anyone is invited. idk why but ive wanted that ever since i was a young boy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 09:33:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>all my work... not for this. not for this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 01:56:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>bro magic is a card game it wasnt the end of shit. you are mad lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 02:06:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>ok fair enough, do you forgive me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 12:54:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I used to know the brand of the table. I'll check back in. the trick is to stand right above the leg btw edit: there is no label on the table but the owner of the store knew so I'll have to do some more research</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 13:00:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>if i dont have at least #4 ima copystrike this video!! /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 02:13:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>that's amazing, thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 02:15:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>I gotta say. I love this subreddit and I am stoked to be here. thank you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Does anyone here use Izotope VSTs with Streamlabs OBS? Help needed</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-09 13:24:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am attempting to use either Izotope Nectar 2 or Ozone 8 in SLOBS for EQ, compression, etc. and I can't figure out how to get them to fully work. I can select them in the menu and open the interface, and the VST recognizes the audio being sent in but SLOBS doesn't recognize audio being sent back out and when I record for tests, there is no audio. I would really appreciate some help if anyone knows what the issue could be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 21:59:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>lmao thank you. this is one of the best yet. i appreciate you</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 21:59:15</DATE>
    <TEXT> lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 21:59:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you for the reply, you might be onto something.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 01:34:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>okay? why do you feel it necessary to tell me who you would think I look like if I lost weight?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-11 01:34:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>rap/hardcore/jail lol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 22:51:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>RIP cassette thing bro I'm here for you. in the pic and in spirit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 22:51:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>thank you my friend</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 07:06:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>you know what? i bet it wasn't even pulled either! /s</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-24 02:50:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>no, they are saying i would look cool if i lost weight. im taking it as a compliment from someone that doesn't know that what they are saying is actually insulting</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>