<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject3904</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I made the crest shield!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 01:11:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/gallery/efEyJjd I #8217;m the cosplayer Sunlight of Astora and I have just completed my crest shield to accompany my elite knight costume, I hope you like it I worked really hard for all of the templating and detailing to the way it was painted. Praise the sun! [Edit: working links] www.Instagram.com/SunlightofAstora www.facebook.com/sunlightcosplay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 04:47:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I will definitely be taking photos in my elite knight set once I remake my helmet. If you wanted to see what my elite looked like check out my Instagram i have all of my progress on there. Instagram.com/subject3904</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 04:48:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do :) I made the Astora sword as well! It #8217;s all on my Instagram find me @subject3904</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 13:36:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s 1:1 from in game! I put a scaled photo in the link, compared to the 1/6 scales elite knight statue :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 13:51:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahah yeah that #8217;s me xD I don #8217;t know why I never posted my elite knight here, I #8217;m always on reddit I just don #8217;t post. When I remake the helmet I #8217;ll post it here :3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I made a full scale Crest shield!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 18:06:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/gallery/efEyJjd I #8217;m the cosplayer Sunlight of Astora and I have just completed my crest shield to accompany my elite knight costume, I hope you like it I worked really hard for all of the templating and detailing to the way it was painted. The size comparison is in the link.Praise the sun! www.Instagram.com/SunlightofAstora www.Facebook.com/sunlightcosplay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 18:31:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I appreciate that friend and I #8217;ll probably do that but it is dark souls so I wanted to share with you guys :) thanks for the heads up on the links I don #8217;t know why they won #8217;t work but who ever wants to go to them can look it up if they want :) unless you know how to fix that?  gt;. gt;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 18:34:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m at work so I #8217;ll see what I can do but I appreciate it none the less :) now that the shield is complete I have the whole elite knight set including the Astora sword!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Self] I made the elite knights weapons from Dark Souls</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 18:38:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 18:39:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I made it out of xps foam it #8217;s really light and sandable. The detailing is craft foam. :) I hope that helps!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 18:52:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>The link doesn #8217;t work but go check out my Instagram I made a hunter cosplay and the holy moonlight sword! Beasthunter saif is such a cool weapon! Yeah foam board sucks upgrade to that xps foam forsure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 18:53:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>That fixed it :) it didn #8217;t register the link without the www. But it also capitalized it and I didn #8217;t notice so thanks for that!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 18:58:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>That #8217;d be cool to see, you should!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 19:30:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apparently it reduces it to much.. :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I made the saw cleaver and blunderbuss!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 02:32:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/gallery/62nhngD The saw cleaver is my favorite weapon from any video game and I #8217;m happy to share the props I built from my favorite game to accompany my Hunter cosplay. Here they are in comparison to the gecco bloody hunter statue! I have progress on both of these weapons on my social media pages! www.Facebook.com/sunlightcosplay www.Instagram.com/subject3904</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 04:30:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It took forever because I made all the templates for the armor trying to make them as accurate as possible, I made the chainmail by hand and the hardest part of all.. I even hand stitched the tunic... Dx thank you so much for the compliment!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 10:51:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 14:46:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should go to my Instagram and look at my elite knight :) it may not look as good as the statue but I think I did a pretty good job. :3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-23 23:10:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! Oh no my hunter has been completed :) these are just two of my weapons. I even made the holy moonlight sword. It #8217;s all on my Instagram :3 I #8217;m thinking about posting my moonlight sword here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-24 01:06:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did make them myself :) I also made the holy moonlight sword!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I made the Holy Moonlight Sword with the abyssal cosmos</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 02:18:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/gallery/4OA103r Made May 21 2017 I never posted this to reddit for some reason but I feel like now is a good time to show you all something I worked incredibly hard for. Created out of foam I etched all of the detail and thinned out the inside to allow the light of the Leds to create the cosmos effect shown in the transformation cutscene of Ludwig #8217;s boss fight. It captivated me, being my favorite boss fight I gave what little prop making experience I had to create something I thought would express my love for this game. My social media accounts for those interested to see my soulsborne work! www.facebook.com/sunlightcosplay www.instagram.com/SunlightofAstora</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-25 13:26:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s one of mine to! Saw cleaver is probably my favorite but you should check out the saw cleaver and blunderbuss I posted the other day :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I made the elite knight helmet</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 21:44:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/gallery/ZgEfuuC hey everyone heres my new finished elite knight helmet I #8217;ve spent almost as much time staring at the elite knight armor as playing the game. Hope you like it and there will be more made soon! you can find my work at www.facebook.com/sunlightcosplay and www.instagram.com/subject3904</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I made the elite knight helmet!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 21:45:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/gallery/ZgEfuuC hey everyone heres my new finished elite knight helmet I #8217;ve spent almost as much time staring at the elite knight armor as playing the game. Hope you like it and there will be more made soon! you can find my work at www.facebook.com/sunlightcosplay and www.instagram.com/subject3904</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 22:24:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s made out of craft foam it almost weighs nothing :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 22:24:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! It took about two weeks and a lot of adjusting to get this result :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 01:37:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Got it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 03:28:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>They made a second one? I hope it #8217;s good.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 04:34:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh yeah man it can! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 06:34:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can see perfectly out of it :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Elite knight cosplay at DragonCon</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:19:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://imgur.com/gallery/TJ3SKuV Hey everyone I hope you like my elite knight armor. I put heart in soul into this. One of a kind helmet design Hand embroidered custom tunic Handmade chain mail Accurately built armor and detailed sword and shield 100% grossly incandescent You can find my work at www.facebook.com/sunlightcosplay www.instagram.com/subject3904</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Self] Dark Souls cosplay at DragonCon</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:24:22</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:27:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am!! I #8217;ll m glad people remember that it #8217;s one of my greatest achievements as lame as that sounds haha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 03:29:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Priscilla yes but ceaseless I hope not hahaha</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:01:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>For those interested my pages are www.facebook.com/sunlightcosplay and www.instagram.com/subject3904 where I posted the making of this cosplay!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:26:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can draw the sword easily and I can attach the shield to my back! Don #8217;t got the shield thing on video but drawing the sword haha https://imgur.com/gallery/TJ3SKuV</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:26:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll take it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 05:39:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hahah thank you! I made both of those costumes :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 07:00:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Amazing chest ahead?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-03 08:17:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well to be fair I chose to cosplay as the  #8220;chosen undead #8221; so i get to change out my weapons like my astora greatsword or longsword without not being faithful to the character ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>