<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject7290</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Need to forget about a crush (14/F)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-17 08:41:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Around a year ago I met this girl through my friends. She was pretty, funny and just fun to be around. We were good friends but nothing more. I was going through a lot at the time and she just made me so happy I can't even describe it. Though we never had an outright conversation about it I showed her that i liked her and she showed me that she didn't feel the same. Later I found out at the time she had feelings for another guy. At this point nothing good can come of me crying over her so I know I have to move on. I just don't know anyway to. No matter what I do she always pops in my head. Any advice?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2012-11-18 00:07:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks guys for the help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Need help building a youtube audience?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-23 07:02:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>My channel is called Generationfilms100 youtube.com/user/Generationfilms100 I've been making videos on there for about year now. The premise for the channel is comedy videos like sketch work. Most of the videos are like that, some are kind of random but I only upload videos I think are funny. Not all the videos are that good I know but some I think are pretty good (What Life is All About, A Normal Phone Call, John Valentime, and Batman's Day in Town). My friends thought some of them were pretty funny and other people around my school liked them. But besides those people watching my videos I don't really seem to be getting that many views and subscribers. I'm having a hard time creating an audience I guess. I don't understand why there are some vlog channels that have thousands of subscribers and a lot of views. I'm not trying to act like I think I'm better then vloggers because I'm not, but I'm frustrated that I put so much time and work into my videos and they turn out pretty good, but not that many people watch them. I don't understand what I'm doing wrong that other youtubers do right in order to create a fanbase or audience. I know I don't have the most impressive videos but I'm in the works of creating very good videos that have pretty good scripts and everything so far on them are turning out real well. But I'd feel bad if I released them but no one noticed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-23 07:11:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was just asking if anyone had any tips for me to use to help me out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-04-23 08:35:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks and I agree that the ones that are up aren't that good. I guess the only thing I can do is keep working to make better ones. Thanks man.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Best city to find punk musicians: Portland or Seattle?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-12 23:18:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looking to find musicians who play punkish kind of music and I also want to move to the Northwest. So what city would have more of those kinds of musicians Portland or Seattle? Thanks for answering if you do</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-14 02:29:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey Rap Critic! How long have you been a fan of Spill, well what was Spill, and Korey Coleman?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is it legal to sample a karaoke version of a song?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-07 03:27:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I recently sampled a karaoke instrumental and was wondering if this is legal or not? If not then who should I clear the sample by? Should I clear it from the people who made the karaoke or the original artist of the original song?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Alice in Chains One Direction Mash Up - I Would? [Pop remix]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-24 06:58:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Alice in Chains One Direction Mash Up! - I Would? [Pop remix]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-06-24 10:51:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Shadow Disorder - Vaporgazing | Mix of vaporwave and shoegaze about being crowded mall</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-09 08:17:44</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>JonTron Theme Hendrix Style</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-17 09:00:34</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Neighborhoods With A Lot Of Musicians?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-25 12:06:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hate to have another "moving to Seattle thread" but I felt like this was a question I've been wondering and haven't found any answers to. I'm a musician moving to town and because I don't know anyone there I was hoping to make fellow musician friends. I'm wondering which neighborhoods do you feel have the most concentrated amount of musicians living in there? I've heard of Cap Hill or Georgetown maybe filling that bill, but I want to make sure I know the exact neighborhood. Not to waste more of your time but I'm pretty awkward and anxious and thus is hard for me to make friends. So it would make making musician friends easier if I lived right next to them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-27 11:01:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Am I the only grommet that actually thinks his movie reviews are better/funnier than his game reviews? No? Okay...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Trying To Protect Pedals While Moving? [GEAR]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-30 14:04:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll try to make this short and simple. I'll be moving from Arizona to Oregon in the beginning of June and will be driving through the desert for at least 2 days in the midst of summer at around 115 degrees. So how do I protect my pedals, gear and guitar? Right now I have a Big Muff Pi, Dunlop Band of Gypsys Mini Fuzz Face, Digitech Jimi Hendrix Experience, Orange Crush 20RT and Squier Jaguar. I'm mostly afraid for the pedals, especially after I heard that some Fuzz Faces are affected by temperature. Any help would really be appreciated, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-01 10:37:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll probably have just enough room to fit it in the back seat with the ac on.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Markiplier Rapes Leafy Video</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-08-21 11:55:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How much will A certificate in Audio Engineering help me with jobs?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-08 08:24:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am currently enrolled in a community college which offers both an associates in audio engineering as well as a one year certificate. I'm pretty low on money, not great at school, and eager to move to a big city to start my recording "career". How much do you think a certificate will help me get in easier with owners of studios and clients? Or is it worth it to get more student loans and another year for the associates instead? I guess I can't get any great sources on whether the certificate is enough, or if people in the industry will see it as "well tons of people have a certificate but if you had a degree I'll consider you better". I know a lot to the business is networking and knowing people rather than formal interviews with formal resumes. I see tons of successful producers with no formal training at all, so that's what got me thinking if all the stress and money is worth it for a degree that is more or less meaningless to the industry. So do you think a certificate is enough or is the degree worth it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How much will a certificate in Audio Engineering help me with jobs?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-08 08:34:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am currently enrolled in a community college which offers both an associates in audio engineering as well as a one year certificate. I'm pretty low on money, not great at school, and eager to move to a big city to start my recording "career". How much do you think a certificate will help me get in easier with owners of studios and clients? Or is it worth it to get more student loans and another year for the associates instead? I guess I can't get any great sources on whether the certificate is enough, or if people in the industry will see it as "well tons of people have a certificate but if you had a degree I'll consider you better". I know a lot to the business is networking and knowing people rather than formal interviews with formal resumes. I see tons of successful producers with no formal training at all, so that's what got me thinking if all the stress and money is worth it for a degree that is more or less meaningless to the industry. So do you think a certificate is enough or is the degree worth it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How much will a certificate in Audio Engineering help me with jobs?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-08 10:35:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am currently enrolled in a community college which offers both an associates in audio engineering as well as a one year certificate. I'm pretty low on money, not great at school, and eager to move to a big city to start my recording "career". How much do you think a certificate will help me get in easier with owners of studios and clients? Or is it worth it to get more student loans and another year for the associates instead? I guess I can't get any great sources on whether the certificate is enough, or if people in the industry will see it as "well tons of people have a certificate but if you had a degree I'll consider you better". I know a lot to the business is networking and knowing people rather than formal interviews with formal resumes. I see tons of successful producers with no formal training at all, so that's what got me thinking if all the stress and money is worth it for a degree that is more or less meaningless to the industry. So do you think a certificate is enough or is the degree worth it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-12 05:11:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you had to be murdered by any character in a TV show, who would it be and why?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is working downtown on 3rd dangerous?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-23 08:39:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll be moving to Seattle soon and begin work at the downtown Macy's on 3rd. I've read a lot about how 3rd, especially the area where I'll work, is very dangerous at night and the early morning. I don't have a car and am planning on using the light rail from Westlake to my apartment on Pine and Broadway. Do you think the area is too dangerous to not have a car? Some days I'll have to come in really early around 5 or 6am or late like 10pm. I heard these are also bad times to be in the area. What do you guys think? This'll be my first time living away from home, I'm 19, and not having a car, so I'm already kinda nervous. Am I just being paranoid? Probably.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to write emotional, non-edgy, lyrics?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-11 08:42:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>My lyrical topics typically center around my depression, anger, and bad personal experiences. A vast majority of artists I listen to also tackle in these themes; Kurt Cobain, Billy Corgan of Smashing Pumpkins, Trent Reznor, Kanye West, Kendrick Lamar, etc. But it seems like most of the lyrics I write come off as "edgy", like an annoying teenager. How is that when Kanye makes a song like FML I feel his emotions, but when I write a song with a chorus that's "fuck the world" it comes off whiny? I know it's kinda odd question, but do you guys have any advice on not coming off as edgy in my music?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 07:46:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you guys so much for the advice, I'll definitely take it. You guys are awesome :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Capitol Hill vs the U District for young person?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-30 07:50:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm transferring over my job and they have several locations within Seattle. The two I'm most interested in is their Downtown location on 3rd and Pike, and a location within University Village. My dream has always been to move to Seattle and live in a big city. I just turned 21 and want to live that young person lifestyle. But I'm torn between which neighborhood would be a better fit for me. I'm pretty introvered but want to finally come out of my shell. I'm a musician and just love the feeling of something always happening. I could go to a show, or get late night sushi, or watch a movie,etc. I want to live in a neighborhood with people my age that feels like something fun is always happening. If I work Downtown then I'd live in Capitol Hill, and I'd live in the U District if working at U Village. So price wise, people wise, and the overall feel of the neighborhood wise which do you believe would be the best of the two? I'm not bring a car BTW. Just walking around when visiting I liked Capitol Hill a little more, but I went in summer so most the students were gone in the U District.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Concerned and anxious about my academic and career future?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-12 08:43:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Currently I am studying for an Associates in Music Production/Audio Engineering. I love creating and recording music, so this program seems almost perfect for me. Unfortunately I know that music degrees don't always lead to somewhat well paying careers. Not that money is everything, I will always create music, but with the debt I am piling up and coming from a not so well off financial family, I am worried about my future. I am also fascinated by with Astronomy, Theoretical Physics, Marine Biology, Economics, and city planning. I spend a large chunk of my free time reading and learning about these subjects. I would love to go on experiments at sea, study the stars, or help a city build proper public transit. To me these also seem like much more stable and well paying careers. I'm essentially trying to create a fall back career if my music doesn't hit off. But, speaking honestly, I am not good at Math or Science. I have always been better at the arts, and my low grades in Math and Science were my ultimate factors in me dropping out of high school. Now I am struggling, but passing, my College Algebra course. I feel I am not smart enough for the rigorous amount of complex math and science to be able to get a Bachelor's in any of these fields. Now I am working minimum wage retail jobs and I hate it. I just don't want to return to that for the rest of my life after graduating from music school. Any thoughts? TLDR; Want a backup career in either Astronomy, Theoretical Physics, Marine Biology, or City Planning in case my Music degree doesn't pay off. But I am pretty bad at math and science. Do I have any chance at these careers, or do you think I should just stick with Music?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I think it's time for me to kill myself</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-21 02:48:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Man the pain of everyday life is just too much, and it's been going on for far too long. I was recently fired from my job where many of the other employees were rude and belittled me. Now I'm unemployed with bills to pay but every job interview I go on leads nowhere. I have terrible anxiety when driving and a few months ago I accidentally committed a hit and run, no one was injured. My court date is coming up in two weeks and they've mentioned jail time very often. I'm trying to go to school for my passion, music, but it just isn't enough to motivate me to get out of bed every morning. I also found out the girl I was into, and was about to ask out today, just got a boyfriend. But my depression and suicidal behavior goes back much further. In middle school I was often bullied and raped by one of my classmates after school. And I'll never forgot the volatile years of my parents marriage and eventually divorce. Those traumas still hurts me to this day. All I want to do in my life is cuddle next to someone that loves me and I love them and we just write dumb cute songs together. I'm a person with so much love to give, so much love I want to show the world and other people, but it seems every time I turn around life just wants to remind me that no one cares about me, that no one ever loved me, and that no one will ever love me. I've attempted suicide three times before during high school, but know I feel it is time to try again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How liberal/left leaning are the Angelenos?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 00:04:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll be moving to DTLA next summer but I currently live in a small town in Oregon. I am Pacific Islander and Japanese, but because of my last name many believe I am Latino. My whole life I have been judged, harassed, and looked down upon for my race. With an almost 96% white population where I live, I constantly am told to "go back to my country" and other racial slurs. I am in no way claiming to have experienced the level of racism of black people and actual latinos, but I have faced discrimination my whole life. The general conception most people have of LA is that it is some kind of liberal paradise, only rivaled by San Francisco. But how true is this belief? How liberal is LA really? I myself am not even a liberal but much further left, but I'm hoping a highly liberal place won't treat me as an outsider. I am 20 and like I said will be trying to live in DTLA. So is the perception that people from LA are open minded and liberal true?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is it weird to ask a lady friend to gon on a trip with you?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-21 19:56:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>This girl and I have been friends for about a month now, going to the same college. I confessed my feelings for her and we went on a date a few weeks ago. I thought it went pretty well but at the end she said she just wasn't ready for a relationship and wanted us to stay friends. It hurt at first, but I accepted this and now we're good friends together. Earlier in the year I had made a plan to stay with my uncle in Los Angeles for a week in July since I am wanting to move there after I graduate. For whatever reason I really want to invite my lady friend with me for this trip. I just keep imagining us having this awesome, movie like summer in LA together. I'm not thinking this as a subtle way of trying to get with her, like I said we talked about it and as much as I still like her and would be thrilled to be in a relationship with her, I still really appreciate our friendship. So would she think I'm weird/have ulterior motives if I asked if she wanted to tag along with me to LA for a week in July?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Advice on giving a woman an orgasm after you've already finished</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 22:53:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I'm a 20 year old college student who's only performed oral sex on a girl before. I've always been a big believer in equality in sex, and therefore I knew that when having sex if I come first then the right thing to do is to keep going until she also comes. I've never really heard of anyone doing this, but I'm sure it happens. Do you have any advice on how to realistically pull this off though? How to get me back in the mood quickly to continue for her?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How to recover files after a restart to default OS?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 09:35:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello, I am using Sierra 10.12 on my 2017 MacBook Pro. I recently accidentally upgraded my OS and after doing so many of my applications stopped working. I decided to restart my OS to its default, that being Sierra 10.12, but foolishly forgot to set up my Time Machine or save any of my files to an external hard drive. So now that I've restarted my Mac to its default OS none of my files are visible. Is there anyway for me to get back any of my files? I've downloaded StellarPhoenixMacRecovery but it was unable to find any files on my computer. Is there any hope for me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-25 05:19:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay I see. Thank you for responding though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The next step up from cutting?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 08:43:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been cutting for 8 years now, since I was 13. It's been a few months now since the last time I cut, but today I cut again and I don't feel anything anymore. I don't feel the pain and therefore that release I need continues to be pent up. I was wondering is there is another step, for lack of a better word, in increasing pain so I can continue to self harm? I don't have enough money to buy drugs, such as oxycontin, xanax, morphine, or even MDMA, plus my social anxiety would make it default for me to get in contact with drug dealers. So I'm trying to find a self harm alternative I can do at home to fulfill my needs without having to go to drugs?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>