<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject4848</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 07:26:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>This happened to me too. Looking through your post history you look super pretty. They are just mean for no reason. The imgur community is horrible so don #8217;t let it get to you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 09:52:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m really glad you #8217;re feeling better! And thank you x3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 20:37:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can confirm this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-03 23:46:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>You definitely should. You look amazing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-04 21:38:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is adorable. Congratulations on being yourself!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 00:47:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>You look really good! What did you do to lose weight? I have been trying for a long time</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 06:07:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Have you made friends through this sub? I #8217;m finding it pretty hard to</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 09:24:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine too :p</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 10:42:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really want this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 11:00:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>I really hope they do</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Alternatives?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 11:12:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I never really talk to anyone about this stuff and up until posting this I usually just bottle up this part of myself. I used to cut myself all the time and it became the main way I handled any amount of stress or depression I felt. I haven #8217;t done it in a long time but at the same time I still think like how I used to when I did. sometimes I just start freaking out not wanting to feel any negative feelings or thoughts and instantly think about how I used to handle it. I #8217;ve heard of the whole rubber band thing but does anyone have any other alternatives that might work? I #8217;ve never posted on here or anywhere about this kind of stuff so I don #8217;t know if I #8217;m doing it right but thanks to anyone who takes the time to reply.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>