<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject8565</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Players social media</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-02 12:44:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone know or have a list of all the Genius/Society Game players' Instagram/Twitter/whatever else ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-04 05:15:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some episodes also have a full version available on http://kshowonline.com/ (just search The Genius)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE> lt;3</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 06:17:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Today is a sad day but thanks to everyone at SF, past and present, for making me laugh almost everyday for the 4 years I've been watching. Here's to greater things in the future!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-25 08:41:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seeing everyone so heartbroken :(( I'll miss their chemistry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 06:56:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't wait for the daily Slamwich videos</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How long would it take to watch every single SourceFed video?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-26 10:48:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>SourceFed, SourceFedNERD, People Be Like, Super Panic Frenzy, Nuclear Family Umm.... Asking for a friend :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-27 10:37:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could also review the podcast on iTunes  #9733; #9733; #9733; #9733; #9733;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-29 05:01:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg yesss this is amazing We'll probably see members returning as guests like YoonG and Hyunmoo did in S2, I hope Also hopefully, there'll be less secret relationships and marriages cause it felt like every case had one last season</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-31 14:04:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this voting for who we want on, or is the cast already confirmed and we are guessing who is on? I've heard both</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-04 06:24:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did this ever happen? :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-05 07:29:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think I read a translation somewhere which said that the cast would also be revealed on the 9th</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Society Game 2 August 2017 ??</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 11:19:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-06 11:20:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>From Pharoh's Instagram</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-09 09:26:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Isn't the Crime Scene 3 cast meant to be revealed today?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-10 05:45:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't know much about Korean stuff but I'm sure Dongmin wasn't known for his "intelligence" either until he won The Genius. Hopefully, the casting team and PD's know what they're doing. Also hopefully, previous members will return as guests</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-21 09:31:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>So is this like a mini episode? Also sounds like they're not doing the individual detective thing they did at the start of S2 :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-24 11:36:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unrelated, but does anyone know why they named these videos Twice TV Special instead of just continuing with Twice TV5 ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 06:23:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hail Bumdi!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-25 08:51:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>The first half of the episode is basically a recap/"Best Of" of some Season 2 episodes (Beauty Park, Fried Chicken Store, the Hunting one) Bumdi only subbed the new Season 3 stuff</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-04-27 15:37:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Creators: Jeph Loeb"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 03:19:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Decent subs from ODK, but of course Bumdi is better Solid first case, Sehyung and Eunji did pretty well, however at points it felt kinda disjointed like when [everyone was crowded around looking at a phone or something and Eunji or Jang Jin were just off by themselves](/spoiler) Also loved that random part at the start was Sehyung just started dancing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 14:54:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think TT and Knock Knock were only connected because they are both Twicecoaster (Lane 1  amp; 2)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-02 15:12:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>It appears Psy will be on the May 13th show according to Naver http://entertain.naver.com/read?oid=109 amp;aid=0003529491</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Positions in Group?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-06 09:57:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've read some "profiles" on the internet that say stuff like Dahyun is lead rapper and Chaeyoung is main rapper, Nayeon is lead vocals and Jihyo is main vocals, etc. So what is the difference between main and lead? Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-12 15:06:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>*oh jji ri jji ri, oh jji ri jji ri, oh jji ri jji ri, oh my boy*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 12:25:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg did Nayeon do ohyo ohyo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Another thread looking for a video...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 12:40:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>It wasn't a SF video, but I remember that it was a series (or supposed to be a series) that featured Lee and Elliott but it only ended up having one episode Something to do with computers I think?? Thanks! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-15 12:48:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>ODK has already done the bulk of the work so if Bumdi just goes in and corrects some of the mistakes, it shouldn't be too hard But idk</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 06:06:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice! Jinyoung was also on the list for potential guests at the start of the season Does anyone know how many people from the potential cast list in Season 2 actually ended up on the show?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 10:02:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>what happened?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-20 14:10:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh no sorry, I mean why did the content of this post get removed? Unless it's just me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-21 11:28:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>damn this is an amazing edit, one of the best I've seen</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-22 13:49:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Source?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-26 07:14:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Semi-new player here (or at least I haven't experienced this before) What does Power Up Chance mean?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Games similar to SSJYP?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-28 14:22:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Other than the SM and YG games**, what other good tapping/rhythm games are there? Can be Korean, English, songs without vocals, whatever, just anything with some good music Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-29 10:47:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lmao at Tzuyu wanting to drink water from out of the Slurpee straw</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-31 14:09:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>It turns out JTBC clarified the [botox bottle](/spoiler) confusion http://tv.jtbc.joins.com/board/pr10010450/pm10042955/detail/n1204 TL;DR [Romeo saw Juliet swap the bottles and threw the botox away himself](/spoiler)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 08:16:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>The event is not bad, but only receiving rewards at the end is kinda dumb :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 13:35:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, a lot of idols this season Hopefully, they are all entertaining/contribute to the investigating and not just there for the views</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-02 13:56:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>SaiDa holding hands at the end</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 07:57:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>So it is just meant to say "Day6 songs clear: 20/20", correct ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-03 09:11:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Knowing Bros ep 76 One of the funniest variety shows imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 09:12:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is the show even real?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-06 14:21:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't think this is a very popular show cause I can't find much about it online, but does anyone know if there are subs for [Game Show](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Game_Show_(TV_series) ) ? https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Game_Show_(TV_series) Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-06 14:24:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is this separate to their Japanese debut?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-07 13:45:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apink and Blackpink back to back would be amazing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-08 09:03:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>so hipster</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-10 08:38:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Palette is my *jam jam* ?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-11 08:57:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>While the case itself was kinda obvious, the episode was still really entertaining. The sets eg. [The drug den inside the mountain, the mountain itself, Sehyung's secret hacking station](/spoiler) were all really cool, and there were lots of good jokes in there as well like [Sehyung as the nature guy and Kim Jihoon making fun of Park Jiyoon for having the same name as the victim](/spoiler) PJY and Jang Jin both did well investigating, and YSH was hilarious as always. KJH continues to do well in finding clues and is starting to become more light-hearted and have fun like he did in S2 I think Eunji's "problem" is that she's too focused on the case and finding evidence, instead of making jokes and being over the top with characters like the others, but I think she did pretty well this episode [I was happy for them at the end when all the main cast voted for the right person and they were all cheering, as well as when they revealed that Jihoon was the real father lmao. And I got goosebumps when they revealed that they were gonna go back to solve the serial killer school case](/spoiler) Overall, great episode with the cast improving and getting to know each other better. Hyped for next week and Kong!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 06:43:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>S1: Jinho, Kyungran, Sunggyu S2: Sangmin, Yohwan, Junghyun, Hongchul, Yooyoung S3: Dongmin, Hyunmin, Youhyun, Ahyoung (not really a genius, but she's entertaining) Last spot could go to Yoonsun (strong female), Doohee (because he got screwed the first time) or Yeonseung (to complete the top 3 of all seasons) Of course, S4 and the cast are still amazing and the people who make you go "wtf" about the casting definitely earn their spot, imo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is there a way to watch V Lives offline?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-12 09:53:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>^^ title, hopefully this isn't considered illegal EDIT: with subs attached as well Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 09:25:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>My inventory is way too full Please send help</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 13:12:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do they have an 'expiry date' thing where they disappear from your inbox?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-19 11:30:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>All my rewards just arrived :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-20 15:41:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sounds exciting! Cool concept, cool cast, if it's anything like Crime Scene then I'm in! Hopefully someone subs :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-24 09:20:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>He was a guest on the final 2-part episode of Season 2, so I guess they really liked him and decided to bring him back</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 15:27:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty good episode overall [Jang Jin finally becomes criminal breaking his streak: Check](/spoiler) [Criminal gets away with it: Check](/spoiler) [Master detective Pyo Changwon redeems himself: Check](/spoiler) [Makjang with many (maybe too many) twists and turns: Check](/spoiler) [Hilarious Kim Jihoon character: Check](/spoiler) [Bringing Jang Sungkyu as the victim was cool as well and he added a lot to the victim's story, especially since he was essentially a bad guy. Only bad thing was that since Eunji and Jinho were pretty much ruled out from being the killer early, they didn't really have many memorable moments other than their cute relationship and "jojang!"](/spoiler) Hyped for Sojin and I'm hoping the finale will have 6 suspects (5 regular + Jinho) with another guest detective, or a 2-parter where the detective becomes a suspect in the second half</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I just realized no one posted anything yet but...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 15:31:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Happy late birthday SSJYP!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>DAY6 covers TT/Knock Knock/Signal on Music Bank half-year special</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-02 15:43:57</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 01:36:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not bad, I didn't know they could speak this good English</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Song from show</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 07:02:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://youtu.be/fLXCa88hnW4?t=1h21m9s starts at 1:21:09 Can't find it on Shazam or googling lyrics Ignore the fact that the show is Korean and there are people talking over it, but I'm pretty sure it's an English song Lyrics: I'm feeling so lightheaded, I see you out and now I have to know if it's love or if it's alcohol</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 08:50:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>[I think they said he lied about losing the gun, since everyone knew Jang Jin had a gun, it would be obvious he was the killer because he still had it](/spoiler)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-03 15:22:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sucks that SFN lost approx 100K subs in the process :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 07:50:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know the first 8 eps of Aloha are out online, but where else can you watch other episodes of TH with eng subs?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 08:12:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>oh haha I meant, I don't have Netflix so I was wondering if there was any other links online</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-04 14:13:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're a lifesaver</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 02:07:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is anyone subbing Hyungdon's new show, Sherlock's Room?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-05 08:57:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is nice! I would do the same but I'm just too lazy ahah</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Will and Suppy: mortal enemies!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-06 09:46:48</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-09 15:20:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty good episode! I think Sojin would be a good person to fill the 'female idol' role if they make a Crime Scene 4</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-10 11:16:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Jennie skrt skrt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-27 13:19:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone here have enough free time on their hands to do some research and see if there are any other celebrities who were MIA during the filming period?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-29 15:12:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>One option is to wait for an event where all songs are unlocked (one just passed last week, so you may have to wait a month or so til the next event) However, I originally got SSJYP for Twice songs as well but as I played through all the songs, I found a bunch of new artists and music that I actually really enjoy now</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anyone know if the new stuff from the 3rd anniversary update of SSMTOWN will be added to SSJYP?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-10 13:59:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-11 14:41:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looks like Dongmin and Junseok are in Nopdong, and Chunsoo in Madong?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-11 15:08:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>New Dalcom coin currency which you can spend on: **A/S/R Card Selector** (basically just pick whatever card you want and you can get it but it's expensive of course), **Theme Exchange** (change a card to another random theme) and **10%/30%/50%/70%/100% Power Up Cards** (you can use these to upgrade cards instead of using other normal cards) Buy inventory slots for 50 diamonds, instead of 50 - gt; 100 - gt; 200 - gt; 400 like it used to be You can get R cards in PCP + higher chance of getting better cards overall It costs less to upgrade apparently, and higher success rates? Also costs 20,000 to upgrade S to R Takes longer for headphones to regenerate https://www.reddit.com/r/superstarsmtown/comments/6snubq/supplement_for_ssm_220_update/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-18 15:10:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is anyone confirmed subbing this yet?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-21 04:12:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>What is the bug?? Asking for a friend :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>What is the best way to organise your inventory?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-28 13:52:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Basically I have a ton of C and B cards in my inventory that I probably don't need, however I obviously need to double-check most of them in case I can power them up because that artist only has a few low cards. Recently I've just been buying more inventory space because it only costs 50 diamonds but that just delays the problem ahah So what is the easiest and most efficient way to get rid all of the low cards I don't need while making sure not to use cards that I actually do need? Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-08-31 14:02:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking of making my own one, but this is very useful. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-10 15:53:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tfw I thought nugu was short for 'New Groups' or something</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-11 12:04:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>What ever happened to Junho's song off his Japanese album featuring Sana? Didn't see much talk about it here</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-13 23:21:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Blackpink has only had digital albums so far, no physicals</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-24 15:16:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Idk if this is anyone from this sub, but Bumdi retweeted someone who said they were subbing the show! Subs out Tues/Wed according to them. https://twitter.com/Bumdidlyump/status/911637290618830848</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-24 15:32:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>This might just be a problem on my end, but I use the web app thingy on iPad and for some shows (mainly Knowing Bros which I'm trying to watch now), the episode loads and starts playing for a few seconds and then the app just crashes. Works fine on my iPhone and computer though Great site though, thanks for sharing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-24 15:35:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>iPad Air running iOs 9</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-24 15:44:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just tried and it crashes as well :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-24 16:07:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just tried a bunch of stuff and the main page seems to be working normally. On safari, when I click on to some shows, the page will load and then crash straight away, while on the app, it'll only crash after the video starts loading Also, it looks like the ones that aren't working are mainly variety-type shows, while all the dramas are working fine. Are they hosted on different servers or something like that?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 14:20:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry for the late reply! Works: Descendants of the Sun, School 2017, Men in Black Box Crashes: Knowing Bros/Ask Us Anything, Running Man, Law of the Jungle If it's too much trouble, then don't worry about it ahah. No one else seems to be having a problem and I can still watch on Phone or PC :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-25 14:30:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah okay, thanks for the help!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-26 15:03:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just finished watching the first ep, and then I come on the subreddit and see this Thank you so much for subbing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-27 15:49:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>If any of the boys are reading this, I feel like they should just make one of those SP7 channel trailers to introduce people to the series</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Are limited themes worth it?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-30 02:42:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Of course, limited themes are cool and look so pretty, but as a F2P person, is it really worth spending 100k RP everyday to try and get them? :((</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 14:09:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can a mod sticky this thread? Or put the links on the sidebar or something</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 14:11:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>There are download links in this thread [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/TheGenius/comments/70jog1/links_to_all_subbed_episodes_of_the_genius_s14/)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-12 14:14:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Burning time too ^pl^ea^se?????</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-21 12:56:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't you get the person who translated 4, 5 and 6 to do ep 3 as well or am I missing something? But good luck guys!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-25 11:22:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn, I wish this was a real thing like RV's red and velvet side :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 12:05:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Underrated twice song ahhhhh!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-27 12:07:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tfw you open a bunch of packs but then realise you haven't started the mission yet :(((</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Will there ever be a MV or studio version of Jihyo's Melody Project?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 14:13:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was so nice ^^^likeylikeygodjihyo</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 06:49:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>How long did this take ? omg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-06 08:02:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I admire your dedication ahahh</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-11-17 11:22:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Become a god and marry her manboy Anubis</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-15 13:47:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I thought they forgot about this tbh Such a good song  #128525; #128525;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-21 10:16:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Event tomorrow confirmed! ^^You #8217;remyheartshakershaker ](https://imgur.com/a/mbdci)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 07:06:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>The internet needs more nice people</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-12-29 16:52:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>https://gfycat.com/craftycreativegerbil</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 14:29:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Yoohyeon because of her great vocals and she's pretty af plus she's good at English :) 2. https://imgur.com/a/44f1g</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-01 14:32:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Finally R #8217;d all groups except Baek Yerin and Twice! (I still can #8217;t decide which theme to use cause they all so good)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Marmello's Hyuna  amp; Youna - Heart Shaker (orig. TWICE)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-13 03:01:58</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-16 13:55:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nayeon is too scared to touch Jihyo #8217;s butt :((</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-24 09:44:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is sooo good, hopefully there is a full acapella version on the album pleasseeee But it kills me because Sally basically does nothing the whole video :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 16:19:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Omg I can #8217;t wait for GoWon to completely ruin me</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-27 16:57:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tbh I think Chuu has the potential to be a decent power vocal, but right now she #8217;s too adorable and cute to be anything but cutesy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Red Velvet playing Bad Boy (The Perfect Red Velvet Night)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-01-30 03:38:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-02 03:59:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn, episodes already subbed. What a dream</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-04 06:32:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn, their chemistry was so good :'(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-10 03:53:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so underrated what the heck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 07:07:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone know how to listen to the show after it airs? There's a Sound K podcast on iTunes but it hasn't been updated since May 2017 EDIT: hasn't been updated on the Arirang website either :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 16:11:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah thanks Hopefully there are some kind souls out there!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 12:17:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Most depressing disbandment of 2018 :'(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-22 13:23:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've listened to iKON's Love Scenario so much, I think it's becoming a problem</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-24 14:19:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Selena Gomez - Outta My Hands (Loco)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7lhU_7XWQkE)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 01:48:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>What app is this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 03:23:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Haha no worries, thanks for the help! I #8217;ll look into it</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-07 12:27:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's probably managers or JYPE telling him to apologise. Idols have apologised for more stupid stuff in the past Also, netizens can get real crazy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-12 13:47:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>[The dance group's video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JYO5rAXsU9s) [CLC's VLive](http://www.vlive.tv/video/62545)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-15 12:09:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>The teaser where we get her name and face *is* the one that's coming out tomorrow, isn't it? Don't scare me like this, I'm still not ready for last girl</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 17:10:36</DATE>
    <TEXT> #8220;I wanna be a banana I do not want a banana peel ya #8221; **Best Lyrics 2018**</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-27 17:14:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Killer bass Killer beat Killer visuals I #8217;m dead already.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-03-30 02:10:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>JIGEUM BOGO SHIPEO</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 16:27:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is such a small detail, but seeing Sorn #8217;s cracked phone screen is so relatable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-02 17:05:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is so informative and helpful Thanks for taking the time to do this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>OH MY GIRL BANHANA ( #50724; #47560; #51060; #44152;  #48152; #54616; #45208;) -  #54616; #45908; #46972; (It Is Said) @ HOT DEBUT TALK SHOW (180402)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-03 09:25:42</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-04 13:44:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely different but I'm excited! [Also, EXID will be the guests in second episode!](https://twitter.com/OH_mes/status/981443431053647873)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-05 02:54:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wouldn #8217;t be surprised if Stray Kids came out before GOT7, just to give them more promotion Plus, the March event is ending and they have a bunch of pre-debut songs, right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 17:44:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, I believe so All other streaming platforms are working fine except vlive :/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sori (CoCoSoRi) - Greedy (orig. Ariana Grande)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-10 18:12:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Weekly Idol - First Episode with New MCs - Episode 350 (180411) [ENG SUB]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-12 14:17:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-13 17:07:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>That last shot is so powerful im getting chills</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-14 13:51:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>underrated group :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 15:47:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>That Twice + Stray Kids encore makes me so fucking happy  #128525; And the Somi and Twice behind the scenes as well</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-20 17:43:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it just me or does the drop of Shining Star sound similar to Twinkle's drop, but at like double speed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-23 11:18:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Great song by my girls, beautiful and catchy af! But why did they make the verses so low in their range?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 06:25:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Girl Front 2. See Saw 3. Chaotic 4. Rosy 5. My Melody 6. Kiss Later 7. Around You 8. One  amp; Only 9. Twilight 10. Sonatine It hurts me to leave out LCM, SITR and HA, but hopefully yall can rank them high. I gotta rep the underrated songs :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-24 17:39:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahah sorry about that, I agree I wish I could place all songs at #1  #128546;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-25 18:12:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, never heard of this show or actress before Is there more plot like this?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-26 17:14:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can #8217;t believe my girls have gone and done it again  #128565; #128557;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 16:09:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Obviously we don #8217;t know the full details of the 1 in 14,000,000 chance of defeating Thanos, but why didn #8217;t Strange just surrender the Time Stone earlier instead of waiting until after they all get their asses kicked and Tony almost gets killed?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-28 17:53:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>So cute, can't wait for their debut!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-29 10:50:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sometimes, I like to imagine Yondu didn #8217;t die, and he #8217;s just sitting up a tree in Wakanda, casually whistling while his arrow kills the massive horde of Outriders</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 12:42:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>That intro to Love Bug... OMG</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-04-30 16:25:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ooh yes, hyped for these girls!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-01 08:08:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ooh I haven #8217;t watched Elementary in ages, is it still good?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 00:10:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>OMG I would cry</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-03 16:20:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>No fucking way omg, I can #8217;t believe how powerful LOONA is and they haven #8217;t even debuted yet</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 04:20:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>But still no SITR choreo :((</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 04:24:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>It might be referring to swallowing cherries to travel to the different dimensions</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 04:25:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Go Won only drinks juice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-04 17:57:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>NO IM NOT CRYING YOURE CRYING</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 10:28:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think she kinda looks like Sally from some angles with that ponytail</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>New villains and A:IW</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-05 15:34:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>The Vulture #8217;s back story was related to the aftermath of the first Avengers movie Helmut Zemo #8217;s back story was related to the aftermath of Avengers: Age of Ultron What kind of cool villains and stories do you think we could get due to the aftermath of Avengers: IW?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-06 16:52:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don #8217;t remember the specific event, but they released 4 LE themes at once and everyone went crazy (in a good and bad way) SSM is actually having a lucky event right now where the first 1000 people to log in at a certain time can buy a LE card that was previously released But apart from that, I doubt they #8217;re gonna let us get previous LEs :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 17:17:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn, I like this way better than the obvious beauty amp;thebeast choice</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 17:21:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally just got back from Hungary and BBC already hard at work on teasers and MV editing</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-10 17:22:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love their choreo but more importantly, I love Miyeon #8217;s top ***LESS*** ***MONDAY*** ***MORE*** ***SODA***</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-11 15:23:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey youuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu - Around You KI KI KISSEU NEUN DAUME - Kiss Later Haseul's high run before the chorus in The Carol Sorireul ttara ttara dallyeoganeun neowa na - SITR AH AH IMAGINE - LCM Sarangi mweoga mweonji A to Z nan ajik mollado - LCM and GF P R E T E N D to be mad - Loonatic The beginning of Starlight ARE YOU READY and DAMN - Heart Attack Come and join us right now, it's just like girls night out - Girl's Talk Orakgarak I'm like see saw - See Saw Woah oh oh oh my life is rosy - Rosy</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 11:12:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wait what the fuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 11:37:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty cool concept actually Got baited by Steve #8217;s previous post :( , hope they do a React to SP7 in the future</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 16:38:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I found this pretty good interview of Koreans talking about it if yall are interested https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lg-h3eopyEM</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 17:12:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Throwback to  #8220;When four girls who denied the Garden of Eden gather, the party begins. #8221; And it #8217;s finally happening I CAN NOT WAIT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-13 17:20:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anyone have OEC #8217;s teaser schedule for comparison?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 14:55:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>What about Wong?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-14 17:08:18</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; You know, it #8217;s me, Chuu, No. 1 in LOO #928; #916;  #128540; Bless my girls, this just keeps getting better</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SUZY - Heart Shaker (orig. TWICE) @ 'WITH' in Taipei Fan Meeting (180512)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 12:57:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 15:32:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>1. Does this [Hwayugi OST](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pG06GddTS5U) by Jimin and Yuna count? If not, I'll be basic and say Excuse Me 2. Used to be Choa, but now I'll probably go with Jimin^hey</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 17:04:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty princess of the gays, Miss Go Won  #127821;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-16 17:09:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Holy moly this concept, what a mood</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 08:22:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Competition for Rookie of the Year will be tough :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 16:08:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>I hope they let Jisoo rest  #128542;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-17 17:09:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Based on OEC's teaser schedule, we may be getting the release date and tracklist tomorrow? Queens only.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-19 17:08:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Shit is getting real, boys and girls If we get LDN Noise tomorrow, I might die</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 17:05:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Bonus news: LOONA just tweeted this, lmao  gt; Grimes, You are LOO #928; #916; #8217;s goddess! It #8217;s an honor to work with you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-20 18:12:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahhhh looking forward to this, hope it #8217;s a mini album Underrated nugus fighting!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 13:12:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not gonna lie, I screamed when I saw this</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 17:15:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, like Rain 51db</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 06:41:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>bbgg#0720 I was browsing r/kpop when I came across Yves  #8216;new #8217; and saw that it had a lot of buzz around it. So I watched it and was so shook because the song was amazing and her dancing was amazing and she was so pretty. I then listened to all the other members #8217; solos and subunit songs and fell in LOVE, binging all the LOONA TVs and Woomanna. Then Chuu came out and she #8217;s both adorable and a power vocal. After that, I started following way too many Twitter and Instagram stan accounts... And that #8217;s the story of how I became LOONA trash.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 05:03:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahhhhh, they #8217;re all so adorable</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 15:43:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>(G)I-DLE already has more songs than Blackpink has had in 2 years How #8217;s that for shade?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 15:05:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree that the Cinema Theory videos shouldn't be allowed on the sub. BBC and the girls have explicitly stated that so I think we should respect it Obviously we know they're gonna be leaked and all over Twitter/Discord/Streamable etc, but that can't really be stopped easily and if BBC wants it to be removed, they'll contact that person eg. loonacunt directly. However, since this is a public subreddit and it's the "official" one, I don't think we should condone it since it's technically illegal Yes, this doesn't really make sense but I hope you understand what I'm trying to say. Yes, we're all gonna watch it anyway but I think since this is the "official" subreddit and we're "representing international fans" in a way, I think we should just play it safe and not participate in spreading the exclusive vids</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-27 17:09:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oof, only bops allowed in the Garden of Eden I can #8217;t believe BBC would tease us like this, love4eva part is the exact same as the MV teaser :( I #8217;m excited for One Way, anticipating Chuu belting out some power vocals in the final chorus Those minor notes in Rendezvous18.6y are also real funky and weird, can #8217;t wait</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 11:13:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the definition of slayed</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 11:18:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Did someone say summer? So happy to see AOA back!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-28 17:05:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don #8217;t mind me crying tears of joy over here, my LOONA TV withdrawals were going through the roof And omg they filmed them at the airport, ICONIC</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-06 17:23:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is 99.9999% never happening, but imagine a collab or reality show with all the English-speaking idols, just messing around and having fun or doing karaoke with a bunch of Western songs...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Upgraded Secret Base Trade Master</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 10:26:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>If he offers you a trade and the Pokemon he wants is not currently in your party, you have to reject the offer. But because you rejected the offer, he will offer you a different trade when you go to talk to him again. So how are you supposed to know what Pokemon he wants in return, go catch that Pokemon or get it from your PC, and then go back to him and accept the offer?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 11:36:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah nice thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-10 17:06:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Literally shook right now, this is some legendary shit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-12 12:06:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is just such a fun and cool song DPR WE GANG GANG</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 11:23:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it still worth getting?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 11:56:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was gonna make a joke about the Jackson 5 but they're actually doing a cover of their song what the fuck</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 12:03:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maknaes were the best while unnies did the worst lmao, this was great</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 12:46:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Physical albums in Japan?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 12:49:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone know if albums are available in physical stores in Japan the day they are released? Or if not, how long does it take for them to be available? Also, are there a ton of Kpop fans in Japan which means the album will sell out quickly? Thanks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>yyxy Repackage Dates?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-14 13:35:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I decided to scroll back through LOONA's Instagram to compare Max  amp; Match's schedule to now October 17th | Loonatic (English Ver.) teaser :-: | :-: October 19th | Max  amp; Match teaser October 20th | Kim Lip teaser October 21st | JinSoul teaser October 22nd | Choerry teaser October 23rd | Loonatic MV released October 24th | Max  amp; Match track list + description October 25th | Group teaser October 26th | Sweet Crazy Love teaser October 27th | Max  amp; Match album preview October 30th | Group teaser 2 October 31st | SCL released Also, there's a new moon on 28th June so we might end up seeing something then So what are your thoughts on the repackage's release? Will there even be one this month? Will there be a You and Me Together/Loonatic type MV for yyxy and what song?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-15 03:50:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I #8217;m mainly looking for Korean albums Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-16 16:43:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>take all my uwus</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-17 17:15:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you #8217;re surprised they ***didn #8217;t*** spoil anything at their concert lmao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 13:53:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! Is it easy to differentiate between all the different trains?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-22 14:18:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah nice thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-26 03:09:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>If LOONA wins, I really might cry tbh  #128557; #128557;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-06-27 04:10:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sexy summer concept hype  #128525; #128525; Also, check out Ashley #8217;s [YouTube channel](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCfB2E_culXfbKpxr7KqzV3Q) if you haven #8217;t already!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>All my shortcuts are gone</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-01 01:52:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>I opened up Narwhal last night and found my shortcuts all wiped and no longer there. I added a few important ones back, but when I woke up again this morning, all the shortcuts were gone again Pls help, thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-06 17:16:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scamberry :( But all 12 signed solo albums for the winner? Holy moly  #128525;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-07 17:04:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Meme queen Hyunjin</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-08 15:58:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven #8217;t started watching Idol Room yet but does anyone have a list of all the segments they #8217;ve done so far? Does it feel basically the same as when they were on Weekly Idol?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 00:50:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for all your hard work!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 00:50:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you very much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 06:31:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>BP and Twice interactions here we go</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 11:08:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chaeng struggling to reach the fruit was adorable  #128525;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 11:11:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not gonna lie, Nayeon starting the song in English had me a bit shook</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-09 17:18:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m so proud of our girls and of our ORBIT fandom!  #128557; #128557;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 08:50:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn, this looks really good if true</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-12 15:40:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sponsored by Marvel Puzzle Quest? What a dream  #128525;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 05:37:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>DTNA probably next week, with a new event and theme?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-13 17:20:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>It #8217;s finally happening and debut is almost here too! LOONA and Orbits ^or ^tteokbokki fighting!!  #128149;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-14 06:01:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>UWU INTENSIFIES</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Autumn and Bruce play Jurassic World Evolution</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-15 04:19:41</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-16 05:14:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>omg she looks so good?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Sorn (CLC) - 007 : CLC IN THAILAND (Part 2) @ PRODUSORN Diary (180717) [ENG/KOR SUBS]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-17 12:55:01</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Coco (CoCoSoRi) starts Kickstarter for 2nd solo single "Sugar Cake"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 05:22:15</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 09:51:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice, this is really cute Especially Louis</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ashley (Ladies' Code) - HERE WE ARE + ANSWER + How Far I'll Go (orig. Ashley + Auli'i Cravalho) @ Rooftop Live (180717)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-18 12:44:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>* [Ashley - HERE WE ARE](https://www.vlive.tv/video/80662) * [Ashley - ANSWER](https://www.vlive.tv/video/80660) * [Auli'i Cravalho (Moana) - How Far I'll Go](https://www.vlive.tv/video/80661) * [Full Rooftop Live](https://www.vlive.tv/video/79968)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-19 11:19:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't believe we've been blessed with so many great GG and solo comebacks recently  #128149;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-20 15:42:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>If that's the case, then I don't think South East Asian and Pacific Islander should be grouped together</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-21 11:16:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there a full version of the encore? At the end of the video, you can see Jihyo invite Yerin and Eunha to the front</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-23 03:33:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just reading this gives me chills</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-25 17:24:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Remember how excited us Orbits were for Line amp;Up and the OT12 performance at the end? This will be like 100x bigger...  #128565; #128565;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 15:38:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>This sounds pretty good! But the teaser says July 30th release and assuming it's KST, shouldn't it be out already? EDIT: [iTunes link](https://itunes.apple.com/us/album/wild-single/1415368646)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 15:56:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah yeah you're right, found it on iTunes, thanks Looking forward to the MV</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-30 17:17:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>HO. LY. SHIT. We #8217;re in the end game now Orbitches</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-01 12:56:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>My uwu meter is off the charts</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-03 04:42:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cube are you okay</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 16:56:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>RIP my faves haseulogy and loonasbian :((</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-04 17:17:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ahhh can #8217;t believe I forgot about this, I could never imagine Twice doing a song like that but we can pray That phat bass is fucking lit though  #128525; #128525;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 11:28:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>*EVERYTIME I COME AROUND* *ANOTHER BAD BOY DOWN*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-06 16:26:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Check out some of Yoojung's choreographies if you haven't already, her dancing is amazing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 11:07:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now I understand what it feels like when reactors go crazy and jump out of their chair because HOLY SHIT ORBITCHES I CAN DIE HAPPY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-07 17:22:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess we #8217;ll have to wait for an official line distrib or a dance practice where we can see who #8217;s singing, but I think it #8217;s kinda BS if they really gave Vivi, a perfectly capable singer, no lines at all in a song EDIT: Ignore this because Vivi actually does have lines, nvm The others (eg. Hyunjin, Haseul, Chuu, Go Won), I am fine with. I #8217;m sure they #8217;ll get their  #8220;share #8221; of lines in other songs. On another note, I #8217;m really happy we got to see JinSoul sing quite a bit and not rap in favOriTe, but I wouldn #8217;t mind if we got a hard rap by Jinsoul and even Heejin and Choerry in the future ^BBC ^pls</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 17:12:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it just me or does this look like a school photo lmao</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-09 17:09:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I like to think BBC reads all our comments and is like "Hmm okay, we'll give Orbits some hope with this animal theory and release Yeojin today", and then next teaser they'll post Olivia and completely fuck up everything</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 03:06:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey Ash!! How long had you been working on Here We Are and how hard is it to learn the singing and dancing? I personally thought that your vocals were quite high, compared to some other LC songs Also, is it possible if you could post some song covers on your YouTube channel? Thanks! Love your username btw hahah  #128525; #128525;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 11:48:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry for jinxing us hahah :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 11:55:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let's go with Yves next! And LOONA for ROTY :')</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Yujin (CLC) - Dangerous Woman (orig. Ariana Grande) (Performance Video)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 12:08:17</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-12 17:16:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello we love Haseul</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-13 11:24:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Daaaamn, fromis_9 really impressed me! Time to start stanning if they start to do more stuff like this Wish they performed HandClap for longer than like 30 seconds though :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 17:08:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>DID THEY FINALLY FIND YEOJIN OMG ITS BEEN OVER A YEAR</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-14 17:12:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Damn this is pretty neat, I didn #8217;t think I could get any more hyped So, day unit is the happy 1/3 concept and night is dark OEC concept?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-17 17:02:03</DATE>
    <TEXT> gt; 1, 44, 72, 104, 195, 231, 265, 297, 420, 450, 483, 542  gt; The times full of anticipation and hope, sometimes full of tears and love. Now towards the 684 days of LOO #928; #916;, Hi High</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-18 17:06:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>Screamed when I saw this tbh Go Won our tap dancing Broadway princess</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 11:04:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>AVENGERS INFINITY WAR FOUND DEAD IN A DITCH</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 11:39:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>The camera struggling to fit all the girls in frame is such a mood</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 12:05:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>When the instrumental cuts out in Stylish.... oof gives me fucking chills</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 11:22:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>To be fair, it has only been two weeks and they didn #8217;t really promote much (apart from the concert?). Hopefully more Koreans will know about LOONA when they do proper promotions Another thing I think is that because favOriTe got released first, it took away abit of the OT12 hype, and also it being a dance, girl crush type track which is much more favorable to the international audience</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-21 15:22:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is an even stupider crime than the first, I love it  #128169;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-22 14:40:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nice this is pretty smart, thank uu for compiling this!! I went Japan recently and I think the most recent AKB48 song they were promoting is called Teacher Teacher. Some of the Produce 48 performances are probably also pretty popular there atm</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 04:20:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>Reminder that you have to vote for at least 10 songs or your vote won't be counted!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 12:17:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ugh someone was cutting onions while I was watching this I'm so proud of them  #128557; #128557;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-23 16:23:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Seeing the views go up in real time was crazy! Hopefully they are legit and more people are finding out about LOONA :))</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Support Gift Project for Haseul!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 16:42:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-28 16:43:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Some fellow kind Orbits have started a Gift Project to raise money for a custom in-ear monitor for our leader Haseul! Feel free to donate as much or as little as you want, all info is in the Twitter thread linked or you can check out their [gofundme page](https://www.gofundme.com/haseul) Thanks, hope you can support and share this around!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-30 17:30:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ok this is gonna be fucking lit</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-09-02 17:05:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is the perfect Oh My Girl concept  #128525;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>