<INDIVIDUAL>
  <ID>subject47</ID>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-20 13:24:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Chapsticks. Always. Never fails. I've invested more money in the Chapstick industry than anyone I know.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-20 13:27:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Same here. I stopped carrying make up in my bag for that reason. But chapsticks... That will always be a mystery. I like to think that someone's fucking with me and I'm not as irresponsible as I think.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-22 09:27:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>What a scumbag.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-26 11:30:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>What the hell is a paradox? I have googled it MANY times and I still don't get it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-26 12:50:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm still... This is why I don't ask... Thank you for trying though, I appreciate it. :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-26 20:21:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>This really helped guys! Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-27 10:52:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't get it. Oops.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-06-29 16:49:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can heavily relate to this post. Especially the point about people who speed up when you try and pass them. I got into a terrible car accident and ended up totaling my car because of that asshole.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-05 13:37:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Driving to the community college that I will be spending my freshman year at... Now it's not so much the driving as it is the college.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-08 23:56:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>'Murica.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-14 11:19:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish I could go with a more positive experience, but definitely having gotten arrested for possession of marijuana during my senior year of high school. I lost a lot of "friends" in the process of this whole mess and received a little more heat than necessary from the court system. I know this isn't the most significant or interesting thing and shit like this happens every day, but my decision heavily impacted my life in every aspect. Texas is one of the worst places when it comes to criminalization of drug offenders. I got hit with a years probation, $600 in fines, 80hrs community service to a place 20 miles from where I live, urine and hair follicle tests one after the other, and not to mention the evaluations, tests, and courses I've had take. This whole process plus my $700 bail bond from ADULT county jail (I was 17 at the time) and hefty bills from my lawyer dried out my parents financially and emotionally during that time. All this for a tiny gram of pot on school campus. I had no drugs in my system either-- I just got unlucky. While I don't think weed is that big of a deal, I do regret putting my family through all that mess. I was nearly expelled from school and passed up my college application deadlines so I'm forced to attend community college for my first semester. I had to put a hold on relationships, cut ties with people, and give up a few things. My reputation as a good kid was suddenly stained by bring dragged out of my school in handcuffs. Teachers never looked at me same and people that I once thought cared, no longer did. I didn't understand WHY people made it into such a huge deal though. I didn't kill a child or try to poison anyone. It's just WEED. TL;DR-- brought drugs to school, got arrested in front of student body, screwed my senior year in HS over and family financially.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-14 11:22:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Say you're pregnant. This works for both genders. Bonus points if you're male.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-07-14 13:36:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Howdy there! Thank you. It really is a truly awful thing to have to go through. The Texas criminal "justice" system is fucked up beyond repair.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-06 18:02:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think we, as Redditors of Houston, would be doing you an injustice if we didn't say SOMETHING about the weather... We have dry winters and wet summers. It gets to be pretty hot here. I can't give you a specific time frame but let's put it this way: our springs are mostly a wave of cold fronts and our summers are hot and muggy. But don't worry, as a Houstonian you'll get very used to it. It "snows" about once every 2-4 years. And Christmas eve last year was about 70F. This isn't to serve as a warning as I love Houston and wouldn't want to live/work/die anywhere else! It's just a friendly fun fact! Don't bother packing TOO much heavy winter couture as you may only wear it once or twice a year. Good luck! Feel free to correct me for inaccuracies, guys! Isn't the weather beautiful today?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-06 18:11:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>He said he'll be coming to Houston this Friday (10/11/2013).</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-06 18:17:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Mine isn't so much passive aggressive "funny" as some of the other comments buuuuuuuuut... When 14 year olds claim to be bisexual but would "never date or kiss" the same sex. I-- I don't understand...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-06 18:19:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Only the classiest of places of course! Omegle.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-06 18:20:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>If I wasn't so poor I would give you gold...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-10-07 04:44:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, I wouldn't even call it snow. It melts the moment it touches the ground. And that's great! You're prepared for the weather!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2013-12-31 05:53:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>What area are you interested in shooting in? I've been looking for a buddy to shoot with lately.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-15 06:25:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Are you drunk yet?"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-01-27 05:23:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Scrolled down through the comments looking for this song exactly. Thank you. *weeps*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-13 17:34:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>The best thing about this gif is that none of the cats actually make it. Thank you for sharing, OP. :')</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-13 18:28:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't ruin this for me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-02-13 18:53:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>stahp</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-03-09 18:29:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>"Sun  amp; Moon" by Above  amp; Beyond http://youtu.be/HY1jBSSamzU</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-16 19:01:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Long time lurker here, but I just had to say congratulations. You must feel insanely accomplished. Just keep up the amazing work!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-17 05:46:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>You went from a 44 to a 38. Any goal for you is possible at this point. Good luck! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-04-25 18:48:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I am too another female that would love to contribute or help out in anyway I can! Edit: sort of maybe replied to the wrong comment. Offer still stands!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-05-05 05:52:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm driving down the freeway... all drivers in every lane line up unevenly and drive at the same speed... Approximately 5 miles under the speed limit. It turns out that it is like this everywhere I go. Welcome to my personal hell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-03 05:06:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>The title of the article is very inaccurate though.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-11 02:00:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>They're so precious! But I'm still wondering why they don't just leave the cubs with their mother? What's the benefit to hand raising them vs. leaving them to be nursed and raised by mommy?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My cat has some sort of death wish.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-20 19:51:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Found this gem in a dollar store.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-06-20 22:57:23</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-20 07:50:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Gorgeous! And I'm seriously digging the bold lip. That color is perfect on you. Also I know this isn't the point, but I love the sticker on your back windshield.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-07-25 08:59:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I don't even understand how the picture and text are related.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>So I started a food blog and I thought that I'd share it with the lovely people of /r/food as well! (x-post /r/cooking)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-05 19:15:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, redditors of /r/food! I posted in /r/cooking as well and hope to get some attention here too! I started a food blog and I lurk a lot on this subreddit as well and always wanted to to share my recipes. However, I've always been a little shy. I hope to start getting a little more involved in the food community of reddit and figure that this is a good way to start! CCW and if there's anything you guys would like to see for me to either do or improve on, let me know! Thanks! My website/blog! http://www.movedatdough.com/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-05 23:39:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely! And thank you so much for saying that. Hopefully I'm going to start posting on /r/foodporn as I come out with new recipes!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-06 15:58:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Definitely Benjamin Netanyahu. If he can kill thousands of woman and children at a time, I'm certain that I wouldn't feel an ounce of remorse for taking him out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Anyone else on My Fitness Pal?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-07 05:45:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hey, guys! I know there was a post about this not too many days ago but I was wondering if there were any other redditors in this sub that use My Fitness Pal. I only have but 3 or 4 people added and I would love to create a network of support! My username is "realisticcats" If anyone else is interested, I definitely encourage you to post your username for others to see. I don't know about you guys, but I'm the kind of person that definitely needs support or other people's eyes on me to keep me in check otherwise I lose motivation. I'm only 3lbs down so far as I have only begun my journey a few days ago and could use a boost. :) Thanks in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-07 06:19:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>On it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-07 06:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My first post to /r/foodporn and it's beef yaki udon! [OC] [1024x978]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 01:10:02</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 02:19:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! It was. I'll link you to the recipe if you'd like once it's up on my blog? It shouldn't take but 30 minutes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 02:39:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 03:07:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>That means so much more to me than I can tell you. Thank you! I just started a food blog and it's not super popular yet so I don't get as much feed back as I would like to. So seriously, you made my day. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 03:08:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Boom! http://www.movedatdough.com/tender-beef-yaki-udon/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 03:08:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 03:14:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I'm definitely *not* here to do that. There are some pretty good submissions here though. I'm just so happy to be one of them and hopefully I can do this regularly!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 03:28:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>For those of you who would like the recipe: http://www.movedatdough.com/tender-beef-yaki-udon/ **edit:** Maybe I'm not doing this right by responding to everyone's comments but everyone's words mean **a lot** to me as a 19 year old newbie food blogger! **edit #2:** For those of you who had questions about the meat, here is what I've managed to find by calling my butchers!  gt; Okay update! So I called my butchers (for those of you who live in Texas, I get my meat from Central Market), and they said that the name of the cut actually IS Sirloin Fajita and that not all stores have it. Apparently it's just a special kind of cut. He did recommend either using a flank steak or skirt. While they DO have the same kind of grain and look very similar, the fat content and tenderness of the meats are not the same. Like I said, he did suggest subbing in a flank or skirt steak. Not exactly the same but it's close enough! Sorry for all the confusion guys!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 04:54:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>THANK YOU!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 05:13:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>At first i was like, BUT WHHHHHHY?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 05:14:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>And so it can be... just make it at home. Super easy! I shared my recipe. :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 05:14:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so so so much! Yet another comment that means a ton to me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 05:29:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's awesome. If you do end up making it, let me know how it comes out!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 05:50:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>...yes.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 05:55:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't add it. I just used them as a garnish. :) Let me know if you try it out!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 06:02:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>How's it going?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 06:20:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're asking the wrong person, bro. I basically live here. On the internet.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 06:44:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>AWWWW! Thank you so much! If it helps anyway, I'm working on my English major and I'm a total goof.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 06:45:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, thank you, thank you! If/when you do, please let me know! Really interested in seeing how it comes out for others. I try making my recipes as easy and as fun to follow with the pictures and all. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 06:50:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much! When you do, let me know! I'm excited for you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 07:02:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! And daniel-san?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 07:17:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Miyako's! It's not really local (I think?). They have a delicious beef, chicken, and shrimp udon! I personally like my take on it better. But Miyako's is gooooood stuff. http://www.miyakosushibar.com/houston_japanese_restaurant.php</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 07:18:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I meant to scatter them for the sake of an artistic photo but uh, really failed. I chose the wrong place mat for that. LOL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 07:22:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm flattered! How can you hate udon?! Is it the texture?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 07:25:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've been meaning to watch the movies. I hear they're putting it on Netflix! Or did they do that already?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 08:08:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.movedatdough.com/tender-beef-yaki-udon/ So if you go to my site and scroll down about a little over half way I actually even posted a picture of the package! the brand name is Myojo and it's instant udon noodles. I bought it at an Asian market here in Houston, Texas called 99 Ranch! Thank you for the compliment!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 08:10:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't be jealous! You can easily make it yourself. There's nothing too special in it and I posted a link to the recipe so you can enjoy it too. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 08:28:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I guess I know what I'm going to watching now!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 08:30:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>Within the recipe and a wok! ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 08:40:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Once again, I cannot tell you how much that means to me! You will absolutely be seeing more of me! I've always been really shy about posting pictures of the food I make or even commenting on a thread here. Now I feel very welcomed and appreciated. I know it's just Reddit but cooking is so personal to me. Thank you so much for your kind words. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 08:41:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have left overs and if it makes you feel any better, I would totally share them with you if I could!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 08:57:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's so flavorful and delicious. Surprise her! ;) And thank you so much! Honestly, I don't even try. It's so nice hearing such encouraging words for something I didn't put much effort into.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 09:12:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I linked you guys to the recipe above! All the details and step by step process with pictures is there. :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 09:13:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good luck on your journey! I'm on a diet too and this bowl was only 439 calories. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 09:26:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yeah, I actually did that on purpose but totally failed because the place mat has ridges. I just wanted to eat my noodles already so I left it. LOL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 09:29:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks! I can't wait for you to try it either! To be honest, I can't think of a substitute. If it's a religious dietary restriction, does it help that the alcohol cooks out during the cooking process? I can't think of a substitute that isn't alcohol so I say just skip it all together if you must. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 09:31:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely! And I'm a girl, haha.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 09:43:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll accept it.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 09:45:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh, right then. Well it's only 2tbs so I have doubts that white grape juice will incorporate as much flavor. I'd just skip it. It'll still taste delicious! :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 17:04:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>The vegetables came out perfect! No, I wouldn't have steamed the carrots if I had added any I like it when my veggies still have a little bite to it but are still wilted and warm. And yes, veggies did go for about 6 minutes. :) I can't wait for you to try this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 17:04:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yay! Please do!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 17:05:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>I say Asian markets! I got mine from an Asian market in Houston, Texas called 99 Ranch. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 17:06:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Really? I just woke up and didn't see the comment. Thank you so very much and I'm sorry about your SO! LOL</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 17:07:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually haven't gone! I thank you so much for the tip!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 17:07:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually get my 5 spice and rice cooking wine at regular markets and I have seen udon too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 17:08:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's totally sirloin fajita meat. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 17:18:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's what the cut is called but honestly I think it's flank!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 17:23:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well then thank goodness it's just a placemat so I can just give it a firm tap outside!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 17:33:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oops, that was my bad for thinking it can be both. Really, I'm only familiar with what cuts work for what dishes and I know that this particular one works for udon because it's so tender. At my butchers the label said "Sirloin Meat for Fajitas (All Natural)" Nothing else. :( Sorry I couldn't be of much help.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 17:41:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Maybe it is a skirt steak then! Probably is. I need to work on my cuts of meat, lol. I'm excited for you! :D thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 17:54:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Do you not live somewhere that has them? :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 18:03:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think it's hanger steak but oh my gosh, they look so alike! I'm going back to my butchers to ask exactly what cut it is today and I'll be back with an update and I'll be sure to make a change on my site!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 18:23:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! This is helpful. Well said!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 18:27:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>**Okay update!** So I called my butchers (for those of you who live in Texas, I get my meat from Central Market), and they said that the name of the cut actually IS Sirloin Fajita and that not all stores have it. Apparently it's just a special kind of cut. He did recommend either using a flank steak or skirt. While they DO have the same kind of grain and look very similar, the fat content and tenderness of the meats are not the same. Like I said, he did suggest subbing in a flank or skirt steak. Not *exactly* the same but it's close enough! Sorry for all the confusion guys!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 18:29:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, I'm going to copy and paste what I said above to another commenter about the meat because I'm lazy. :D  gt; Okay update! So I called my butchers (for those of you who live in Texas, I get my meat from Central Market), and they said that the name of the cut actually IS Sirloin Fajita and that not all stores have it. Apparently it's just a special kind of cut. He did recommend either using a flank steak or skirt. While they DO have the same kind of grain and look very similar, the fat content and tenderness of the meats are not the same. Like I said, he did suggest subbing in a flank or skirt steak. Not exactly the same but it's close enough! Sorry for all the confusion guys!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 18:33:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>It was at Miyako's! Like I said, not super local, but definitely a good place for sushi and noodles if you haven't been there before. http://www.miyakosushibar.com/houston_japanese_restaurant.php</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 19:36:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds delicious! Winter peas are also an awesome idea. :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 21:24:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>What do you suggest? :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 22:40:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually don't use MSG. But the pink peppercorns and sesame oil sound like lovely additions!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-08 23:19:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've never seen it either. But it's a big supermarket. It's called Central Market. It's partners with a grocery chain in Texas called HEB. I wish I could give you more details. But I don't know, honestly. :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 01:54:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my goodness, I nearly jumped out of my chair when I opened that image! That makes me so so so so happy that someone tried it! Please feel more than welcome to leave a comment/rating on the actual recipe on my blog by the way if you get the time. Your adjustments sound delicious and I'm sure others would appreciate the suggestion! Sriracha sauce is life. Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 03:05:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yay! That's so awesome! Did you enjoy it? Did you make any adjustments to it? It looks great. Feel free to stop by my recipe page once more to leave me a rating/comment. That makes me so happy that people are actually making it! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 04:14:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually really like your bowl. Mine was a gift from my mom. She got it from the Asian market I've been mentioning-- 99 Ranch Market here in Houston, Texas! I looked at the bowl and there's 0 branding on it so I can't even tell you what company made it. I'm sorry!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 04:15:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you live in Austin then you have Central Market as well! :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 04:20:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh perfect! Yeah, I believe the carrots can account for some sweetness. :) Where did you find your udon? I'll definitely be on the lookout for that brand! Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 04:24:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well H-E-B and Central Market are pretty much the same kind of store anyway, am I right? Oooooooh, are you trying out the recipe?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 04:26:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh gosh, how did I not guess that? I used to work there.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 04:29:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Nope! I'm half Ukrainian and half Jordanian. But I love me some good Japanese food. I've actually never tried mentaiko! What do you make with it?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 05:14:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh god, I wasn't paying attention to your user. ; _________ ; I'm sorry.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 05:21:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you, I'm so happy you gave it a try. :) I'm definitely going to hunt for Japanese markets and higher quality ingredients. And that's nice! I bet you have some great recipes yourself you need to share.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-09 05:31:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Honestly, I don't measure either but obviously if I'm going to share my recipes I have to measure everything out. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-10 12:16:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>When you say to respond with love instead of hate during the upcoming AMA, what do you mean exactly? How do we go about that? Because I'm harboring some serious negativity for their "misunderstandings." I'm finding it difficult to come up with anything that's not going to be considered hateful.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Back again with cheesy whole wheat pizza from scratch! [OC] [1024x678]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-12 05:11:49</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-12 05:13:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>The recipe for anyone interested! http://www.movedatdough.com/perfect-whole-wheat-pizza-dough/ My recipe for the pizza sauce is also on there. And I promise not to reply to every single comment this time, lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I was told that you guys would enjoy this: Cheesy whole wheat pizza from scratch! (x-post /r/foodporn)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-12 21:49:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-12 21:51:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here's my recipe for the dough: http://www.movedatdough.com/perfect-whole-wheat-pizza-dough/ And my recipe for the sauce: http://www.movedatdough.com/easy-homemade-pizza-sauce/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-13 18:57:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>:D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-14 21:36:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Those look divine! And such a lovely picture too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-16 07:52:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yay! Happy you enjoyed. Definitely feel free to make adjustments to your taste. :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Its my baby bithday</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-18 00:58:39</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Its my baby bithday [x-post /r/trashy]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-18 01:08:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-18 01:11:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh I'm sorry, it slipped my mind. Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-18 23:30:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're asking all the right questions that have no answers.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I made some moist blackened tilapia for dinner tonight! [1024x678] [OC]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-20 02:28:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-20 03:44:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Recipe for anyone interested! http://www.movedatdough.com/blackened-tilapia/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-20 03:51:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>The secret ingredient is cream cheese. I've made this recipe before. They're so incredibly soft and delicious. http://www.justataste.com/2013/09/secret-ingredient-best-chocolate-chip-cookies-recipe/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-20 04:03:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>"We're going to go ahead and brush the tops with butter. Real butter. If you use margarine, we're going to have to stop being friends." Thanks for sharing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-21 08:19:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think my vagina shriveled up looking at this.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The magic of Macy's!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-22 02:29:40</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-22 03:24:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was livid. Especially since school starts next week and I completely hit pan on my last one! I called customer service and they were apologetic. They're sending me a new one in exchange for the broken one. But according to the conformation email, it ships out on the 25th. The day classes start. Yay! The Macy's next door to me is sold out of my color so all I can do is wait. :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-22 05:42:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I usually use my card to buy clothes and such from them. And I got an email advertising free shipping, so I figured, hey, why not buy some makeup? Never doing it again.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-22 05:58:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry to hear that! Along with the LM finishing powder, I also got the Anastasia brow powder and it was one piece. Only the foundation suffered. I say give it a shot anyway. I'm just disappointed.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-22 06:15:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks, that's a good suggestion! I actually thought of this. But the powder was just everywhere when I opened it and I was too furious to make it my responsibility to fix. If I had broken it, then that would have definitely been an option. But it arrived in the flimsiest packaging In this condition. I paid $46 dollars for it to come in one piece. Not to have to fix it myself. :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-22 07:13:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have to send it back, unfortunately. I wish I could keep this and fix it AND have a new one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-22 07:32:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's such a bummer! What website are you ordering from?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-08-22 19:06:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>Already on it. ;)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Mouthwatering lasagna rolls with meat and 3 cheeses! [OC] [1024x678]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-02 20:41:10</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-03 03:07:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's actually not a cannelloni. I took a sheet of lasagna, spread the fillings, and rolled it up. Is that still considered cannelloni?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-06 22:24:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's beautiful! Great job!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-14 07:20:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have something similar that I picked up from Jordan when I spent the summer there. They're pretty great! They burn for A LOT longer and I also find that the smell and over all effect on the tobacco while burning is very pleasant. They don't crumble apart the way other coals would. I highly recommend them.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-16 18:08:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now that's just fucking adorable.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-20 07:40:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>Don't bring weed to class.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-20 07:42:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sunscreen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-20 16:31:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was thinking of Skincare Addiction.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-22 06:49:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's incredibly elegant! I'm so jealous.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-22 06:53:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're so beautiful. I can't think of a single person that can pull off a lippie like that. Your eyes have a lot of character too. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ulta makeup haul courtesy of my SO. Featuring Too Faced, Urban Decay, Smashbox, and a few other goodies!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-22 19:33:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-22 20:02:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dude, it was **so** hard. but I couldn't do that to my SO, lmao. I love the angled crease brush! It's really soft and picks up product well. I was not expecting that!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-22 20:10:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Would you do me a solid and link me to the brush?! I'm seriously lacking in the face brush department. I should I have put down a product and went with a blush or powder brush of some kind. :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-22 20:14:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not one to use iPhone emojis on reddit but...  #128525; #128525; #128525; #128525; #128525; #128525; #128525; #128525; #128525; #128525; #128525;.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-22 20:29:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sorry about that! http://bit.ly/1x1R4Mt</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-23 00:11:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're all ladies in my heart.  lt;3</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-23 01:19:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're asking the wrong person! All of this was his idea. Never asked for it and never had to drop hints. I guess he just knows what the vagina wants, you feel me?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-23 04:45:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're very welcome. Thank you for the compliment!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-23 17:01:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually did not know that! Is that online or in store? I'll tell my SO. Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-23 17:03:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! I bought it without even swatching in store because I wanted it just to complete my Pulp Fiction collection. I LOVE IT! And I'm glad you enjoy it too!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-23 17:38:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ugh, I love their phased out palettes. I have the Too Faced Naked Eye palette and from what I've seen, it has been discontinued. Plus, I love the packaging. My SO has the receipt. Man, you have me all excited now! Thank you so much for telling me this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-09-27 16:53:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cloudy With a Chance of Meatballs. I would certainly enjoy a chance of having meatballs every time the weather gets a little crappy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My friend's cats: Beavis and Butthead! It's not hard to tell which is which.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-02 22:39:05</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-07 19:44:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm on mobile so I'm going to apologize for formatting in advance. I have pretty dry to normal skin and a little bit of rosacea on my cheeks. I've had problems with especially dry and patchy skin in the past but my face has never looked like this up until a week or so ago. Sorry for the crappy pictures... This is embarrassing for me. You can see the redness, breakout, and texture of my skin. Even with makeup, it looks disgusting. http://imgur.com/n36WrMf http://imgur.com/UctJCxS AM: -Clean amp;Clean morning burst skin brightening facial cleanser -Neutrogena Oil-free face moisturizer for sensitive skin PM: -Clean amp;Clear night relaxing deep cleansing face wash -I usually moisturize with coconut oil after this and go to bed. This has been my routine for pretty much my whole life. Never had the need to change it up. But now I'd really like to start fresh and do something completely different but I'm so clueless. I do wear makeup but never had this issue before. I don't know what to do and people are starting to notice like my mom, my sister, and my best friend. A lot of times, those little red dots with come to a tiny head. Usually I just leave it alone but sometimes pop them. I don't take vitamins regularly, I'm not on birth control, and I don't drink water as often as I should. Not sure if you guys need this info or not but I really don't know much about skincare at all. Any advice, home remedies, or product recommendations would be so appreciated! Thanks in advance! :) EDIT: uploaded the same picture twice.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-17 01:13:40</DATE>
    <TEXT>I scrolled through this thread just to find this. Chuckie has effectively traumatized me as a child. I can't even look at the movie poster without my heart jumping out of my chest.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-30 06:38:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>The shittiest gift I've ever received were knockoff *used* Victoria's Secret body mists. I'm a photographer, and last year, as a gift to a friend of mine, I gave her a photo shoot with her fiance. I gave her all the photos on a USB, fully edited and polished. I mailed it to her since she lives 45 minutes away from me. Later that week she calls me crying about how much she loves the photos and that she has a gift for me. I was to meet her in the middle so I can pick it up. I refused at first because that's not why I took pictures for her. She was persistent, so I gave in! Yeah, not sure why I'm providing such an extensive back story for this. But it's always a crappy feeling to put so much effort to people's gifts and not receive as much in return. It's the thought that counts though, right?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-30 06:42:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>[Apple filled]( http://donutdb.com/img/donuts/72/bite.jpg)... *hnnnnggggggg* Great, now I'm craving a donut. Sigh, now if only my city still had a Krispy Kreme.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-30 07:26:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Legally Blonde. If I have no internet or Netflix is acting up, I have a backup of Legally Blonde downloaded on my iPad. I can never get sick of that movie!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-30 07:54:03</DATE>
    <TEXT>Pretty much what went through my mind! I try not to judge, but it's not like she's struggling financially or anything. Just thoughtless! :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-30 07:56:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Get this in my mouth. Now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-30 07:59:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>"no homo lmao" Just... stop.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-30 08:26:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>On the Internet, yes. But not when it's in real life of course. It's usually followed by retarded chuckle!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-30 17:14:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>You put my feelings about people who do that *so* perfectly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-30 17:17:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It did not, unfortunately. We're not even that close of friends.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-30 18:22:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I finished my bottle (squeeze bottle? idunno LOL) of Laura Mercier's tinted moisturizer SPF 20. I have dry skin that can be sensitive to certain products or have foundations look patchy on me. But this... this stuff, guys... It's my holy grail product. It had damn good coverage for just being a tinted moisturizer. I'm sad for now but I will be repurchasing during the VIB/VIB Rouge sale!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-30 18:30:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yay, I'm so excited! This is my first exchange. I have high hopes that I won't be discouraged from doing it again next time if things don't turn out. I've heard waaaaay too many stories about being swaplifted. Hopefully these new rules will prevent that. Good luck to everyone!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-31 01:26:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes, Hogwarts is beautiful. You should share pictures of your school now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-31 01:35:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>That Sara McLachlan animal abuse [commercial.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9gspElv1yvc) Gets me in the feels every time.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-10-31 01:50:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel you-- I've gone through *so* many different eyeliners just to figure out which ones are best for tight lining. Unfortunately, I've found that no eyeliner won't transfer at least a teeeeeeeeeny bit. That being said, my holy grail tight lining product is [Too Faced's bulleteproof liner](http://www.sephora.com/bulletproof-24-hour-eyeliner-P387588?skuId=1626258)! It hardly transfers to your waterline at all. It's pretty damn black and super easy to apply. I think that has something to do with it being waterproof. Nevertheless, I highly recommend it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-13 07:48:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>WHAT? WHERE?!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-15 20:49:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>You have the kind of look I'd expect to see in an 80's film (compliment!). Your color choice is perfect here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-15 21:11:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>I once cashed in 500pts for a perk I found at a Sephora inside JC Penny. I just happened to be there when I saw it gazing at me from across the room... Sorta. It was a Tarte perk. It had a deluxe sample of Tarte's blush in "exposed," an olive green gel eyeliner, an eyeliner brush, a sample of Lights, Camera, Lashes mascara, a translucent finishing powder, and a dropper of their Maracuja oil. I ended up loving all the products except the eyeliner which dried out SO quickly and got to the point where it would crumble off of my lids even if it were still creamy in the pot. Also, the maracuja oil smells really weird and as many times as I've used it, I see no difference in my skin. :( So basically this; http://tinyurl.com/lox2kym (except that green shimmer was replaced by a gel eyeliner + a brush)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-16 03:56:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I think that's just how it is tonight. Today is my first day back at Toontown since Disney closed it. It has been super laggy and the district I was in has been reset. Ugh.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-16 04:27:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>LOL not sure why I'm getting downvoted for that, but alright.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-19 10:32:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's a perfect idea! I'm so excited to see Houston near the top of this thread!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-21 01:53:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Laura Mercier smooth finish pressed powder, Dior Diorshadow mascara (black), Tarte Amazonian clay blush in dollface, and Fresh advanced therapy lip treatment (aka the holy grail of lip balms)! These products haven't failed me so far. I've been repurchasing these things for years now.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-28 22:44:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>wait... srs or not srs? ; - ;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-11-30 07:38:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Not OP, but Stila's liquid liner was my first ever mid-high end eyeliner and I've repurchased more times that I can count. I'm not a master at wings, but the felt tip pen makes it so easy and effortless. Plus it has stood up to sweat and tears. I can rave about it all day! So yes, 10/10, do recommend. Very easy to apply and totally worth the $21.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-02 09:24:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure, I'd love to have you as a friend! My toon's name is Freckles. 54 laff, peach cat. I'm usually on pretty late as well. Let me know whenever you're on and would like to add each other.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-02 09:53:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sure am! Where would you like to meet?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-02 09:55:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>COMINNN!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-04 08:45:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>What are we looking at, OP? Is that palette too difficult for you to store?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I envy whoever gets to pull all that plastic off the windows.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-04 08:54:30</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-04 18:50:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well that's disappointing to hear. EDIT: "go hear" h8 U mobile.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-05 03:37:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! I was heading over to Central Market and just stared.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-05 09:26:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>Now I know what I'm making for breakfast! This looks so incredible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-06 23:09:29</DATE>
    <TEXT>Could you maybe show us some swatches? :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-07 00:49:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>I purchased Sephora's in-house baked luminizer in "stardust." It's only $14 which I thought was a steal. I also got a Tarte creaseless concealer that I've been meaning to try and wasn't able to score it during the VIB/Rouge sale. And Clinique's High Impact mascara! $20 off my purchase left me at $39. I wanted to grab the Nars lip pencil in "Dolce Vita" and "Bettina" but they were sold out.  #128532; http://i.imgur.com/m7t5QoT.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-07 02:53:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! I tried it this morning. I was pleasantly surprised with the coverage. The formula is pretty thick too. I put a couple of dabs around my eyes and on my trouble spots as well during my routine-- HUGE MISTAKE. A teeny tiny amount goes a long way. I ended up using waaay too much. A *small* dab in the inner corner around each eye will do the trick, use a beauty blender or a concealer brush (I used the Eco tools one). All in all, I really really like it! If you're interested in a before and after or a swatch, I'd be more than happy to do that for you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-07 03:25:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>ON IT, BOO.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-07 04:32:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>As promised! http://imgur.com/a/6P4yI</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-07 04:50:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>DAMMIT! I was heavily considering purchasing this as I had quite a bit of money to spare when I received the email. Hauled a few things off of Sephora instead. The regret I currently feel is... *strong*.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-07 04:51:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're absolutely stunning! That lip color suits you so well. I love it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>my super modest makeup collection!! omg guys it's so small, how embarrassing !</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-07 05:09:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I did a before and after using Tarte's Marcuja Creaseless concealer and thought I'd share it with everyone! I think I found my holy grail.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-07 06:13:50</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-07 06:17:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>no ccw, k?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-07 06:57:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I highly recommend it! It's a pretty thick formula (very creamy) and little goes a loooooong way. It's $24 at Sephora! I have a problem with creasing more than I do dark circles themselves and I'm happy to say that this stuff did an amazing job. I didn't even use a setting powder.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-07 19:17:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely! I did this in front of my crappy lamp late at night so the lighting wasn't great. I'll get that done for you when I start my routine! EDIT: Alright, so it's super dark and cloudy outside and I can't catch any natural light. Hopefully tomorrow will be sunny and I'll definitely give it another go. So sorry!  #128532;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-07 19:20:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually haven't tried it. And honestly, it was a either this or the KVD one. I went with Tarte simply because I love the brand and haven't tried KVD products before. I'm super interested in finding how it compares though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-08 00:47:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I can PM you a better picture on another day if you'd like?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-08 04:30:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>I definitely swear by Tarte! Still super interested in trying NARS as well. Let me know if you end up getting a hold of it please!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-09 21:18:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>Cheese. I hate cheese. I can't stand the smell, taste, or texture of it. You know, unless it's on pizza or something like that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-09 21:20:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>You're a good man for this. Thank you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-09 21:58:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>A word for when something gets stuck in your shoe.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-10 00:05:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Apologies. I knew that was going to happen, lol.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-17 08:19:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have yellow toned dry skin as well and I second this comment! Bobbi Brown's skin finish seems to be the best I've tried so far (out of brands like Tarte, Laura Mercier, Benefit, etc). I wear Warm Beige 3.5 and it's perfect. 10/10 do recommend!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-18 03:09:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>It looks great! I personally think you could have used a lighter hand on the inner part of your brows though, as they seem a bit harsh in that area. But of course that's just my opinion. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-22 07:30:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm seriously impressed. I love how you kept the look classic Grinch and also what you did with your eyebrows. You're so talented!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>That fish has seen some shit.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-23 00:50:38</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-23 18:34:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>That was fucking stressful to watch. I hope that crazy bitch gets what she deserves.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-24 18:12:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>What?! So did you propose?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-27 20:13:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Um, no products list? The rest of us may also want to achieve the butthole look too. *reported*.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2014-12-31 08:31:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Commenting in case anyone finds it! I'll be on the look out myself.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Good Girl Gina is secretly hood af</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-01 23:29:47</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is this what it's come down to, Facebook?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-05 21:06:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>When a nigga at the club</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-05 21:21:53</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-05 22:45:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is a very thoughtful thing to do for your wife! Bless you.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-06 05:41:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>*NOOOOOOOOO*</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-08 06:57:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>I owe them a trip in the next 30 days anyway. I'm already half way to Rouge for 2016 (oops) and they sent me 10% off code to use by then. My Sephora doesn't have them in store yet so far though. Thanks for your response!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-08 06:59:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did do a quick search and did not see that. Thank you! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My Sephora haul, ya'll. That Rhymed. Plenty of never before seen goodies inside! Just kidding. [swatches included]</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-09 05:16:24</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-09 05:37:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>bless u 5eva /u/gordonshumway85. Seriously. I did not know that. Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-09 05:37:59</DATE>
    <TEXT>:** shucks</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-09 08:58:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>We probably would be.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-09 09:06:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh my god. I fucking love this. Not Tryna step on anyone's toes here, but 2015 banner? yas?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-09 18:51:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm on the fence about it tbh. I redeemed the 500pt reward for it after I placed this order at my Sephora, not realizing that now I'll have two of the masks. Let me just say that the texture is very interesting and very gooey. It's super black and opaque. Instructions say to liberally apply it to your face avoiding all of your hair, eyes, lips and brows. No lie, this shit will rip your hair out when it's time to peel off. But the only way to get it to peel off is to apply half of that sample. Because if it's too thin, it won't peel off. So I wouldn't say it's at all economical and it has REALLY mixed reviews. I don't like the smell much either. I did notice my skin was super soft afterwards though. I peeled off what I could then used a warm cloth to remove the rest. I'm meh. I say try it! But I wouldn't purchase the full size. That's just my opinion of course. Some say it's their holy grail mask!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-09 19:46:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Anytime! And I say 100pts on the mini but of course it's all up to you. There will definitely be better rewards, skincare or not, for 500pts.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-09 19:53:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>This is my first Sephora blush in that form. I have their cream blush which I freakin' LOVE. Like, that mf does not go anywhere and it provides such a beautiful glow. Anyway, so this particular blush is totally buildable and the texture is super smooth. It's not super "buttery" and not especially creamy either. But it's softer than the Tarte blushes if you're familiar with those. It's easy to pick up product with a light sweep. And it was only $15, mind you! If you're considering buying it, I say go for it.  #128527;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-09 19:54:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>I know what I'm having for lunch today.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-10 01:02:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tried the face wash last night! I used a cleansing balm (clinique) to remove my makeup, exfoliated, then went in with the face wash and holy hell I need to buy a truck load. What the packaging does not mention about this wash is that it has an amazing icy cooling effect to it! I really enjoyed the S amp;G wash and my skin felt **super** soft and clean after using it. 10/10 srsly.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-10 01:23:56</DATE>
    <TEXT>I called the Rouge hotline and apparently it's a holiday special exclusive to sephora. They currently only have 210 in stock on their site, according to her. So I will definitely be hoarding a couple to get me through the year.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-10 01:28:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've used this before and it felt like the exact same thing: http://i.imgur.com/FqUOeQk.jpg But seriously, I do feel like there are better options than that mask.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-11 20:36:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>can u lippie swatch under nicks malk so we can actually identify those colors? then maybe this post won't be a complete waste of everyone's time. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-11 21:12:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I second your opinion! Both of OP's necklaces are good looking. I just think a dress like that could better benefit from something more simplistic. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-11 22:41:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I will definitely look into that. I'm always open to trying new skincare products.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 02:09:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yay! I'm so happy you got to play with everything. I love this look for you. I'm also very excited to see that the NYX lip cream doesn't make you look Nicki Minaj-esq.  #128514;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>It's my first week on Keto and I plan to slowly but surely take over my parent's pantry.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 03:01:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 03:06:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>You should just put that behind you and look forward to doing a better job this time! You managed to lose 20lbs the first time which is a huge accomplishment. You clearly know what you're doing and I have full faith in you! Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 03:22:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>Both my dad and I LOVE cooking. I have more spices than we can even fit in our cabinets, so I think I'm set there. Is there any particular one you like using the most? :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 03:26:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did hear about that. Keeping them in stock just in case. Maybe like breakfast replacement of sorts. As a full time student, my upcoming schedule is practically going to keep me in school from 7 in the morning till 7 in the evening. I read that lots of people like to keep them handy in case. Thank you for the reminder, seriously. I need to keep that in the back of my mind! Edit: I cannot spell.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 03:30:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm crossing my fingers. I'll try to only have one for if I reeeeally feel like I need it. All this information is so helpful as newbie. Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 04:31:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Absolutely! This is just my pantry of back ups. I love fresh homemade food. I usually don't eat processed at all. I'll make an exception for the Atkins bars though. I actually have a food blog. Although I've been on hiatus, I plan on plunging back in and adding some keto friendly recipes to share with everyone. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 04:32:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I GOTCHU, GUH.  #128076; #128149;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 05:51:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've got plenty of that in the fridge. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 06:11:02</DATE>
    <TEXT>Real food is in the fridge, of course. I'm not going to live on the contents of my pantry but I do like to have options. I've been getting plenty of eggs, salads, keto pizzas, and some stirfrys. I just like to have these things in my pantry as someone on the go in case of emergency.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 08:59:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yassss! And it's damn delicious! http://www.ruled.me/low-carb-pepperoni-pizza/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 20:30:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Yes! What brand is it? Shower me with recommendations!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 20:31:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>What brand is it?! :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 20:39:26</DATE>
    <TEXT>I haven't used it yet but it smells divine! I bought it from World Market of you have one of those where you live. In the exotic food/snack sole they have an entire wall dedicated to sugar-free Torani syrups. The had all the classic flavors to special kinda like the Belgian cookie, salty caramel, maple, etc. I even got a tiny travel sized one to keep in my purse in case of "emergency."</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 20:40:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can't live without it! Ever whipped it with a little mayo and put it on a sandwich? It's delicious.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 20:41:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>World Market! If you have one in your area, that is. They have tons of flavors!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-16 20:48:12</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ooh, they have it at GNC. I'll be trying it for sure. Thank you for this!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-17 05:20:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>I made tacos wrapped in lettuce as opposed to low carb tortillas. I grilled chicken thighs in a homemade marinade (chipotle Tabasco, various spices, mayonnaise), wrapped them up in a lettuce leaf with heaps of avocado, queso fresco, sour cream, and a couple light shakes of tabasco. They were sooooo delicious and quite filling! 503 calories, 5 net carbs</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Starting a circle of fellow /r/Keto-ers on My Fitness Pal?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-20 00:18:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there a group of fellow keto Redditors to join? I tried doing a search but it seems that all posts about MFP are older than 5 months with mostly inactive users. Would anyone like to add me or comment your username below so maybe others can add you? I'd really like the support and to be able to support you guys as well!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-20 00:19:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>**username:** dasme_ :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-20 00:57:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much! I had no idea how to search for groups!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-21 05:28:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>That looks delicious! A good way to get a lot of water out of your zucchini is to slice it the way you want it, lay them out on a tray with paper towels, and give it a heavy sprinkle of salt all over. Let it sit for ~10 minutes and you'll see all the water being extracted from it. Just make sure to wipe off the water and excess salt. You can do this with any vegetable with high water content. Also, I too made a keto lasagna tonight! My recipe was a little different than yours though but still absolutely delicious. http://i.imgur.com/zo4jOli.jpg</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-24 06:01:36</DATE>
    <TEXT>Looking at these photos made me so hungry. I love it. Great job!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-01-27 07:41:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>http://www.myfitnesspal.com/profile/dasme_ :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Katy Perry came in like</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-02 02:49:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-02 07:06:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's in reference to Katy Perry's performance during the halftime show. :) http://youtu.be/J4ZfjQw0hqY</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[Measurement Check] calculator says I'm a 38E/FF -- currently wearing 36DD</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-07 01:31:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hello, everyone! This is my first time posting to this subreddit after lurking for so long. I've read everything I could on the sidebar including the rules, but forgive me if I make a mistake here or there. I live in the U.S., if that matters! Anywho! With the help of the size calculator and measurment guide, I was determined to be a **38E/FF** with the sister sizes **40DD/E** and **36F/FF**. I did the best I could and my measurements are as follows... * Under bust (snug): 40in * Underbust (tight): 34in * Over my breasts (upright): 44in * Leaning at 90 degree angle: 47in * Laying down on my back: 44in According to the breast root guide, I seem to have narrow roots. Very similar to the first set of photos in the blog post. As for breast projection, by the looks of the spectrum guide, I seem to be most similar to "bust I." I currently wear bras from Victoria's Secret, all of them being a 36DD. My breasts are always spilling out of them and it's super embarrassing because it usually shows through my shirt. They're obviously ill fitting. It looks like [this](http://bit.ly/18VUozH) but with a tad more spillage. That is **not a photo of me** by the way. It's actually one of the first photos that pop up on Google when searching for "ill fitting bra." I really hope I provided all the information I was supposed to! Thank you to everyone in advance. I really appreciate it and have always loved how helpful everyone is in this community. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-07 01:40:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>I just stretched it out as much as it would, went up to about 38. Honestly, the band is super comfortable and I haven't had any issues with it being too tight, leaving marks, or being too loose.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-07 05:12:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I really appreciate it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-07 18:50:05</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm full on bottom. My breasts aren't that firm either. Even with the sidebar, I can't find a link to an online store with those bras you mentioned. :( All I can find are t-shirt bras. I like a little more support than an average t-shirt bra. Where can I find the Cleo Lilly/balconette? Is there a store where I can walk in and try on a 38E/F? I hear Nordstrom is a good place to do that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-09 06:51:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Frying queso panela in a pan with some butter is amazing. It has its own saltines and gets slightly crisp and browned on both sides. It's delicious!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[FP] I finally perfected my recipe for keto carrot cake cupcakes with a cinnamon maple frosting! Just in time for my birthday next week.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-11 23:21:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>So as I said, my birthday is coming up and I fucking LOVE cupcakes. I absolutely do not want to cheat and I love this diet too much to do so anyway. It's been exactly a month and I'm closing in on 10lbs down. I feel so much better and my skin looks clearer than it ever has. Anywho, I'm not a fan of cheesecake and I don't much love the idea of a meat cake (blasphemy). So I've been trying to work out the kinks in this carrot cake recipe for weeks now. I've finally achieved a spongey moist carrot cake with a rich and maple-y frosting! It's truly delicious and pretty much indistinguishable from a regular cupcake. http://imgur.com/Aj0UXeB This recipe makes 15 cupcakes and enough frosting to ice 24. For the cake-- * 3 eggs * 1/2 tbs caramel flavored syrup (sugar free of course) * 1/2 tbs vanilla extract * 1/4 tsp maple extract * 1/4 cup melted butter * 1/2 cup organic unsweetened Apple sauce * 1/3 cup unsweetened coconut milk * 1/3 cup brown sugar Splenda * 2 1/2 cups almond flour * 2 tbs coconut flour * 1/2 tsp cinnamon * 1/4 tsp nutmeg * 1/2 tsp baking powder * 1 tsp baking soda * 1/4 tsp salt * 50g finely shredded carrot * 15 pecan halves (for garnish-- totally optional) Frosting-- * 8oz cream cheese * 2/3 cup of sugar free Pillsbury vanilla frosting * 3 tbs coconut milk * 1/4 tsp cinnamon * 1/4 tsp maple extract Preheat the oven to 350. Mix the almond flour, coconut flour, baking soda, baking powder, cinnamon, nutmeg, and salt in a bowl and set it aside. Separately, beat together all the wet ingredients and the sugar using a hand/stand mixer (if you have one, otherwise a whisk works great too). Add the dry ingredients until well incorporated and then fold in the shredded carrot. Scoop even amounts of batter into 15 cupcake liners. Bake for about 18-20 minutes or until the toothpick inserted comes out clean. Allow them to cool before frosting! For the frosting, beat the softened cream cheese, sugar free vanilla frosting, maple extract, coconut milk, and cinnamon together in a bowl. Decorate each cupcake with a tablespoon of frosting an a pecan halve on top! You will have left over frosting, by the way. Each cupcake is 8.2 net carbs and 230 calories including the frosting but not counting the pecan as a garnish. I'm not super proud of using a pre-made frosting as a part of my icing but after testing the recipe out a thousand times, I found that it just tastes so much more like the real thing this way. The cake is spongey and moist and the frosting is rich and so delicious. And I realize that this isn't the healthiest recipe in the world, and neither is it the lowest in carbs. But I love baking and can't imagine a birthday without cake. I just thought I'd share for those of you who are interested! EDIT: The cake on its own is 7g net carbs and the frosting is 1.2g for a total of 8.2g net carbs.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-11 23:43:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Unfortunately, I tried using light olive oil and sunflour oil in two separate tests, it doesn't give the moisture, true cake texture, and flavor. With the brand I use, half a cup of organic apple sauce adds 5g net carbs to the recipe. I tried doing my best to cut out and substitute ingredients to make this as low carb as possible while trying to do minimal damage to taste and texture. Unfortunately, apple sauce was not one of these things. :( Thank you for the suggestion, I appreciate it greatly! I'm absolutely willing to tweak this recipe further in the future with your suggestions!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-11 23:48:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Please do! It's so worth it. And if you end up making substitutions, share it with me. I'm always looking for ways to improve. :D</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-12 00:03:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I feel like not everyone will have an EXACT same breakdown of carbs per ingredient as I had because some brands have a lower or higher amount of carbs depending on what brands are available to you. As soon as I get the chance, I'll provide you with a breakdown of my own! And I completely agree with you. I tried going for more coconut flour and less almond but the result was awful and pretty much inedible. I wish I had taken a picture. The consistency was terrible, flavor wasn't so bad. But I'd rather have no cake than eat what I made that day LOL. It came to a point where I'd rather take the plunge and ration my carbs just to have this cupcake, in all honesty.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-12 00:28:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Here are the screenshots from MyFitnessPal! Sorry they're iPhone screenshots. These are of course total carbs not counting fiber and the frosting isn't counting sugar alcohols-- I already did that math for you guys LOL. The apple sauce comes from HEB/Central Market (a grocery store here in Texas). Brands that got cut off in the screen shots are Torani (caramel syrup), 365 Whole Foods (butter), and So Delicious (coconut milk). http://imgur.com/a/PUhXn I hope this helps!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-12 02:16:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I tried that. I can show you the bag! It was disgusting as well. The cupcakes sank in the middle and had a bitter aftertaste.  #128557;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-12 03:50:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much for helping me try and find ways to spare on calories. It means a lot! I spent a lot pf money in groceries (mainly the almond flour) and threw out a lot of cupcakes for this. I'll continue to experiment and come back with an update if I crack the code!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-12 19:25:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually have not. I didn't know I could. That's going to be my next test! Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-12 19:26:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let me know how you like it! It's easy and SO delicious!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-13 08:30:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>What stretch of highway are you taking?! You don't take 45 back and forth? That sounds horrible.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-14 08:00:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Parks and Rec!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ol' dickhead ass</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-18 00:04:16</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-18 17:52:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I didn't know that subreddit even existed. Subbed!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Ol' dickhead ass (x-post /r/blackpeopletwitter)</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-19 07:09:18</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-23 17:51:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I definitely feel your pain-- I just got done with testing this recipe last week and just added it to my blog last night. I hope it's something you're looking for. http://www.movedatdough.com/keto-carrot-cake-cupcakes/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-24 01:02:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! That means a lot. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-24 06:53:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Sugar free BBQ sauce? Can you suggest a brand or two? I'm have a hell of a time trying to find some good keto friendly BBQ sauce. As a Texan, I used to slather that stuff on *everything*.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Kuzma just mildly enjoying the ride to my University</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-25 04:09:19</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-02-25 22:00:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's an Abyssinian!  #128512;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-03 04:55:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just a few hours? I was out of it for the whole week!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Saw the cutest polydactyl cat today at the cattery. Her name is Lee and I wish I could have taken her home!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-04 05:21:43</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>HIFW my SO takes me shopping</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-04 21:46:31</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-04 22:11:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I agree! She's gorgeous and only a year old. I'm pretty sure someone is going to scoop her up soon.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-12 06:16:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>I sent you a pm! :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Classic Kanye</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-03-19 06:33:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Female cat is really puffy around her abdomen? Please help!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-03 22:30:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Species: Feline Age: I'm not sure, my mother think she's about 5 years old. Sex/Neuter status: female/spayed Breed: I can't tell what breed she is. Body weight: 9lbs History: She used to belong to our asshole of a neighbor. When he moved out, he left her behind. She hopped into our backyard and I felt bad for her. She's extremely well behaved, playful, litter trained, so sweet and is very affectionate. After bringing her cat food for a month, we gave her a flea bath and kept her inside the house with our other cat (male/Abyssinian/12yo). She's been in the house with us for about month now. We noticed her abdomen area was very puffy when we brought her inside. She loves to lay on her back and stretch and it makes the puffiness visible. It's especially visible when she's wet (bath time). I'm very concerned and will be taking her to the vet soon. But for now I'm waiting on my mother to get her insurance just in case it turns out to be something serious. Does anyone have any idea what it could be? She doesn't seem bothered when we touch it and she doesn't cry either. Either way it doesn't look normal at all. I've never owned a spayed female cat either. Here's a photo of her when we gave her a bath a few days ago: http://imgur.com/9OgMu4X And her just generally laying down and chilling out: http://imgur.com/zS6RXFk http://imgur.com/kjukYXN http://imgur.com/HFEg7DY General location: Houston, TX Thank you so much to everyone in advance! I apologize for formatting as I am on mobile. I hope I provided enough information.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-04 02:00:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>He's already had so much misfortune as it is. His house was on foreclosure (fraud and other problems with the FBI led to this) and was forced to move. He was also the bad apple of our neighborhood. He adopted her for his son who hardly ever got to see and just neglected her. Thank you so much for reassuring me! I'll be jiggling her all the way to the vet next week.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-04 02:01:38</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you for your response! We'll be taking her this following week for a wellness checkup.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-04 02:02:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>We're taking her in for an appointment this week! Thank you for all the information. I can breathe easy now. My mom kept bringing up the "c" word and it psyched me out.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-23 20:55:43</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually think their selection of salamis and sausages are great. They're different from other delis and markets. I'm half Ukrainian and have been going to the Russian store ever since I could remember. It is small and narrow, but they have a pretty awesome variety of imported cookies, cakes, and candies. You should definitely go and show me your haul! You should try the moscovskya kalbasa (Moscow kielbasa) and their Hunter'a sausage (they look like long sticks). Their bacon and veil sausage is also delicious! Just get a little of everything. Try the tarkhoon as well. It's a green soda. It should be sold around the deli somewhere. Enjoy your spread!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-23 20:58:10</DATE>
    <TEXT>If it exists in Texas, try Spec's! The Russian general store doesn't sell hard liquor from what I've seen.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-04-26 05:41:34</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was at Miller outdoor theater and I saw it. I'm pretty sure it was a shooting star though!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-12 17:55:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>If your designer hadn't located the Coke machine, what do you think you would have used for the entrance instead? Your bar is gorgeous and really unique. I haven't seen anything like that here in Texas! EDIT: evil autocorrect</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-12 23:21:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>I actually am in Houston. I'll absolutely check it out. Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-25 04:41:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>That looks delicious! Where can I find those ice cream cones? And that particular brand of ice cream? Is that from Whole Foods or Trader Joe's, perhaps?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-05-25 05:17:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-05 21:19:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's... Is this legal?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>This notification from QuizUp</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-08 05:30:59</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-11 04:48:53</DATE>
    <TEXT>That's because it's a WORKSTATION.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-15 18:04:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>I also live in Houston and would like to know what kind of spider this is so that I can select the right rifle/tank/blowtorch to protect myself and my family against it. Seriously. What is that? I've never seen in my life living here.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-15 18:10:17</DATE>
    <TEXT>Why are you wasting your time with mascara you PLEB? Get yourself some eyelash extensions and refill them as frequently as possible. Then post a selfie onto here TIPSY AS FUCK to show them off!!!! :) glad I could help, loveyyyyy.  lt;3333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333333</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-15 18:12:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>But did it taste good?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-15 20:32:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>Then love and a cup I shall give it. Thanks!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-17 07:54:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>OMG I'm always late to these things!!!!! you are SOOOOOO brave and unique! Now my question is, if you could have your boyfi build you your very own battle station with his womanly hands, what shade of teal would it be?????? ? ??? ??</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-21 23:31:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Everyone ITT seems to score almond flour for $8-8.99! The cheapest I can find in Texas is $8.99 on a rare occasion. It's $9.99-11.99/lb on average here!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-07-24 00:48:45</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love how shimmery the eye look is. My CC is that you are looking a little washed out and I think a nice warm pink lipstick would help this look out a lot!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-07 00:55:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Wow, that Chickfila employee handled that situation so well. She was so sweet and patient. I'm glad Vante fired that jerk. Fuck him.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>If Blue Bell don't taste the same...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-24 06:51:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 04:19:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Legally Blonde.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-25 04:32:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>I was 19 and he was 36. It doesn't sound too bad when you think about it. But he had an old guy mentality that made it feel like I was doing a 70 year old.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I really like this nude gradient lip I did this morning! CCW is always welcome.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-28 02:27:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-28 02:34:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Products list! ~FACE! Clinique Dramatically Different moisturizer Est #233;e Lauder Double Wear in "pure beige 2C1" Tarte Maracuja Creaseless Concealer in "fairly light neutral" Too Faced Chocolate Soliel Bronzer in "chocolate" Sephora cream blush in "coral flush" Hourglass ambient powder in "luminous light" MUFE setting spray ~EYES! ABH Brow Powder Duo in "auburn" ABH clear brow gel Too Faced eye primer Inglot eye shadow in a shade that matches my skin color. I can't seem to get the shadow out of the palette. :( Laura Mercier creme eyeliner in "espresso" Sephora eyeliner in Infinite Beige Tarte's Lights, Camera, Lashes mascara ~LIPS! Josie Maran lip and cheek oil in "limitless pink" Mac lipstick in "peachstock" Too Faced Melted lipstick in "melted berry"</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-28 03:36:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-28 04:26:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>OMG! Cherry Cherry Bang Bang looks gorgeous! Are they available in pretty much all drug stores now?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-28 04:31:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hopefully we have them at my local CVS or Ulta. I'm going to check it out. Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-28 06:04:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! I used a little of the lip and cheek oil all over my lips and applied Peachstock all over. I then lightly dabbled the Melted lipstick inside the center of my lips and used a lip brush to blend the two colors into each other without mixing it too much. I used peach stock again and repeated the step with the Melted lipstick. I just kept blending so it didn't look too weird. I'm really bad at describing things so I hope this helped.  #128557;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-28 06:13:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>Good luck! It was actually pretty simple. I think any good peachy nude + berry pink will help! The lip oil underneath helped with blending a lot, so definitely try and get your hands on something with a similar consistency to wear as a base.  #128064;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>My carb splurge breakfast when I have zero carb dinners. I present to you, LC French toast!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-29 01:15:29</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-29 01:17:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>I've lost 55lbs since January and decided to treat myself to my ultimate craving since dinner tonight is going to be zero carb and I had a date with my treadmill soon after. Some of you will probably crucify me for these ingredients but here's how I made it: 2 slices of Nature's Own high fiber bread (7g net carbs each. 1/4 cup heavy cream 2 eggs 4 pumps of Torani's SF French vanilla syrup 1/2 tsp cinnamon 1 tbs butter Whisk the cream, egg, syrup, and cinnamon in a shallow bowl and saturate the two slices of bread roll everything is absorbed. In a pan, melt the butter and fry up your custard soaked bread until it's golden and crispy! I did this over medium heat then turned up the heat towards the end to get it crispier. I topped mine with a thin slice of butter and a light drizzle of Hungry Jack's sugar free pancake syrup. I've tried 3 different brands of SF pancake syrup and Hungry Jack's is by far my favorite. It's sweetened with Splenda and it's NOT runny. Ate it with a side of SF whipped cream, 4 small cut up strawberries, and 2 slices of applewood smoked bacon! Macros according to MFP: http://imgur.com/CnAyUFN I accidentally grouped two slices as one serving. I meant it to be a slice per serving as when I make this, I only allow myself one slice. So take that as 7g net carbs a serving, not 14g (unless you're doing both then that's 2). Tastes exactly like the real thing I've been craving for SO long. I don't find myself starting to slip, developing cravings, or stalled when I have this for breakfast so as long as I track myself accordingly for the rest of the day. EDIT: Serving info.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-29 03:41:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'll take this to /r/Keto instead then. Thanks.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-30 01:17:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you! This was my first time putting my face on reddit. Glad it went well.  #128514; #128150;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>SWATCHES OF MY FAVORITE MAC LIPPIE AND OTHERS  lt;3333333</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-31 03:20:09</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>I have a couple of questions about the rec center</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-31 03:30:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm sorry if these questions have been asked before. This is my first semester at UH using the rec center and I had a few questions. First, what's the best times to go? I plan on being there by 7AM tomorrow (I commute). Is that an okay time or a packed time? Second, are there hair dryers in the ladies locker room? And can I borrow a towel for the showers or will I have to bring my own? Third, what's the locker situation? Will I have to rent one or are they available for free? Are they in the locker rooms or outside? Should I bring my own lock? That's pretty much all I have. Thanks in advance!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-31 04:47:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you SO much for your response! I'm definitely going to opt in for the towel service. $15 a semester sounds better than carrying around a bath towel in my bag.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-31 17:36:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>I noticed! I just left the rec. I had a great time! I can't rent the locker in the locker room overnight can I?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-08-31 18:28:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you so much! Definitely doing this. I'm not having the most fun lugging around a heavy backpack of toiletries.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-05 06:51:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>wax off and regrow sweetie  lt;3333333</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>We all know this guy...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-10 17:53:25</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>The "I'm not interested" starter pack</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-10 18:59:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Call it the iBlinker</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-13 00:47:55</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>He the real MVP now.</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-09-21 22:50:46</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-10-30 04:12:35</DATE>
    <TEXT>UH? I think I saw this in my friends story today.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Keto friendly ramen place for you Houston Ketoers!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-02 23:20:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>I'm not sure if this is a super well known place here in Houston, but I tried this ramen noodle house called Samuri Noodle in the heights that serves our beloved shiritaki noodles. This is my first encounter with a restaurant that actually serves them so I'm sorry if I'm overly excited about it. Normally I would make my own soup or buy the broth and add the noodles at home. But finally there is a place that will serve it! Anyway, just wanted to put it out there in case anyone has been craving some good ramen! It's called Samuri Noodle 1801 Durham Dr, Unit 2, Houston, TX 77007, United States My boyfriend and I's ramen! I got the stir fry ramen and he got the mushroom one with a pork based broth. http://imgur.com/IQLeX2i This is now my go-to place for rainy days!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-03 00:07:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>I believe that is the same thing! I would call and ask to double check but that sounds about right. :)</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2015-11-16 05:08:15</DATE>
    <TEXT>Oh for fuck's sake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Thanks, facebook!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-05 21:16:07</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-07 02:55:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Russian General Store on bissonnet has them!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-09 01:42:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>You just have to flash your student ID. They don't run it or anything. You can still use it if you have it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-10 01:31:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Tout Suite!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-17 01:30:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>There's a ton of cops over in entrance 14 in front of Flemming. They've surrounded two cars. No idea what's happening but it prevented the buses from circulating. http://imgur.com/FCRlQZ5 http://imgur.com/jjrhYqT</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Houston's rail is starting to evolve</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-29 18:33:28</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-29 19:10:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Exactly. He was speeding down the track. I've never seen anyone drive on it before.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-02-29 19:30:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>I did change it. I just need to shut off the light and I don't know how. :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-03-29 01:16:11</DATE>
    <TEXT>/r/keto</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-04 20:14:08</DATE>
    <TEXT>Does anyone know when exactly the permits are going on sale? The article just says late April.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-12 03:31:37</DATE>
    <TEXT>I second this! Had my ticket completely dismissed. I believe the fee was about $130-$150. Completely worth it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-18 12:45:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>Westheimer and 6-10, inside the loop. The rain and lightening have definitely lightened up a bit in the last 20 minutes. My backyard is about ankle deep in water but the streets are draining pretty well. It seems like UH has cancelled classes till 10 so I'm counting on that.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-21 19:39:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>Dasme_ A lot of my friends on MFP haven't logged on in +6 months. :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-21 19:45:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Congrats for being so dedicated! I'll be here to cheer you on!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[FP] Keto nachos!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-26 01:36:19</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lately I've been really wanting a keto equivalent of nachos. I've never been a fan of pork rinds at the beginning of this diet. They always tasted kind of... off? But I recently found a bag of chili lime flavored chicharrones and decided to give it another shot. I AM IN LOVE. They were so delicious dipped in guacamole! A very satisfying snack. Anywhooooo! I decided to layer the chili lime pork rinds, sharp cheddar, ground beef cooked with a little mild Taco Bell sauce, guac, sour cream, and pickled jalape #241;o. It was so delicious. I'm surprised I'm just now doing this after nearly a year and a half of keto. Next time I might make a LC queso dip to pour on top. I portioned them out a little at a time so that the pork rinds wouldn't get soggy. Came out perfect! Here she is! KCKO! http://imgur.com/ySgcegz</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-26 05:10:42</DATE>
    <TEXT>Correct. Except I portioned mine out in such a way that I eat them before they get soggy. But definitely don't do a huge plate with all the fixings. There's no enjoying that before they get all mushy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-26 05:11:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>HEB brand! It's a grocery store chain here in Texas. I also thought they were awful the first time I had them. But these chili lime flavored ones have changed the game for me. ESPECIALLY with a side of guac!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-26 05:12:48</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds so freakin good. These are HEB brand as well! I love HEB.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-26 05:51:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks for the tip. That sounds absolutely delicious. And super convenient. I can get pretty lazy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-26 06:33:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's totally worth it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-26 07:05:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you live anywhere near the Houston, TX area, the Kroger on Buffalo Speedway has them! The carry all their flavors. The will sell out of the extra special flavors like birthday cake, mint chip, and mocha chip pretty quick though. Other than that they usually always have vanilla, chocolate, strawberry, and lemon cake.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-04-29 05:09:13</DATE>
    <TEXT>PM'ing!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-04 21:34:30</DATE>
    <TEXT>You thought Grotto was mediocre? I was going to recommend them till I saw that. They have my favorite one, personally. However, you can always try Piatto Ristorante! I haven't tried it but my sister says it's delicious and she's also not partial to Grotto's. Good luck!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-04 21:44:50</DATE>
    <TEXT>Ah, I see. Being Russian, that's exactly how I like my chicken soup. I'm not familiar with a REAL traditional Italian wedding soup. If you find what you're looking for, make sure to share!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Made keto crepes stuffed with homemade Nutella and strawberries with sugar free whipped cream!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 05:13:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-26 05:25:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>The crepes were 1.6 net carbs each and super satisfying. I found them easy to make. They held up well and flipped easier than any other recipe I've tried. Makes 4 crepes! I got this from a recipe online but unfortunately I only have screenshot and no link so if anyone knows the source and can provide before I can find it, please throw it in! 1/3 cup heavy cream 2 eggs 1 tbs melted butter 1/2 tsp vanilla 1 tbs swerve teeeeeny pinch of salt 2 tbs coconut flour Whisk the wet ingredients together, add the coconut flour, salt, and swerve. On medium heat spray a nonstick skillet with some Pam or use coconut oil or whatever fat you want. Add 1/4 of the batter and swirl it around the pan. Very carefully flip it when the cr #234;pe becomes fragrant and golden around the edges. I stuffed mine with homemade Nutella and chopped up fresh strawberries . I don't have an exact recipe because I was experimenting. But basically it involved pulsing hazelnuts, a mild vegetable oil or coconut oil, Torani SF hazelnut syrup, sea salt, unsweetened cocoa powder, vanilla, heavy cream, Splenda. No exact measurements. Everything to taste and texture. Tastes exactly like biting into a Fererro Roche! I don't miss the original Nutella. I've satisfied my cr #234;pe craving now!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 01:14:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>The gif quality is impressive. Would you mind sharing what model dash cam you have?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-27 06:49:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks so much!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>[FP] When eggs start to get a little tiring, there's smoked salmon stuffed avocado!</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-31 18:29:27</DATE>
    <TEXT>Just an easy late breakfast I whipped up. After a year and a half eggs can start to get just a liiiiiiiittle bit tiring. Super easy stuffed avocado! The filling is 4oz Neufch #226;tel, 1tbs mayo, 1tbs sour cream, 1/2tbs chopped fresh dill, 1 super finely chopped green onion, 4oz chopped up smoked salmon, salt and pepper to taste! Tweak anything to taste. Add more or less dill. Maybe hot sauce if that's your thing! Just put it all in a bowl and whisk it all up really well. I used a medium avocado and dug out a super teeny bit of the inside to make some more room for dip and put a spoon full inside. Garnished with more dill and devoured it. It was filling and delicious! http://imgur.com/rDRme0M</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-05-31 19:16:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-01 02:17:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds delicious! I didn't have any capers on hand otherwise I would have thrown that in for sure.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-01 02:22:14</DATE>
    <TEXT>That sounds awful! I love deviled eggs though.  #128128;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-02 00:36:41</DATE>
    <TEXT>It's low fat cream cheese! It has less carbs than full fat variety. So for me it's a better option.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-02 03:22:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>Try the Mac paint pots! I use Soft ochre because my skin leans on the yellower side. I lightly go over it with an eyeshadow the same color as my skin tone. It does a great job at covering up my discoloration and veiny lids!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-04 18:30:04</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are so welcome and I'm happy you enjoyed it!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-05 01:51:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>If you're looking for a flavored yogurt variety, Kroger has Carbmaster! They come in a bunch of flavors and I believe they're about 4g net carbs a cup.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-06-07 08:22:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are beyond welcome and I'm so happy you enjoyed it!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>ID this medium yellowy brown spider haunting my car? Houston, TX USA</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-29 05:27:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-29 06:10:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>I wish I could have gotten a more clear photo but I was freaking out and had to pull over for the photo and to remove it with a towel. Is that spider anything to worry about? I'm pretty sure it's still alive in my car wrapped in the towel...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-07-29 22:27:32</DATE>
    <TEXT>Toyota!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>How do inheritance laws work in Jordan?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-11 07:05:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>To keep a long story short, my father who is Jordanian, passed away last month. So now it's me (F22), my sister (F23), and my mom (F46). We all live in the U.S. but my sister and I have dual citizenship in Jordan. My father had assets and properties and money in Jordan all in his name but once again left no will. I heard that there's some kind of law that says my my mother will only get 1/8, my sister and I get half, and his brothers will take the rest. Is this true?? Is there any way to fight it in court? We are flying up there in a month and I want to be prepared. My father worked very hard for what he had and barely even talk to his brothers. This all just seems very unfair and not what my dad would want. If anyone had any information they can share or any advice I would greatly appreciate it! Thank you  #10084; #65039;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2016-11-12 02:11:23</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you very much, this really helps. I'm going into this completely blindsided and feeling like a second class citizen just for being female. I'm sorry for your loss as well. I am so not looking forward to this process. We're going to Jordan in January for about two weeks. Is two weeks enough time to get anything done?</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-04 05:02:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I love what a coward he is. He chooses to pick on a bunch of 20 year olds and when he's confronted he can't even own up to it. If she wants to wear a headscarf and practice her religion freely she should be able to do it without being called a fucking terrorist by a GROWN man. Honestly, I really thought Sugarland would be the last place you'd see something like this happen considering how large the Muslim population is. He deserves to be shamed for picking on a 21 year old girl.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-19 06:55:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Spec's sells low carb sweet and sour mix among other sugar free mixers. I like to throw it together with vodka, whiskey, or even Bacardi coconut (4g carbs per 1.5oz) if I budget correctly!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Is anyone selling a fall 2016-spring 2017 parking pass?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 21:25:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>It seems that I have lost my WC garage pass for the second time this year and it costs the full rate ($550) to replace. Is anyone selling a pass I could buy just for the semester? I've been paying for parking every day and it's getting really expensive. Help a fellow coog out. :( for some reason my EZ tag sticker which is routed to my pass won't open the gate for me so I'm at a loss here. Any advice would be appreciate in this situation. All passes are sold out so I can't even purchase an economy pass to hold me over.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-01-24 22:28:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>My problem is that I misplaced my pass last semester. This semester I'm positive my pass slipped in between the windshield and dashboard of my car but I'm have a hard time reaching it and it's driving me crazy. But after the second time getting a new pass you pay the full rate. It's insane. http://www.uh.edu/af-auxiliary-services/parking/parking-on-campus/student/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>HOP OFF MY D MOM</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-02-28 07:50:33</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>"I want you as my husband not my ATM"</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-03-22 00:21:20</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-05-26 11:54:55</DATE>
    <TEXT>For some reason when I click the link for the green room it takes me to App Store to download whatsapp rather than to the app itself. :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Best store to buy skincare from in Amman?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-04 22:43:58</DATE>
    <TEXT>Hi! Left important parts of my skincare regimen at home and my face is suffering the consequences. Is there a store in Amman that has lots of options for skincare? I'm looking for masks, toners, creams etc. I don't want to end up in a store that sells fake products or the real thing priced at 5x retail. If there's a store like Sephora that would make me so happy! Thanks guys!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-06 02:47:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thank you!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-06-16 02:39:33</DATE>
    <TEXT>What would you even call plan b in Arabic? This could come in handy.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-07-31 05:43:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Okay, now it's Houston's turn...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 20:57:44</DATE>
    <TEXT>Current routine #8212; AM:  #8226;Shea Moisture Raw Shea Butter Facial Wash and Scrub w/ Frankincense  amp; Myrrh  #8226;Clean amp;Clear Dual Action Moisturizer Oil Free w/ Salicylic acid and acne medication  #8226;Cover FX primer with Salicylic acid and then I go about my usual makeup routine PM:  #8226;Clinique Take The Day Off Balm + a warm wet towel to remove makeup  #8226;Shea Moisture Raw Shea Butter Facial Wash and Scrub w/ Frankincense  amp; Myrrh  #8226;First Aid Beauty Pure Skin Face Cleanser  #8226;Clinique Acne Solutions Clarifying Lotion Step 2 Toner  #8226;Clean amp;Clear Dual Action Moisturizer Oil Free w/ Salicylic acid and acne medication on the face minus my forehead because it makes the bumps on my forehead worse somehow  #8226;Nooni re-pair revitalizing cream moisturizer on my forehead I #8217;ll mask every so often as well. My skin has never looked like this ever before in my life. I don #8217;t find that not wearing makeup helps at all either. It started at my forehead while the rest of my face was clear. Then it spread to the sides of my face and my jaw/chin. I did go to a dermatologist who prescribed me with RetinA I believe but I have yet to get it in the mail from the pharmacy my insurance sent it to. Sometimes the bumps will completely go away on my cheeks for a few days the return even worse. I don #8217;t know what to do...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 21:06:01</DATE>
    <TEXT>It actually got better when I started TTDO again. I actually never had it previously. I #8217;ve been using TTDO for years but when I switched to Lush Skincare, I got it for the first time ever. I stopped using lush and went back to TTDO and it went away completely. However around the spring time of this year it came back all over my forehead (not my face) and I have no been able to get rid of it completely. Sometimes it would even itch a little bit and get red and almost irritated looking. I started this new routine in August and it has gotten MUCH better on my forehead but now it #8217;s on the sides of my face and all over my chin!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 21:12:47</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll give it a shot but the clean and clear is a new addition to my routine and I find that sometimes it makes the sides of my face bumps reduce. But I will try removing it completely and see what happens!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-09-21 21:47:49</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;ll look into trying this! I hate the smell of ACV but I #8217;ll do anything to get my normal skin back. :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-02 01:21:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>Today is my day 1. Again. I started keto in January of 2015 at 230lbs. I dropped to 170 by April of 2016. In October of 2016 my father passed away and I used the depression and grief as an excuse to eat whatever I wanted. Now I weigh in at 195lbs. A whopping 25lb step backwards from my lowest weight. I don #8217;t want to keto anymore as I feel it #8217;s just not sustainable for me. My current plan is to bike 5 days out of the week and eat a clean 1,200kcal a day and close to the ground (protein, veggies, fruits). The only thing with a label I #8217;m allowing myself is crystal light to encourage water intake (I #8217;m SO bad at drinking water) and Halo Too for my sweet tooth. I want this so bad. I #8217;m tired of making excuses for myself and being insecure about my arms in tank tops and how bloated my belly looks. I hope today will be the start of a productive journey to be happy with my health and the way I look. Good luck to everyone!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-29 18:33:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>The basic in me wants to know where I can find this hat...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>More like  #8220;next level trash #8221;</TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 07:07:14</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2017-10-31 15:03:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live on the edge</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-02-13 07:14:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>I live in a major city so we frequently get famous people dining in. The most memorable guest I #8217;ve had is Gucci Mane. I waited on him not long after he got out of prison. He was out with his entourage and was incredibly humble! He ordered a strawberry lemonade (for those of you who get the reference). My coworkers nagged me to get the balls to ask for a group photo. And as much as I didn #8217;t want to bother him, I eventually asked as politely as I could if we could all get a group photo after he was done with his meal. He smiled big at me and said that nothing would make him happier. His smile in the pictures are so genuine so I didn #8217;t feel bad asking anymore lol. Other than that I #8217;ve waited on Young Dolph, Slim Thug, a few NBA player from Orlando Magic and the Houston Rockets, Beyonc #233; #8217;s choreographer, and 2 local news anchors. Everyone was pleasant! Haven #8217;t had anyone get all uppity or snobby with me.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-02 01:47:06</DATE>
    <TEXT>I have never been so intimidated watching someone make a drink. Can #8217;t tell if it #8217;s the mustache or the shaking technique...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Trouble coming up with a drink name and garnish?</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 04:35:46</DATE>
    <TEXT>So I bartend at a seasonal concept craft cocktail bar  amp; grill. Every season we as bartenders have an opportunity to pitch our drink ideas for the new drink menu. I started bartending there at the beginning of the last menu so this is my first chance to make a contribution and I #8217;m really excited! So my first drink consists of 1.5oz spiced rum, 1oz of a rich guava syrup I batched, .5oz lime juice, 2 dashes ango bitters. Shake it like your mama gave it to ya. Strain into highball glass packed with fluffy ice. Splash of topo Chico on top. I made this at home and so far my friends love it. Perfect summer drink. Pretty pink color. Problem is I have no idea what to garnish it with or what to name it. Second drink I have not tested yet. But the idea is gin, lemoncillo, lemon juice, lavender simple syrup, I was thinking of presenting it in a snifter glass and freezing a sprig of lavender in a large rock. Again, haven #8217;t tested made this one yet nor do I have any idea what I would name it. We are having a bar meeting sometime in the next two weeks and I hope one of my drinks make the cut. All advice and suggestions are greatly appreciated fellow bae-tenders  #128553;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 05:13:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>Let #8217;s hope the bev director is a Simpson #8217;s fan!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 05:45:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Howdy. That is a cute name! Thank you. I was thinking for the lavender drink,  #8220;Nobody Puts Baby In a Corner. #8221; Hit me up if you #8217;re ever in Houston!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 06:37:31</DATE>
    <TEXT>I do have access to one. Candied guava isn #8217;t a bad idea at all. I may give that a shot tomorrow at work! As for the lemon lavender skewer, thank you for the advice. I will definitely try that out as well.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-09 17:21:16</DATE>
    <TEXT>Thanks so much for the ideas! I #8217;ve never used egg white in a gin drink before. I #8217;m really hoping the simple syrup will take on a lavender color so the drink isn #8217;t yellow. I want it to be lean on greyish/clear.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-15 07:41:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m selling my 2009 c300. I recent replaced the steering wheel lock/ignition switch through the dealership. It has a brand new battery and the starter switch and engine are in over all excellent condition. It has 77k miles on it. Not sure if it matters to you, but I #8217;m in Texas. I listed my car on a few sites. Here #8217;s a link if you #8217;re interested.. https://www.cars.com/vehicledetail/detail/736593980/overview/</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Joined the camaro family today! Introducing my new 2017 Camaro SS1. Now to come up with a cool plate/name for her...</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 23:16:00</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-22 23:53:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>I #8217;m still learning  #128578;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-23 00:31:54</DATE>
    <TEXT>Well I am from Texas...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-24 09:16:20</DATE>
    <TEXT>We are literally in the exact same boat. 23, single, working my ass off and just bought my 1SS yesterday. Congrats!!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-05-26 18:21:52</DATE>
    <TEXT>That color is gorgeous, congratulations! Especially if you black out the rims. That #8217;s first thing on my list for my SS.  #128064;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-07-10 18:01:51</DATE>
    <TEXT>A sleepyhead comment if I #8217;ve ever seen one!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE>Can #8217;t tell if I hate it or</TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 18:20:26</DATE>
    <TEXT></TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 18:26:25</DATE>
    <TEXT>As one of the two a week you might be seeing around these streets, I promise I don #8217;t drive like a dick. :(</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-08 19:54:24</DATE>
    <TEXT>Style is generous term for whatever this poor Frankencamaro is.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-10 05:23:21</DATE>
    <TEXT>Can someone translate? I want to laugh too...</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-15 09:39:57</DATE>
    <TEXT>Lucky</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-20 19:09:39</DATE>
    <TEXT>Has anyone ever taken the Light Rail purple line to campus? I live about 10 minutes away inside the loop and this is my first year without a parking pass. My plan (so far) is to park somewhere and hop on the purple line to UH since there #8217;s a stop along Wheeler behind the Hilton-ish. The dilemma thus far is that I have noooooo idea which stop to park at along the purple line. There are no  #8220;park and rides. #8221; Has anyone done this before? I start class tomorrow pls halp.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 05:35:18</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is there a towing risk? I #8217;ve been paying $7 for all day parking at this lot directly across the convention center stop.  #128557;</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 05:50:07</DATE>
    <TEXT>Is it hard to find parking there? And would you know which rail stop it #8217;s close to? Sorry, these are my last questions I promise.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 06:01:28</DATE>
    <TEXT>That is so helpful! Okay would you say it #8217;s relatively safe for a 23 year old female alone? I don #8217;t remember what that stop looked like.</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-25 06:09:00</DATE>
    <TEXT>You are the best!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 00:50:09</DATE>
    <TEXT>My twin!</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  <WRITING>
    <TITLE></TITLE>
    <DATE>2018-08-31 02:19:22</DATE>
    <TEXT>yes</TEXT>
    <INFO>Reddit post</INFO>
  </WRITING>
  </INDIVIDUAL>